Poor parents.
They put in so much effort
in naming their kids...
while friends destroy them
with nicknames.
And those names stick forever!
Here are Mr. and Mrs. Iyer.
After four struggling years...
they still couldn't agree on a name.
Child's name?
-Rishab.
-Ronnie.
Rama Shankar.
Nobody had the guts
to argue with Grandpa.
But little did they
know that Rama Shankar
was destined to be
a left arm fast bowler.
And we would rechristen him as...
Akram!
Hey, Akram!
-Aunty, is Akram home?
-Shut up!
What's with you kids?
Why do you call him Akram?
-Oops!
-Don't you dare call him Akram!
I won't let him play with you guys.
He is the team's
left arm fast bowler.
Why can't they call him
Rudra Pratap Singh or Ashish Nehra?
There are so many other
good left arm bowlers.
I will get him to bowl with his
right hand, I don't like that name.
His naming was an emotional affair.
My father was very happy
when I was born.
So, he named me Happy Singh.
And when my son was born,
I was promoted.
-Guess what we named him!
-What?
Go on. It's a simple question.
Promotion Singh?
Lucky Singh!
But whatever poor Lucky Singh said...
the opposite would come true.
India is going to win today!
No!
We've lost the game!
Come on.
We should never watch
the match with him.
So we called him...
Lucky, why does everyone
call you 'Unlucky'?
Maybe because I am unlucky.
Now, Laxman was the younger kid.
Always in his brother's hand-me-downs.
It's almost new.
We bought it last year.
It's time for school.
Let's leave.
Wow, you're back in
the second hand pants?
My bad luck is really bad!
He'd made up his mind
to save for new clothes.
So we'd stop calling him Second Hand.
And here is the James Bond of movies.
The name is Jhangyani.
Balwan Jhangyani.
He hated wearing underwear.
So, tell me...
why don't you wear an underwear?
Because it's in style!
Hrithik, Shah Rukh, Salman...
nobody wears it.
You should also give it a try.
-Cheers!
-We had no option but to call him
Janghya! Get us some water!
"Janghya! Get us some water!"
His pushy parents pushed him
into everything.
Karate.
Skating.
Cricket.
Etcetera... etcetera...
That's why we called him,
the all-rounder
Aflatoon, let's play!
Can't! I have tennis class!
This kid was on mute.
So naturally, we named him...
Hey, Silencer.
Come down!
Indian by birth, Chinese by spirit.
His nickname... Shaolin.
And this is me.
The mastermind of my team.
Ghatotkach!
Ghatotkach is the right answer.
Even our gang had a nickname.
Chillar Party! Shut up!
Creating a ruckus all day!
We had two enemies.
The oversized neighborhood
cricket team.
To whom we lost all cricket matches
Losers!
How about winning for a change!
So we can also celebrate!
Such losers!
The day we win,
I swear I'll burst a cracker in his house.
Our other sworn enemy, Loose Motion.
Not the lady, her pommy!
She would poop all
over the cricket ground.
And so we hated dogs too.
I wish I could wring its neck!
-We can't do anything to that dog.
-Why not?
We'd be the prime suspects!
If another dog lands up here
we'll end up playing hopscotch.
Got it?
He is right.
Poo! Poo, lots of poo.
There will never be...
another dog in our colony!
Unlucky! Not again!
You are not to say positive things!
My left eye is flickering.
Is that a bad omen?
I am coming,
Listen to me carefully
Hey! Why are you peeping inside?
I'm here for an interview.
Hey, Uncle!
-Uncle!
-Hey, kiddo!
-Let him in.
-Let's go, Buddy.
Come in. Welcome.
How are you?
We both are awesome!
Like two peas in a pod!
Wait here, I'll be right back.
Come, Buddy.
And our worst nightmare came true.
There will never be
another dog in our colony!
Come on.
Him?
-What's your name?
-Fatka.
And him? Who is this?
This is my friend, Buddy.
You think he can clean all the cars?
-Of course, sir!
-Sure, he is a bright kid.
-Fix his salary before you leave.
-Yes.
Listen!
I don't want any complaints.
About you or your dog.
-Got it?
-Yes, sir.
Work hard, kiddo!
There shouldn't be any complaints.
Greet him.
Mind your own business and
don't poke your nose into anything.
The people here are very nice.
Except for the secretary, who's a pain.
As if I'm planning to marry him.
But where will you stay?
This called for an urgent
meeting that very evening.
I guess the cycle
has lost three kilos.
But you, not a gram!
What's your problem?
What's so funny, lollypop!
We need all information
about our new problem.
Why?
First information...
then action.
Balwan, come home, right now!
Why, mummy?
Do you want me to come and get you?
With him it's action first
and then information!
Okay, don't forget your tasks.
-So, Buddy...
-No!
This is how they say it in Punjabi.
"I'll polish you from head to toe...
you'll be unlucky no more."
Gosh! He even knows my name!
He knows my name!
He talks to the cars.
In English, Punjabi and Japanese too.
Akram?
He takes tea on credit...
but buys biscuits for his dog.
Second Hand?
Both of them have blissful
afternoon snoozes.
And watch TV standing
outside the Electronics shop.
The spoilt brat doesn't
even go to school.
Okay guys, see you after dance class.
That idiot, ruined our game.
Silencer?
No use asking him.
He talks to his dog as well.
Anything else?
It's true!
Remember how
Doctor Dolittle talks to animals?
He does, doesn't he?
Janghya!
Your Dad has a DVD library, right?
So?
We need to do something about that!
"Talks to his dog!"
He does, I swear!
I swear!
As usual he's exaggerating!
Alright, Buddy.
Now give me a good night kiss.
I told you he talks to his dog.
To weaken our enemy
we need to strike on his business.
Why?
Because a weak enemy cannot blow his...
Guitar?
Drums?
Trumpet.
Oh! Trumpet!
Where are you taking the flour?
It's homework.
So now they're teaching
kids to cook in school!
Carry on.
It will be useful when you grow up!
Hang on.
Take some vegetables too.
It's a basic course, not advanced.
So what do we make with this flour?
Dog poop!
Black pepper.
Mold.
Orange poop?
It looks like this
when I have orange juice.
Idiot, add some yellow to it.
What is this?
Poop.
Who did this, Sir?
Not him, he is my business partner.
Buddy would never do such a thing.
What kind of a dog would
climb up to poop like this?
Wow! It looks so real!
Nice and healthy!
Poop is never healthy.
It's just nitrogenous waste.
What are you doing? Don't touch it.
It's fake.
-Throw it away!
-Sir, just smell it.
I will give you one tight slap!
Throw it away.
Throw it away from the car!
No! We forgot to add the odor.
You should've farted on the poop!
Bloody Chillar Party!
Hurry up!
Hey, you! Pass the ball.
Buddy, step aside.
A new problem everyday!
Why don't these kids like us?
Anyway why should it matter to us!
Where is the washcloth?
It was right here.
Buddy, have you seen our washcloth?
This guy is tough.
But no match for us.
-Want a bite?
-No, thanks.
Buddy!
Come out. Here's your birthday gift.
Buddy?
Buddy!
-What's wrong?
-Have you seen Buddy?
Buddy!
Buddy...
What's the matter, Arjun?
Mom...
if I'm mean to someone...
who has done nothing mean to me
then am I a bad boy?
Well, if you are feeling
guilty about it...
then you are still a good boy.
Finally.
Now his fragile body will
get some glucose and carbohydrates.
There goes your brain ticking again.
Why don't you think with your heart,
for a change?
Where are you going?
For Group Studies.
There's a lot of pressure!
Wow! You're growing up!
I don't think so.
What about tomorrow's match?
What about the team's captain?
There he is.
He's injured!
I'm sorry. I didn't do my homework.
Our super-fast bowler is injured!
While their striker Shoaib Akhtar...
is getting bigger
and stronger every minute!
He can really pack a punch!
In the last match, he knocked off
our five batsmen.
And my head too.
Well, we do have a back up.
In our colony? Who?
Janghya!
Me? Thanks, man!
Go get the kid with the dog.
Fast bowler!
Chillar Party wants to talk to you.
About what?
He wants to know why.
Don't you know?
We need a fast bowler!
So, big deal!
It's for our colony's
pride and honor.
And he belongs to this colony.
What was that again?
It's for our colony's pride and
honor and you're a part of it.
Fine. But first you have to say sorry.
I want everyone to say sorry.
I am saying sorry on their behalf as well.
That's not good enough.
Everybody has say sorry.
Wonderful!
Chillar Party is on
their way to lose again!
Let's start.
Hold on. Where's Shoaib?
Let's toss?
Five minutes!
Where's Shoaib?
Hey! Mummy!
Go away!
And Fatka scores the first boundary.
Don't worry
Give others worry!
He who messes with you
Give him a thrashing
Don't fry my brains
Move aside
Just move aside
I am coming
Listen to me carefully
Attention everyone!
Though everyone played very well.
Only one player can
be named Man of the Match.
Janghya!
Me?
Get the garland.
Man of the match!
"Janghya, get the garland."
Janghya, come fast!
Buddy!
Sometimes they fight
Sometimes they are stubborn
Sometimes they are
At each other's throat
But they became friends eventually
They are sweet
They are spicy
Now they are one gang
I hate milk.
But my mom forces me to have it.
You're so lucky.
If you don't drink milk you'll
get something else to eat or drink.
At least you don't go
to bed on an empty stomach.
I get to eat on some days.
Or I go to bed hungry.
That's why I have
no complaints about milk.
Like little chicks
They are always together
Always running here and there
In a group
They are different colors of Holi
They are different,
But they are together
When they are on your face,
They all look the same
One is laughing
Another one doesn't have a single penny
They are all different
It doesn't matter to them
They are sweet
They are spicy
Now they are one gang
I envy your life.
You're a free bird.
No one sets rules for you.
Like our parents do.
Your mom cooks for you...
and pampers you.
Your father works hard all day.
So that you can get a good education.
When you fall ill,
your parents look after you.
Fine, no one sets rules for me.
But then, no one is there
to love me either.
Still envy my life?
They are just like pretzels
They just came out of a pan
They are twisted and hot,
But they are sweet
They are a gist of wind
You can't get hold of them
They will blow
In the direction they wish
One gets mother's love
Another one faces thorns on his way
Their destinations are different,
But their path is same
They are sweet
They are spicy
Now they are one gang
This colony is called Chandan Nagar.
So why do you all
call it Cartoon Network?
Because everyone here is a cartoon.
That's Mr. Boring!
He's unbearable!
-Hello!
-Where are you going?
There goes Akram!
I've seen you play,
show me your batting stance.
That's not the way you hold the bat.
It's not proper.
Your fingers should be parallel
and your top hand should be heavy.
Parallel fingers are
of utmost importance.
And remember, chin on your shoulder.
Do you want me to bowl to you?
Can I bowl?
-Are you going to spin the ball?
-No, it will be a fast ball.
-Fast?
-Okay?
Okay.
Parallel fingers, chin...
it should be like this always.
Don't bowl on my legs, okay?
Hello, how are you?
Okay?
She is the superstar of our colony.
Toothpaste.
Superstar?
Haven't you seen her on TV?
She's the one!
She thinks she's
a star and ignores us.
But I kind of like her.
Chillar party!
And who's this guy?
He is Googly.
Googly?
Just listen to him!
Hello!
It's surprising to
see you all together!
What's the occasion?
See you later.
-Bye, uncle.
-Bye.
How was that?
God has a wicked sense of humor.
He's made a truck and
given it the horn of a cycle.
His voice dwarfs his talent,
keeps him jobless.
We learnt a lot from Fatka.
Even some things that we shouldn't have.
What's up, old chap?
So you've found your way home!
You should have had
lunch with that punk.
Don't be a pain, mom!
I'm beat.
Don't mess with me.
Come again?
What's eating you up?
Take a chill pill.
"What's eating me up?"
"Take a chill pill?"
-No, mom!
-Let it go!
Is this what you are learning?
-Stop it.
-I'll teach you a lesson.
-Shameless.
Don't worry, son.
Who will describe Mahatma Gandhi?
-I will. I will, madam.
-Balwan?
Gandhi was that dude from India
who had sent the
Brit losers packing.
Got it?
Don't you take interest in your child?
"Gandhi the dude?"
What if all the kids
start speaking this way?
Is this what you teach your kids?
Jack and Jill went up the hill
And planned to do some kissing
Jack made a pass,
And grabbed her back
And now two of his front teeth are missing
Applaud, you idiots!
Goodnight, son.
Mom that's not how you say it.
So how do you say it?
Eat out, slurp in, burp out, crash in!
Go wish your dad good night.
That's not how you say it, dad.
Eat out, slurp in, burp out, crash in!
If you go out to meet
Fatka, I'll thrash you.
Let's meet tomorrow.
-Please, dad.
-When?
Dad, just a minute.
Why? You are not going anywhere.
Stay here.
He has a fever, Dad.
No. In fact, you've got
the loitering fever.
Got it? Get inside or
you'll get a spanking.
Take him home.
It's curfew at home.
Same here.
Everyone's angry...
and he is too sick to clean the cars.
Fatka could lose his job.
Do you have an alarm clock?
Of course!
At 5:45 a.m, Mr. Rooster
comes out in his balcony.
We must finish by then.
Hey, H2O, did you see anything?
Yes.
Even we have seen things.
Going to the movies lately
with a certain Mr. Sharma's maid?
Do you still remember seeing this?
No.
Great, we'll forget
your movie visits too!
Alright. Get lost.
What?
The rooster!
Hurry up. Hide.
Who did this?
Catch it, catch it!
Come!
Come, come. One more!
Oh, no!
Are you guys not talking anymore?
Why not?
Their parents aren't
too happy about it.
What do they say?
They think I'm a bad kid.
Buddy, doesn't care.
He likes me for who I am.
I wish my interviewers
were as considerate.
May I say something?
I hope you don't mind.
Go ahead.
I was thinking about you.
You were?
Your audio and video don't match.
I know.
What if you only use your voice?
What do you mean?
No one knows if it's
a boy or a girl on the radio.
I am Manisha...
and you are listening to 98.3 FM,
Radio Mirchi. It's hot!
And here's a brand new show,
Morning Masala.
Let's begin this bright
morning with a bright number.
In life...
we often fail to understand people.
People didn't understand me.
And we...
failed to understand him.
He might come across as shabby...
but his advice got me a job.
Or should I say, got my voice a job.
D.J, hit the bass!
How the times have changed, Dubey.
Earlier, I'd be invited
for bridge inaugurations.
And now it's come down
to a kids' playground.
All thanks to the recession, sir.
Tie this ribbon properly.
-Put up the ribbon!
-It will be done.
-Yes.
-Come on.
Come on.
Sir, it's Tandon.
-Yes, Mr. Tandon.
-Greetings, sir.
Are there enough people to welcome us?
Or is this a waste of time?
-No, sir. There are enough people.
-Very good.
-Okay, sir. We are waiting for you.
-Yes, we'll be there soon.
He's got a crowd he says!
-Welcome, sir.
-How are you doing, Mr. Tandon?
-Fine, Sir. Thanks to you.
-Greetings.
-You didn't have to do this.
-It's my pleasure, sir.
This is Mr. Sharma,
in charge of maintaining the garden.
Very well done.
Come, sir.
He is the Treasurer of
our block, Mr. Iyer.
Welcome, sir.
Kids, move aside.
How nice!
Dogs are also here to welcome me!
Go ahead. I'll take care of this.
Welcome, sir.
Whose dog is this?
Get him out of here.
Why, sir?
-Are you arguing with me?
-No, sir!
Take him and get out of here.
You're here for a free lunch?
Why do you say that?
Applause!
Didn't you hear me? Just go away!
Uncle, stop! Don't hit him!
Where do you get the time, sir?
Don't, Buddy.
-What's going on?
-I don't know, sir.
Move away.
The dog attacked me, sir.
Take him away.
Fatka, get him away.
What happened?
The dog attacked me, sir.
Dubey...
Whose dog is this?
-Sir...
-Whose dog is this?
He's ours.
Sir, these children
are from my colony.
It was my mistake.
I should have crushed its neck.
If you'd done that...
we would've lost a good opportunity.
Do you have any issue...
that will get us into
the limelight again?
An issue?
Dubey...
politics thrives on issues,
and today we were served one.
Now watch me make a mountain
out of this molehill.
In Mumbai, Welfare Minister
Mr. Shashikant Bhide...
has launched a campaign
against stray dogs.
He had this to say to our reporters.
If my secretary is not safe
from stray dogs...
how can the common man feel safe?
That's why the nuisance
of stray dogs must end.
For a safe Mumbai.
But, sir, not all stray
dogs are dangerous.
Will you let me finish?
We are not against all stray dogs.
If people feel that the stray dogs
living around them are not dangerous
then they can get them an N.O.C.
i.e. No Objection Certificate.
And they have a month to do this.
After a month,
dogs without an N.O. C
will have no place in the city.
Thank you.
Let's create a safer Mumbai.
These are minister Bhide's orders.
Dogs like Buddy, beware.
Try saving yourself.
Tandon, Bhide here.
Did you watch the news?
Yes, sir.
So to make this mission a success...
capturing that dog is vital.
Yes, of course.
Because that dog sparked the war.
Don't worry, sir. I'll handle it.
Buddy stood up for his friend.
So how could Buddy be wrong?
Don't worry, we will get the N.O.C.
My dad will handle it.
My dad fears nothing, not even ghosts.
Our decision is that
this dog won't get an N.O.C.
And our decision is...
Buddy won't go from here.
We decided we wouldn't let Buddy go
but we forgot that we were only kids.
Rama Shankar.
Enough of this doggy nonsense!
Come on!
No! I won't leave Buddy!
Let go of me!
We won't let him go!
They are only kids they'll
be fine in the morning.
Console us, make us laugh
Run your hand across our hair
We will become quiet
We are kids
We are a bit immature
We will become quiet
If I lack something
Or others lack something
I wonder why everyone thinks
Kids don't have any feelings
Console us, make us laugh
Run your hand across our hair
We will become quiet
We are kids
We are a bit immature
We will become quiet
So what's an N.O.C?
Very simple. Even Janghya knows this!
Right, Janghya?
Just like there is MIB...
and LOTR, there is N.O.C.
What does it mean?
Don't you get it?
In MIB, M stands for Men.
In LOTR, L stands for Lord.
Similarly N.O.C. stands for...
No objection certificate.
Hey, I was getting there!
I've never got a
certificate for anything.
Why do we need a certificate?
It is a certificate from the society
that allows Buddy
to stay in the colony.
But our colony people are against it.
What is this?
It's our colony Rulebook.
It says that if more than
50 percent of the residents agree...
then Buddy can get an N.O.C.
Then even Tandon uncle
can't do anything.
There are 60 apartments in our block.
What's 50 percent of that?
That means we need 31 signatures.
So we have to go to 31 apartments?
Long live the Revolution!
Are you all with me?
-Long live the Revolution!
-Silence!
We've decided, we'll fight for Buddy.
And we will fight till the end.
If they slap us on one cheek...
we'll slap them on both.
Right?
He said yes.
So what's the strategy?
We have only 27 days...
to get the signatures
from our parents and neighbors.
If I ask my dad for a signature,
he will spank me.
Do you want to save Buddy?
-Yes or no?
-Yes.
Get kicked or slapped or shouted at.
Do whatever it takes.
But get the signature.
So, what's an N.O.C?
No Objection Certificate!
Get kicked or slapped or shouted at.
Do whatever it takes.
But get the signature.
Dad?
Dad...
What is it?
-I won't sign.
-Please!
I told you once. Now get lost!
If he wants the moon,
should I get him that too?
I don't have time for your nonsense.
Focus on your grades!
Hey! You won't get it!
Shut up!
You think you'll be
able to accomplish this?
-So...
-Sign.
I'll sign,
but to protest you must sing songs.
Like...
-Let's revolt!
-Sign...
-Very good!
-Now sign.
Wait, there's more.
Revolt...
-Can you sing in a higher pitch?
-Alright.
We'll do or die now!
-You kids are doing a noble deed.
-Uncle, sign please.
-Where do you want me to sign?
-No signature!
You expect me to sign this nonsense?
Right, darling?
-Sorry.
-I understand.
I told them no a thousand times!
He's scared of his wife.
Just like my dad.
Nice muscles, bro!
What do you want?
Can you get dad's signature?
Did you fail again?
No, we want to pass Buddy's petition.
Alright.
Even a movie star doesn't
create such drama for an autograph.
Get kicked or slapped or shouted at.
Do whatever it takes.
Dad.
But get that signature.
-You want me to sign?
-Yes.
Give it to me.
You'll have to dance for me.
Start.
Come squeeze the heart
Break the pot at night
Now dance to this.
My hopes are burning in my heart
Not good enough. Get lost.
Get out!
Get lost!
Don't come back here.
What a waste!
Dad.
Thank you, Dad!
You want me to complain to your dad?
Get lost!
Didn't I say no?
No, thanks.
-Please?
-No!
But I'm not signing!
What?
You stole my banana!
Look at me and say it!
What happened?
After so much of effort,
we have only 10 signatures.
It's so frustrating!
-Buddy?
-Buddy...
Why are they refusing to sign?
What is their problem?
They're afraid of the minister!
He scares them.
What's wrong?
What's bothering you?
I'm wondering why everyone
is afraid of the minister.
Because he is very powerful.
How?
He has public support!
And that makes a person powerful?
Yes.
You think even we should
approach the public?
If you truly believe
in what you're doing, then why not.
If I do this, dad will scold me!
If your actions bring about something
good, then it's all worth it.
This glum look doesn't suit you.
Are you here to mock us?
I'm here to help you.
How do you expect to do that?
You're also a kid and kids
are never taken seriously.
You think you're super smart in here
but in the real world?
What do you know about the real world?
I know you call me "Toothpaste."
Because you're on TV!
So if you want to be seen and heard
and match up to the Minister
you have to go on TV, like me!
How's that possible?
What's the big deal?
These days even a hen laying five eggs
qualifies as breaking news.
But what will be our breaking news?
Our Buddy doesn't even lay eggs.
Does he?
Good morning, son.
Mom, where is the newspaper?
Since when did you start
reading the newspaper?
Please, mom!
Go take it from your brother.
Even the newspaper is a hand-me-down!
This news is a real eye opener!
We'll be back after the sensational
story of a criminal...
Another breaking news!
A beard that cures jaundice.
Does this make any sense?
Let me watch!
Osama Bin Laden issued
another warning.
And with that the
stock market crashed.
People sold their shares.
How will this phenomenon
affect our markets?
We will keep you informed.
Today's big debate,
what would be Osama's next step?
Have you heard of Osama Bin Laden?
No.
Don't you watch the news?
Oh, God!
The world is doomed!
Have you heard of Osama Bin Laden?
Yeah.
You watch the news!
Why is everyone in Chandan Nagar
refusing to sign the petition?
Who will win the due
between the pen and the sword?
What did he say?
Who? Tell me, who?
Who is keeping apart two friends?
When will the wait end...
for these innocent kids?
The kid is a dog-whisperer
but nobody believes it!
-You talk to Buddy, don't you?
-Well...
-Don't you?
-Yeah.
But how do we get the
reporters to hear this?
And here is some amazing news
a dog named Buddy in
Chandan Nagar, talks to people!
If you can't believe this...
go there and see for yourself.
Googly said that a lot
of reporters will show up.
They'll ask a lot of questions
but don't be scared, okay?
Nothing scares me.
You think you can handle this?
Don't worry.
I'll take care of it.
I think...
So, how many reporters?
Not even one.
I think nobody will show up.
Kids, there's a reporter here!
-Reporter?
Hey, Unlucky,
you should have said that earlier.
The talking dog lives here, right?
Yes.
Ten copies of The Daily Sensation!
30 rupees.
Make that one.
Three rupees.
Here! Over here!
Talking dog in Chandan Nagar.
The kids of Chandan Nagar
are trying to save Buddy
from the law passed by
Minister Shashikant Bhide.
For this they need 31 votes
and have succeeded in getting 10 votes.
The article also says
that they want public support
to save the talking dog.
That will help them
gather enough votes...
to keep Buddy safe
from the minister's law.
How immature!
Interesting.
Sir, nobody reads this rubbish.
Dubey...
it might be a small spark.
But it must be doused...
before it becomes a wild fire.
Mr. Bhide has sent this for you.
He wants to have a word with you.
Hello, Tandon.
Chandan Nagar is getting famous.
I had no idea.
Of course!
You were caught sleeping!
You didn't even realize...
that the kids in your
colony have outwitted you.
You've been fooled!
Sir...
Be ready to read tomorrow's headline.
And it will appear
in every newspaper.
"Chandan Nagar Colony's
Secretary arrested."
But why, sir?
He employs children as labor.
And, I'm sure you know...
that child labor is a crime.
Sir...
So, think about it, Tandon.
You either go to prison
or you fire the kid!
Good night...
and sleep...
No, hold your pants tight.
Very funny.
Good night, hold your pants tight.
We got five more signatures!
Don't worry, we will get
the rest of the signatures
and Buddy won't go anywhere.
What's the matter, Fatka?
Answer the door.
Laxman?
-What are you doing here at this hour?
-What?
-What!
-What happened?
Lucky!
What is it?
Fatka got fired.
Like little chicks
They are always together
Always running here and there
In a group
They are different colors of Holi
They are different,
But they are together
When they are on your face,
They all look the same
One is laughing
Another one doesn't have a single penny
They are all different
But it doesn't matter to them
They are sweet
They are spicy
Now they are one gang
It's a crime for adults
to employ children.
But, Dad...
Arjun, it's against the law.
There's nothing we can do.
Fatka is an orphan.
If he doesn't work,
he won't have any money.
He'll starve.
The kids are devastated.
There has to be a way out.
I'm helpless.
The minister has a personal
interest in this case.
-Personal interest?
-Yes.
The kids are to blame.
Tell me, why did they have to print
-the talking dog story?
-I know--
That's what led to all this!
The law says it's a crime for
adults to employ children.
But there's no law that says
that a kid can't employ a kid!
Don't clean their cars,
you can clean our bicycles.
And we will pay you
from our pocket money.
We won't give up so easily.
They are stubborn
Very stubborn
Long Live the Revolution!
Balwan, come home, right now!
Forget it!
Coming, Mom!
Where's Lucky?
He's out with his friends.
What about his homework?
He completed all of it.
Yes.
That's very sweet of you.
We'll put it on Buddy
when he gets the N.O.C.
We need 16 more signatures.
And only seven days to go.
We have even run out of 'Breaking News.'
But we have to do something.
Something that makes
the front page headlines!
With photographs.
So what do we do?
Walk around the city in our underwear?
Do you have the guts to pull that off?
-I was just kidding--
-Do you have the guts?
You think it'll help?
It just might.
Let's do it.
But half a dozen kids won't help.
We had to go ahead
with the underwear march
but to make it huge,
we urgently needed some money.
Hello, sir. Fatka here.
I used to work in your hotel.
Sir, I need some money.
I'll return it next month.
No, not for illegal work.
Okay, Sir. Bye.
Where did all this money come from?
Are you doing something
you're not supposed to?
I've been saving money
to buy new clothes.
But nothing is more
important than Buddy.
Hold on! Stop!
We need to rock it.
It's an undie parade.
While adults might not support us
we were sure the kids of
the city will stand up for us.
They'll be in their underwear!
What do I choose? I choose this.
This?
This!
Don't pressurize me, man.
You know I don't wear underwear.
Jhangya's not here, is he?
It's my dad's!
If ants take a united stand
They can even scare an elephant
Even a tiny thorn can give immense pain
Fight them
Fight them all
Fight them all, take them over
They are very stubborn
These kids are very stubborn
They are stubborn
Today, we can see a novel protest
on the streets of Mumbai.
A large number of kids,
in white underwear
are parading towards the Kranti Ground.
These kids are parading
to save their dog.
If a nail stands erect
The Tyre goes boom
If the razor slips on your mustache
Your reputation will be gone
Stubborn! Stubborn!
Stand tall
Fight them
Fight them all
These kids are very stubborn
Kids are stubborn!
-Buddy!
-What is all this?
-We want to save our Buddy.
-Who is Buddy?
-Buddy is our dog. This is to save him...
From the new law
that the Minister has passed!
-Long Live the Revolution!
-Buddy!
Buddy! Buddy!
BUDDY VS BHIDE.
-Have you seen my white underwear?
-Yes.
-It's right there, on TV!
-What?
Your underwear seems very unique.
It's my style, madam.
-Buddy!
-That's my son!
Buddy! Buddy!
-Buddy!
-What's his name?
We have to save Buddy!
-Akram.
-Akram?
When a small bird collides
Even a plane crashes down
One matchstick can
Burn down the entire jungle
One matchstick can burn down
The entire jungle
Kids are stubborn
Stand tall
Fight them
Fight them all
These kids are very stubborn
These kids are stubborn
Buddy! Buddy!
We look after stray dogs.
We can issue an N.O.C for
Buddy and keep him with us.
But then he won't be with us.
And it won't be worth fighting for.
Buddy! Buddy!
This city belongs to Buddy too.
Who are we to decide his fate?
I think he deserves an N.O.C!
What do you think?
-He should get an N.O.C.
-And you?
If I lived in that colony,
I would've granted him an N.O.C.
The public verdict is
that Buddy deserves an N.O.C.
With cameraman Manoj,
this is Aditi for Zee News.
As you can see thousands
of kids have gathered here...
Hello? Yes.
Tell them I'm busy.
Everyone's saying just one slogan.
It's the Chief Minister.
-Save Buddy!
-Chief Minister.
I have only one question for you
are you with them in the protest?
Yes, sir?
How many votes have the
kids managed to get?
We're short of one signature.
And one day to go!
How do we get that signature?
Sir, congratulations!
The dog is history,
I had a word with Tandon.
There are no more signatories
to sign the petition.
The final decision will be
taken tomorrow, anyway.
No, Dubey.
These kids have insulted
me on national television.
It's time to avenge that insult.
They like showing off their
underwear, don't they?
The dog is gone!
Now, I'll strip them
on national television.
I'll make them beg for mercy.
These things can be solved amicably.
The kids think I've been unfair...
but they shouldn't have
paraded in their underwear.
Instigating other kids is wrong.
Let them come...
and discuss it with me on the TV.
LIVE. Heart to heart.
But why on TV?
I want the people to know...
that their welfare and interests
are important to me.
A safe Mumbai...
is a happy Mumbai.
Thank you!
Minister Bhide has invited the children to
discuss their problem live on television.
Now we have to see...
if the kids will show up
to debate with Mr. Bhide.
The entire nation awaits.
Moreover...
Yes?
Yes, Mr. Saxena.
-Hello.
We'd like to remind you
that exactly a month ago...
The Minister had...
I didn't favour the protest.
But my son insisted and I gave in.
The Minister is a jerk.
He enjoys troubling the kids.
I think the kids did great.
The newspaper published the story.
The children had the undie
parade and it's all right.
But now it's time
to put a stop to this.
What will they do on TV?
The minister will rip them apart.
-And all for a dog.
-Yes.
They should just forget about this.
I agree...
but there's something
you haven't realised.
This fight isn't
about the dog anymore.
It's about the kids.
Our kids have fought
this battle on their own.
And at this hour of reckoning...
we want them to surrender?
So what do you expect?
You want us to see our
kids get humiliated?
I am not saying that!
If they'll be laughed at, so be it.
The defeat will be worth it.
At least they won't be termed as cowards.
I feel like thrashing the minister.
One thing is certain.
-The kids have been very brave.
-Yes.
Mr. Saxena...
I don't know about the other kids...
but our kids will
surely put up a fight.
Mr. Iyer...
our kids have fought
this battle as a team.
If they go, they go together!
At least I want all of them to go.
I believe they should go.
We should let them go.
Remember this.
Whether you win or lose out there...
for us you'll always be victorious.
None of us slept that night.
Maybe it was our
last night with Buddy.
We will go to the studio after school.
You can come with Googly.
Okay.
It's an important day for you.
You should wear a new shirt.
If Buddy gets the last vote
before the dog squad arrives...
please put this collar on him.
-They are just kids.
-They will be fine. Don't worry.
Don't be scared.
Don't bite the dust this time.
Don't spare the Minister!
Console us, make us laugh
Run your hand across our hair
We will become quiet
We are kids
We are a bit immature
We will become quiet
We fell in a moment,
We stood up again
I wonder why everyone thinks
Kids don't have any feelings
Today is the day of the verdict.
Final verdict will be passed
on the Buddy Vs Bhide case.
Praise us to the sky and leave
We will become quiet
We are kids
We are a bit immature
We will become quiet
It all began when Buddy
attacked Shashikant Bhide's PA.
This minor issue has now snowballed
into such a major fight.
And today you will
have to take the decision
whether the verdict should
be in favor of the kids
or in favor of the minister.
Just distract us a bit
Show us an airplane
We will become quiet
When we hurt ourselves,
Just console us
We will become quiet
When we run into the table,
Shout at the table
We will become quiet
We are kids
We are a bit immature
We will become quiet
We fell in a moment,
We stood up again
I wonder why everyone thinks
Kids don't have any feelings
Uncle, I think you will win today.
Give us false hopes
Buy us an ice-cream
We will become quiet
When we weep give us a hug
Hello and welcome to
The Battle Hour.
Today's episode is one of a kind.
On my right is Mr. Shashikant Bhide
who began the drive to put an end
to Mumbai's stray dog nuisance.
The drive is scheduled to start today.
And on my left,
are the kids from Chandan Nagar.
They've managed the impossible in
trying to keep their dog, Buddy safe.
So there's a lot to look
forward to in today's show.
Hello, kids!
It's nice to see you dressed today.
I was afraid you might
show up in your underwear.
I am scared of these kids.
Because they are the
future of our nation.
If the future of our
nation is built on lies...
it's a matter of grave concern.
They lied when their
colony refused the N.O.C.
They claimed one of them
could talk with the dog.
And the story got published,
to humor the kids.
Am I right?
When that did not work,
they resorted to cheap tactics.
They instigated the kids of
our city to parade in their underwear.
Why?
To prove that they
are right and I am wrong.
Am I wrong?
I'm trying to get rid of stray dogs.
Is their colony at fault?
The residents don't want
stray dogs in their colony.
If dad does not get ice
cream for their children...
he becomes a bad father.
Doesn't he?
The residents opposed the dog,
hence they are bad.
The Minister is bad!
Do you go to school?
Of course. you do!
Well...
I'd like to see...
what you're taught in school.
This book doesn't teach
you to lie or create a nuisance.
Where did you learn that?
Tell me.
From your parents?
Teachers?
Why aren't you answering?
Answer me!
Where did you learn all this?
I don't think they
have anything to say.
This farce is over.
I have to get back to serious work.
I have to worry about
the future of our country.
Let's go.
Good bye.
Viewers, we have to end--
Come again?
It's here, in my school book.
Page 23, paragraph four.
How about an example
of something right?
Buddy is our friend.
We had promised Fatka
that we will save Buddy.
Good!
We knew we might not win against you,
but we showed up for Buddy.
Your thugs would've captured Buddy...
if we hadn't helped him.
Fatka, would you
like to say something?
I used to feel bad that unlike
these kids, I would never go to school.
And I wouldn't turn out to be good.
But, I don't feel bad anymore.
Because adults seem to forget
all that they were taught as kids.
So, how does it matter
if one goes to school or not?
The verdict of the battle between the
Minister and the kids is before you.
We will see you next
week with a new issue to discuss.
We will ride on the small fairies
We will fly in the sky today
We will fly
They have labeled us with many tags
We will get rid of them all today
We will fly
Let us look at the world
Through our own eyes
Let us learn something
On our own
At a place where we wish
Somewhere far away
From your world
We want to build a school
Where we can teach you things
We want to remind you
What you have forgotten
We want to build a school
There's a line on our little palms
We look after it with utmost care
Buddy! Buddy!
Whoever we meet
We meet with a smile
Leaving the enmities behind
We will fly
Look
From our perspective once
Learn something from us
Once in a while
At a place where we wish
Somewhere far away
From your world
We want to build a school
Where we can teach you things