Encoded By CharmeLeon
B******!
Madam, no smoking in here.
Mahi Arora!
Come sit...
Madam...
Shinde, throw away her cigarette.
Yes, madam?
Do you want to
lodge a complaint?
Against whom?
Did you get into a fight?
Should l call for
a lady constable?
Did some one assault you?
lf you don't talk to me,
l am helpless.
Your phone is ringing.
At least answer your phone.
lf you don't talk,
how will we know what's wrong.
Please say something.
What's the problem?
Mahi... let's go.
- Come on, let's go!
- She wants to lodge a complaint.
Sorry, sir. There's no complaint.
Who are you?
l am her secretary.
Let's go.
Get up!
Mahi, get up.
Let's go.
Come on.
This way... good.
You shouldn't have
come to the police station.
Mahi, against whom do you
want to lodge a complaint?
Move away!
Allow us to go!
Mahi... Are you getting married
to Aryan Khanna?
What is your relationship
with Aryan Khanna?
Mahi, did you know that
lsha was attending the same party?
Mahi...
Out.
- l am ready.
- Action.
Mahi Arora.
What can l say about her...
Unpredictable.
But journalists like me have to use
adjectives for them.
So there were a few...
lmpulsive, vulnerable, drama queen.
Mahi Arora was a star...
but she was different
from the other actresses.
She was fabulous at interviews.
Her words,
they always struck a chord somewhere.
She was bit of a rebel.
And why not?
A broken family,
parents fighting everyday...
disturbed childhood...
And then?
Mahi got a reason to be wild.
And she fled her home to Mumbai.
lt's a well known fact
that the film industry...
adores complicated stories.
Thus, Mahi Arora became...
The star!
Good morning, Rashid bhai.
- Hi!
Happy?
- You are looking lovely.
- Yes!
- So, how's it going?
- All well.
Rashid bhai...
cancel all appointments for today.
But why, Mahi?
Well, l want to rest all day.
So l look fabulous
at the success party.
Alright.
- What do you think guys?
- Superb!
Like you always do.
By the way guys...
did you see Gayatri Reddy
at the premiere party?
My God!
She was bitching about you
to Rhea Mehra.
Really?
Can't these actresses
ever be happy for their peers?
Mahi, you must watch out, okay?
Please, Andy!
When have l ever
competed with them?
l just want to have fun.
Also, the film is a hit.
And, l've got some
good titles ahead.
So, who cares about
what they say?
l completely agree.
Gracy...
my cigarettes.
Anyway...
l've brought
some outfits along.
Please try them on, babes.
Let's decide what you will wear
to the party tonight.
No, l don't want to.
Choose any you like.
l will just wear that.
Okay then.
Red?
Red.
By the way,
Aryan is also attending the party.
Oh come on!
Has he ever attended
any of you functions?
He won't attend
like always.
Rats, come on, be positive.
lt's possible that
tonight he might attend.
God knows!
Sameer!
Sameer, l love you.
l love you Rhea!
Love you Danish!
Abbas Khan!
Hey Gayatri!
l love you Gayatri!
Angad, its said that,
soon you'll be promoted...
from Vice-captain to Captain
of the lndian Cricket team.
Well, this is a film party and...
l'd appreciate if you would not
talk about cricket now.
Gayatri, everyone's talking about
the rivalry between Mahi and you.
Would you like to
comment on that?
Mahi and l are just acquaintances,
there's no rivalry.
And l'm really happy that
Sameer and Mahi's film is a hit.
That is why l'm here.
Well, Abbas you...
you've been such a rare sight.
l am really surprised
to see you here.
l'm here to give my
best wishes to Sameer.
l heard you are
writing your biography.
Vibha!
Why do l have to write
my own biography?
There are plenty of ex-editors
from various publications.
Someone will do the honors.
That's so typical
Abbas Khan, you know!
- Hey Rhea!
- Congratulations.
You deserved it completely.
Yeah!
l told you that the
film will be a super hit.
Thank you.
- Your new film, Custody, is out, isn't it?
- Yes.
Everyone's been talking about
your performance.
But, you know, l've been so busy,
haven't had the time to watch it.
Oh! l'll have
a screening for you.
They're bonding
as if they were sisters.
Such hypocrites.
Meet Kalpana,
SM Channel head.
Hello.
This is Mukesh Tyagi.
He is a big project designer.
Meet Shaheen Khan,
she's an upcoming actress.
Her debut film 'Mumbai Love'
was out recently.
Wow! That's great.
She's also doing
two regional films.
He didn't make it.
l told you, right?
Get me a drink.
Mahi...
- Get me a drink, now!
- Okay.
Action!
Cut!
Number taken
clap out.
And 5... 6...
7... 8.
Cut... cut it.
Cut it.
Mahi, it's simply not happening.
We'll shoot after the break.
Break for lunch.
Mahi, you need to focus.
lf you need more reharsals,
then just do it.
Fine!
Please give her
some easy steps...
So many retakes...
Tablet.
l'm sorry, babes.
That jerk off, Sameer Khan.
l don't watch his films,
so how could l come for his party?
Well, the party was
for my success too.
And you told me
you would attend.
l couldn't say no
when you asked me.
l didn't want to hurt you.
You did the same by
not attending.
Rats told me that
you wouldn't come.
Come on, Mahi.
That psycho b****!
Why are you taking her seriously?
Because you
don't take me seriously!
That's nonsense, Mahi!
lt's true.
lf you took me seriously,
l'd know.
Babes! l am sorry, okay?
l f***** up! l am sorry.
Please babes, come on...
You know what...
l'm coming to your place,
after the pack-up.
l will make up for everything.
Aryan...
l've sent my passport
to your office.
The visa for the Bahamas
takes about 15 days.
For God sake, Mahi!
The Bahamas trip is three months away!
So what?
l am so excited.
This holiday is very
important for me.
We've never been on
a holiday together.
ls that my phone?
Where is it?
Perfect timing!
Yeah!
Really?
l'll be there in 20 minutes.
Yeah.
Damn!
Akshat isn't feeling well.
l've got to go home.
l am sorry babes.
Hey.
What's wrong with my Spiderman?
How're you feeling?
Since when does he
have a fever?
As soon as he got back from school.
He was feeling weak,
so l called the doctor.
Go to sleep.
You will be okay.
l love you.
Sorry, Aryan.
Akshat insisted to see you...
that's why l asked you to come over.
Were you at your place or at Mahi's?
How does it matter?
l see...
By the way, the lawyer called.
He said the divorce documents are ready and
l should sign them.
- So do it!
- l will.
But, l want to ask you something.
What have you thought about the
Bandstand apartment?
What's there to think?
l've told you before that
l am keeping it.
l've given you this apartment
as well as two more in Goa.
But l don't want it for me.
l want it for your son.
His school is nearby the place.
lsha...
you know l bought that apartment
for my parents.
You can move them
to your place in Malad.
This is unbelievable!
You know, l just can't believe this!
Three properties... 100 million settlement...
and you still want more!
l didn't expect this from you...
l too had a lot of expectations...
let's not go there.
lt's better you take a decision
about the apartment...
so l can sign the documents,
okay?
You are too much, lsha!
Thanks so much, Rhea,
for this exclusive interview. Really!
Anything for you, Tamanna!
You're coming with me
to Spain, okay?
l would love to. Thanks again.
Okay, bye baby, see you.
Yeah, Nisha?
What?
Really?
Shit!
l was certain it would happen.
No chance at all?
Sure?
Okay, l'll call you later.
Hey babes!
- Babes...
- Hi!
Babes, what happened?
You seem tense, what's wrong?
Do you know the owner
of Panache Diamonds?
- Yes, that dude, Jay Sanghvi, right?
- Yes.
What about Panache?
Their endorsement deal was
up for renewal.
- My team has been trying for the past two years.
- Okay...
But even this year,
they are continuing with Mahi.
lt's fine.
lt's not fine!
lf l get this deal...
it will be a clincher.
What now?.
You know...
Jay Sanghvi... he is bisexual.
And, he has the hots for you.
Listen...
l really need this.
Dude, not a word outside.
Bro... l know.
ln this industry,
both zippers and lips should be opened carefully.
Say hi to Rhea.
Okay, bro.
Mahi...
Rhea has won
the Panache Diamond endorsement deal.
lt's okay.
l can't endorse everything, can l?
You take everything very lightly.
Yes, mom.
l will see you soon.
- Are you going to Noida?
- Yes.
- Are you going for the dinner?
Hi mom.
Hi Mahi.
Hello Mahi, congrats.
l heard your film is a hit.
Yes!
When is the next release?
l don't know.
You can read about it in the papers.
Oh yes!
l've recommended you for the
Padamshree award.
Really?
Thanks.
Come...
You came to Delhi three times
last month.
Yet you didn't come here.
Well, if l had,
l would've had to meet your 'special' cabinet minister.
And, you know l don't like him.
What about your 'special' co-star?
The last time you were here...
you had said his divorce would
be finalized in six months.
lt's been eight months since then.
Did you talk to him?
Did he say anything?
- ls he marrying you or not?
- Mom, stop it!
All those questions!
Have l ever asked you
about your relationships?
Because you aren't my mother!
Look Mahi...
l know you are quite insecure
about this relationship.
And, one day this insecurity
will develop into an obsession.
lt could backfire and...
you'll be left with
neither relationship nor career.
l think you are confused, mom.
You are talking about yourself,
not about me.
l am very different from you.
My life is fully under control.
l am sure it is.
But do you know...
you had said the same about
your previous relationships?
Do you remember?
We'll complete the dubbing in the evening.
Next week you have two events.
A spa opening in Hyderabad and...
ajewelry exhibition in Jaipur.
Take care, Mahesh!
- Hi Tamanna.
- Hi Mahi.
You were here to interview my director?
Yes.
Ever since you joined Mumbai Daily,
you haven't called me.
Come on, Mahi.
lt's not that.
l was busy, that's all.
Busy?
With Rhea Mehra, right?
You've put her on the cover page
twice in one week!
ln fact, she does a lot for you.
Free vacations for your family...
new laptop for you... shopping in Dubai...
She is such a nice person!
That's absolute nonsense, Mahi.
Rhea is a close friend.
ln fact, l've known her even
before she became a star.
How sweet!
That's why you publish
all the negative things...
she has to say about me.
Mahi!
Wake up, Tamanna.
You are the associate editor
of Mumbai Daily.
Film stars aren't your friends.
They are friends with your position.
By the way...
speaking of positions...
l'm having dinner with
your group editor tonight.
l'm sure we'll talk about you.
B****!
Rats, where are you
Weren't you coming here?
What?
Are you serious?
Rashid bhai, pack-up for today.
Today is the last day, Mahi.
The dates are locked.
Tell them l got food poisoning.
That's it, Aryan.
Hold her close...
more passion Aryan...
feel it...
hold her close...
Gayatri, look into his eyes.
Yes!
That's good!
Aryan, bring in more passion...
Encoded By CharmeLeon
more passion.
Cut it! Cut it!
Encoded By CharmeLeon
Hello Mahi...
- Arup...
- Yes, ma'am?
- Tell your boss that l'm in his van.
- Yes.
What's going on, Mahi?
Encoded By CharmeLeon
You left your shoot to come here?
You didn't even tell me.
Are you spying on me?
Why? Can't l come?
Aryan, this love making scene
wasn't in the script.
There's only a month for the film's release.
And suddenly this scene pops up?
For God sake, Mahi.
Encoded By CharmeLeon
The director thought this was crucial
for the second half...
so he added the scene.
ls that so?
Why didn't you tell me about it?
What does that mean?
Encoded By CharmeLeon
Since when are we discussing
each other's scenes?
Why can't we?
We are even getting married soon.
The fact is you don't want to commit.
You want to keep
this macho playboy image...
and add such scenes
whenever you want to!
l can't believe this, Mahi.
l'm divorcing lsha.
What else do you want?
The divorce is not because of me.
We've been together for a year...
while you filed for your divorce
a year and a half ago.
l am not a fool.
l know everything,
okay?!
l don't know, Mahi...
how do l explain things...
l'm tired of your explanations.
l want a commitment...
do you understand that?
- lf you can't commit then...
- Then what?
Then what, Mahi?
lsha keeps nagging me
because of you and...
l can't deal with this, Mahi.
Mahi, l think we should
take a break.
We won't see each other
for a few days.
lt will give us both time to think.
Hopefully, until then my divorce
will also be through.
Let's see how it goes from there.
Aryan...
you know l didn't mean to say that.
l love you.
l hate that you keep this a secret.
At parties... you behave like a co-star.
lt scares me.
lt scares me a lot...
that you too will abandon me.
Why is this stuff so complicated?!
l just want us to be happy.
Please don't leave me,
please!
Please!
Hi Gayatri.
- Hi Rihan, how are you?
- How are you?
Good, come... sit.
What's going on? No gossip...
You have to give me something.
What's the latest inside scoop?
- You want some hot gossip?
- Yeah, baby, of course!
Come here.
Our shoot was interrupted
because of Mahi.
Oh really?
- This is tomorrow's headline.
- Okay!
Are you reading the book or
just looking at it...
like other actresses?
Very funny!
This is just not done.
Mahi, get hold of yourself.
Constant medication is not the answer.
Practice self-control.
Think positive... that's the best treatment.
Tanvi, right now l don't want a lecture.
l need my medication.
Are you writing the prescription...
or should l go somewhere else?
- Mahi...
- Write the damn prescription, will you!
Whatever!
And now...
the Best Debut of the Year - Female goes to...
the gorgeous, the beautiful...
Shaheen Khan!
Wow...
- Congratulations!
- Thank you so much!
- Well done.
- Thank you!
Thank you!
Thanks!
Debut of the year, wow!
Thanks to mom.
Thanks to my friends.
Thanks to my director.
Thank you so much.
This award is dedicated to
all the small town girls...
who dream to make it big in Bollywood.
That's it!
Her career is over.
How is that?
lt's bad luck.
My mom says, whoever got this award
never made it big.
l was also offered this award
but l refused.
And now, ladies and gentlemen...
The Monarch Universal
lifetime achievement award.
May l please call on stage...
the yesteryear legend...
Shagufta Rizvi.
And to present the award...
may l call on stage Mahi Arora and...
MD of Monarch Universal,
Mr. Hasmukh Thakur.
Congratulations Shaguftaji,
we are so happy for you.
Come please.
Thank you!
Good evening everyone.
People talk a lot after winning an award.
But l won't say a lot.
lf you start counting your memories,
their value fades away.
That's why,
l want to extend my gratitude to all the people...
who stood by me through everything...
and especially, to those who
didn't stand by me.
Because it is from them that
l learnt the most about life.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Akil bhai, nothing doing.
The deal was of 10 million
and an award.
You can't back out
at the last minute.
Listen Gayatri...
Everybody knows that
the 'Mahi and Aryan' pair is very popular.
They will get the
'Number one pair' award.
Popular, my foot!
Their pair if popular
only in the magazines.
My last picture with Aryan
was a super hit!
Especially overseas.
And, our next film as a pair
is out in two weeks.
lf l don't get this award...
l won't perform on stage.
You won't perform?
But Gayatri,
the award is decided by ajury.
- How can we...
- We can't do anything.
Okay.
Then why don't you get
the jury to perform.
Let me know.
Okay!
Come, let's talk to Aryan.
Hell yeah!
Hello beautiful...
- What?
- Make up, baby.
You look gorgeous.
Really?
What is it?
Nothing.
Just missing you.
- Really?
- Yes.
Coming into my room
just before a performance...
that means
you want something.
Tell me.
You really know me very well.
Actually... the thing is...
l have a request.
Aryan Khanna... A request...
This is serious.
Baby, the thing is...
my film with Gayatri
is due for release.
And the producer of the film
was wondering if the award...
that you and l were to get...
was given to Gayatri and me.
You know,
it would boost the publicity.
But that's...
that's only if it is okay with you.
Really.
What do you want?
Yes.
That's it?
l'd have said yes
even if you had sent a text.
Who cares about
a 'number one pair' award with you!
You and l are the real pair, right?
Always, my sweetheart.
- Make up!
- l don't care, baby.
- Prem, please cover that.
- lt's covered.
Look at dad, Akshat.
lt's quite dangerous
to perform such stunts.
How cool.
l will also become a hero like dad...
and do Superman movies!
- Of course you...
- Akshat!
How many times have l told you
not to talk to strangers.
You talk tojust about anybody!
Let's go!
Don't pull it.
lt goes off balance.
Stranger?
l mean, how dare she...
Relax.
Mahi... relax.
Just listen to me.
Aryan is with you.
He is divorcing lsha.
lt's obvious lsha is
venting her anger at you!
Andy...
Aryan should control lsha,
he didn't say a word to her.
How could he?
He was busy in the shoot.
He did not even know, darling.
Mahi, listen,
it doesn't matter what lsha does.
Aryan is serious about you.
Nothing else matters.
Bullshit!
lf he is so serious about you...
then why did he tell you not to attend
Rohan's anniversary party?
That's not what Aryan said.
All he said is, come to the party
after lsha leaves.
Right Mahi?
So tell me, what's wrong in that?
- Right Rats?
- lf you ask me, everything!
Mahi, Rohan is your co-star too.
And he has also invited you.
Why can't you attend?
Of course she can.
- But a little later.
- l don't think Mahi should go late...
That's nonsense Rats.
Why do you always have to
complicate things?
Seriously...
Oh, really?
Oh! Of course you are
looking fabulous.
You make a lovely couple.
Thank you so much, Abbas.
lt's our anniversary and
you are throwing this party!
lt's really sweet of you.
Don't be silly.
This was Zara's idea.
Thank my lovely wife.
Yeah totally.
These actresses are unbelievable!
She is cozing up to Rohan's wife...
to land a role in his next film.
Such a fraud!
Come on!
Who isn't!
Well, Rohan's wife was also an actress.
She want let it happen.
l like that!
l'll catch you around.
- Hey!
- Cheers!
Hey beautiful...
Shaheen Khan, she is hot.
What's the report?
Sameer Khan has been recommending her.
Really?
She is okay at acting
but nothing to be excited about.
l've heard that she doesn't meet
her co-stars after pack-up.
You know a lot about her.
Before that Danish Kapoor makes
a move on her...
l have to do a film with her.
Easy, Rohan.
lt's your first anniversary.
Or you'll end up using my divorce lawyer.
True!
Thank you, Angad.
Thank you so much.
l'm glad you took some time off
from the cricket series.
Oh come on!
You're like a sister to me.
l won a five day match in four,
just for you.
You're too sweet!
Come on guys, we have to
take a picture!
- Oh yeah!
- Anything for you Gayatri.
Hi Zara.
Mahi?
Sorry, l'm late.
Yeah.
Congratulations Sheena.
Thanks, Mahi.
lt's really not easy to spend
a year with Rohan.
You deserve an award for that.
Mahi, let's get you a drink.
l will help myself.
- Don't worry, Zara.
- Okay.
Guys, let's just chill.
- The worst thing that can ever..
- Hi!
Congratulations, Rohan.
What's up, Danish?
Hi Mahi...
Thanks, Mahi.
What a surprise!
Did you think l wouldn't come?
Have fun, Rohan.
Bye.
Yes ma'am.
- A glass of red wine, please.
- Sure.
Your drink ma'am.
What's this nonsense, Mahi?
l told you not to come here.
Please leave.
Why?
Rohan is my friend too.
l am invited as well.
Stop this drama and leave!
What's the problem?
Every one here knows about us.
Why do you hide it?
Mahi, this isn't the place
to talk about it.
Don't worry, Aryan.
lt doesn't matter how you treat me...
l won't embarrass you.
Because l love you.
Damn it, Mahi!
A vodka tonic please.
Sure sir.
Mahi, leaving so soon?
At least finish your drink.
There, l've finished it.
And by the way...
l'm not leaving!
lt's not my fault Aryan...
l couldn't help it.
You only think about your image.
Does it matter to you
what people say about me?
That l am a loser.
And l am sick of it.
l was on my way out.
But that b**** of a wife you have...
why did she have to talk to me?
What the f*** does she mean...
at least finish your drink!
She provoked me.
l had to do something.
You never say anything to her.
So l had to!
Aryan, say something.
Every time l talk about us...
you never say a word.
Can't you see,
it is driving me crazy?!
Aryan, l really need to know.
Do we have a future?
Or are you just using me?
l can't deal with this any more!
Aryan, this isn't a film.
Say something...
l need to know.
Why the f*** aren't you reacting??
You want me to f****** react?
Mahi, just get out.
What do you mean by
'get out'?
l mean just get out!
Well known actress Mahi Arora
was seen at the local police station.
lt's said that she was there to
lodge a complaint.
But nothing has been confirmed yet...
Yes, mom.
l told you...
don't trust that b******.
Please, not right now!
Why don't you come to Delhi for a few days?
Just to get away from all this mess.
No, l...
Mahi...
lt's unfortunate that you publish
any nonsense you want to.
So you can go ahead.
But, l'm saying this for the last time...
Mahi is only a co-star. Nothing more.
Superstar Aryan Khannajust confessed...
that Mahi is only a co-star.
Nothing more.
As ajournalist,
every time l analyzed Mahi's situation...
l couldn't help but think that she is stupid.
But every time l met her,
l only had compassion for her.
She was so lost...
So alone.
She had a bi-polar disorder.
She was looking for real emotions,
in a success crazed world.
But alas!
Her split with Aryan Khanna...
her own insecurities...
finally, the film industry.
They all supported Aryan.
After all he was a superstar.
Actors that Mahi had helped in the past...
also abandoned her.
They all ruined her.
Mahi...
you can only lose to others when
you've lost to yourself.
You always look for happiness in others.
That's your problem.
Look for happiness in your work.
Concentrate on your career.
You just have to stop playing the victim.
Take charge!
Declare to the world,
that Mahi Arora is not over.
Hi...
l am Pallavi Narayan.
Will you have something?
No, thanks.
Mahi...
l'm not your regular PR person.
l build images.
l make brands.
But l am already a brand.
You are...
but a fading brand.
You have two small budget films...
some mid-level endorsements.
lf you don't take charge,
you will soon be over.
l have prepared a rough strategy for you
for the next year.
The first three months
we will build your image.
The next quarter we will get some,
A-list endorsements for you.
And then...
focus on some A-list films and
by the end of the year...
you will be back!
Bingo!
With a brand new image.
When the old image is so strong...
how can we build a new one?
You will do it.
lf you say something confidently...
then film industry even takes
the lie for a truth.
Your image is very confusing.
Neither a wild child
nor conventional.
The film industry doesn't like
confusing images.
But now that's over.
Your image will be of a
powerful star.
Who will be very confident
about her every move.
No matter what's troubling you...
always look confident.
You have to be a player now.
l will have a...
Vodka with coconut water.
How do you know?.
l know a lot about you.
Your favorite color,
turquoise blue.
Your favorite non-vegetarian food,
lamb ribs.
Your favorite holiday destination,
Koh Samui.
Don't worry.
l'm not stalking you.
Film magazines help me fall asleep.
Hi... Angad Paul.
Who doesn't know you?!
Vice-captain of the lndian Cricket team.
You know, we've seen each other
at some parties.
Last time, at Zara's party.
l know.
Encoded By CharmeLeon
l didn't want to bring it up...
l know, it was embarrassing.
You probably thought l was a
drama queen!
No,
l thought you have a lot of guts.
So, everything good now?.
Encoded By CharmeLeon
Everything's not good...
but l am.
Encoded By CharmeLeon
l have moved on.
And, how's Gayatri?
Encoded By CharmeLeon
You know... moved on.
l am so sorry.
Why sorry?
l'm not sorry at all.
Encoded By CharmeLeon
Even our drama was
all over the newspapers.
Didn't you read?
Encoded By CharmeLeon
l don't read newspapers and magazines.
Why?
Encoded By CharmeLeon
Who knows what people
are saying about us!
Cheers to that.
Cheers.
Alex, isn't Mahi looking gorgeous?
She is,
but how does it matter?
Who will sign her?
She's moody, impulsive,
over-emotional.
Alex, whether its
Hollywood or Bollywood...
every legendary actress has
these three qualities.
Oh yeah!
Now, no one can stop her.
Hope she survives.
From whom?
Herself!
Angad, you are crazy!
That's why you and l will get along well.
l think l should leave now.
l just had to be here.
l couldn't help it.
Thank you for rescuing me
from this boring party.
lf you wish,
l can rescue you every day.
What are you doing tomorrow?.
Anyway, whatever you were to do,
cancel it.
Really?
Tomorrow is my cricket match,
you must come.
lt will be fun.
Why?
Why...
Because if you do,
we will definitely win.
l'll think about it.
l'll try.
Good night.
Wow, Mahi!
lnvitation to the match.
That's great publicity.
Clever move.
Pallavi, that wasn't a move.
lf it wasn't, then it should be.
You have to go there tomorrow.
Go to the match.
And make sure
you are seen with him.
Angad Paul is a great catch.
Pallavi, he is a really nice guy.
But to manipulate him...
Mahi Arora...
this is the film industry.
Either you manipulate
or get manipulated.
The choice is yours, babes!
- Thanks, Lobo.
- Your welcome sir.
l was under a lot of pressure before the sixer.
So what did you do?
lf l can't concentrate, l sing.
When the bowler is taking his run-up,
l start singing.
At that time l was singing...
Khoya Khoya Chand...
Khula aasmaan...
...and then took a shot!
You really are mad!
By the way,
my team is grateful to you for my century.
And so am l.
Grateful?
Excuse me.
Yes..
Mahi...
in exactly ten minutes,
leave the restaurant.
And don't forget...
look surprised.
Yes, l will see you soon.
Okay, yeah bye.
What is it?
Nothing. Let's go?
Sure.
Yes, we will meet tomorrow.
Yeah!
Shaguftaji...
how are you?
How are you, Mahi?
l'm alright,
l was shooting on the next floor.
What are you doing here?
l have a shoot on this floor.
Why are you sitting here, in this heat?
Where's your van?
l guess l don't have one.
Since it's only a three day job,
l didn't get one...
You didn't?
- Excuse me!
- Yeah!
- are you from the production team?
- Yes.
Take care of that.
Yes, ma'am.
Where's Shaguftaji's van?
- Don't worry Mahi...
- What do l say!
The producer's wife keeps a tab
on every little thing.
A van for a character artist?
You tell me?
l am helpless.
l am sorry.
Shaguftaji, please come with me...
l'll manage.
When the shot is ready,
you can fetch her from my van.
- Yes, ma'am.
- Shaguftaji, please come.
Mahi, why do you get so upset?
l am used to these things.
We didn't have these vans
when l was a young star.
We would open an umbrella, sit under it...
and start shooting.
lt must've been difficult back then...
no privacy?
l don't know, Mahi.
The entire film unit would
do things together.
Directors, heroes, heroines,
side actors, junior artists...
everyone had a good time.
That's why nothing seemed difficult,
l guess.
ln those days,
relationships were valued a lot.
These days its fame and success.
But don't we become actors
for fame and success?
Yes, we do.
Whatever fame gives us...
it takes away a lot more from us.
We fail to see in the glow of glamour...
how much we have lost.
When we realize it, it's often too late.
Everything is on schedule.
l am so happy, Mahi.
Seven A-list endorsements
in four months.
11 high profile events and
you are on every cover page.
l think we are on the right track.
lt's all thanks to you, Pallavi.
That's all very nice but
you are essentially a heroine.
You have to sign a film.
Rashid bhai!
l think he is absolutely right.
A heroine gets commercials and
endorsements based on her films.
And, it's high time you signed a film.
Abbas Khan...
is making the remake of
a super hit South lndian film.
He's also shooting the entire film abroad.
lf you get this film...
you are home!
But l've heard that
he is considering Rhea Mehra.
Gayatri is also desperate to get it.
So, what are my chances?
We will know the answer to that
only if you try.
lt's very simple.
Either you join Rhea and Gayatri in the race...
and defeat them.
Or sit here and accept defeat.
lt's up to you.
Mind blowing.
Excellent shot.
We will set up for the next shot?
Yes, sure.
Okay!
l'm at a shoot, mom.
Talk to you later.
Just a minute, it's urgent.
Pratap's political party is organizing
a cleanliness drive in Mumbai.
He wants you to attend the event.
Forjust 10 minutes,
as the chief guest.
Tell him to contact Rashid bhai
and to finalize a deal in 2 million.
What? Are you crazy?
You will charge your mother?
That too for a social cause?
Stop over reacting, mom.
lt's the ruling party and they are loaded.
l'm doing it for 2 only for you
otherwise l charge 3 million!
Mahi, please.
l've promised Pratap.
You know...
Mom, l don't have time for this.
We'll talk later.
Surekha, come on.
Yes.
Rhea has been celebrating her
25th birthday for the past five years!
Surekha...
They write such things about every heroine.
No, you don't know.
She is very shrewd.
l know her since she was
a struggling model.
She knows very well how to be at the right place,
at the right time.
She will do anything to achieve her goal.
Madam...
Anything.
She is at least 31 years old.
She forged her age in her
birth certificate and passport.
l know it.
lt's true.
Remember the film 'Bad Boys'?
She made a passport before that film.
Anyway, what have l got to do with it.
l like to focus on my job.
l'm not at all interested in such gossip.
l forgot something...
the flowers!
Madam, l'll get the flowers.
Hi mom...
what were you saying about
Pratap Khurana's rally?
Fine, tell him l will do it.
Done deal.
Long live, Pratap Khurana!
Mahi...
l request Mahi to say a few words.
Thank you!
Actually, l don't know a lot about politics.
But what l do know is that...
a cleanliness drive is important for every city.
l'm happy that Pratapji and the national party
have organized this.
And l shall begin
the drive from his constituency.
Say it with me...
Clean Mumbai, Healthy Mumbai!
Thanks, Mahi.
l know film stars get paid a lot
to attend events like this one.
But you're doing this only for your mother.
l am really grateful to you.
Any time, Pratap uncle.
Let me know if l can ever help in any way.
Thanks.
Actually, l'd like a small favor.
Of course.
There's this actress, Rhea Mehra.
She has forged her age in her passport.
l think, if you could alert the authorities...
Yes, no problem. l will do that.
Shinde, hand me the passport.
What's the matter, officer?
Madam, you have to come with us.
But what's the problem?
We need to question you.
Get her.
Please come.
The breaking news at the moment.
Airport immigration authorities
have detained actress Rhea Mehra...
for forging her age in her passport.
Rhea Mehra was on her way to Paris
with her friends to celebrate her birthday.
Sources tell us that until the enquiry is through,
Rhea Mehra can't travel overseas.
We tried contacting her,
but could not get through.
Nice?
Very nice.
l think it's perfect.
- What do you think?
- lt's beautiful.
l am very happy.
You are looking beautiful.
Why don't you try the other
three outfits too, please.
But that commercial is after 10 days.
lt's fine.
l know but l want to finish the alteration soon.
Thanks to Rhea's passport controversy...
Gayatri is doing Abbas' next film.
And that diva!
She won't wear any of Rhea's outfits.
She has changed the entire look.
Two weeks before the shoot!
Just imagine, l am so harrowed...
Mahi, what's wrong?
What?
l don't know, l was just wondering...
Does Abbas have a problem with me?
Even l wanted that role.
l sent Abbas a long text...
but he didn't reply.
Weird!
Michelle, excuse us for a minute, please.
Sure.
Thank you.
A text to Abbas? Are you crazy?
Abbas cannot reply to any heroine's text.
lf he does, his wife Zara will kill him.
Yeah!
After his affair with Christina,
Zara gave him an ultimatum.
lf he does any hanky-panky with any heroine...
he will be a dead man.
ln fact, Zara handles the casting of
heroines for Abbas' films.
She chose Gayatri.
See, it's just between you and me.
Don't say it was me.
Just telling you as a friend,
okay?
Let's try other outfits.
Come on...
Michelle..
This is your third cigarette.
Why are you so tense?
What's wrong?
Nothing.
What's the matter, my dear?
Work stress, Angad.
My career is going downhill.
What nonsense!
Film offers are pouring in.
You're doing commercials.
Media is writing about us.
What else do you want?
The films offered are not interesting.
Commercials don't really help.
You will be fine.
Angad, l never do this but...
l'm comfortable with you and
so l'm saying this.
Please talk to Zara for me.
Abbas is doing Nikhil Anand's film.
lf Zara's recommends,
Abbas won't refuse.
But Mahi...
l've never discussed
Abbas' professional life with Zara.
lt's a bit weird, you know.
l know.
But l believe l am perfect for this role.
Abbas has signed Gayatri and
you know how she is.
Anyway, forget it.
l don't want to force you.
What's the worst that could happen?
My career will be over.
And l'll end up buying a cricket team
with some businessman!
What else?
Zara...
You know Abbas and l know Gayatri.
She is a slut.
You know about outdoor shoots.
Abbas' affair with Christina?
You plan on going back to your mother again?
Angad, all actresses are like that.
Who can you trust?
l mean, we need an actress.
There is one safe option,
Mahi.
Abbas knows she is seeing me,
he will be careful.
With all due respect,
Mahi is no saint either.
l've heard and seen a lot about her.
But now she is with me.
You know l am serious about her.
Otherwise l wouldn't be here.
Angad, don't you like anyone
apart from actresses?
The others aren't as beautiful.
Please talk to Abbas about Mahi.
For me, please!
Please talk to Abbas.
Head and Shoulders
Shampoo and Conditioner.
Cut please!
We are done with this shot.
Thank you!
Okay, so l'll wait in the van.
Go for your next change.
Your call.
Hi...
You are joking!
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
Yeah!
l will see you in the evening.
Bye.
Hi Pallavi... Angad called.
l have some breaking news.
l'm Abbas Khan's heroine in
Nikhil Anand's next film.
Spread the word!
Angad, is it?
No.
You know something,
Nikhil is a slave driver.
He's made us work for
seven days straight.
l mean, it's an outdoor shoot,
and not even a day's break.
Totally exhausted.
Anyway, l'm calling for an
early pack-up today.
Need to relax.
l want a glass of red wine.
Hey... you like red wine, right?
Yeah.
ln fact,
some fan here gave me this bottle of a...
50 year old Chateau Margaux.
Wow.
l would hate to have it alone.
Why don't you come over to my room.
We'll have it together.
What's wrong?
You see...
l'm on antibiotics.
So, l can't drink wine.
For how long?
About three days.
That's not a problem.
Today is Tuesday, we'll have it on Friday.
l'll tell Nikhil to give the crew
a day off on Saturday.
So that we will have
all the time on Friday night.
Good idea.
Coming...
Hey!
Hi.
Looking gorgeous.
Thank you.
Come in.
Surprise!
What's up, man!
What do you think?
Mahi got this idea to surprise you.
Fantastic!
Come...
Hey.
l have to say, Abbas.
Of all your heroines,
Mahi is my favorite.
Yes l agree.
From now, Mahi is my favorite too.
- Come...
- Yeah!
So what are you love birds upto?
Red wine, Mahi?
Sure.
Nice, very nice.
Abbas, getting Gayatri to do an item number
was a fab idea.
l know.
The first trailer should feature only this song.
ln fact, the publicity for the film should...
only focus on this item number.
Also, get a poster featuring only Gayatri.
Solo poster?
But Mahi is the heroine.
And the hero?
This film is on my shoulders.
Mahi is yours.
Deal with it.
Wow!
You were fantastic, baby!
Thanks, dear!
- You are a genius, Abbas.
- Great job!
You did it man.
Thanks brother.
Hey... That was amazing,
l am so proud of you.
You look hot!
Great!
Abbas just rocked again.
Outstanding!
Thank you.
- Congrats, sir.
- Thank you.
50 million weekend opening! l'd predicted this.
Thank you!
Sir, mark my words,
your film will touch 1.5 billion, at least!
You suggested Mahi for our film.
She hardly had eight scenes and
she didn't even act well.
Alex, she looks lovely.
Oh come on!
We need an actress.
Not some... decoration. Mahi is out.
Congratulations, Abbas.
You did it.
No, Mahi, we did it.
Gayatri... Lucky mascot of my film.
Come... come.
There you are.
l'm glad you agreed to do this item song.
Thanks!
And you really rock,
you know that?
Come on Abbas!
Anything for you.
What is it, Mahi?
lt's not fair, Nikhil.
l'm barely visible in the film.
Mahi, you know Abbas.
Once the shoot is over,
right from editing to publicity design...
Abbas controls everything.
He cut me out of the editing too.
You know what, Mahi, cheer up.
Look around... at the public reaction.
The trade guys are predicting
a 1.5 billion business!
And, in our industry, only hits matter.
That's the success mantra, right?
Mahi, you were brilliant.
Absolutely mind blowing
Thank you!
Announce a sequel.
lt has to rock.
Nikhil, Gayatri's item number
was a killer.
Thanks.
- Congratulations bro.
- Thanks bro!
Second half was mind blowing,
this film will make 1 billion.
Mahi looks upset.
Her role was reduced to nothing.
lt's obvious.
She pissed off Abbas, Aryan...
if she does this to every hero...
she will end up
a thumbnail on the posters.
Mahi.
Let's go.
Calm down, Mahi.
What do you mean, calm down?
Not one good review.
The critics are saying, 'Abbas Khan is the star
and Mahi is just a showpiece'!
My role was chopped off!
The film is a super hit,
and that's all that matters.
You've got three calls
for endorsements!
You've been offered two major films.
Pallavi...
Encoded By CharmeLeon
am l a good actress?
Come on, Mahi.
Encoded By CharmeLeon
Answer the damn question.
Am l a good actress?
Encoded By CharmeLeon
Or not?
Mahi, you are a star.
You don't need to be an actress.
l do.
Encoded By CharmeLeon
l do, indeed.
Mahi Arora.
You're a big star.
Encoded By CharmeLeon
Why do you want to do
a Tapan Guha film?
You know l'm
an eccentric film maker.
My next film, Tarranum Jaan,
is about a prostitute.
lt has sex...
Encoded By CharmeLeon
abusive language.
l make realistic films...
while you're a commercial heroine.
l work on a small budget.
And stars like you have
a thousand issues.
l promise, Tapanda,
that won't happen.
Listen, this is my
first Hindi language film.
You won't have free dates...
your price is a problem.
l have a start-to-finish schedule.
You can't take up
any other work for six months.
What say?
You decide the dates
and the price.
When do we start?
Keep it properly.
Dada, how's it going?
The traffic in Mumbai...
Ma'am, sit.
Hi!
l am Promita.
Of course, Promita Roy.
Oh, please sit.
You know, Mahi...
l am so glad you're doing this film.
lt's a kickass script and
your role is superb.
l know but l'm not sure
if l can do this.
- Why?
- lt's the first time l'm doing such a film and...
l haven't won as many awards as you.
Please!
l don't take these
awards and critics seriously.
Perhaps that's why they take me seriously.
You know, Mahi...
this film will transform
your glamorous image.
l'm a regular fixture in dada's films.
l've done four films with him...
and that's why l'm in this too.
What's that term...
Special appearance!
Alok, get me a cigarette.
Mahi...
Don't smoke in public
or this isn't your brand?
Let's go over the lines.
Promita, lt is not just lines...
concentrate on your acting.
Hey, you please switch off your phone.
Concentrate on your scene.
Do you remember your last line?
We will be zooming in.
No, i don't want.
Cut! Cut it!
Mahi, feel the complexity of the emotions...
Please lie down.
Listen, l am the customer
who is looking at you.
Mahi...
Yes, dada.
Now we will shoot scene 20.
This is a four-page scene.
We will shoot one shot,
one scene, no cut.
You have to memorize all your lines...
and you have one hour.
Here, get started.
But... one hour?
This is how small budget films are.
Cut down on the BBM
and concentrate on your work.
Hi!
Hi! When did you arrive?
That's a cold reaction.
l thought you'd be happy to see me.
Of course, l am.
lt's just that l'm drained
and l've a four-page scene.
Excuses!
l called you, l sent texts...
you didn't answer.
This isn't a match
to keep score of the calls.
Oh please!
Look, this is an intense film.
l have to concentrate on
my performance every day!
You're lucky.
lf l don't talk to you,
l can't concentrate on my performance.
That's why l keep calling you.
All season l was...
l am sorry.
l forgive you!
Surprise!
We've been dating for a year.
lt's time to get married.
My family is also happy for us.
Angad...
l don't know what to say...
Say, 'yes'!
Look, l really appreciate it...
but right now, l'm just not in
the frame of mind.
l need some time.
Of course, baby.
You can take all the time you want.
But say yes, my dear.
What are you saying?
Don't tell me what to do.
One day no budget forjunior artist,
the next day, cut down on shoot days.
And you expect me to make a film?
l've made five films!
And four have won the National award.
l know this is my first Hindi feature film,
but do not take me for granted.
l've seen the rubbish you've
made with big stars.
Tell your bosses...
they can't make a film sitting in
the comfort of an AC room.
l sweat and toil to make a film.
l know that, dada...
Do not disturb me on the set like this.
Dada, listen...
Let me concentrate, please!
Now what?
l'll sort this, don't worry!
Partho!
Action!
You slut!
You're stealing my customer.
Hey! l don't need to steal.
He chose me.
You're lying.
This is the third customer you've taken.
Stop doing that or
l'll smash your face so bad...
you'll look scary in the dark too.
Cut it!
What is wrong, Mahi?
You sound like a machine.
Feel the character.
You are not Mahi, the heroine...
here you are my character,
Tarranum, the prostitute.
Feel the character.
This kind of acting is fine for Bollywood,
not for my cinema.
Make her more real.
Realism.
You bloody idiot!
Give me that phone.
Get out, go and kneel down.
Where was l...
No, can't happen like this.
Pack up!
Just relax, Mahi.
The thing with dada is...
he wants realism in everything.
And he feels you can't portray that realism.
But, relax, it will come.
l don't know what dada wants me to do.
l know.
Get dressed and come with me.
Come on! Get ready.
A lot of foreigners come here.
l mean, what do you call that
oh yes, documentary.
- Come here, handsome!
- Don't worry about anything.
Come.. come..
Don't worry about anything.
Promita, what place is this?
l am scared.
Don't be scared.
Just get in.
Aren't you...
the 'Halkat Jawani' girl?
Yes!
Mahi Arora.
l mean...
you are a fabulous dancer.
Can l get you some tea?
No, thanks, madam.
We are here to observe you.
We are shooting for a film.
And we're playing characters, just like you.
Really?
So you are here to study our mannerisms.
How these girls live, eat, abuse...
how they go about their profession.
All of you, listen to me.
These heroines here...
are saying that they will play our part.
lf you take up ourjob...
what will we do?
Well said, Hamida bai.
Well said!
Anyway
you can watch us all you want.
We are open for business.
Another thing...
we won't charge you to watch us...
unlike your movies.
- Don't you agree?
- Yes, madam.
Go on, you can talk to the girls here.
- Valli bhai...
- Yes, madam?
- Why don't you call for some kebabs?
- Absolutely!
Get it from Habib's counter.
Hamida bai...
the police are all over the place.
This way, quick.
l will lead you out through the back door.
Hurry up!
Let them out through the other exit.
This way.
Quick!
So, how was the research?
Wasn't it exciting?
Research?
Promita, you are crazy!
Being crazy is part of the excitement.
lt was an adventure.
That's what makes us better actors.
You need to relax, Mahi.
l need a drink.
Come on, let's go to my place.
You know...
you are a good actress, Mahi.
The pain that's within you is what
you need to express on screen.
Then you'll be miles ahead of everyone.
Never mind.
How many boyfriends have you had?
Don't look so shocked.
l'm sure you keep a count.
l've had 17.
The serious ones!
Don't worry, l don't want an answer.
You are beautiful.
By 4 take 2.
Action!
l told that jerk.
'You want it,
you do it here'.
'l'm not coming to some cheap hotel'.
Cut it!
Very good.
That was good.
Mahi, very good. Very nice.
What's the next shot?
By 2 Take 1!
That was nothing!
Now, listen to this.
A slut has four admirers.
One in the north, one in the east...
one in the west and
another in the south!
lmpressive, Tarranum Jaan.
Cut it!
Don't hit me.
Bloody theif!
- This is wrong.
- Get out!
Slimy jerk!
How dare you don't pay!
Cut it! Okay!
Very nice shot, Mahi.
Very good.
Very nice, Mahi.
- Very nice, isn't it?
- Absolutely!
Give me the script.
Mahi, please listen to me.
What happened that night, it was nothing.
lt was just a moment.
For God sake, l'm not a lesbian.
Anyway...
my special appearance...
today was the last of it.
l'm going back to Kolkata.
lt was great working with you.
l am sorry that we couldn't be friends.
l wish you all the best, take care.
Promita...
you take care.
Thanks.
Mom, stop it.
We had fun this weekend.
l shouldn't have come to drop you.
Mahi, getting irritated won't help.
You know l am saying the truth.
You know it's not easy
taking such decisions.
Why not?
You always complained that
Aryan wasn't ready to commit.
Now when Angad wants to marry you...
what's the problem?
Don't you love him?
Of course, l love him.
But right now,
l want to concentrate on my career.
He also has his career.
What's the rush?
Mahi...
whether you marry Angad or not,
is your decision.
But let me make this clear.
Tell Angad what's in your heart.
Don't keep him hanging.
Don't do to him what Aryan did to you.
Get it?
l knew it!
Everybody told me that you won't marry me.
l didn't want to accept.
Try to understand.
l'm not saying l don't want to marry you.
All l'm saying is right now we need to
give time to our careers.
What's the rush?
You wasted a whole year with that excuse!
How much more time do you want?
lt's all nonsense.
Just excuses!
When you heroines have love,
you chase a career...
when you make it big, you want love!
You greedy women!
lt's not that your career will end
if you were to marry me!
l was ajerk!
Angad!
l thought you were different.
l thought you weren't happy,
l wanted to rescue you...
l loved you, Mahi.
Angad, please!
Enough is enough!
l can't do this anymore.
Actresses like you can't love someone.
You can only act as if you do.
Please, relax.
You only know how to use others.
l don't want you anymore!
Hello...
What?!
Tapanda, you can't do this.
How can you shelve this film?
You can't shelve this film.
l can do anything l want.
Bloody corporate film makers!
They're trying to teach a National award
winning director to make a film!
Sometimes they say the film is serious,
sometimes they want humor.
They want to add an item number...
Bloody no aesthetic sense!
Teaching me to make a film!
l will talk to them. l'll sort everything.
No, it won't help.
l've decided l'm not making this film.
But...
how can we shelve this film now?.
Because of this film...
l sacrificed all other work!
Now you're walking away from it!
Mahi!
Tapanda, please!
l have lost all patience.
l know you've put in a lot of effort for this film.
l know you've sacrificed a lot,
but everything is not lost.
This experience will...
make you a better actress.
Tapanda, please!
That's when you'll thank me.
Bless you.
Tapanda...
Gracy, just get out.
Pull the blinds.
Just go!
They say...
to make good friends,
you have to be one yourself.
Unfortunately film stars can't think of anyone
but themselves.
lf Mahi had a true friend...
she wouldn't have been so scared...
wouldn't have made so many mistakes.
Tarranum Jaan was a big mistake.
And Mahi resorted to punishing herself.
She was ruined.
Her rivals and newcomers
replaced her.
Shagufta Rizvi was the only person
with whom Mahi felt at peace.
When l met her during that time,
l wrote...
that Mahi had brought
this upon herself.
lt didn't matter
whose fault it was...
it still hurt.
Encoded By CharmeLeon
Poor Mahi.
The things she did to get rid of her pain.
So, what have you decided?
We've heard that you
are seeing a psychiatrist.
Encoded By CharmeLeon
You have also mentioned that
you drink regularly.
Encoded By CharmeLeon
So...
Having scrutinized your family background
and your professional life...
the adoption panel has concluded that...
you are incapable of being a single parent.
lncapable?
What do you mean?
How did they decide?
Have they ever seen me... met me?
Some forms tell you
l am not capable?!
Tell me, sister.
Encoded By CharmeLeon
Tell me.
Mahi...
Encoded By CharmeLeon
To become a good parent,
you need patience and emotional control.
Qualities which you clearly don't have.
Practice for a few more years...
and apply again.
Good day.
Sister, you can't do this.
This is wrong.
l will sue you.
Do you understand?!
Yes, l take psychiatric help...
Yes l drink, so what?
Let's go...
come on!
So what?
l'm not fit to be a mother?
Let's go...
l will sue you!
Hi Mahi.
What is this, Pallavi?
You should be happy.
So what if you couldn't adopt,
at least you are on the front page.
You need to pay
to get such coverage.
What nonsense!
How could you release
this story without my consent?
Excuse me?
Since when do l need your consent?
You've forgotten the time...
when l made you sneeze into a storm?
You didn't object then...
there was no problem.
Because this is my personal life.
Wake up, Mahi!
ln this industry, there's no difference between your
professional and personal life.
Your life...
is public property.
l used it to plan your comeback.
And now you've ruined it.
Thanks to my PR skills,
you still make headlines...
and that makes you interesting.
What else do you have?
No films, no relationships...
actually, nothing!
Get out!
Right now!
You are fired.
And don't ever show me your bloody face.
Get out!
Can't face the truth, can you?
Someone has rightly said...
There are people and
then there are actors.
Mukesh, Mahi has given you
two super hits.
One with Rohan.
She deserves to do another film
with you. Please.
Rashid bhai, you know very well that...
things in the film industry change every Friday.
Mahi's last hit was with Abbas.
And that was a year ago.
Moreover she's not on good terms
with the heroes.
Not just me, no hero
would want to work with her.
Not to forget that crazy phase...
that film on prostitutes...
Tarranum Jaan!
She wasted nine months.
Nine months!
ln these nine months so many
fresh faces have been launched.
The industry waits for no one.
Mahi is neither professional,
nor a box office success.
l have a suggestion.
Tell Mahi to do a reality series.
Or marry a rich NRl.
Mukesh, look at this...
South of France.
Mind blowing.
Superb, isn't it?
Great job, fantastic.
Alright, Mukesh. See you.
Mahi...
the lifespan of a heroine is
quite short in our industry.
lf you sit here doing nothing,
you'll lose that too.
What can l do, Rashid bhai?
Nobody is giving me any work.
There's a good script,
it's a small budget film.
The director and producer are new.
What's that term...
New wave cinema.
Shall l fix a meeting?
There's also an offer
to make an appearance.
At the wedding of an industrialist's daughter...
you'll be the bride's friend.
The money is good.
What do you say?
Ladies and gentlemen...
Here is your seat ma'am.
Alright!
Here is your boarding pass.
Thank you.
l'll get it for you.
Hi...
Won't you invite me in?
You look beautiful.
l know, l have hurt you a lot.
l often thought about talking to you.
But l just couldn't.
Then l saw you on the flight and...
l realized how much l missed you.
We were so happy.
What do you want, Aryan?
l love you, Mahi.
After we broke up, l realized that...
l know what you're thinking.
After we broke up, l had three affairs.
You know what...
l...
l kept comparing them to you.
And l was disappointed.
They were just not like us.
l really love you, Mahi.
Why?
Why now?.
Because no one ever loved me like you did.
l know...
l know all of this seems sudden.
But, really... think about it.
We were really good together.
Please, come on.
l would've done the same if l were you.
So, l guess this is it then.
You are precious, Mahi.
Take care.
Aryan.
l am so sorry...
l am so sorry.
ln the battle between the heart and the mind,
the heart has always won.
ln any case, Mahi never followed her mind.
Mahi and Aryan patched up...
and her career restarted
with a small budget film, 'Annie'.
Aryan was serious about her,
but Mahi was not sure.
The wounds of her past were still fresh and...
she found accepting this difficult.
Though Mahi was living with Aryan,
she wasn't with him.
Having a rough day, Mahi?
Not at all.
l've noticed you don't seem happy...
not as much as you should.
Mahi...
How will l know if you don't tell me?
l don't know...
There's this fear that...
if l'm too happy...
all this will end.
The past...
keeps haunting me.
Listen, Mahi...
things need time to heal.
We need to give some time...
to our relationship, to each other.
for things to be normal.
l think l have a plan.
Let's do a film together.
A big budget period film.
Alex and l are producing it.
On that pretext...
we will be together.
That will be our comeback.
What do you think?
l think we will have a blast.
Please, Andy, don't tell anyone about this film.
Aryan hasn't made it official yet.
lt is a period film and l want you to
research the costumes thoroughly!
Anyway, Andy, we'll talk later.
Yeah!
See you later.
Hello ma'am.
Please sit.
Thank you.
Mr. Nair, Annie is due for release in two weeks
but there's no publicity.
There's no buzz.
The promos are aired a few times
but not on all channels.
How will that help?
What can l say.
We had allocated 30 million for the publicity but
you had the climax reshot.
The publicity funds were used for that.
But the new climax has improved the film.
Anyway, now we have to be aggressive.
Get a new PR company.
Radio, TV...
the publicity of Annie should be all over.
This film...
has to be a hit!
Definitely. We will try our best.
We have to!
We're investing 1.5 billion for this film.
lt's already a very risky project.
We can't afford to increase
the risk by signing Mahi.
She is over, Aryan.
What?
l am sorry.
l didn't mean that.
But our company is new.
This is our first film.
We need a blockbuster.
Everything should be new.
Music, casting, locations, everything!
The audience has seen you and Mahi.
And they love us.
They used to.
Come on!
The audience always wants
a new lead pair.
l spoke with the distributors.
They will buy into it if we sign Shaheen Khan.
She has had two super hit films.
She is the star of the moment.
And she has got dates.
You discussed this with her?
Relax.
l sort of talked to her secretary.
Alex, l've promised this film to Mahi.
And l am really serious about it.
Yes, l can see that.
No wonder you're getting emotional.
But, please Aryan...
l'd suggest you keep your
professional and personal life separate.
Don't mix them.
Besides, l'm not saying
you shouldn't work with Mahi.
We will adjust her in our next film.
She is not right for this film.
Look at the budget.
Just think about it.
Very less corwd.
What will we say?
l couldn't help it.
There are two major events,
so they've gone there.
They promised they'll show up...
let's see.
You should've changed
the press conference dates.
This doesn't make sense.
Sorry, Mahi.
Shall we start.
Mahi, are you marrying Aryan?
Does that mean, you will retire?
We are here to talk about 'Annie'.
Let's concentrate on this.
No personal questions, please...
l request you to stick
to professional questions.
You are right, Mahi.
So, let's talk about your professional life.
So answer this professional question...
There are rumors that you had signed
Aryan's home production...
and now you've been replaced by Shaheen.
ls this because you are
not the star you once were?
Your response?
Actually, you journalists should write film scripts.
The stories you create to get back!
lf a heroine buys a car, its a gift from a businessman.
lf she buys a diamond, she is engaged.
lf she goes to a hospital, she's getting an abortion.
lf she visits LA, it's for plastic surgery.
God forbid if she goes to Dubai...
you create a rate card for her!
People should learn to make stories from you!
You are digressing.
You still haven't answered my question.
You do know you're no longer part of
Aryan's home production, don't you?
That is not true.
l am the heroine in Aryan's film.
There's your answer!
Any questions about Annie?
Any question?
l guess not.
So, let's wrap this up.
Mahi...
Mahi please...
What attitude!
She has gone mad.
What nonsense is this.
Yes, Rats?
Mahi, l've been calling you...
why didn't you answer?
l was at the press conference.
That's precisely why l wanted to talk to you.
Everybody is saying that Shaheen has replaced you.
l know.
Tamanna asked the same thing.
lt's true.
l just spoke to Shaheen's secretary.
They have even discussed the dates.
Shaheen is doing Aryan's film, not you!
l will talk to you later.
Do you want me to twist my ankle?
Come on Aryan.
Give us some easy steps.
We need to talk.
Now!
Just a minute.
You are lying, Aryan.
Did you talk to Alex?
No, l told you l didn't talk to Alex.
You didn't?
That means l am still doing your film?
Okay, listen...
l talked to him...
See! l knew it!
Baby, please listen to me.
l talked to him but we didn't decide.
He wanted to sign Shaheen.
And that got you excited!
Couldn't you tell him that l am doing this film?
You are still doing this film.
Let me talk to Alex.
Fine, talk. Do it now.
Relax, Mahi.
l will do that in my time.
Everything will be fine.
Liar!
You said the same thing when
you were with lsha.
l shouldn't have trusted you.
You are a cheat.
Liar!
Bloody b******!
Relax, Mahi!
lt's not as big as you're making it out to be.
Really?
Then why don't you say that
l am the heroine of your film?
Because l need to talk to Alex.
There are many other decisions.
After all the budget is 1.5 billion.
Relax, l'm telling you l will sort this out.
l'm not a star anymore...
that's why you're doing this.
Baby, that's not true.
Really, then tell me...
that l am the heroine of your film!
Mahi, listen.
Tell me now!
Am l the heroine of your film or not?
You are for me!
Wow!
What an answer!
You care about no one!
Come on, Mahi!
l just knew it, you care about no one.
Alex, l told you l wasn't sure about Shaheen.
Then why is the media talking about it?
You know how the media is.
A mere mention
and they create headlines!
What nonsense!
No one apart from you knew about this.
Anyway, l can only do this film with Mahi.
Why are you getting so emotional about Mahi?
This is not an emotional decision.
Go through the script. Mahi is perfect for the part.
Either we do this film with Mahi.
Or we don't!
Okay?
Aryan...
Silly chap.
Ram...
Aryan Khanna's film is shelved.
Come on, Mahi...
pick up.
Come on, pick up...
- What's wrong, sir?
- Nothing.
Sir, your ticket to Delhi.
You have to go from here,
we're running late.
Just cancel this, please.
Sir, how can l cancel it?
People are expecting you.
How dare he...
Mahi is a star!
l will not spare him.
l'll show that b******.
l am not over.
Yes, Mahi?
Where are you?
l'm at home. What is it?
Come to my place.
Now?.
Yes, right now!
Please.
That's not possible.
Pallavi, l need you here,
right now.
Mahi, what's the matter?
l will tell you when you get here.
Come here now.
lt's too late...
l cannot come.
Forget the damn time!
Pallavi, come here.
Right now!
Alright, Mahi, calm down.
l'll be there.
That b****** Aryan!
Encoded By CharmeLeon
He has signed Shaheen for his film.
Pallavi, you have to do something.
l need 'Annie' to be a hit.
This film has to work, professionally
and personally.
l am sorry, Mahi.
There's nothing l can do.
'Annie' will hit theatres in two days.
Even if you start a publicity campaign
and spend on marketing...
it won't help this film.
You have to do it.
Please Pallavi.
Please!
You are my only hope.
Think of a gimmick.
Encoded By CharmeLeon
You have to do it
'Annie' has to be a success.
At least on the day of release.
Encoded By CharmeLeon
'Annie' is a small budget film...
centered around a woman.
Only a controversy can get people
to watch this film...
but, we have nothing.
l don't care!
You can do it.
l know, only you can do it!
l know...
l know, you can do it.
Do something...
please!
What can we do...
What will help to sell the film?
You don't have anything to sell
the film on.
l have something.
l have...
Will this do?
Genius, Mahi.
Yes, Pallavi?
Mahi...
the tapes have been leaked.
Listen... don't answer any calls.
And, don't react at all.
Hello?
Why are you screaming?
What is it?
Bollywood woke up to a furore as...
Mahi Arora and Aryan Khanna's
tapes were leaked online.
This clip has surfaced one day before...
the release of Mahi's film.
We still don't know if this video is real or morphed.
Bollywood is silent.
We've tried to reach
many eminent personalities...
but no one is willing to comment.
Nearly every one is unreachable.
ls this a tactic against Mahi...
or a cheap publicity stunt?
Mahi Arora's career is down but...
l don't think any girl would
do that to herself.
l am sure someone has morphed the video.
There should be an enquiry.
Mahi is in shock right now...
and she can't give a statement.
The video is doctored.
l request the media...
not to give this video undue attention.
But if people think that Mahi...
has done this to publicize her film...
then l feel they have lost their mind.
Thank you.
This clip has surfaced one day...
before the release of Mahi's film.
ls this a tactic against Mahi...
or a cheap publicity stunt?
Down with Mahi...
Oh shit!
Ma'am, shall l set the table?
No, you can eat.
Okay, ma'am.
Yes, Pallavi?
Mahi... it's a bumper opening.
Both multiplexes and
single screens are rocking.
Really?
We have done it.
l will keep updating you.
Bye.
Based on the crowd behind me...
it is obvious that either Mahi's video...
was a well orchestrated stunt or a fake.
Whatever it was...
it seems to be helping Mahi's film...
pull in the crowd.
The Mahi Arora CD controversy...
seems to have helped her dipping career...
as her latest film, 'Annie'...
shows the silver lining at the box office.
With a record breaking first day collection.
We are Mahi's fans and we will watch 'Annie'.
We love Mahi.
Due to the controversy...
people will watch 'Annie'
Even l will watch it.
What do you have to say about the controversy?
l can't comment on the controversy.
But the film is a super hit in our theatre.
You can't trust movie stars.
They will go to any lengths
to make their film a hit.
Mr. Prahlad Kakkar, what do you
have to say about this controversy?
Who will decide if the CD is real or fake?
There's no point in debating this...
everyone has their personal choices...
then why so much of drama?
After all it's a democratic country...
Rashid bhai, you don't look happy.
You think this is wrong?
How does it matter?
Your film got a bumper opening.
Both multiplexes and single screens
have reported 95% bookings.
As for right and wrong...
who am l to say.
All l know is...
the Mahi l had met ten years ago...
she...
would've asked this question
before anything could happen.
Not after.
Here is your calendar.
you don't need me anymore.
Sir...
the media is waiting for you.
You have to say something.
ls Mahi's film a success?
With a scandal like this,
the film had to do well.
That's all l have to say.
Okay, sir.
Thank you.
Thank you, Mr. Tony!
Not right now. She is very tired.
She can't talk right now,
but l will convey your message.
Thank you.
Okay. Bye.
Mr. Vikram...
With the offers pouring in...
Mahi will be busy for the next two years.
Right...
l can only promise you
one film, not two.
But l will surely get her to talk to you
Alright, bye.
See you.
There Mahi...
this is the fact about our industry.
One success and they are all back.
Anyway...
have you thought about what you're
wearing to the success party?
A gown, maybe?
Mahi, this controversy will fade away.
ln a few days, people will forget about it.
You should too.
l'll see you.
Hello, Manish...
The media was trying to locate Mahi...
while she is here at
Shagufta Rizvi's funeral.
lnform them to send the team here
right away!
ln this film industry that
venerates the rising star...
no actor has come to attend the final journey
of beloved actress Shagufta Rizvi.
ldiot, Mahi is inside.
Mahi Arora! Come on.
- Cut!
- Let's run this later.
We fail to see in the glow of glamour...
how much we have lost.
When we realize it, it's often too late.
Hey Mahi.
Mahi, Please tell us...
has bollywood hit their own with you scandle?
What is the hidden story behind it?
ls it true that you leaked the tape?
Your PR company...
Excuse me, aren't you Mahi Arora?
No.
This answer simplified Mahi's complicated life.
For years she looked for happiness
outside the crowd...
and in the end,
she found it by being part of the crowd...
living an ordinary life.
Encoded By CharmeLeon