Listen it's 9.30 pm,
Let's put off all the lights.
Okay.
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
Rocks.
Why did you choose such
a controversial subject..
..for your first movie?
Look.. madam.
You only see sex..
..controversy and
scandal in Ragini MMS.
I..
I..see a story.
A boy takes a girl
to a lonely bungalow..
..for a dirty weekend.
Out there he shoots an MMS video.
The MMS goes viral.
The boy..went missing.
The girl says that there
was a witch in that house..
..who killed the boy.
But we cannot entirely
trust the girl.
Because it's said that..
..the girl went insane
after the incident.
Since the last 3 years..
..she's been in a mental asylum.
Now that is a story.
I will shoot my film..
..where Ragini's MMS was shot.
Horr-ex film.
A combo of horror and sex.
And after watching the
film the audience won't know..
..whether to be terrified or excited.
Rocks, one more question.
- Go ahead.
You've worked with all
the top actors in the industry.
But you've hired
TV stars for your film.
Is it because after
your last movie flopped..
..no big actor wants
to work with you?
This was a conscious
decision, okay.
My story.
My story is real.
This incident is real. Stars.
Stars will make it look fake.
And as for the female lead,
that is a surprise.
She's an actress that makes..
..all the other stars
run for their money.
She is going to put the..
back into Ragini.
Ladies and Gentlemen,
I present you..Ragini.
"There are many
beautiful-beautiful girls..."
"But all eyes staring at you..."
"There are many
beautiful-beautiful girls..."
"But all eyes staring at you..."
"But what do I say about me.."
"Even the moon praises me..."
"Every part of my body.."
"Oh my baby doll of gold.."
"This world is of copper.."
"Because of dancing all
night your feet are paining..
..let me apply Zandu balm on them.."
"You will feel tired because of dancing
too much, take rest in my arms.."
"Because of dancing all
night your feet are paining..
..let me apply Zandu balm on them.."
"You will feel tired because of dancing
too much, take rest in my arms.."
"My anklet will keep creating
noise if your feet pains.."
"I will apply Zandu balm on them.."
"My anklet will keep creating
noise if your feet pains.."
"I will apply Zandu balm on them.."
"Everyone always talks about me."
"This world is of copper.."
"Oh my baby doll of gold.."
Thank you. Thank you.
Hold it.
The action was superb.
What an entry.
Is this skull fine?
And you are?
- Gina. Art department.
Yes, whatever.
Leave it.
We'll make a blockbuster.
Yes, daddy. - Tanya.
Hi.
Is that Ashish Kapoor? - Yes.
Please tell him
I loved his last film.
Just loved it. - Sure.
I am sorry, daddy.
Nobody, it's just Rocks.
If she wasn't Ashish
Kapoor's daughter..
..I would've never
made her my assistant.
What a waste.
She never does any work..
..or good for anything else.
Sunny's room.
Sunny's makeup room.
Sunny.
Close your eyes. - Why?
Did you sign her cheque?
Close your eyes.
Hello, gorgeousness.
No one taught you to knock?
Actually, no.
I just wanted to ask
whether it hurt too much.
Hurt when?
When you fell from Heaven.
Why are you knocking
when the door is open?
Because that's what gentlemen do.
Please come in.
You called me.
You two haven't been
introduced properly.
This is Satyakumar.
Failed novelist but in future..
..he's going to be
a super-hit script writer.
Because he's met me. - Hi.
I read your last novel.
You read books?
And scripts too.
If you had sent
your script on time..
..I would've read that too.
I should go. - Yes.
Anyway, we've already
talked too much.
And anyway, you've to
get ready for the after-party.
The entire cast
and crew will be there.
And the two supporting
actors of our film..
..Monali and Maddy,
you can meet them too.
Sorry, I can't.
I've to visit the mental
asylum tomorrow morning.
Mental asylum? Are you okay?
I finally got permission
to meet Ragini.
Ragini?
Why do you want to meet Ragini?
Research, obviously.
So if you will excuse me, goodnight.
Research?
How did porno turn into Rituporno.
Why are you laughing?
Has the guy who'll
shoot the making reached?
Yes, sir, he has.
Hi, I am Karan.
And I am going to take
you behind the scenes..
..of India's most awaited film,
Ragini MMS 2.
I know that you all want
to see Sunny Leone, and not me.
Anyway, the rest of the
film unit will arrive tomorrow.
Till the while we
will control and do.
And you know that the
joy of a horror film set..
..it's best experienced
alone at night.
Let's check it out and be scared.
Ragini MMS, Day zero.
Come.
What is this?
Why has this not been
painted for shooting?
This does not look proper.
Who's that?
What is here?
This room seems familiar, right.
This is the same room
where Uday and Ragini..
Someone make my MMS too.
What the hell is this?
Handcuffs, and pink.
Uday, you are a scoundrel.
And Ragini, you're kinky too.
I've got to watch
Ragini's MMS on this bed.
Oh yeah.
Dirty little thing.
Who's there?
Who is trying to be funny?
Who's in the cupboard?
Who's that?
You know Ragini?
Be careful.
Hi, Ragini.
I am Sunny.
We're making a film..
..about what happened
with you and Uday.
And..I am playing Ragini.
Tell me, Ragini, people say..
..there's something in that house.
There's a witch in that house.
She killed Uday.
She won't spare me either.
She will kill me too.
She's right here.
Standing behind me.
She will kill me. Save me. - Ragini.
Ragini, there's no one behind you.
- No, no, please save me.
No, no.
Ragini, calm down.
I killed him.
His blood was accumulating
near my feet.
Ragini..
I was enjoying it.
I killed him.
Please save me.
Standing behind me.
Ragini, there's no one behind you.
Please save me. - Calm down.
I'm not a witch.
Ragini, I am sorry.
I didn't kill my children.
What are you doing?
Nurse.
Ragini, no!
Come.
Doctor, I know what
happened with Ragini.
We all know what
She attacked herself.
That's what I am trying to say,
doctor.
She didn't attack herself.
She was compelled to do it.
- What do you mean?
Doctor.
I'll handle it. - Yes.
Yes.
Doctor, please listen to me once.
Come sit.
Let's sit and talk.
Tell me.
Doctor,
I know you won't believe me.
And I was trying to explain to Dr.
Batra that..
Ragini's cell is colder than normal.
Ragini feels no sensation.
Cold and hot..
Pain.
Ragini keeps repeating
the same action all the time.
And the doctors are treating her..
..for multiple
personality disorder.
Look, there's no one
solution for such problems.
Every case is different.
And to know that..
..we've to get to
the root of the problem.
Don't worry, give me some time.
Excuse me. - Yes, ma'am.
Who is she?
She's Dr. Meera Dutta.
She just arrived
from New York last week.
She's a bit strange, but..
..she's one of the best
psychiatrist in the world.
Why strange?
Because she chooses
only those cases..
..for which medical
science has no answer.
Hello, gorgeousness.
Is it hot or is it just you.
Hi.
I am sorry,
he's the original spoilsport.
What happened?
Upset over something?
Nothing.
I just got a headache.
Since I met Ragini..
..I am feeling a bit sick.
That's bound to happen
if you meet a psycho.
Stay with normal people.
And you will stay happy.
And you think you're normal?
Stop the car.
What's written here?
No admission before
sunrise or after sunset.
What's that? - No entry.
Nonsense.
It's an ASI signboard, Rocks.
It must mean something.
- Who is ASI?
ASI means the Archaeological
Survey of India.
I've read that they
put up such signs..
..when some place
is actually haunted.
The Bangar and Ajabghar forts..
..in Rajasthan have the same signs.
You're terrified for no reason.
I am sure my over-enthusiastic
art department must have set this up.
For the shoot.
You mean we're about
to reach the location? - Yes.
It's just two minutes away.
Couldn't you find a
jungle close to the city?
Ask Satya that.
It was his mind-blowing
idea to shoot in this bungalow.
Shall we?
Yes.
Hey, writer. Let's go.
Rocks, a house at
such a place is fine?
The house is a dungeon
from the outside..
..but from inside it
is as beautiful as you.
"Ragini"
Are we all going to stay here?
Not all. Only the important people.
And the rest of all crew?
The rest of the crew
will stay at a hotel.
Because they think
there is a witch here.
What if there is really a witch here?
Then we'll cast her
in this movie too.
The rooms here are good, right?
They are better than the hotel which
is 2:30 hours away from here.
'Stay miles away from the house.'
'That house is jinxed.'
'Keep away from that house.'
Mr. Rocks, I want to
discuss few ideas with you.
Mr. Rocks,
I have doubts about my character.
Shall we discuss them?
Mr. Rocks, don't you think that..
..the graph of my
character's a bit down.
Although my character
has many shades.
Red, blue, grey, magenta.
Oh no!
It's got no feelings.
Mood. Mood.
What is the sunshine of my character?
This is my room. - I can see that.
Right.
This one's my favourite.
Favourite.
It was a hit show.
PKGSNR.
What?
"Pyaar Ke Geet Sunaja Re."
Right after I left the show..
..the channel had
to shut down the show.
My fans messed up everyone.
Why are you asking all this?
Are you a journo? - Journo?
Smarty with pony.
You're a fan.
You want an autograph?
Take my photograph, okay.
Take it.
I am looking for my room. - Room?
Your room.
I see. So you're an AD.
Look, Mr. AD.
This is the VIP area, okay.
Actor zone.
Now get out.
Now leave. Goodbye.
On your way out tell the spot boy..
..to get me a sandwich and a tea.
Brown bread and green tea.
He has come to take a room.
Excuse me, Satya,
I've been looking all over for you.
If I would get my cheque then
I would discuss with you.
Satyakumar?
Satyakumar.
The Satyakumar.
Excuse me.
If I can get a copy of my scenes..
..then I could practice.
No one introduced us.
Parvinder Dhillon.
Friends call me Maddy.
I have many doubts about a scene.
Can I clarify it with you?
She has just one scene.
Sir, talk to me.
I am sending you my BBM pin.
Kindly please add me.
Tell me your pin first.
Then we'll discuss my scenes.
Along with emotions.
Give me your pin.
Tell me. - I am thinking of
getting a new phone today.
Without internet.
Rascal.
But how will I contact you?
Busy?
A lot.
Fine.
Then I won't take
much of your time.
Look, as soon as
I write your scenes..
..I'll keep giving it to you.
What problem do you have with me?
I don't have a problem with you.
But the fact is you're
wrong for this film.
I can't believe you just said that.
Because I feel I am a
complete misfit for this role.
But I didn't think anyone
had the guts to say that to me.
My mother always says.
That I always speak the truth.
It's all her fault.
She shouldn't have named you Satya.
I tell her the same thing.
Well, at least
we agree on something.
Yes.
Friends?
Shall we go down?
Everyone's waiting.
And then Monali sees the witch.
Hey, leave the witch,
where is the heroine? - Sir.
Yes. Yes.
Because I have met Ragini.
That's why I feel that at that time
I will feel a bit disappointed.
Yes, when I had met her..
Her face had a different expression.
So I wish to bring that
expression in my acting.
What do you think?
It's so worst.
Look at your face.
It's sulking.
As if you've missed
one of my big episodes.
What can this writer do?
I'll go straight to Rocks, best.
All your actors either
go to directors or writers?
What about us actors?
Excuse me.
As you know I've 2 BF's
in Lokhandwala back-lane.
I will compromise
only for Rocks sir.
That Tanya,
Ashish Kapoor's daughter.
You can stop dreaming about her.
Settle with her. Gina.
Who knows where she's got a tattoo.
She's already got so many holes,
I am already confused
Patwardhan Villa.
Dahanu, Maharashtra.
Built in 1920.
One of India's haunted houses.
The locals say they
often feel a presence here..
..as if the house doesn't
want anyone to enter inside.
Many deaths have been reported here
in the last 100 years.
The last reported incident
was Ragini and Uday.
Infact A.S.I have put a
board outside this house.
That after sunset
and before sunrise..
..no admission inside.
What could have happened here?
Patwardhan, spice merchant.
100 years ago,
he was India's leading chili trader.
He had got this bungalow
made for his family.
Who...is this woman?
And why has her face
been cut out in every picture?
Is she Patwardhan's wife?
Oh my, God!
That means children were sacrificed?
Come in.
Listen.
Excuse me, sorry. Not today please.
I've already taken my eye-lash off.
So? - So I cannot hookup with you.
Crazy woman,
my lighter's not working.
I came here for that.
As if I am the only one in this house
that has a lighter?
Will you?
Such a bore?
Take it.
Give me one.
Now you're asking for a drag.
Next you'll ask for something else.
Don't mind,
but I don't want anything from you.
Thanks.
That's what all the
girls say in the beginning.
Did you hear? - Yes, your blabber.
Turn around.
Someone just passed by here.
There's someone behind you.
Yes, you're behind
me since we came here.
First you were crazy.
Now get lost from here.
Now get out.
Please, look behind.
I saw someone.
Who is it?
There's no one.
So duffer.
If you build muscles
it doesn't make you a macho man.
Coward.
Get out of here.
You've been blabbering nonsense.
I felt like someone..
Okay, please.
Coward, get out from here.
Come on, get out.
So bad.
Hail Goddess! Hail Goddess!
Hey!
Are you mad?
Hail Goddess! Hail Goddess!
This is my room.
- I didn't say this is my room.
What?
Two minutes.
Don't go anywhere.
I'll be right back.
What is it?
Who died?
Stupid.
What do you want?
Listen. - What?
Take this.
This is tomorrow's call sheet.
You weren't answering
your phone so we freaked out.
Were you busy?
Maybe.
What do you care?
Now run along.
Sunny.
You here?
Yes, why?
Then.. wait.
Oh no..
What..
How did you get out of
the shower so quickly and..
Excuse me!
What's this? I asked you
to wait for me in the shower.
Are you freaking mad?
I was in your bathroom?
Do you think I am gay
to make out with myself?
Only you can answer that, Maddy.
Why are you feeling shy? - Listen.
There's a limit to pranks.
Enough of this charade.
Hello.
I am not a cheap man.
I still get 600
friend request daily.
Nonsense..
She was with me in the shower.
Why don't you tell everyone..
that you were with me in the shower?
Bloody pervert.
What..
Dude.
Was Sunny really with you?
I swear I never lie.
Hello.
Rascal, you sent
mind-blowing stuff.
Send few grams more.
Okay.
Thanks.
Next time I'll imagine
Katrina or Kareena.
Or Vidya.
But 25-30 kilos less.
Oh Vidya.
"Ragini"
Sound.
Roll camera.
Rolling.
Take 15.
And action.
Uday.
Uday, where are you?
Save me.
Save..
Cut. Cut. Cut.
Cut it!
Someone give her, her lines.
Rocks.
Can I just take five?
Take ten, babiness.
Someone bring tea.
If she takes five
after every break..
..then we'll be in trouble.
Experience, sir.
Experience.
You see,
my experience in television..
..comes so much in handy.
I see.
- There are so many shots.
Reaction shots.
Expressions.
There are so many
expressions on my face.
I'm filled with talent.
Would you like to see it?
Romance.
Cut.
Intense.
Revenge.
Cut.
The joy of becoming a father.
Mother's death.
Cut.
That's talent, sir.
Experience.
That's where you get it from.
She has experience too.
Sir, only from adult movies.
These things don't teach you acting.
Doing an emotional scene means
pushing to the limit.
Sunny.
Maddy.
Imagine there's no one here.
No cameras.
Just you.
And your efforts finally succeed.
What?
I come close to you.
Take off my clothes.
Then take off your clothes and..
..pull your hair, and kiss you.
And what will you do now?
Now do it with feelings.
I'll give you the clue.
Maddy.
Oh, Maddy.
Oh, yeah!
What happened, Maddy?
I admit that adult films
don't make you an actor.
But you couldn't
do that much either.
When the blood rushes
back to your brains..
..then answer me.
One more.
Keep that mood on.
Let's do it.
I mean let's go for take.
I think you did the right thing.
Such people don't understand
any other language.
So you're telling me that all the men
on this unit think I am a w***e.
Not all men.
Only those whose brains
are in their pants.
So all men.
No. Not all men.
I am sorry.
It's not my mistake.
I don't know what's wrong with me.
Since I came here I feel strange.
Come with me.
Why do you feel strange?
Are you fine?
I don't know. I mean.
Headache and..
Sunny.
Shall I do your touchup?
Just five more minutes.
Okay.
What happened?
Nothing.
Remember one thing.
No matter what happens,
I won't let anything happen to you.
Okay.
Satya. - Yes.
You were right,
not all men are alike.
Don't want too many lights, got it?
Let's go
Hello, babiness.
Hi.
Come.
Excuse me.
I mean come, sit. Sit.
Come.
Rocks! Rocks!
Why don't you show me the monitor?
I love the director's angle.
Yes.
What will I do now?
We will hang you upside down.
And you've to pretend
as if you saw a witch.
Okay?
Did you rehearse your lines?
Help! Help!
I've been practicing it since
I was a kid. - Yeah, very good.
Come on. Hang her upside down.
Come, come, please.
Please sit.
Come.
Okay, ready.
Stunt boys, lift her.
Save me! Save me!
Okay, turn her upside down.
Save me. Help!
Everyone ready?
Okay, roll sound. - Rolling.
Camera. - Rolling.
Take one.
Action.
Help! Help! Help!
Help! Help!
Help!
Very good, very good.
What a performance.
Very good, scream some more. - Help!
Help!
Scream some more. - Save me.
Bring me down - Come on.
Cut it.
Bring her down!
Monali. Monali. - What happened?
Two girls.
Whose two girls?
What are you saying?
Brilliant performance, Monali.
Brilliant.
What an improvisation.
You were in the character.
Wow! I really enjoyed that.
Clap. Clap.
What a performance.
Very good.
Amazing, very good.
Enough, shut up.
Pack up.
Come on, guys, move it.
Push, push.
Come on. - Hurry up.
We've to get out of
here before nightfall.
What if it's a night shoot?
We'll see then.
We don't want to spend the
night with ghosts and witches.
You know,
when Rocks came to meet me first..
..he said he's a
big fan of my acting.
What did he say to you?
That he loves my books.
And you believed him?
Basically, he knew that..
..you're the right person
to write Ragini's story.
I knew that.
He never reads any of my books.
Of course he doesn't.
Pandey never even reads his messages.
Are you going to waste
more time on Rocks?
I am thinking about Monali,
not Rocks.
About what happened on the sets?
What if Monali really
saw something on the ceiling?
Monali is a drama queen.
She can do anything for attention.
There are no ghosts here.
Ragini's mother doesn't
think that. - What?
Ragini's mother believes
there's something in this house.
And I should stay
away from this house.
Yet I brought Rocks here.
Now I feel I put
everyone's life in danger..
..for the sake of my career.
Satya, don't be silly.
We're all here for our careers.
Not for you.
If anything happens to anyone..
..then I will never forgive myself.
I don't know about others..
..but something will
definitely happen to you.
If you keep drinking
whiskey at this rate.
Then tomorrow you'll
feel hammers in your head.
Are you stopping
me from drinking? - No.
I am stopping you
from drinking alone.
Careful, madam.
After two drinks, even
boys like me look handsome.
"I've surrendered myself to you."
"I am yours, only yours."
"My days are restless,
I spend it tossing around."
"I want to spend
the night in your arms."
"My heart speaks to yours."
"I want to spend
the night in your arms."
"Come dwell in me."
"When you touched..I came alive."
"My desires..found a voice."
"I want to spend
the night in your arms."
"My heart speaks to yours."
"I want to spend
the night in your arms."
"Come dwell in me."
It stopped raining.
Shall we go?
Yes.
Oh my god.
That's strange.
The entire family died.
But Patwardhan only gave the names
of his kids in the obituary.
That's weird.
What about their mother?
Coffee.
Finally. Here comes
my great assistant, Nishant.
Yeah. - Where were you?
Getting coffee beans from Brazil?
What difference does it make?
Even if I had come any later..
..you would've still been here.
Just stuck to your seats.
I don't understand how
you work so extensively.
And you're so busy.
Yet you find time
for these free cases.
I mean what's the idea here, boss?
I am on to something.
Dr. D, ghosts, spirits,
witches, haunted house rumours.
..have been spread by them.
It's the job of Rock's PR machinery.
You know what the
problem with you guys is.
You are too cynical.
Anyway, where's the footage
from Ragini's mental asylum.
I saw it.
I'll show it to you.
Careful.
Ragini's sitting
on her bed like this.
And there are no
expressions on her face.
And she's just rocking
front and back.
For freaking two years.
I mean I died of boredom.
I am so glad you liked it.
I need the tapes
on my table tomorrow.
But listen to.. - Tomorrow.
But listen.. - Yes.
"Ragini"
Who is it?
No please mother.
I'm not a witch.
My back hurts.
Sunny.
I've been looking all over for you.
What are you doing here?
What am I doing here?
What do you mean?
I hope you haven't
started sleep-walking?
Don't do that.
You'll find the entire
crew walking behind you.
Come on.
Get some rest.
And shoot? - Shoot?
Today's a night-shift.
Today is Rock's special moon night.
Come on.
Dr. D, I think my
life is passing me by.
I told you a thousand times
there's nothing in that video.
There's nothing, nothing, nothing.
And I said until we
don't see all the videos..
..we won't move from here.
Neither you nor me.
Shut up.
Great.
"Ragini"
You lost.
Satya, why are you so grumpy?
Come down, we're all having fun.
Come on.
Rocks is cheating and
getting all our secrets out.
You know Tanya and Kunal
are having an affair..
..since the past two months.
Listen, please don't
tell anyone about this.
Don't we have anything else to do?
We aren't going to make
a status update about your affair.
Yes.
Satya, wait, wait.
It's an amazing game.
Amazing.
I tell you..
The game's called 'Never-Ever'.
I have Never-Ever'.
Okay.
So anyone of us will start
a sentence with 'never ever'.
And if you've done it,
then your drink..bottoms up.
Get it?
It's simple.
Like I..I will say..
Yes.
I have never ever
done in an airplane.
So if you've done it in
the airplane, then your drink.
That's it. Right.
Come on.
No one's forcing him.
There you go, sir.
Ready?
Everyone, ready.
Satya, your turn. Your turn.
I have never ever played this game.
What's the connection
with their clothes?
Punishment.
If you don't take sip
in a 'never-ever' turn..
..then you're punished.
All and all it's a drinking game.
If someone doesn't
sip in your round..
..then you can punish him.
What happened, babiness?
Where are you lost?
I am just waiting
for my life to leave me.
Why did I just say that?
Now my turn, please.
Now come on you say..
I have never ever,
ever killed anyone.
Kill what?
Are you crazy?
What is the problem?
I got this, guys. Got this.
Sunny took a sip
because everyone says..
..that she can kill with her looks.
Kill-bill.
Rocks is so funny, right.
Monali, you said this only
for getting punished, right?
Come on, guys.
A big punishment for Monali.
- I told you.
Oh no. Now I'll have
to take my dress off, right?
Come on.
No, no, no, wait.
What's your problem? Don't worry.
Take it off. - No, no, sir.
We said..you'll get a punishment.
We haven't said which punishment.
Your punishment is.. - Hold on.
Hold on. Hold on.
I will decide Monali's punishment.
And Monali's punishment will be..
..that she will
have to kiss someone.
And who?
Me..
Let me see.
Sunny.
Me? Why?
You just broke a rule.
You took a sip at I
never ever killed anyone.
Unless you really killed someone.
I haven't yet.
But I could kill you
for making me do this.
If you do this.. I am ready to die.
Get ready to die.
Come on kiss me.
Come on.
Cut it or I'll spill it.
That was..awesome.
Wow!
Thank you. - Superb!
Whether she dies or not..
..but I will definitely
die of happiness.
But if I die then who
will s***w all of you.
Come on. Party over.
Come on.
Kunal. - Yes, sir.
Why hasn't the unit's
bus arrived yet?
Sir, I've already called thrice.
But they aren't answering.
Then call someone else in the bus.
The moon will be out soon,
we cannot delay.
We shouldn't be late.
She's right. - Yes sir.
Everybody, come on.
Back to work.
Gina. - Yes.
Blood, acts, handcuffs? - Handcuffs.
Oh no, give me five.
Ma'am.
I came to say that I've
to go home early today.
Why do you want to go early?
Didn't I tell you, ma'am?
I am fasting today.
Tonight evil powers are worshiped.
What happened? Scared?
Do you believe in
ghosts and spirits?
Sir, I believe in God..
..so we should believe
in evil powers as well.
Today's a full moon night.
Tonight evil powers
are at their full strength.
That's why we observe
fasts and hold venerations..
..to calm them.
B****t. This is all b****t.
Madam, I think this girl
has been possessed by a witch.
How do you know? - Dr. D.
Please don't start again.
If this goes on, then you two..
..will have to spend the night here.
I don't know about your witch,
but my witch..
I mean my girlfriend
will chew me alive.
Try to understand.
Sir, this is no joke.
Ma'am, there's a saying in sect..
..that a witch posses someone..
..when she wants to narrate
her incomplete story.
Oh really. Is it so?
So how does she narrate her story?
Backwards.
Whenever she possesses
someone's body..
..she speaks backwards.
She never speaks normally.
Of course.
Get me my food. - Yes, ma'am.
Nishant, you want to go home, right.
- Yes, Dr. D.
Go home we'll continue tomorrow.
Dr. D, take some break
from the ghosts. Good night
I'm not a witch, I love my son.
But I just love my son.
I'm not a witch,
I'm not killed my daughter.
I don't believe it.
- I'm not a witch.
What did she say?
I like my daughters.
But I just love my son.
I'm not a witch.
I like my daughters.
But I just love my son.
I used to fast every Monday.
For five years I fasted every Monday.
After that my son was born.
I will never forget
that inauspicious day.
Their father had gone
out of the city for some work.
Here I come.
All three were playing hide-and-seek.
And then suddenly I heard her scream.
Mother!
By the time I came, it was too late..
I was not aware of anything.
I could not understand anything.
I was wondering why
my son is not getting up.
For hours, like a crazy person,
I held him in my arms..
..and sang lullabies to him.
And then someone gave me some hope.
And your biggest duty is sacrifice.
I had gone so crazy
in the sorrow of my son..
..that I did not even hear
the screams of my daughters.
Hold this.
Shut your eyes and say the chants.
The word spread in the village.
The Tantric ran away from
there at that very moment.
And for the villagers
I became such a mother
..at the hands of which..
She's a witch!
Killed her own daughters.
They hung me from a tree.
I kept screaming..
yes, I have made a very big mistake..
..but I am not a witch.
I've not killed my daughter.
- I'm not a witch.
No one heard my voice.
Not even their father.
I am just a mother.
Who was sad about her daughters..
Mother!
I will not spare anyone.
This is my house.
Mother!
I'm not a witch.
This is my house.
I will not go from here.
Mother!
Tonight this witch
won't spare anyone.
She won't spare anyone alive.
She won't spare anyone.
I won't let it happen.
I will have to do something.
I'll be right back.
How are all of you?
Who's under the bed?
Come out.
Who's there?
Hail Goddess! Hail Goddess!
Someone's playing with me.
Who's there?
Sunny.
In the morning you won round 1.
But I am a specialist in round 2.
I am coming.
To have some fun in the jungle.
Where is it? Where have I kept it?
Today I'll show her real man force.
Shall we?
And he had to resign from his post.
And in the news,
in Rane Mental Asylum today..
..a death happened in
a strange manner.
The one who died..
producer and director Rocks..
..was making a film
based on her life.
We are talking about that person..
..whose MMS was leaked
some years back.
Recently Ragini was
in the news again..
..when famous film director Rocks..
..announced a film on her.
But unfortunately,
Ragini can never see this film.
Along with Ragini's death..
..her dreadful story is over too.
Hello.
Hello, aunty, this is Satya.
Yes. - Aunty, I am very sorry.
I don't know what to say.
No need to say anything, Satya.
I tried explaining to you.
But no one listened to me.
Ragini wasn't crazy.
The truth is...that she
was possessed by a witch.
Aunty, even if we believe..
..that Ragini was
possessed by a witch..
..then where did she go?
I pray that she went
back to where she came from.
Aunty...
Aunty, when did Ragini die?
Four days ago.
Four days ago..
- The heroine of your film..
..came to see my daughter.
The same day.
'Since the day I met Ragini..
'There's something in this house.'
Aunty, the mark on Ragini's arm.
The mark vanished from her arms too.
How can a mark vanish
from a person's arm, Satya?
The mark hasn't vanished,
neither has the witch.
Hello. - Thank god.
Hello, Mrs. Shinde.
Yes Doctor, tell me.
I want to talk to someone
in that house now.
I will send Satya's number right now.
Sunny.
Where are you hiding?
That's..
Sunny.
Strip-tease with me.
I am a TV star.
Whenever I shoot
a wedding night scene..
..the show gets full TRP.
Where are you?
Sunny dear, come to papa.
Come on..
Sunny.
I..
Out in the open, in the lake.
Fine with me.
Why feel shy from mother nature?
Sunny Leone, give it to me.
Sunny, I'm coming.
The water is very cold, no problem.
Sunny will heat it.
I'm coming.
Hold my hand.
Where are you?
Hey, this donkey has come.
Sunny.
I have caught you, come outside.
The number you're
trying to reach is busy.
Please call later.
Hello. - Rocks,
listen to me carefully.
It's a matter of life and death.
Whose? Yours or mine?
It's Sunny.
She is possessed.
She's been possessed by a witch.
And you've gone crazy.
Rocks.
"Ragini"
Excuse me.
He said he's my BF
and you believed him.
You know he was
my neighbour in Delhi.
That's why we're so
frank with each other.
So please don't be so jealous.
You've to choose today.
Either him or me.
What choice?
Please, Manish.
Don't be so jealous.
I've been a tomboy
since I was a kid.
So all the boys are
very comfortable with me.
All boys.
You've found someone
on the sets as well, right?
Are you crazy?
Are you mental?
Monali, it's too much now.
I know that you..
- Listen to me, okay.
I need a secured
boyfriend for myself.
Not insecure ones like you.
Okay.
I know you're definitely
up to someone on the sets.
I know this very well.
Excuse me, I am not cheating on you.
Please don't be a fool.
Oh no!
You've spoiled my mood.
Go to hell. - Monali, listen to me.
All men are like that.
Worst.
Rocks!
Hello, babiness.
I never told you that
I am your biggest fan.
In fact, I was just watching..
..your doctor-nurse
video in my room.
And then I thought to myself,
"Rocks..
..you are an idiot".
You're right here and
I am watching a video.
And so...I came to say..
Hello, sweetness.
Feeling shy.
Don't be shy.
It's only me.
I'm not a witch.
Dirty talking in Marathi.
But I don't know Marathi.
Say it in English.
Say f**k me.
Say it.
F**k me!
But you..
I think I should drink less vodka.
What am I doing on you?
What am I doing?
What do you mean?
Look, let's not pretend
with each other anymore.
No one will ever know..
..whatever happens
in this room tonight.
Not even your writer boyfriend.
Rocks, what are you..
Now f**k me.
F**k.
Rock's voice from Sunny's room.
Rocks!
Oh no. What's going on?
This is bad.
Compromise.
The heroines these days, I tell you.
They are so bad.
Now I'll make Ragini MMS 3.
Threesome, here I come.
Rocks!
Can I kindly join?
Rocks.
That Sunny..
She's possessed. - She killed Rocks.
She's possessed.
Meaning?
It's okay.
Satya.
Hi, I am Dr. Meera Dutta.
Ragini's psychiatrist.
What are you doing here?
We don't have time.
There's a spirit trapped here.
If we don't free her soon..
..she won't let anyone go from here.
We'll have to do something about it,
and quick.
Please.
Keep quiet.
Sorry.
It's coming from
behind the cupboard.
Satya.
You all are coming?
We cannot leave from
here even if we wish to.
She will not let us leave.
Carefully.
Can't see anything.
Come here.
What are you doing?
Calm down.
I thought as much.
We'll have to perform
their final rites..
..or their souls
won't attain salvation.
Do whatever you want, doctor.
Just save Sunny, please.
I am a doctor, Satya.
But I will try my best.
Last year I met
a sage in Rishikesh..
..and he gave me few mantras..
..which separates
the soul from the body.
I never thought they
would be of some use, but..
..I guess that's our last straw now.
Are you sure these
mantras will work?
Right now there's
just one thing we can do.
Believe.
It has to. - Yes.
Please do fast, doctor.
Monali!
Monali, get the chair.
Oh no!
I will not spare anyone.
Tie her up.
Carefully.
Satya, we don't have time.
Let me go.
If I don't read these
mantras quickly..
..then she won't go.
What's the point of
tying me to the chair?
All three are going to attack me?
Come on, baby. Come on.
Come on.
Satya, what happened?
Come on, take me now.
F**k me.
There's no use.
Carefully.
Please help me.
It hurts.
Satya, please help me.
I'm not a witch.
I didn't kill my son.
He's mine.
I won't go from here.
Go away from here.
Return to the darkness
you have come from.
Sunny. - Wait.
Wait. - She's dead, Satya.
Sunny.
I think she's dead.
Monali.
Her life's stuck in that.
We'll have to break that, Satya.
No, Sunny. No.
Satya, don't listen to her.
Just break it right now.
Don't do that.
Satya, don't listen to her.
What if something happens to Sunny?
Nothing will happen to Sunny.
That's not Sunny. - I love you.
I said break it.
Don't do that. - Come on, Satya.
Break that.
Hold it.
Sunny.
Sunny. - Sunny.
Sunny, get up.
Sunny, open your eyes. - Sunny!
Sunny!
It's okay.
Please take me away from here.
Yeah.
Are you okay?
Satya.
As soon as you two get
out I'll call the police.
He'll do the final
rites of everyone.