"Like buds we are, naive kids."
"Naughty we got, when knickers kicked in."
"Of same colour, our knickers are."
"Man, my buddy you are."
"Like buds we are, naive kids."
"Naughty we got, when knickers kicked in."
"Of same colour, our knickers are."
"Man, my buddy you are."
"Up on the shoulders, into the ears.."
"In by-lanes and closed stores.."
"We took a leak as we pleased."
"Toilets are something never we leased."
"Up on the shoulders, into the ears.."
"In by-lanes and closed stores.."
"We took a leak as we pleased."
"Shooed we were by the people displeased."
"Shoes you are, I am your lace."
"My broken buttons, you stitch."
"Drunk I get, when you drink."
"Shoes you are, I am your lace."
"Man, what is this that you have done!"
"Chaos is when this world laughs."
"As we came of age, we started chasing girls..."
"Now we use oil, little is the gel left in the hair.."
"The thrashing we got from our parents ruined our picture.."
"Now we look like riddles, people try to diddle us."
"Shoes you are, I am your lace."
Tomatoes, radish, round gourd.
A new cover for the fridge.
'Aunt Richa taunts, I'm the female in my family.'
'I care a damn.'
'I'm a better cook than her.'
'I can boost, I am better than most.'
'Last Holi, I made ladyfinger chips.'
'Everyone in the vicinity still remembers its taste.'
'It's my childhood dream..'
'That I own a restaurant.'
'The one that belongs to me.'
'Somewhere in near future.'
'But there's still time for that.'
'First I need to clear high school.'
'Do you always end up denting your car?'
'Do you keep getting demoted at work?'
'Does your wife cheat on you?'
'Do you keep flunking your exams? No problem.'
'Seek our sage's blessings. Hot and fresh.'
'A blessing as hot and fresh as a home-cooked meal.'
'And now watch, The Food Treasure.'
Kuku.. - Yes, papa?
When are you getting your results?
It will take another day or two. - Why?
Papers are getting checked in Chennai.
Chennai!
They are hard markers.
But mom, I had prepared so well for them.
It's hard marking.
That's why you scored such marks.
Then everyone must've scored similarly.
Of course! Will I lie to you?
Come with me. Stop crying and drink some water. Come on.
Here, Rs. 20.
Rs. 20? It's Rs. 40. - How?
You have two kids.
So? - So, can't you read?
Public student, Rs. 20. Government student, Rs. 10.
Free for failures.
So, one of my sons failed.
Failed? How? How much did he score? - 85.
And this one? - 37.
F-37 means passed.
For me 37 means failed.
How? Give me Rs. 20. - He has failed.
What are you staring at? Let's go.
Give me Rs. 20! - He has failed! Let's go!
Loser! He'll always be a failure! Nonsense!
Leave your footwear outside! The carpet's new!
Can't you see! You are just barging inside!
We've taken them off.
We're here to check the results.
Did you check out the queue?
Can't we skip the queue?
"Can't we skip the queue?!"
"You think you are entering your own wedding?"
'This man can sell sand to desert dweller and ice to an Eskimo."
He is my best friend. His name is Ronnie Gulati.
Yogesh, Kuku.. - So?
He doesn't have a mother.
He's a motherless child. What are you saying?
He is always worried.
This poor soul does all the household chores.
He cooks for his younger sister. He looks after her.
Do you want him to wait in the queue?
Shouldn't he rather go take care of his house?
Think before you speak.
Okay. Fine. - Show the results.
Come with me, Kuku.
Move. What's this commotion? - Come with me.
Move. It's so hot..
Sit on his lap, and he'll show the results.
Move aside, Raju.
Excuse me. Yogesh..
Please move back a little.
So, public or government? - Public.
Okay. Number?
15,419 dollar. - Dollar?
Helps remember the number.
Okay. And yours?
Add one.
15420?
15420.
"Grandpa's Grandson!"
You always seek sympathy over my dead mother.
It gets the job done.
Here you go..
89!
90!
89! - 89!
So? - 90!
Let's go! Party time!
Pay up! - Let's go! 90!
89! - 90!
Party!
90!
90%!
Kuku got 90%...!
Papers must've leaked!
'I've been getting tutored by Seema since the last 7 years.'
'But the real reason is Mitali.'
'She stays across the street.'
'I'm 5.10".'
'And she's 5.9".'
'Our heights match, Ronnie says.'
Mitali. - Yes mom.
'Mitali's mom, Malti.'
'They are well-known in our vicinity.'
'People gossip about them.'
'They take a lot of lifts.'
'But only from big shots.'
'But that's not true.'
'It's all rubbish!'
'One day, I too will give her a lift.'
'And I know..'
'Mitali won't refuse it.'
What are you doing? Let's go.
Nothing. Let's go.
My cousin too has it. In that he runs like this.
Where's the community centre?
The community centre? - We are new here. We don't know.
What..? - Grandpa says, first rule in business
Never waste time on something that won't give any return.
Let's go.
This is a shoe.
Now tell me what is this? - Sole.
Not a sole. Ordinary shoes have sole.
This contains a shocker.
Big cars have shocker, so that they don't get shock.
So that their outer beauty remains intact.
That's why this too contains a shocker.
So this shoe can never get damaged.
So, should I prepare the bill?
Let me tell you something special about it.
Its' design too is amazing.
Superb!
The air flows in from here and flows out from here itself!
Cross-ventilation. - Exactly!
Check it out!
Uncle, isn't the tick the other way around?
You are look at it in the wrong way. Here, now it is straight.
When you walk wearing this, it will be straight. Right?
Just like an aeroplane.
Great! Let me see.
Are they original?
Tony! - No! He's joking!
What kind of a joke is this?!
You mean, I've a warehouse full of shoes..
And I keep stamping shoes with Nicky logos and selling them stealthily?
No, uncle. Sorry, uncle. - He was joking.
He doesn't know. - It's okay.
How much does it cost?
Rs. 1550, only for you.
How much will you sell it for? - 1550.
Discount?
One rupee. 1549..
So, should I prepare the bill?
Should I buy them? - Buy them.
Prepare the bill. - Wonderful.
God bless you. Tony! - Yes.
There's a Tony here and a Tony there as well.
I'm not talking to you.
You've started lying a lot.
Why did I lie to you?
Don't you work in a sari shop?
Yes. So what?
It's been months..
You didn't send a sari for me.
I'll send you one soon. - Yeah, right.
Hey, you speak as if I've never sent you anything.
What did you send? Tell me.
Don't you remember the mobile phone? Didn't I send it to you?
That mobile phone? It's useless. - Why?
Your mother.. - What happened to her?
Nothing's wrong with her.
Your mother keeps playing games on it.
She doesn't let me have it.
I'm calling you from a STD booth.
You've not done anything for me. You haven't sent anything for me.
You don't even enquire about my wellbeing.
It won't make any difference to you if I die.
Don't worry. I'll send something for you.
Who is it? - My friends.
Hang up. I'll call you later.
You have time for your friends, but not for me.
How are you Suresh? - Why did you marry me? Tell me.
It's been six months since I last saw you.
Why do you say so? - Why did you marry me?
Listen.. - You don't have time for me.
'Ronnie's grandpa has a Sari Shop in Geeta colony.'
'All the stock lies in the warehouse.'
'And it is delivered to the shop as and when required.'
'But for us, it's our joint.'
'We enjoy our booze here.'
'By booze, I mean fruit beer.'
'A fake beer. But it gives a feeling of being sloshed.'
I'll ask dad to buy me a second-hand bike.
A bike, why?
I saw Mitali today.
I see her everyday. What's new?
I've been going around with her since ages. Got it?
You've been going around on foot where as she is racing ahead..
On bikes with boys.
Dogs! - True!
I'll get them for you.
He's talking to his wife. - Don't worry.
He is blushing.
True love. - Why would I lie to you?
Bottoms up?
Bottoms up!
"I'm sloshed. I'm sloshed. I'm sloshed."
I'm sloshed.
I'm sloshed. Fruit beer gave me a high, man!
"Kuku!"
90%..
You got a gold medal in Olympics.
90% in physical education.
You choose this as the fifth subject without my permission.
Are NASA guys into bodybuilding these days?
Do scientists exercise?
What about the other subjects?
Maths..
44..
And English?
Papa, no matter the subject.
This is the first time he scored 90%.
It's not like he got 'Compartment' in the others subjects, like always.
Papa, we deserve a treat.
Fine.
Make cottage cheese for dinner.
Here.
Manage everything with this.
And this.. - Thank you, papa.
"Kuku!"
This is for the college form.
Go to the college tomorrow and fill up a form.
Oh yes, do you have a passport size photograph?
Yes, I have it.
Fine. Go.
Now go.
Damn..
They have impinged the whole street.
Do you bloody own the street!
I rolled down my car's window and said..
"Apologize!"
Hello. - Hi.
Desraj, isn't this the safari suit..
..that you wore for Pintoo's tonsuring ceremony?
It's been 12 years, but it still looks the same.
Father has a sharp eye..
Anything he sees gets imprinted in his brains.
Forever. - All cheer for Desraj!
I'll blow this bomb on the DJ's head! It'll blow up like bang!
It'll blow up like boom!
Bang! - Boom!
Bang! - Grandpa!
Babloo and Pintoo plan to blow a bomb on the DJ's head.
Hemanshu!
Yes, grandpa!
What's going on out there? Go and find out.
Okay Fix it.
Bye. I'll call you back.
Excuse me. Babloo. Pintoo.
What are you doing? Move aside.
There goes the bomb.
The party is on! It's on!
There goes your bomb!
You are not eating anything. This is not right.
Ronnie?
Kuku! I was just about to call you.
What's all this? - Even I didn't know.
Everyone gave me a surprise when I got home.
All of a sudden.. Grandpa.. - What are you wearing?
Don't make fun of it! Grandpa got it for me.
Don't I look dashing in it? Fits perfectly, doesn't it, Chota?
I'm looking handsome, aren't I?
It fits you well. - I know, man.
What's happening? - Yeah. It's a party.
Grandpa has invited freeloaders. He's offering them free cold drinks.
It's nothing. Don't worry. We..
Why are you eavesdropping?
Go and meet Suchi. - Go.
We'll have our party at the warehouse.
We'll drink our brand.. Wait..
Our brand.. Here's 100 bucks. Buy two.. - This..
We'll have fun on Sunday. A party at the warehouse.
Just a second! They won't let me live. Coming!
Go.. - Wait. I'll be back in 10 minutes.
Have dinner before you leave. Don't just leave. Okay?
And don't forget to buy our brand's.. Just a second!
Coming, uncle. Why don't you just kill Ronnie today!
Hello, auntie. Hi. How are you?
How are you, Kuku? - I'm fine. Everything's great.
My baby..
Auntie, Ronnie.. - Where's your father?
He.. - I cannot find him.
Did you have dinner? - Yes, well..
It's okay. I'll pack some cottage cheese and flatbread.
Okay. - Eat and give some to your father.
Okay? - Who is he?
Ronnie's friend. - Hello, auntie.
They don't have a mother.
No, it's okay. You are just like my kids.
Right, Chota?
My son..
Come give me a hug.
Switch it on.
Hey, they have made the announcement.
Let's go. Let's go, son.
Come with me. Look at this!
'Ronnie Matching Centre.'
Ronnie's settled for life.
Not yet. - Why?
They have just inaugurated the shop.
People need to buy, they need to sell, make profit..
Only then will the shop run smoothly.
Who knows whether it will? - How can it not?
Grandpa's 60-year-old sari shop is right next to it.
People, females who go there to buy saris..
Will they leave without buying blouse and petticoat?
Point. - God bless you son.
Surprised? His life is set.
'Kuku and Ronnie. Ronnie and Kuku.'
'What's in a name? Both of them are same-same.'
'But after they grew up, everything has changed.'
Excuse me.. - Yes?
Photo.. Kuku Mathur.
Yeah. Just a minute.
Here, your photos.
Listen.. Your friend, Ronnie, I have his photo with me.
Please give it to him.
'Now the confusion was clearing.'
'Not even 20 Kukus could match-up to a single Ronnie.'
Water! Water! Water!
Water! Water!
You want to submit your form?
You want a form?
Why are you standing in a queue?
Take it from me.
Water! Water! Water!
Sir! What's this? My form?
We're closing for the day!
Again?
Excuse me..
The counter closed.. - 100 bucks.
With such marks forget about the state college.
Go for physical education. It will be done.
Done.
Booze!
Ronnie...? - He's not here.
Where is he? - He didn't tell me.
Hey..
What have you got?
Yes, Kuku? - Where are you?
Where are you? - At the warehouse.
You had promised. It's Sunday.
Today is Sunday? - Yes.
I keep my shop closed on Mondays.
We will meet on Monday. You do your own thing.
But you promised..
What "you promised, you promised!
I told you, I am working. Don't you understand?
I'm not sitting idle like you.
You keep calling me after every two minutes!
Sir..
Why are you leaving?
Drink with me.
You got the booze, I'll get the glasses.
No, I have some work. - What?
"Kuku!"
Ronnie is now a businessman.
Now, what are your plans?
"Kuku!"
College.
Education.. For another 2-4 years.
Then a job.
Just like your father.
Life completely changes.
One doesn't get government jobs these days.
Go for a private company.
Like me.
"Kuku!"
Hey, Kuku..
Now you too are one of us!
Welcome.
Have you lost your mind? - Why?
What are you saying! Get lost.
I don't want to drink with you.
What did I say? - Get lost!
Come on, everyone. Get in a line.
Do you want an invitation? Get in a line!
Six in each line. Make three lines.
You need to run from this pole to that tree.
Okay? You will start running when I blow the whistle.
Hello, ma'am. Welcome. - Hi.
Why are you looking over there? Concentrate on your run.
Get in the line.
Come on, get in the line!
Take your positions.
Get..
Set..
And go!
What are you doing?
What are you looking at?
Sir, the sole came off.
Complete the race.
Useless!
Kuku Mathur, Chaar Minar. - Sir..
You are here for admission? - Sir, he stepped on my shoes..
I don't want arguments. Just answer my question.
You won't get admission. Scram.
I'll get it if you want me to.
What will you get? Have you seen your face in the mirror?
You look awful.
You want admission.
Heed my advice, always leave your house with a coin in your pocket.
Why? - Strong winds keep blowing.
You might fly away.
Sir..
He wants admission. Scram!
Sir.. - I told you to leave.
I wonder what they think before coming here.
Mr. Sharma.. - Yes?
Who's next?
Water! Water! Water!
Water!
Okay. Water! Water!
Water! Have a glass.
What happened?
Nothing. - Tell me.
You didn't get selected?
Then take up a job.
Why are you sulking because you didn't get a selected?
Will you do a job? A job?
500 bucks.
It's just 500 bucks. I'm getting you a job.
You'll have to go to Noida.
Think over it.
Scene 15, Take 2.
Silence.
Mood.
Feel that your friend has ruined you.
I'll narrate from here and you'll read from there.
Camera! Action!
Ajit! My friend.. - Hold it higher.
You betrayed me.
You pretended to be my friend.
And behind my back you had an affair with my wife!
One friend ruined another friend's life!
You pretended to be my friend.
I'll kill you!
Hold it properly! -If there is no troublemaker..
..there shall be no trouble.
Dolly! Wake up, Dolly!
What is it? - I need to test your fidelity.
Ajit was my friend. - Hold it properly.
But now he will have to die..
Because of you.
But.. - And if you refuse, I shall kill you as well.
No, Amit! Don't do that, Amit! Don't say that, Amit!
You've been unfaithful to me. I shall never forgive you.
No, Amit. It's not so!
Hold it like this! Like this!
Action!
Take 48.
"Hey girl..!"
"Hey girl, switch on your computer!"
"Catch me on internet."
"There are thousands of likes on my photo."
"On Facebook, love me!"
"Come on, add me!"
"Log on, girl! Tag me!"
"I have a thousand friend requests pending!"
"Back off!" - "On Facebook, love me!"
"Come on, add me!"
"On Facebook, love me!"
"Hey girl...!"
Kuku, leave that. Get water for me.
Do it properly.
Go!
"Hey boy!"
"Back off!"
"I feel like sharing the galaxy with you."
"I think I should do it before it's too late."
"Oh Bubbly, I love you." "By God."
"I should download you in my dreams."
"I should make you my friend."
"We will make history here."
"My love shall never shut down."
"My love, please say yes."
"Don't back out!"
"Our worlds shall unite!"
"On Facebook.. - Love me!"
"Come on.. - Add me!"
What are you looking at? Go and do your job. Go, hold the styrofoam.
"I've added you."
"So what do you think?"
"I love you."
Hold it properly! What are you doing? Sit down!
"Okay. Thank you!
Keep it down! What are you doing?
Don't you know how to do this? What are you doing?
You told me to sit down. - I told you! Shut up!
"Hey girl!"
Very good. - Nice take, I think.
Very good, madam. Excellent.
What are you doing? Can't you hold it properly?
Very good, boys. - Come with me. - Kuku, get an umbrella for me.
What are you doing? Go!
Where are you going! - I wonder where they come from!
Hurry up! - A burden on earth.
Mr. Sharma, look at this poster. I have printed 1 lakh posters.
What is this? - Have a look.
The hero's photo is larger, like always.
If CDs don't sell like hot cakes then tell me!
Half yours and half mine. It's the same. - Shut up.
Rosy ma'am, tea. Thank you.
How is it? - Nice.
What is this?
Don't you know how to make tea?
How much sugar have you added?
One and Half.spoons, as instructed. - One and One forth.
I have One and One forth spoons of sugar in my tea, not One and Half.
Didn't you think it's necessary to ask me?
One and Half... a little less than One and Half and a little more than one. One and One forth. Got it?
But I was told One and Half.. - Stop your nonsense.
Apologise. Apologise to her.
Apologise. There's no harm in that.
Do you need an invitation to apologise?
Sorry. - What "Sorry"! Get lost!
And listen, clean my Scooty. I need to leave.
Scooty? - Do as she said. Get going. Go.
Do it. It's just a Scooty. Go.
Go. Get going.
Scram. Leave. Go.
What's going on? Is this a joke?
What kind of people have you kept?
I kept him on Mr. Sharma's recommendation.
I don't like him. - Tell me something..
First of all, you place some hearts near my photo.
Highlight my photo if you are increasing its size.
Baby, we will have big hoardings of you during the release.
Big ones. - I have seen your hoardings.
My photo should shine.
The hero will shine. - Stop it.
Movies don't sell because of the hero.
The heroine should be visible.
They have turned me into a laundry boy.
Mr. Sharma..
We'll shoot the next scene in a desert.
The scene goes like this..
From a distance we can see our hero coming, riding a horse..
Kuku. - Yes sir.
Come with me.
Write whatever I am saying.
Our hero is coming, riding a horse..
On his left hand he is holding the horse's rein..
..and on his right, a tambourine.
Mr. Sharma, the same tambourine which Rishi Kapoor used?
The same tambourine. Write same tambourine.
Now, in this shot I reveal the heroine..
And the heroine turns, in high speed.
And right then, strong winds start blowing..
And our hero who is on a horse, his long hair blows in the wind.
Sir, the hero doesn't have long hair.
If they aren't long then ask him to make them long by tomorrow.
This is not fair. Do one thing..
Call for a curly hair wig. He has an option between that or this.
I won't compromise with my shot.
Understood? - Yes, sir.
Our hero jumps off the camel..
But wasn't the hero was on a horse, sir?
So what? Option. Camel's option, horse.
And as soon as the tambourine plays, it starts lightening in the desert.
And it starts raining.
Sir, it doesn't rain in desert.
But the winds can blow. A windstorm can come. Write it down!
Five helicopter fans. Note it down.
Winds will blow, windstorm will come. Whatever we want will happen.
Go, follow him. Hurry up and give this list to him. - Sir..
Just a minute, sir. Sir..
Who is it?
Tea. - Yes, keep it here.
Thank you.
Kuku..
"Kuku!"
How much sugar did you add today?
One and One forth spoons. - One and One forth?
Yes. - Then why are you so scared?
I don't bite.
No, last time you made clean your Scooty because of the sugar. - Yes..
So this time, thinking about what you might make me do..
I added One and One forth spoons of sugar.
So cute, Kuku.
You will clean the Scooty today as well.
You will, won't you?
Look, don't think that I am like other snobbish heroines.
I am surrounded by selfish people.
I am supposed to do it.
I cannot be polite to anyone During the first meeting.
After all it's the question of Rosy's image.
Anyway, now say happy birthday.
Happy birthday. - Thank you, Kuku.
Now tell me, what will you do for me?
Shall we go shopping?
Clean the Scooty then we will go.
Okay?
Listen, what's your plan for tonight?
Tonight? Nothing.
Then listen, I need a Favour from you. - What favour?
I promised my best friend..
..that we both will go on a double date on my birthday.
I know it is senseless, but she is my best friend.
Rosy, what's a double date?
Kuku, you don't know what a double date is?
You are so cute!
Double date. Two couples on a date.
She'll come with her boyfriend and I'll come with mine.
Then, go.
With whom?
Last night I had a break-up with my businessman boyfriend.
Oh shit. How?
He didn't call at midnight to wish me.
Can you imagine! - Very bad.
I kept waiting for his phone call.
So many people called me, I didn't attend any calls.
Not even my parents'.
I kept waiting for his phone call.
I think I waited for 20 minutes.
Finally, I got irritated and called him up at 12 20am..
Can you imagine, that scoundrel was busy on another call!
My call was kept on waiting.
So cheap. Shameless.
You deserve better. You'll find someone better.
Then I will when I will. But what should I do today?
I cannot ditch my best Friend at the last moment.
She will think that I am avoiding giving her a treat.
So now what?
Please, Kuku, please come with me as my businessman boyfriend?
Please. Just for today. - No. I cannot.
We will go for dinner. You will be my businessman boyfriend. - No.
Anyway, look at you. You are so handsome.
You look like a businessman.
She won't doubt it even for a moment.
She knows all my other friends.
Please come with me. Everything will be fine. I promise.
We'll lie. We'll say that you have a textile business.
We will say that and leave. Okay?
No, restaurant. We'll say that I own a restaurant.
Okay? - You can say restaurant.
It's not like saying so will make you own one.
You'll come with me, right? - Yes. Okay.
Pack this.
I'm taking this. My birthday gift. - How much is it worth?
Hey come on, buy it for me.
Come on, Kuku. Nothing can go wrong. I am with you.
Just be confident.
There they are. Hi!
Mitali!
It's my birthday!
Hi!
Thank you.
'I spent 7 years in the same tuition centre..'
'..because she used to stay across it.'
'Today, finally, I was in front of her, face to face.'
'But as her best friend's boyfriend.'
'That too for just one night.'
I'm so happy.
'Kuku Mathur, this was biggest hoodwink of your life.'
'This is what I thought.'
Kuku, you know, Mitali and I are 2 30am friends.
Every night we talk at 2 30am.
I think we haven't missed a single day.
Too much. Kuku is into restaurant business.
It serves delicious food. Tell her.
And look at this. He bought it for me today. My birthday gift.
A heart-shaped ring. - Happy birthday, everyone.
Finally.
Pinkie, a pink cake especially for you.
Happy birthday. Happy birthday. - So sweet. Thank you.
Mitali, I swear you look like the titanic heroine.
Stop that, you meet her everyday.
Meet him. My boyfriend. Kuku.
I was just telling Mitali. He has a nice restaurant.
We will all go there together some day.
Kuku..
Restaurant...?
You know Kuku?
Mitali, Pinkie plays innocence well.
Either he is fooling her or she is making a fool of both of us. - What..?
Anyway, that is your personal matter.
Let me tell you, he is a pauper.
He was in my brother Ronnie's class.
They just cleared high school. He is a cheapskate.
He stealthily drinks fruit beer with my brother's money.
What...? - And a restaurant business?
Restaurant.. He doesn't know the B of business.
His father works at L.T.C. He stays in a flat.
'This wasn't a double date, it was double trouble.'
'I had such a punch line brewing inside..'
'..that it would have stunned all three of them.'
'But it never surfaced.'
Kuku, you are taking things too far now.
I'll slap you for lying to the girls here.
Get lost from here.
He sometimes borrows my brother's clothes.
Whose t-shirt is it? - Mine.
Get lost. - Kuku is that true?
He's such a liar.
Mitali, he lied on my birthday. - It's okay.
It's been going on for three months.
We'll cut your cake. Get a knife. - Forget about the cake.
Let the cake go to hell. I'm not in the mood.
It's okay. - He betrayed me.
Does he pay for my booze?
Mitali too is one of them! "I don't know the B of business."
Here's your booze. I don't want it.
Grandpa, that's 110.
What are you saying? It was 110 yesterday.
I just counted. It's 115.
I drink! Damn! Everything belongs to them.
Mitali is his girlfriend.
I told you, the difference between yellow and blue..
Sonu, what's Ronnie's friend doing here so late in the night?
Where's Ronnie? - Not here.
Damn..
I had told you. You can't see properly. You don't understand!
Let it be. It's not my fault.
Hey! Come here!
Come in.
Yes, grandpa? - What work do you have with Ronnie so late in the night?
It's nothing, grandpa. I needed to return something to him.
Ronnie has gone to distribute calendars.
Give it to me. I'll give it to him. - No, it's okay. I'll return it to him.
What's in it? - Nothing.
Beer. It's beer.
No, it's not beer. It's fruit beer.
Check the bags. Come on, we'll just find out..
Let go.. - Let go of it.
Hey, it's beer.
It's fruit beer. Check it properly.
You drink alcohol?
Hey.. - You drink alcohol?
You are trying to spoil our Ronnie?
What are you saying, grandpa? I don't drink.
Ronnie asked me to get them. - You are lying.
Why would Ronnie want them?
You think we are stupid?
One tight slap and the structure of your face will change.
I'll thrash you so hard that you'll forget where you stay.
You'll forget your father's name.
By the way, what's your father's name? Where do you stay?
Grandpa, he is Mathur's son.
The one who has a wretched scooter? Look, it's parked outside.
Mathur? - Yes.
Who Mathur? - The one whose wife died due to electric shock.
The one who stays in a 40-yard house, behind the gutter.
Stop your nonsense.. - The 40-yard house?
Near the gutter. - You should stay within your 40 yards.
Why have you come here?
It's rightly said that the children get spoiled..
.. if they lose their mother.
And such people need an excuse to do illicit deeds.
Don't you have any shame?
Or have you lost of it?
Is this what your parents have taught you?
Why are you blaming my parents?
Stay within your limit.
You are Ronnie's grandpa that's why I am staying quiet.
Otherwise, even I know how to abuse..
Look how he is talking to grandpa!
Kuku, why are you talking to grandpa in such a manner?
Have you lost your mind? - You don't know anything.
They have been accusing me since so long.
Grandpa saw liquor bottles in his hand.
He has been abusing grandpa since then. - Yes.
Look, that's how your friends are. - Ronnie, they have been..
Look down when you speak to me!
Apologise to grandpa. - Why should I apologise?
They have been abusing me, they should apologise.
Just because the Gulatis have opened their second shop..
Everything you will say will be right?
Just because I am a Mathur, I am not rich, I am wrong?
Why are you blabbering nonsense?
Hey.. - Have you lost your mind?
Apologise to grandpa otherwise we'll be done for good.
We'll be done for good? You have changed.
I'll see each one of you. I'll see you as well.
Get lost! - Hey! Watch out!
Don't you dare come here again!
Ronnie! Ronnie!
Ronnie! Ronnie! Ronnie! There's Ronnie everywhere!
I'm fed up of this Ronnie.
In school he used to say don't tell anyone..
We have a sari shop. We'll joke about it.
Now he has become a businessman by selling blouse and petticoat.
Ronnie Matching Centre.
Not Ronnie Matching Centre, you are a mismatch!
Mitali too is one of them.
Everything belongs to the Gulatis.
Tell me if I don't teach these Gulatis a lesson!
What happened, Angry Young Man?
'He's brother Prabhakar.'
'My first cousin from Kanpur.'
'He's always at the right place at the right time.'
Prabhakar..
Hello. - Hi. Come here.
Why are you getting so hyper?
What's your problem? Tell me. I'll help you find a solution.
Have a seat.
I provide solution to the world.
Tell me what happened. Do you have problem with your job?
What happened?
I don't know whether this is a job or a punishment?
I knew it.
Damn, they keep me running Around the whole day.
And that director thinks that he's from Hollywood!
Tell me what's my fault if it doesn't rain in desert?
What should I do if the hero's hair doesn't grow in a day?
Tell me, if the heroine has One and Half spoons of sugar..
..instead of One and One forth in her tea then what harm will it do to her?
And that hero, he thinks he is Bollywood's superstar.
Enough. Enough. Enough. - They have ruined me.
No, don't say that. Enough.
It will all be okay. - I wanted to open a restaurant.
You will open a restaurant. You will.
They tell me to make tea, clean the Scooty.
Everything will be fine.
I'm telling you, in time, everything will be fine.
Forget about all this.
Tell me, who is Ronnie?
'When someone suffers from a stomach-ache..'
'The one in front of him becomes a doctor.'
'I too consider Prabhakar to be my doctor.'
'And I told him everything.'
'You know what conclusion did Prabhakar make out of it?'
So basically, Gulati and sons have taken you for a ride.
Taken me for a ride? - Yes.
This is a very old problem.
I have also suffered because of it.
'I had a childhood friend, Bindu.'
'And I had a childhood sweetheart, Sunaina.'
'I loved her in my dreams and planned a family as well.'
'But my best friend played a cheap trick and stole her away from me.'
Sunaina belonged to him.
Then what happened?
What could've happened?
Whatever that was done was done by Prabhu.
I did it.
Priest, do you want imported liquor?
What do I need to do, Prabhakar?
Evil powers hover over this child.
What?!
There's just one solution for that.
What...? What's the solution?
Just tell us. We are ready to do anything.
Bindu, say something, please.
You will have to change his name.
From now his name will be..
Prabhakar.
My Prabhakar!
Prabhakar, baby, finish the milk.
I love you, Prabhakar.
Prabhakar, wear your knickers.
Why are you roaming around naked?
Prabhakar!
Deenanath Shukla.
Full name.
'And at that very moment, I made Prabhakar my godfather.'
Sulking won't help.
He didn't just insult you, he insulted me as well.
You are my brother.
I swear. I feel humiliated.
If this was Kanpur I would've made Gulatis apologise..
..by threatening them with my knife.
End of the topic.
Brother, I feel like running away from here.
You don't run away.
Elope with his girlfriend.
He doesn't have a girlfriend.
Then his sister.
She's just like a sister to me.
Then I'll elope with her.
What's the big deal?
You get emotional too soon.
Your problem is his business, right?
Do one thing, make the income tax guys raid his shop.
How will that help?
All their stock is in the warehouse.
Then set the warehouse on fire.
Got it?
Are you getting me?
You are not, right?
Then listen to me.
Set the warehouse on fire, burn everything..
..take everything out of there and sell them.
Whatever cash you get from that, with that we'll open your..
Restaurant.
Are you getting me? You are smiling, already.
Restaurant..
Is there any other option?
I am giving you the throne and you want to go on exile.
Let go of my hand. Don't hold it. Let me go.
What you do mean? - What do you mean by what do I mean?
Do I need to explain everything?
Do you want to be a businessman?
I want to.
Do you want to ruin Ronnie?
I want to. - Do you want to open a restaurant?
I want to.
Do you want to place a bigger board than theirs?
I want to be a businessman, ruin Ronnie..
..open a restaurant and have a bigger board!
Very good!
But how will we do this?
When will this happen?
'It will happen. It will happen on Monday.'
Everyone is requested to attend the prayer meeting..
..on Monday at the Monday market.
Everyone is welcome to come.
We need to cajole Goddess with a lot of love and devotion.
Everyone is welcomed to this market.
Hail the Goddess!
Say it affectionately.
Hail the Goddess! - Louder!
Hail the Goddess! - Hail the Goddess!
Excuse me..
Do you wish to drink imported liquor?
Yes.
He is my cousin. He needed your help.
Come on, Kuku.
Your cousin is my cousin.
Won't one brother help another?
Tell me, how can I help you?
What you need to do this..
You have come from Kanpur today?
No, yesterday. - Yesterday.
Now listen to what you need to do.. - Where in Kanpur do you stay?
Somewhere in north. - In north?
Where? - Do you know your way around Kanpur?
Yes, I've been there a lot. - You have.
Do you remember the Jharkarkati bridge?
Jharkarkati bridge? Yes.
Going below it, take a left towards Anand Vihar.
Yes. - The first house on the right side.
What are you saying? - Yes. Right there.
My kin's in-laws stay there.
I've been there quite often.
That means you are very close.
I'm so happy.
Jhakarkatti.
Are you done?
Yes.
Can we get down to business? It's okay. - Oh yes. I forgot.
The thing is, during the prayer meet..
Everyone in the vicinity will be there. - Yes.
So it's obvious that the Gulati family will also be there. - True.
Where will you be?
I'm always at the warehouse.
At the warehouse. - Yes.
So, you don't need to do anything. - Okay.
We will come there at night. - Okay.
We will knock at the door. Open it for us.
Okay. - We will go inside.
We will load all the stock in there into a truck.
Wonderful.
Then we will again go inside. - Again? - Yes.
We'll set the warehouse on fire.
Is that all? -Yes, that's all.
Then consider it done.
Give me that glass. - Just a minute.
Just a minute.
Shake your head a little. Shake it like this.
We have to set the warehouse on fire.
I won't do this. - Hey..
You cannot force me. - Sit down. Listen to me.
You cannot force me. - Sit down.
Sit down. - Sit down.
Fire.. - Just a minute.
A few moments ago you were talking about relationships.
You were addressing me as your brother.
I told you do a small favour and you want to run away!
I am forcing you? - It's not so, brother.
Why is it not so? Listen to me.
I am saying this to you..
..because Vibhishana held the key to Lanka's downfall.
And you are our Vibhishana.
Did Vibhishana do anything because he was greedy?
Did he?
He didn't, right? Then?
But he benefited, right?
The warehouse stocks goods worth Rs.15-20 lakhs.
What are you thinking about?
I am addressing you as Vibhishana..
Is your brain filled with filth?
Your brain is filled with filth. Spit it out!
Spit it out! - Yes spit it out.
You must be feeling lighter? - Are you?
Come here.
Look, he has been watching us for so long.
But brother is not calling him.
You are not calling him.
Keep this here.
That's enough. That's enough, brother.
From tonight, we are partners.
Partner? - Partner.
Cheers! - Cheers!
Tittu, increase the sound of the drums.
Tinku, yes..
Yes, take the guitar.
Mike okay?
Okay.
"Let's welcome the Goddess.."
"With a hope in heart."
"Goddess fulfils everyone's wishes.."
"We should keep welcoming her."
Hello. Hello. Mike testing. Mike testing.
Hello. One, two. One two.
Monu! - Yes, sir?
What's wrong with you! How many times have I told you to check the mike?
Come on, place it on another point. Check it now?
Is it working fine now? - Good. Good.
Very good. Very good. - Hello. Hello. Hello.
Devotees, your Goddess is here.
Every one of you will together say, welcome.
Welcome. - Welcome.
Goddess, seasons greeting. Goddess..
Very respectfully, to You we say..
"Welcome, oh Goddess!"
In this meet organised by Lali Lalchand and Party..
..lies a hidden opportunity.
You just need to tell us, how many times Lali..
..uses the word welcome during this program.
The one who gives the right answer will get Goddess's..
Treasure!
All the devotees will raise their hands!
Sinners won't raise their hands!
Hail!
"Every season we welcome You."
"For every reason, we welcome You."
"Give me the permission to welcome, oh Goddess."
"Welcome, oh Goddess!"
"Everyone say it together, welcome."
"Everyone say it from your heart, welcome."
"We welcome You with pomp and show, but softy."
"Welcome, oh Goddess!"
"Welcome. Welcome. Welcome."
"Play it!"
"Bend a little!"
"Welcome. Welcome. Welcome."
"Welcome, oh Goddess!"
Wait, ma'am. Welcome, brother.
Sir, we need to make a request.
Yes, we will sing it. For sure. - Hey..
We have got a request.. - Just a minute.
Brother.. - Introducing the superstar of television..
A great artist, performer, my brother..
What's his name? - His name is O.P. Tyagi.
Oh yes. He played Jatayu in the serial, Ramayana.
O.P. Tyagi!
Goddess is about to join us.
Have a look..
You won't get to see such a sight again.
Tyagi played Jatayu.
Here, he has come as a lion.
Where's brother?
A huge round of applause for the lion.
"Hail the Goddess!"
We have got a request. And the name of the hymn is..
1, 2, 3!
"I'll go to Goddess' heavenly abode!"
"Say 1, 2, 3!"
"I'll go whenever Goddess beckons me!"
"I'll go to Goddess' heavenly abode!"
"Say 1, 2, 3!"
"Say 1, 2, 3!" - "All hail!"
"Oh Goddess who is as pure as fire!"
"We all always hail to You!"
"Hail the Goddess! Oh Goddess!"
"Hail the Goddess!"
"I invited Goddess!"
"I welcomed Her time and again."
"I've opened the windows of my heart."
"You've opened Your doors for me."
Watch out! - Be careful, partner.
"Lali says, heed my prayers."
"This is all I think about."
"I welcome You to my house."
"I'll adorn You with garland of roses."
"With Goddess.."
"With Goddess I'll have my photos clicked."
"Say 1, 2, 3!"
"5000.."
"I'll offer a stole worth Rs. 5000."
"Say 1, 2, 3!"
"I'll have prayer meets for 16 Fridays!"
"I'll adorn Goddess with 16 embellishments!"
"Barefoot.."
"I'll go there running barefoot!"
"Say 1, 2, 3!"
"I won't take a bus! - I won't!"
"I won't take a train! - I won't!"
"I won't take a flight! - I won't!"
"I won't take a Maruti car! - I won't!"
"I won't take a Metro! - I won't!"
"I won't take an auto-rickshaw! - I won't!"
"Goddess' love will beckon me and I'll be there in no time!"
"Barefoot.."
"I'll go there running barefoot!"
"Say 1, 2, 3!"
"Welcome, Oh Goddess.. "Say 1, 2, 3!"
"Welcome, Oh Goddess.. - "Say 1, 2, 3!"
"Say 1, 2, 3!"
"Everyone.. - "Say 1, 2, 3!"
"Devotees.. -"Say 1, 2, 3!"
"Sinner.. - "Say 1, 2, 3!"
"Kids.. - "Say 1, 2, 3!"
"Seniors.. - "Say 1, 2, 3!"
"Ladies.. - "Say 1, 2, 3!"
"Gents.. - "Say 1, 2, 3!"
"Sisters.. - "Say 1, 2, 3!"
"All hail! - "Say 1, 2, 3!"
"All hail!"
"Yeah!"
"Come on!"
"It's 1, 2, 3!"
"Your father was stunned."
"Your brother was beguiled."
"I don't know why you wanna do me like that."
"You were betrayed, day and night."
"You were screwed."
"Neither are you a lion nor am I a cheetah."
"We are all scapegoats!"
"You were stunned."
"You were beguiled."
"It's 1, 2, 3!"
"Lord Rama name was taken and Lanka was set on fire!"
"No insurance was taken either!"
"These hues of modern age engulfed everything."
"Lord Rama name was taken and Lanka was set on fire!"
"It wasn't BLTTE."
"Say 1, 2, 3!"
"Everyone.. - "Say 1, 2, 3!"
"Devotees.. - "Say 1, 2, 3!"
"Now your time's come."
"1, 2, 3."
"Game over!"
"Everyone say, all hail the heavenly abode!"
"Yeah."
What is it? - A courier.
From where? - Delhi.
Sign here.
What? - Write your name..
Your name!
Here. - No, here?
He sent a sari!
It's beautiful!
It was just here.
She keeps the mobile hanging around her all day long.
Why doesn't she just disappear into it?
Damn the games!
Hey Suresh..
What? - Your wife's calling you.
Hello? - Hello.
Got it? Did you get it?
Did you wear it? Did you?
Will you ever say something or you'll just keep making noises?
You didn't inform me.
I never inform. You know that.
I just do it.
How do you look in it?
What can I say?
You can see it for yourself.
I swear, if I was there..
I wouldn't tell you, I would've just done it.
Hey..
Naughty.
Who's being naughty?
I am married to you. It's not a joke!
You too are just too much!
Hello. Hello?
Hello. - My game..
Over.
Switch that off.
Switch it off.
Get your phone out.
Type a message to Ronnie.
Do it.
My dear friend..
Sorry to hear about the fire at your warehouse.
I am outdoors.
Working, shooting.
Coming back in two days.
Then I'll call you.
Your friend. I love you.
Write it.
Now keep that in your pocket and listen to me very carefully.
Have you planned everything?
Yes, I have planned everything, brother.
You found a cashier?
You got the place? The location? And everything else?
I haven't done all that. - No, you haven't done all that.
I'm feeling scared for you.
Give me the money. I'll invest it.
Okay? You'll get double returns.
And by the time you would've made all your plans.
I have made all the plans.
I'll make you cut the inauguration ribbon.
You are making me emotional.
I'm always ready to cut!
It's just like there's no relief for the chicken or the egg.
Now what does this have to do with the discussion we just had?
Tell me, is it related?
Who's the chicken and who's the egg?
Who? - It's just a phrase.
I know it is a phrase. I am not illiterate!
It was fitting the context.
You have won the contest.
Actually, brother.. - You got a lot of money.
How many more contests do you want to win?
I think it will be very difficult for you.
Now listen to what I am saying. Rather, jot it down.
Your restaurant will get build on its own, with magic.
Just like this. Three, two..
"Fortune is smiling upon us!"
We don't want waiters in our restaurant.
We need waitresses.
Waitresses! - Waitresses!
Excuse me, where's Tikona Park?
What? - Tikona Park.
Tikona Park? - Yes.
I don't know. I am new here. - Come on man!
Grandpa used to say..
Never waste time on something that won't give any return.
He was absolutely right.
You are doing great!
Now you just wait and watch!
'One rides on high confidence when he just becomes a businessman.'
'It was the same with me.'
Hello, aunt. - Hi.
How are you? Can I drop you somewhere?
No, thank you. We don't want to go anywhere.
No, we do. Thank you, son.
Come on, he will drop us. He is a nice boy.
Mummy! What are you doing?!
No, mummy. We don't want to go anywhere.
Get in. He will drop us.
Mummy.. - Take the first left and then..
Take a right from the signal, then a left from the circle.
Third lane from right, the fifth house. I know.
He is so smart. - How do you know?
Seema Didi Tuition centre, bang opposite your house.
I was a student there.
Son, do you work in a vegetable market?
No, mummy. He has a restaurant.
Of course, I do. Aunt, the DDR, the sweet shop next to it..
I renovated the wretched place and.. - Show her the menu card.
It must be here.
Let it be. We don't want to see the menu card.
Come on, mummy!
Look, aunt, we'll anyway go home and cook.
Come to my restaurant. I'll cook you a nice meal.
And I'll prove my point to you as well. Okay?
Son, do you make kidney beans with rice?
What are you doing, mummy?
Of course, aunt. - Let's go.
We'll have lunch and then go home.
"Like a key made for every lock."
"Like gloves are made for the winter shock."
"Like biscuit are made for a tea bath."
"And you are made for me.."
"Like songs are made to be hummed."
"Like canteens are made to run on credit."
"Like politicians, to make money."
"And you are made for me."
"You.."
"Are made for me."
"Yes, you are made for me."
"You.."
"Are made for me."
"Yes, you are made for me."
"You and I.."
"For each other.."
"We are made.."
"Yes! Yes! Yes!"
It's nice, but very dry.
Oh really!
You own a restaurant hence you don't like food from elsewhere.
By the way, Kuku, don't you think this name Kuku is a little funny.
Ku-ku-ku-ku-ku-ku.. - Hey!
Doesn't anyone in your family have a funny name?
No. No one in my family has a funny name.
Wonderful. Here I spot two lovebirds!
You guys please..
Hey you wayward bird!
Mitali, you turned out to be very smart.
You were all over Himanshu on a bike just yesterday..
And now you are going for long drives with this Kuku.
You stole my boyfriend because he has a boyfriend?
And you?
You gave her a lift and reeled her in, didn't you?
She has a loose character. A bloody gold-digger.
Rosy.. - What?
Just shut up, okay! - Shut up.
Shut up! When? Why? How? Where?
Why shut up? Why is everyone being shut up here?
Listen up, "Shut up" girl. Don't act smart.
The whole vicinity knows everything about you.
Rosy, why are you guys.. - Settle down, wild cat!
Mitali, what do you think this Kuku is?
He used to serve tea at our production house.
He used to hold the Styrofoam.
He used to clean the Scooty.
He used to slouch while walking.
Take this, take that. From here.. - Hey Monkey, get going from here!
Hey Hrithik Roshan, every movie has just one hero.
And I am the hero of this movie.
Got it?
You? A hero?
Have you ever seen your face in the mirror?
Hey! - Shall I tell you his boyfriend's tales?
Boyfriend? - Yes.
We came here to have a cup of coffee.
We don't want to drink coffee.
We don't want to discuss this matter. - Take him away. Leave.
We don't want to discuss this matter.
We are leaving. We are decent people.
Let's go. - Why should we leave? - Take her away.
Why should we leave just because a worthless tea server said something?
Who are you calling a tea server?
Who is he? - Back off! - Let it go.
I'll tell you all the tales about his boyfriend.
What does he think of himself? - Should I tell about your boyfriend?
Say whatever you want! I don't care! - Let's go! - Take her away!
Bloody spot boy! - Haryanvi actor.
And you! You turned out to be gay!
You said those dialogues of heaven's bird in front of me..
Leave! - Did I say anything?
I didn't say anything.
Let's enjoy.
Churanlal.
What?
My paternal uncle's name.
Gimmy uncle..
My maternal uncle.
And do you know what my maternal aunt's name is?
What?
Polly.
Mithu. - What?
My name.
Mithu?
"There's a lot to talk about."
"This life is meant to be spent with you."
"A sign is enough to say it all."
"That you.. are made for me."
"You.."
"Are made for me."
"Yes, you are made for me."
"You.."
"Are made for me."
"Yes, you are made for me."
"You and I.."
"For each other.."
"We are made.."
What is this, Kuku!
I've been calling you since the past one month!
You aren't answering my calls. You are disconnecting them.
Talk softly. - It's been a month you've not being coming for work.
You should at least return the company's goods if you have left the job.
My father wasn't keeping well. That's why I couldn't come.
Your father was unwell, but you were fine, right?
Talk softly. I'll give them to you tomorrow.
Please leave. Please. - Okay. I am leaving.
But don't forget it. - I won't.
Son, where have you been going if not at work?
Well..
This is it, papa.
Kuku Kwalti..
Where did you get the money to do all this?
Uncle, you know, as there a queen behind every king..
There's the same story behind every business.
And the title of that story is "sponsor".
We have one.
You didn't get me? We got the money.
Then why did you hide it from me?
Who is the sponsor?
I'll introduce him to you.
Hey! - Hi.
George says..
George?
George Bush, the one in America..
Okay. - What does he say?
There are two things in a business.
Capital and return.
But you don't get return from the capital.
You get return from talent.
One day he feed me.
What did he feed me?
Sweets?
Potatoes.
Sweets made out of potatoes.
Sweets made out of potatoes, sir.
Just imagine. He fed me sweets made out of potatoes.
Right then I decided..
I decided that I will invest in this talent.
Thank you very much, sir.
Being a third-person you recognised my son's talent.
Thank you. - It's okay.
I thought that as my son didn't join NASA as a scientist..
..he has failed in the trial of life as well.
Sir, these has been something that has been worrying me these days.
Why? - Our company is getting privatised.
But Kuku..
Sorry, son.
I didn't support you.
I'm sorry. Sorry.
I'm sorry, son. - It's okay, uncle.
It's okay. - It's okay.
I'm sorry, son.
It's okay, uncle.
You are again reading.
I used to score good marks in school. Ask me how.
How? - How?
Ronnie? - Who else?
How are you, bro?!
I'm fine. - You've become a big shot.
You've started such a big restaurant.
You didn't call me.
I was going to call you..
Cool. It's okay. It happens.
I can understand.
Do all the workers work under you?
That's great.
You remember our teacher Kalpana ma'am in the seventh grade? - Yes.
She used to always leave a remark on your report card..
"Kuku Mathur can do better."
I never understood what it meant.
I understood that today.
You have proven it, bro! Kuku Mathur can actually do better.
What did I do? My grandpa owns a sari shop.
He made me sell blouses.
Gulati Sons became Gulati Sons and Grandsons.
It's great. - What's great in that?
You are the one who is great.
I am proud of you.
It's doing well.
I've brought a gift for you. Unwrap it.
What is it? - Open it. Have a look at it for yourself.
It will bring back fond memories. - Fruit beer?
What else!
Air-conditioned!
It blows cool air! - Just..
Who invested in this business?
My father took a loan. - Great.
You tell me about yourself. How's work?
It's going just fine.
You know that the warehouse caught fire on the night of the prayer meet.
Goods worth Rs. 15 lakhs got burned.
15 lakhs? - Yes.
We are facing a little cash crunch since then.
You were there. - Yes, I was there.
Chota was dressed as the Goddess.
The TV star that plays the role of Jatayu had come.
Forget about it.
I made you sentimental, didn't I? - Yes.
Why are you eating this? - Chutney. Get some chutney!
Chotu! Why didn't you get the chutney?
Why are you taking so long?
Drink it. - Tell me, how's life?
'Time used to fly when we used to drink at the warehouse.'
'But that day when Ronnie came to the restaurant..'
'I just felt that we should consume all the fruit beer quickly..'
'So that Ronnie leaves this place.'
You didn't print calendars?
I was going to but.. - Print them. Has big impact.
Menu card. Shall I take them? I'll distribute them.
Okay - Okay?
It was fun to meet you after so many days.
Kuku Mathur. You do your job. I'll call you tonight.
I'll go and distribute these. Okay.
'I was feeling a little strange that day.'
'I couldn't sleep at night.'
'I stayed back at the restaurant.'
'I got up with a headache.'
'I had warm water.'
'I did yoga.'
'I didn't suffer from constipation either.'
'Yet I was feeling a little strange.'
Kuku.. - Yes.
Is Sunday a holiday for businessmen as well?
I was just enquiring because you didn't go to the restaurant.
I am just getting ready, papa.
Nephew? - Yes?
What's wrong with him?
Forget about him, uncle. I am worried about you.
What's wrong with me, Prabhakar?
You said that your company is getting privatised.
Yes, so?
Look, uncle..
Please don't mind but..
..there's a vast difference between MA, BA and MBA.
It's not so. You can think over it. There's no hurry.
You can think over it.
I meant that you may have to pay dearly because of computerization.
Blessings wish to reach you..
..but there are a lot of obstacles in its path.
Traffic jams, no entry, railway crossing, check posts..
By the time blessings pass through all these, it's exhausted.
It's shattered.
How can blessings meant for you..
..reach you hot and fresh?
What should we do for that?
I have some money.
No, we don't need money.
You paid the entry fee, right?
Then why should you pay every time?
We need your devotion, your dedication, your sacrifice..
That is what we want.
Begin. - Okay.
Any devotee who wishes to ask a question to him can raise his hand.
Calm down.
Me! Me! Me!
Hey, give it to me.
Yes, ma'am?
Hello, sage.
I have two sons.
They have always been fighting since they were kids.
We have split the property.
I sometimes stay with one and sometimes with the other.
I cry a lot.
Do you enjoy eating fried bread with tangy chutney?
What?
Do you? - Sometimes.
Which chutney do you use? The red one or the green one?
The red one with dry ginger in it.
Try using the green chutney this time.
Okay. - And offer green bangles to Goddess.
Okay. - She will bless you.
Praises to the sage!
Me! Me! Me!
You..
Hello, sage.
I keep studying all year around.
But I mess up doing the exams.
My family too has warned me that if I don't clear..
..my exams this year that they will make me sell vegetables.
Do you drink alcohol? - No.
Never. I never even touch it.
A cap full? - Never.
Have friends ever given to you saying it's a cold drink?
No, no, no. Never.
Do you have a liquor shop close to your house?
Yes, a little ahead of my house.
On the left? - No, on the right.
It will be on the right side when you are returning, right?
Yes.
While returning, buy a beer from the liquor shop..
Chilled or room temperature?
Chilled? - Okay.
And give offerings to Goddess. - Okay.
Praises to the sage! - Thank you.
Praises to the sage!
Excuse me, let go of it for a second.
One question! Just one question!
Calm down! Silence!
What do you want?
Blessings!
What kind of blessings do you want?
Hot and.. - Fresh!
Praise the Lord! - Praise the Lord!
Praises to the sage!
You can add him on Facebook, Twitter and Whatsapp.
I, too, want to meet him.
Rs. 500 for a private session. Any time, any where.
Do you understand what faith is?
Belief?
When a person's faith in a statue decreases he comes to me.
And put the same faith back in something else and return it to him.
Faith.
Look..
My faith in you.
Your faith in me.
But how will I know that my faith has been restored?
A signal.
A sign.
A lighting..
Or a sound.
And you will believe that there's faith.
Enlightenment.
What did you just say?
What an amazing thought!
What an amazing thought indeed!
My soul spoke! Amazing! - Look! I've got goosebumps.
I've got goosebumps. - Yes. But when will I get enlightenment?
You will, you fool.
Today it was my turn. Soon it will be yours.
Enlightenment.
Her blessings will always be with you. Go.
Greet him. - "Distances were expunged.."
Sage.. Get up. Get up. - "And we got close.."
"It's a strange experience."
You have met him. Now everything will be fine.
"Let me just express my feelings now.."
"This is a strange co-incidence!"
You are seriously so disgraceful!
Just a minute. I'll call you back.
What is it? - Where's Kuku?
Kuku! What happened?
He's not answering his phone.
He's answering all my calls.
Is he ignoring you?
You are not someone who can be ignored.
Hey, I was just saying..
You are such a scoundrel, Prabhakar!
I swear! What are you doing?
I couldn't understand when and how will this enlightenment happen.
Kuku, Chota is crying. - What?
What is it? - You just come home quickly.
Chota! Open the door, Chota!
What happened? - I don't know. She isn't opening the door.
Open the door, Chota.
Chota! - Chota!
Open the door! What's wrong?
She has been crying since the time she returned from school.
She's not telling me what happened. - Chota!
Move away, Mitali.
Chota, please stop crying.
No, brother. Please don't open the door.
Please don't do anything stupid.
Chota. - Tell me what's wrong.
No, I don't want to tell you anything.
Do you remember what mom used to say?
We will solve all our problems together.
I am coming inside. And you will tell me what's wrong. Okay?
What's wrong, Chota? - Chota.
What happened? - I will fail, brother.
Why? You said that all your exams went well.
I leaked the exam papers.
I was well prepared. I had to only study three chapters.
But brother Prabhakar kept saying "Ask how!"..
"Ask how one can get more marks without studying."
So I asked.
He took me to Friends Colony.
To the Printing Press.
We leaked the papers from there.
English, maths, science, social..
All the papers were the same.
But then madam came to know about it.
She changed the Sanskrit question paper.
Don't cry.
To me, Prabhakar always looked liked a criminal.
He did this with me as well.
If I wanted I could have topped.
If I wanted, if not a restaurant, I could've opened a food stall.
But I got influenced by Prabhakar and leaked the paper.
And I got influenced by him and set Ronnie's warehouse on fire.
You set Ronnie's warehouse on fire?
What are you saying, Kuku!
I cannot even apologise to Neetu ma'am.
Kuku this..
'A signal.'
'Or a lightening..'
'Lights will switch off and on.'
'Enlightenment.'
Light, truth.
Enlightenment!
Mitali, it's enlightenment!
Mitali, it's enlightenment! - What?
I'm getting enlightened.
This is enlightenment!
The light of truth.
I have realised what mistake I have made.
I will apologise to Ronnie.
I will tell everything to Ronnie.
Don't cry.
Mitali, I will apologise to Ronnie.
I will apologise to him.
Papa?
Did you leave office early today?
I didn't leave early, son. I've left office forever.
What do you mean? - I mean, I took VRS.
Look, I have got millions.
Now I will invest this money in your business.
Why?
Your brother Prabhakar gave me a very good idea.
What's the use of a private job?
I am sorry, papa.
Kuku, it's okay. - I am sorry.
Hey..
My son got emotional.
What's wrong with the lights?
I think the voltage is down.
Maybe you need to understand.
Everyone has reasons, not just one. Do you understand?
Don't you have any shame? - Wait.
You are a criminal!
You made me a thief! - Wait.
What happened, Angry Young Man?
You happened, Prabhakar Shukla! You!
I ruined my best friend because of you.
Chota flunked because of you!
My father lost his job!
Calm down, Mathur. Please let me explain.
What will you explain? What will you explain?
You made me steal and then you stole from me.
You sold goods worth Rs. 15 lakhs and gave me 12 lakhs.
That night when you tore Ronnie matching centre's calendar..
What was going on in your mind?
What difference does that make? - No, no, no.
What was more important at that moment?
What difference does that make? - Friend or business?
Yes?
Business.
So, I tried my best and made you a businessman.
I fulfilled my promise.
Kuku Mathur, I only showed you the path.
These are your deeds.
And it's not as if you have done something big.
It's not like Ronnie's grandpa did a noble deed and made that warehouse.
Every businessman has to use another to become a businessman.
Now tell me what's more important for you?
Business or friend?
Friend. - What did you say?
Friend. - Speak louder. I didn't hear you.
Friend. - That's fantastic, brother!
Go to your friend and give him a hug.
God willing he will forgive you.
Go. Go. Go.
Good luck. Listen..
Blame it to me. I'll handle it. - Okay.
Most welcome.
Go. Run!
Run! Run!
You are.. no you.
What the..
Ask him that shop's address! - He doesn't know.
He is new to the city.
Look at this! This yellow one. - No.
Look at its border.
Rs. 500.. - Rs. 500! We don't have any sari worth Rs. 500!
The cheapest one is worth Rs. 750.
I'll show them to you. - Get them out.
Drink a cold drink for her. - No? - No?
What colour do you want? Tell me at least something.
Check out their gentry and then show them the saris.
Here. Show her this magenta sari. She will like it.
Welcome, madam.
Get a cold drink for her.
We sell all kinds of saris.
For parties, for birthdays and for special prayer meetings.
So, which one do you want?
Suresh. - What kind of a sari is Suresh?
I mean which Suresh do you want?
My Suresh.
That's fine. But where are you from?
Darbhanga.
Darbhanga?
You are Bihari's wife!
She is Bihari's wife! It's okay.
Have a seat. I'll call Bihari! - Wait!
Call Bihari!
Himanshu! - What happened?
This sari is from that lot! - Which lot?
The lot that got burned in the warehouse.
The sari from the lot that got burned in the warehouse?
What is the sari from the lot that got burned..
..in the warehouse doing with you?
How did you get it?
Bihari gave it to you, didn't he?
Bihari gave it to you? Move aside!
You are wearing our sari and smiling!
Go and call Bihari!
Call Bihari! - Bihari!
Hit him!
Why are you hitting him? - Move aside!
He hooked up with my girlfriend using my money!
What are you waiting for? Get the car!
Move aside, Ronnie!
You just wait and watch! We'll turn him into a ghost.
He has locked horns with Gulati's.
Bihari, I'll get back to you as well.
Hey but brother.. - Let's go.
What are they saying? Kuku cannot do this.
He did it.
Aunty! Aunty, where's Ronnie?
Upstairs.
Kuku? What's wrong?
Kuku!
Ronnie.. I'm very sorry, man.
Sorry? Why are you sorry?
Well..
You set our warehouse on fire, didn't you?
Tell me the truth, you set it on fire, didn't you?
Yes, but..
Don't you have any shame?
If you needed money you should've come to me.
Thief. Why have you come here?
Grandpa and Himanshu have gone to thrash you.
You have come here to save yourself. You are doing this drama.
What are you saying?
I didn't come here fearing anyone.
I came here on my own. I was enlightened.
Damn the enlightenment. Get lost from here.
He was enlightened.
Chota flunked in her exams.
She told me how Prabhakar made her leak the papers..
She flunked.
How my father lost his job because of Prabhakar.
And I ruined my brother's life.
That's when I was enlightened.
That's when I realised that I made the same mistake.
I set my brother's warehouse of fire and started my restaurant.
I have left my business and came here.
Please forgive me.
Wait a minute. - What are you doing?
Oh damn.
Drive. - Just a minute.
Yes, Ronnie? - Where are you?
We are almost there. We are stuck in a traffic jam.
Don't worry. We won't spare him today.
We'll turn him into a ghost! - You are stuck in traffic jam?
Saw? They are stuck in traffic jam.
I didn't come here out of fear. I was enlightened.
Kuku! That's Kuku's voice. Kuku is in our house!
Kuku is in our house!
What are you waiting for? Drive!
Move aside! - Turn the car around!
Please forgive me.
I don't have a mother.
Bunty Rocky come here.
Come on! - Kuku is here!
Monu catch him. Sonu take out the hockey.
'The Gulatis wanted to send me to prison but the sage saved me.'
'But he couldn't save everything.'
'The money papa got from VRS in the morning..'
'We lost in the evening.'
'We lost my restaurant as well.'
'Ronnie couldn't do anything to help.'
'It was my fault.'
'But one thing was given.'
'I was not going to spare brother Prabhakar.'
I won't spare him today!
Prabhakar?
What happened?
It's nothing, uncle. - How did this happen?
Tell me, what are you wearing?
Please tell me.
Wait a second. Who is it?
I am Prabhakar. - Prabha..
Same here. How are you, kid?
And I am..
'What's the solution?'
'From now his name will be..'
'I love you, Prabhakar.'
'Prabhakar's father.'
'Today, after a long time Papa came to our room.'
'We have never seen him behave like this.'
'It felt as if we three were missing mom a lot, today.'
Papa..
I am sorry, papa.
All this happened because of me..
Son.. It's neither your fault nor Chota's.
I, too, got influenced by Prabhakar.
If only I would've believed in you..
I would've given you money for your restaurant.
Dad I made a grave mistake.
I don't know. The sari is so nice.
Look, this is a perfect match.
You won't get a better piece.
This isn't matching either.
It is an orange sari and you are showing me maroon cut-pieces.
So much of my time has been wasted.
I cannot find the right colour.
Chotu, show them to her. - Show them to me, Chotu.
Yes, that one.
You got it. Keep it aside. I'll eat it in some time.
Eat.
Who are these guys?
I don't know.
Himanshu.
Yes? What happened?
Who are these guys? - Insurance guys.
Insurance?
They have come to give the insurance money for the warehouse.
The warehouse was insured?
Then what! Do you think we are crazy?
What's for lunch? - Then why did you take money from Kuku?
Stop chanting Kuku's name!
Don't take his name in front of me! Mummy, reason it with him.
Get this straight. We are Gulatis. He burned our warehouse.
Do you want me to invite him home and feed him?
Don't we deserve to get even that much?
Forget the food give him some sense. He has lost his mind.
Even God would've forgiven that motherless child.
Everyone knows that he didn't come to us fearing anyone.
He came on his own, to apologise.
Ruining all his hard work. To rectify his mistake.
But why would you forgive him?
After all you are a Gulati.
Eat your lunch.
It's not matching at all. Show it to me. It's not matching.
I don't know. I have been to so many shops.
What's happening, Ronnie?
Aren't you getting any stock?
You know I need to go for a wedding the day after tomorrow.
I need to get the blouse stitched from the tailor.
When will he stitch it? When will I wear it?
This is a matching centre but nothing is matching.
Tell me something.. - Yes.
Are they your kids? - Of course they are mine!
They don't match!
Damn you to hell! I don't want to buy any blouse!
I don't want to give you any blouse!
Leave! - We are leaving!
First go and check your brains!
Pack all this.
Mitali..
I am sorry.
All this happened and I didn't tell you.
It's okay, Kuku.
Everyone makes mistake.
But it's more important to realise your mistake.
Don't worry. Everything will be fine.
This one.
I'll check it.
Greetings, Mr. Mathur. - Greetings.
Mr. Mathur, we have come from the sanctuary.
Yes. - We have a small post-funeral ceremony.
It is a simple function.
We need to make arrangements for lunch.
You can cook any lentil except for pigeon peas.
Flatbread, a dry vegetable.
You'll be giving complimentary pickle, right?
What is this?
Son, they've come here to give a catering order.
Yes, son.
We have come from the sanctuary.
Mr. Dharshanlal served the sanctuary for 35 years.
He passed away.
We have brought his catering list for his ceremony.
Sorry. We are no longer into this business.
Come in. - You don't do it?
What are you saying?
It is a noble deed, please accept the job.
We don't do catering.
You don't do catering? Then what do you do?
I know everything.
It's all because of the money. - Yes, it's because of money.
This world is going crazy over money. - Come on, papa.
They cannot see anything.
Come on, papa. Come inside.
What are you doing, Kuku? - Oh God!
So what if we no longer have a restaurant?
We can get into catering business.
Opportunity is knocking at our door.
Mitali, please. You don't know.
Come on, papa.
Look, son, your girlfriend is right.
How can we let go of the opportunity of getting into catering business?
I don't want to do it!
But we want to do it!
Enough! Enough! Enough!
Goodbye, Mr. Mathur.
Goodbye.
Your job will be done. - What are you doing?
That restaurant was mine. You cannot use my name.
That's great, son!
You have been using my name since the past 19 years.
Did I ever object to that?
Mathur, the father, was born before the son.
Got it? - And then Ronnie Gulati was born.
Fruit beer?
I know why you are here.
Tell grandpa I'll anyhow repay the balance in4-5 months.
Don't worry.
Have you lost your mind, Kuku?
You think I am here for the money?
There is a vast difference between me and Himanshu.
I had come here to give this to you.
What's this?
Kuku and Ronnie Catering services.
I have been working on it since so many days.
And what were you thinking!
I had to face uncle.
When I came to know that grandpa is going to get the insurance money..
And he took uncle's VRS's money..
I too got that.. Enlightenment.
That grandpa is not always right.
I fought with him and asked for my rightful share.
We have always been together.
So, we will do the business together.
Kuku and Ronnie Catering services.
I am a Gulati.
But I am your friend.
You will fight with your grandfather and help me?
Why?
Because you don't have a mother.
"In the stir-fried lentils.."
"In boiling potatoes.."
"In the spice mix.."
"In a sari's fall.."
"In female company.."
"Under Shabho's skin.."
"In good times.."
"I am in a soup."
"With me I have.."
"I have our treasured friendship!"
What are you making? It smells great.
Smells great? I am boiling water.
Anything you make smells great.
Hey! Naughty!
What happened! I am married to you! It's not a joke!
"My life is a lie. My death is a lie."
"My life and death.."
"Life.."
"With me I have.."
"I have our treasured friendship!"
"Hey Kuku!"
"Listen, Ronnie!"
"MATHUR!"
"GULATI!"
"Eeny Meeny Miny, and a faster Mo!"
"Speeding on the highway, got hit on the one-way."
"Parathey Wali Galli, no sugar in the buttermilk."
"Life is a mess but arrogance survived."
"It's a mess, cash crunch has made my girl.."
"A little angry. - I say, this month.."
"It's very cold."
"Give example."
"Whiskey no soda, marriage no (ghada)donkey."
"Nail no hammer, when I got under a blanket.."
"I was thrashed in it."
"You were taken.."
"You were taken for a ride!"
"When I try to move ahead, I am pulled back by the minister."
"The one who throws empty bottles at a bar is a sinister."
"I dug a grave and jump into it, it's a booby trap."
"This is a mess, applaud, clap."
"They watch the show but they don't pay, they carry.."
"AK - 47... Is what I say..."
"Fire-crackers are on sale, but the season is of Holi."
"You were taken.."
"You were taken for a ride!"
"Enough of this!"
"Stop playing the song!"
"He creates music on computer!"
"You were taken.. You were taken for a ride!"
"Now it's cold in summers!"
"This song is sponsored by Gulati and Sons Sari shop."
"Shut up, you.."