Slow slow, it's on the right...
the blue house... stop here
He)' Bilqees!
Yes Rukmani?
Is this a car or ajar?
They've come stuffed like pickles,
to arrange the marriage.
Slalekum!
Hope you didn't lose your way Sir.
Lanes in our neighbourhood,
very naughty...
...send you spinning like atop.
Slalekum! Slalekum!
- Walekum
- Please come...
Walekum
Please come...
Don't you have a lift?
It's just a few steps...
we'll reach the top in seconds...
Pooja... Gullu's best friend...
How are you?
Please come...
We can get a lift put in two days...
...but climbing stairs pervents
a heart attack
- Yes, but you lose your breath...
- Please come...
Gullu!
- Aadaab!
- Please come!
- Aadaab
Please... Please help yourself.
Please take a seat.
Thank you.
Gullu, show Mr. Montu
your books.
Get to know each other.
Yes, yes... go son
Come
Mummy cold drink
Don't be greedy...
you'll get a bad throat
So, how much have you saved?
Jewellery worth three lakhs,
three lakhs for an AC Car...
...and nine lakhs
in a fixed deposit...
I will break it as soon
as the wedding is fixed.
Total fifteen lakhs.
My Gullu topped the whole
Andhra state in the 12th grade.
She is a Gold medallist,
look at her certificates.
She even got admission
in an American college.
Poor girl didn't
get a scholarship...
...or she would be
studying there right now.
Along with the job,
she's doing her B. Com as well.
As soon as she finishes
her third year...
...she will become
Assistant Manager.
Fifteen is bit on the lower side.
I can arrange for a couple more...
up to seventeen.
She's pretty, she's earning as well...
it's 0k, let's say yes
Player of the year
in basketball and badminton.
Basketball
0k... after all,
she's a motherless child.
You can start shooting.
Congratulations Mr. Abdul...
Congratulations Mr. Abdul.
- Congratulations uncle.
- Congratulations big sister...
...congratulations brother.
Let's go Mummy.
What happened Montu?
I said let's go,
these people are wasting our time.
I don't want them,
I don't want this match.
But what happened my son?
What happened is that
your Mr. Montu is a fraud...
His bio data said,
fluent in English...
...but he says 'bilu' for blue
and 'flim' for film...
He asked me if I watch bilu flim...
Tell me Booji...
...how do I answer to that...
...if his pronunciation
of blue film is so wrong!
And for Education qualification,
he wrote degree from llM.
IIM means?
Indian Institute of Management...
International Institute
of Mahbubnagar.
Mr. Bad-english-bilu-flim-
fake-diploma-holder- Montu...
You have wasted our time!
Wasted out time, tang, samosa,
chips, biscuitmeverything!
And your mummy...
...she's been making faces
over everything since she's come...
Gullu!
Take her away quickly
before her face permanently...
...becomes like this...
Gulrez, Pooja... don't misbehave.
Come on, let's go! Come on Montu!
Who will wed such a bratty,
dark-skinned...
...uncouth, ugly-looking girl?
Bye Montu...
Bye
Sister, our Gullu is just joking...
She's just a kid... Please
don't leave, she will say sorry...
Please hear me out...
Ismail bhai... Bhabhi...
- Montu...
- I came here because of you
What did I know they are beggars...
...everyone said
they are very well known...
Such a long resume he had sent
and not one thing was true
Booji, snacks?
Today if your mother was alive...
She would say,
Mr. Qadir...have a samosa.
You just keep eating samosas
What is the samosa's fault?
Booji has gone sad and
the samosas have gone cold!
Gullu!
It's quarter past seven
Slalekum...
...slalekum...
Oh, still in bad mood...
Tea not sweet?
Gullu, it's quarter past eight,
come for breakfast.
Booji... come on,
we're getting late...
I've been waiting so long...
You always delay us...
Bhai Miyan Slalekum!
Slalekum
Stand straight,
you'll be late for school.
Gullu, you dismissed
another case last night?
Yes Aunty...and in record time!
- Namaste brother
- Namaste
Ready Booji?
Let's go.
Booji, soon as we have
loads of money...
...we will buy a big bungalow
and settle down in Jubilee Hills.
There will be no Rukmani aunty or
Bilqees aunty to trouble us there.
Are you listening?
Booji?
Radha-Raja Reddy case result
will be declared today, right?
What do you think? Who will win?
Radha or Raja?
Say something.
I don't know. Drive quietly.
Booj! How can I marry some
'bilu film' watching fraud?
All I'm asking for is an intelligent
husband, is that too much?
If one has just enough money
for a handful of oilyjalebis...
...one can't buy a kilo
of Pula Reddy's...
mexpensive pure-ghee gulab jamuns.
With the dowry that I can give...
...we will only find
these bad-English types.
How do I get an Oxford dictionary
product for fifteen lakhs?
Then why did you send me
to a private English medium...
...you should have sent me
to a Government school.
I wouldn't have gotten
addicted to English.
Or you should have married me off
right after school.
You know lesser the age,
lesser the dowry!
If I had married you off at sixteen
wouldn't I have been jailed?
Won't you be jailed
for giving dowry?
What can one do about that...
In our country you can't buy a
house without paying black money...
...and you can't get married
without dowry.
God knows how many baby girls
are killed everyday...
...by their own parents.
You too should have given me
rat poison, with gulabjamun.
The whole dowry head-ache
would be over.
Don't talk nonsense.
Only two years left
for my retirement.
Soon as you get hitched,
I can rest easy.
Hitched? I don't want
to get sorted Booji
Yes, you just want to unsettle me!
Everylhing will be fine, just stop
bringing jerks to marry me off.
Of course Gulluji,
the boys I call are all jerks.
You only want Mr. World...
...no Miss World?
Why Mr. World,
I'll get Mr. Universe.
Sure you will!
- Khuda Hafiz.
Mr. Qadir...Sir,
please hear me out...
Sir, you are the senior-most
clerk in the registrar's office...
...you can postpone my boss's
court date if you want.
You will profit in exchange.
I don't want your profit.
Sir, cash or kind, your choice.
You can take the whole family
on a vacation to America.
Recently Mr. Mudgil
took his family there...
I said no! Now get out of here!
You moron!
The date will get changed anyhow.
Mr. Qadir... why so stressed?
They are openly
spreading corruption!
Forget about him. Want to bet
on the Raja Radha Reddy case?
It's a bet! Raja Reddy
will get six years in jail.
What are you saying Mr. Qadir?
Raja Reddy supplies milk
to the whole state...
...he's the 'Milk King'...
Nobody is king
when it comes to 498a.
Radha Reddy has filed a case of
dowry harassment under section 498a.
There is no bail in 498a, and
if the husband is found guilty...
...he goes straight to jail.
Mr. Supreme Court, you will lose.
We'll see who wins!
Radha Reddy, victorious in the dowry
harassment case, thanks to 498a.
The power of 498a has delivered
justice to Radha Reddy...
...who has been harassed
in a dowry case.
Her husband Raja Reddy has been
convicted for 6 years in prison.
Radha Reddy Ma'am, your husband
has got a 6 year jail term...
...how does it feel?
I am very happy, thanks to 498a.
The honourable judge has sent
my husband to jail...
...ordered him to give me
ten crores cash...
...a flat to live in and four lakhs
monthly alimony.
Long live 498a.
Like you just saw...
You are wasting your time
as a clerk Abdul Qadir...
...you should become an advocate.
You know the law better
than these LLB lawyers...
Once again I will have
to treat you to biryani.
Once again a winner!
Qadir bhai...yourjudge has arrived.
Oh my God!
Good morning sir...
- Good morning...
- Sorry Sir
My foot is sprained, be careful...
Heel is too small...
show me something else...
Ma'am, I've shown you all
the ladies styles in the shop...
...now I can only show you
the gent's shoes, if you like?
Why should I wear gent's shoes?
I don't like anything. I'm leaving.
Ok no problem Ma'am.
You're welcome. Do come again.
I'm leaving this damn job now!
But you love shoes...
I love shoes, but not stupid
customers like that lady.
Relax!
Look, your coffee-shop guy.
He's so handsome!
Whats the use?
We've been saying 'so handsome,
so handsome' since a month.
He doesn't even look here.
We don't exist for cool dudes
like him, poor sales girls like us.
Oh my God Gullu!
He's coming this way...
Hi! AmjadmAmjad Baig.
Gulrez Qadir. How can I help you?!
Am lookin' for a cool pair
for my mum.
Repeat please.
I want to buy shoes...for my mother.
No no... in English.
Your accent is so yummy.
I am looking for a cool pair
for my mum.
- American accent?
- Yeah...
I've been watching you for a month.
And I've been waiting for you to
have the courage to enter the shop.
I'm somewhat of a wimp.
So...your mom's size?
Yes, yes...
Huh!
Cool...come!
Where in America do you live?
New York?
Jubilee Hills... the Hyderabad one.
Born and brought up.
So this American accent?
I work for an American
software company...
...but I'm shifting to
America in three months.
I've got admission in MBA.
New York?
Kalamazoo.
Oh Kalamazoo
Kalamazoo is in the state
of Michigan...
Michigan's capital is Lansing.
Kalamazoo is in the state of
Michigan, Michigan's capital...
Michigan, the capital of Lansing.
Lake Ontario to the west.
East, Lake Erie.
South west is Ohio,
capital Columbus...
...in the south is Indiana,
capital Indianapolis.
And right in the centre will be you,
Kalamazoo!
WOW!
You're quite deep into USA huh?
It was my dream to study
shoe-desgining in America.
But I became a shoe sales-girl here.
I wish we could both go.
Actually, come with me!
You will become a famous
star-shoe designer.
I will do your marketing...
designer brand... Gullu, what say?
Soft, sublime,
The scent is your's-
Let's go?
I am blooming.
Soft, sublime,
The scent is your's-
lam blooming.
Sour, sweet,
The words are your's-
lam chirping.
You're an old longing,
A new playfulness.
Make me believe
Are you for real or not?
Oh my, my tongue is slipping-
I have turned poetic!
I'm humming, I've turned romantic...
Poetic, poetic,
I've turned poetic...
The moon tricks me and walks away,
It appears to me in the day.
It picks new dreams for me...
It pulls me by the arm,
The wind blows me away,
It finds new ways for me.
Poetic, poetic,
I've turned poetic...
You're an old habit,
You're brand new trouble.
Make me believe,
Are you for real or not?
Oh my, my tongue is slipping-
I have turned poetic!
I'm humming, I've turned romantic...
Enough!
I'm hungry...let's eat kababs?
I am a vegetarian.
Really?
Everyone is turning
vegetarian in America.
Amjad! What will we do?
I love you,
but I love Nalli, nahari...
...kabab, biryani,
haleem also very much.
I'm a hard-core non!
So you eat. Yes, you can eat.
Who's stopping you?
All relationships are like
that in America...
...you do what you like,
I'll do what I like.
I really love you!
Remember this my friend...today
I will eat only vegetarian with you.
Gullu...
Let's begin the gift ceremony.
Bride's mother will gift
a brand new car...
Mummy, come on mummy!
Thank you amma
Bride's uncle will gift
two pure gold wrist watches...
One for the left hand,
one for the right.
Very nice dowry
On top of all the gifts...
I have given one crore cash dowry
to Pooja's in laws.
Pooja's husband is an IAS,
that's his rate.
Gullu!
_Amju
~ Hi!
The next presentation...
Bride's aunt will gift a gold set.
Give her a big hand!
Please
A mixer griander and 32 inch LED TV
from the bride's uncle in Dubai.
You turned out to be quite brave...
coming here without an invitation.
I missed you!
I was too busy with the wedding...
Pooja wouldn't let go of me...
Gullu! I missed you so much!
Will you have a love
marriage or arranged?
My father will hang me from
the fan if I have a love marriage.
You?
My Booji...should be okay.
Hopefully.
Did you tell Booji about me?
No. Should I?
Should I convince my father
to bring a proposal to your house?
Are you proposing to me?
We've been together
for more than a month.
Okay!
We rejecting boys speaking
English very badly...
For Gullu, only good
English speaking.
Amju-Gullu... Perfect coupling.
You needn't worry about dowry,
we don't want anything.
The love with which Amju has come,
I mean all of you have
come from Jubilee Hills...
...you would obviously not
bring the filth of dowry with you.
Send you daughter in one outfit,
we'll be happy.
We just need some help from you.
Of course. What help?
For his higher education.
I told you...
Yes Kalamazoo!
What a robust name, Kalamazoo.
So... what help can I offer you?
College tuition, travel expenses,
living and food expenses...
...not for him alone...
for the bride as well.
After marriage, we won't force
your daughter to stay with us.
She will also go with Amju.
We are very open minded...
Very good...
Amju, I hear you're a vegetarian?
Here, the help list!
Oh okay...
It's just eight lakhs.
Not eight, eighty.
Eighty!
Please go through it.
It's all accounted.
Every penny will be spent on them.
Nothing on us.
You never said anything
about this Amju?
Have you spoken
to Gulrez before this?
Yes... he's spoken to me,
held my hand...
Said I love you a hundred times.
0k... but the match is being made
with our permission.
It is arranged.
Amju, how can you do this
if you love me...
...how can you ask for money?
This is understood dear.
He will go to America,
get educated, earn millions...
...only you will enjoy the benefits.
We're just asking your father
for some help...
...not asking him
to build the Charminar!
But you are educated,
with an American accent...
...going to do your MBA...
So?
Doctors, engineers,
IAS, IPS, all ask for help.
What's wrong with MBA?
Amju, I'm an ordinary sales-girl,
where will I get eighty lakhs from?
But your father works
at the court...high court!
Yes, but I'm merely a clerk,
not a lawyer.
My salary is only thirty
thousand per month.
I have some jewellery
and cash for the dowry...
Hey, hey, who's asking for dowry...
Help, help!
Sorry help...
I can help up to fifteen lakhs.
Fifteen?
Nowadays even the note-books
cost more in America...
There's a long line of people
waiting to help my Amju.
Not bits and pieces, full help.
Amjad, you won't say anything?
Dad, my education will cost
only sixty lakhs...
...why are you asking for eigthy?
That's unfair.
Unfair? What's unfair?
I pawned my jewellery to send you
to an English medium school...
...now you're misbehaving with us
in fluent English!
I'm Sorry...
- Amju!
- Gullu
My Child!
What kind of misbehaviour is this?
You won't get anything here...
...no burger, no hot-dog,
no cold-drink, no help... Nothing.
Get out of here...
- Get out...out!
- She's gone crazy!
Gullu calm down...
Leave! Just leave!
I love you Gullu.
I hate you Amjad.
Gullu, I want to go
to Kalamazoo with you...
...climb the Statue of Liberty
with you...
Go hang yourself...
bloody vegetarian!
- Gullu! Gullu!
- Let's go!
Mr. Abdul Qadir! This is not right!
Your daughter has made a very
big mistake! A very big mistake!
Get lost...
or I'll beat you to a pulp.
You want help?
Here, take help...take help...
Radha Reddy Ma'am, your husband
has been jailed for six years...
...how does it feel?
I am very happy, thanks to 498a...
The honourable judge
has sent my husband to jail...
...ordered him to give
me ten crores cash...
...a flat to live in and four lakhs
monthly alimony.
Long live 498a.
They cook the most delicious
biryani... Amazing!
Try this piece, it's very tasty...
No, no... I'm done.
With the baghaare baingan...
Ok fine.
Only after giving anaesthesia
of my favourite food...
...from my favourite restaurant,
will you perform surgery...
Out with it...what's up?
Booji, I don't want
to get married at all...
...whether it's a bilu flim cheapster
or an American accent MBA.
Nobody values companionship,
friendship, love, affection...
...they're all just parasites.
All boys are not alike Gullu.
They are Booji, you don't know!
Have your cold-drink.
Anyway, I have decided...
I will fulfill my dreams.
You and I are going to New York.
I will study Fashion Designing,
I will be a famous shoe designer.
You just enjoy!
Come on, which bank will we rob?
We will put 498a, like Radha Reddy.
It's a law, not nail-polish!
We'll use the law.
First, we will change
our name and appearance...
...and post my photo and bio-data
on a matrimonial site.
Boys will line up to marry me.
We will interview them...
...and choose the most
greedy scoundrel.
I will marry him in a fake ceremony.
The next day we will use 498a...
...and file a dowry harassment case
against the groom and his family.
To avoid jail-time they will agree
to an out of court settlement.
We will then ask for eighty lakhs
in cash! They will have to pay up.
We will take that money
and off to New York.
Isn't it a great idea!
You want to bribe me with dinner
to pass this dangerous plan?
There's no danger Booji!
Shut up... just shut up!
Never speak of this
stupid plan again!
Let's go!
You think you're too smart...
trying to use 498a
Booji!
Hey ldrees, clean table number seven
- Slalekum!
- Walekum
My tea today!
You're up very early.
I was planning all night.
We will change our name, dress,
appearance and look for our target.
Not here, everyone knows us
in Hyderabad. In some other city.
Don't start again!
Listen to the full plan at least...
We will go fully prepared.
I've found out the name of the guy
who makes fake passports...
...here in Laad Bazaar,
he'll make it in two days.
Don't worry, I will wear a veil
while giving the photo and money.
- He wont recognize...
- Stop it now!
If Bilqees and Rukmani hear this,
they will report you.
We will have to buy
hundred dirhams...
...we will photocopy those
and make bundles.
What?
We need cash for all this,
so break the dowry deposit.
It will finance the whole mission.
Where did you learn all this from?
The internet has everything...
...from child delivery
to bomb making, all recipes.
Anyway... One minute...
Bhopal, Ahmedabad, Delhi, Lucknow.
- Where do you want to go?
- Jail!
Tell me Booji,
I have to book the tickets.
Booji!
The whole world asks for dowry!
If I con some money out of a greedy
dowry monger, what's the big deal?
In India, one woman is killed
for dowry every hour!
I swear by Google...
see for yourself.
Booji, we've been insulted a lot.
Now we will avenge those insults.
We will fulfill our dreams.
Don't marry, if you don't want to.
If you want to study...
study right here in India.
We have Fashion Designing here too.
I will only study
in the New York College.
If you don't want to help, then
don't. I will do everything myself.
If you commit this crime Gullu...
I will report you myself
and send you to jail.
Ok, I will marry the
"Bilu Flim" jerk tomorrow.
He will make me watch them as well.
Gullu don't be stubbborn...
Who knows, he will make
a blue film of me!
Then you'll be happy?
Gullu! Gullu!
Gullu won't you say Khuda Hafiz?
Ok don't, I won't either!
Booji! Booji!
Did you get hurt?
What happened?
Don't you know how to drive?
- Sorry, I blew the horn...
- What happened?
- ...but he didn't hear madam...
- I'm alright, it's just a scratch.
I'm fine, I'm fine.
Let it be...come let's go.
I should call Mohan Rao.
- Let it be now...
- Should we call an ambulance?
No, thank you so much.
Thank you.
Sir please listen to me.
Sir my father has had an accident,
how can I leave him alone?
It's an emergency leave Sir.
Fine, fire me if you like,
but I can't come today.
Fine.
Idiot!
Come on, don't fuss.
Gullu... If I had been crushed...
you, on your own...?
Why are you scared?
Nothing will happen to you.
I won't trouble you again... Sorry!
Why should you be sorry?
Before something really happens
to me, we will fulfill your dream.
Come on, let's go to New York.
- No Booji, no...
- Yes!
If the whole world is
feeding off dishonesty...
...why should we starve
by being honest?
I couldn't become a lawyer...
...but you will definitely
become a Fashion Designer.
So what's the plan,
where will we go to trap our prey?
Bhopal, Ahmedabad, Lucknow, Delhi?
Lucknow.
Good choice partner.
The food is great in Lucknow.
Daddy... stop scratching.
My beard itches...
more so when I'm nervous!
Then scratch stylishly... like this!
Good morning, Sir.
- Daddy, what are you doing?
- I'm sorry!
I'm sorry!
Sir, my payment?
One...
- Two...
- Excuse me?
I'm sorry!
Sorry!
What are you doing?
Keep your hand here.
Daddy...
Welcome sir!
- Namaste, Ma'am!
- Welcome, Sir!
Namaste, Sir!
Thank you.
One big size soot please.
Sorry?
One king size suite please
- Suite
- Sure... your names please.
Abdul Qad...
Habibullah, Sania Habibullah.
Shahriyar Habibullah.
Ma'am your Photo ld's please
- Done?
- Yes Ma'am. Thank you
Thank you so much
Habibullah...
Habibullah... Habibullah.
What's your name?
My name is Shahriyar Habibullah.
This can't be our room...
- Daddy!
- No sir, this is your room.
- Sure?
- Yes Sir!
Good day Sir. Good day Ma'am.
- Good day...
Oh!
Yes
Thank you Ma'am. Have a nice day!
Get up, why are you sitting?
I'm practising to be Habibullah.
Done... come now,
there is a lot to do...
Here, your phone is ready.
- Should I call Ismail Qureshi?
- Yes, Ismail Qureshi!
Hello Slalekum,
this is Abdul Qadir speaking!
Shahriyar Habibullah!
Habibullah Habibullah
- Who is this damn Habibullah?
- Ok relax, relax, relax... relax.
Shahriyar Habibullah,
Shahriyar Habibullah.
Hello, yes, Slalekum... This is
Shahriyar Habibullah speaking.
No, not from Dubai,
we're in Lucknow right now.
Are you Ismail Qureshi?
You had put your bio-data
on the matrimonial website.
Yes, I want to fix
the time of appointment.
Please come at ten...
...no, no, not at night,
ten in the morning.
Yes, Khuda Hafiz.
- Done!
- Done. Easy?
Now you'll make the next call?
Yes, this is Shahriyar
Habibullah speaking.
Yes! Yes!
This is Shahriyar Habibullah...
...to fix the marriage-interview
appointment...
...please come at twelve.
Obviously, you will come
with your son...
Mr. Babbar Khan,
this is Shahriyar Habibullah.
I've called to give you
your time slot...
...four thirty at the
Jahanpanah 'soot'
- ...no don't wear a suit.
- Suite Booji, suite.
Please come to the Jahanpanah suite.
If you're busy, we're busier!
We can't wait a week for you.
No Mr. Abbas you listen to me...
...come at 7pm tomorrow
or else, goodbye!
Does the bride's family ever take
a proposal to the groom's house?
Your appointment
is for seven thirty.
You can come at seven fifteen
and ask anyone in the lobby,
"May I want to see Shahriyar
Habibullah from Dubai".
Our room is called
the Jahapanah suite!
From Haidaﬂ Kabab,
Tafiq Haider aka Tam.
Great, now even cooks are looking
for brides on matrimonial sites
Who knows this kabab
might get slaughtered himself.
Hello... Shahriyar Habibullah
speaking, is this Tariq Haider?
Ok, his father?
Please note the time,
tomorrow 8 pm. Khuda Hafiz!
Ok, next...
All done.
The entire day has
gone into making calls.
I'm terribly hungry.
Where's the menu?
Dal, 250 rupees! Curry, 500 rupees!
Chapatti, 75 rupees!
Is their barbecue
studded with diamonds?
It's a five star Booji,
so the rates are also five star.
No! I don't like
this waste of money...
See this...dal is 50, veg curry 75,
kofta 50 and roti only 20.
This is Haidari kabab, the one
that belongs to Tariq Haider!
Here, Haidari kabab has arrived
Tariq bhai, table for five of us!
How much longer Tariq?
Half an hour is up, Tariq bhai...
Wait! Wait!
Everyone will get a table...
Ok, next number...Julie!
- Julie!
- Yes, we here...we here!
- Come, come, come... you hungry?
- Yes.
Tariq! I am waiting for an hour...
...but you are giving entry
to the "white" dames.
Mr. Chaudhary,
they will eat fast, feel good...
...and then burp praises
of Haidari Kabab on Facebook...
- ...the whole world will listen...
- Okay, okay.
Hang on for a few minutes...
...till then wash down
a seekh with cold-drinks...
Ok, ok...hurry up
Mateen, 4 seekh plates
for Mr. Chaudhary...
- I'll just get it Taru bhai
- What is this Tariq...
- I've been waiting a long time...
- You're next...almost there...
Ateeq, menu here...
think of the order till then...
- Ok madam, come...
- Yes.
- You U.S?
- No...
Amrica, England?
No, I am from Germany...
Oh ho...Germany...
Germany football...
So delicious... so delicious...
like Haidari Kabab...
My friend is from England.
Oh...England Queen...
Queen also very delicious...
- Ok madams, here is your table
- Yes... Thank you
Okay. So, what's the special?
- Special
- Yup
Okay'
This ispecial, this ispecial...
...all ispecial no ordinary...
I order? Cheap and best...
- Okay?
- Hey Maxeen...
-Yes Tam Bhai
Two plates kabab, two sheekhs,
two meat balls, two kofta,
...four chapattis at table number
sixteen... Two kheer, two kulfi...
I'll just get it brother
Ok...what about Julab Gamun?
Julaab Gamun!
Oh my... Gulab Jamuno...
- Hey Maxeen,
-Yes Tam bhai...
2 gulab jamuns as well.
Right away, with sugar syrup
Sania Habibullah?
Father-in-law...
Shahriyar Habibullah!
Coming
My God he is so yummy...
When did you arrive?
Didn't recognize me?
My portrait is posted
on the matrimonial site...
I have an appointment
with you tomorrow...
- Hey Mateen
- Yes bhai?
Special feerni here...
You haven't paid, have you?
Hey Mateen, have you
taken their payment?
Yes I have...
Dimwit, can't you see
who they are?
Are you trying to insult us
by taking money from them?
Go get the money back...
Allow us to pay the bill...
Why will you pay,
you're my father-in-law-uncle!
That will be decided tomorrow...
after the interview.
For now we will pay.
Let's go daddy!
Khuda Hafiz. We'll meet tomorrow
Look now, myself
Big Boss...Haidari Kabab.
I will decide who pays here
and who doesn't.
We ate, we decide.
Sania... he is saying so lovingly,
so we should relent.
Love?! This is hooliganism!
Is your daughter so uptight
about everything?
Excuse me! I am not uptight!
Here's the money... including tip...
...we're going, the bill is settled.
But the heart is not settled madam.
Please take this money, or else...
Or else?
Or else, what?
Arm-wrestle with me...
winner pays the bill.
We're leaving... Come on.
Okay let's see what you got.
No Sania...
It was a joke madam.
You're a very serious number.
Was the curry too spicy?
- Mateena, get madam a cold drink.
- Right away!
Don't create a scene Sania...
We can't let him
insult us like this.
Swear on kabab...
no insulting madam...
Shut up and start.
Cheers for Taru bhai!
Hey...you didn't even say ready,
steady, go...
Oh, you weren't ready Mr. Macho?
I am always ready.
- Sorry better luck next time.
- Come on now
Actually... for you,
there will be no next time.
Your interview... cancelled.
Your appoint... cancelled.
- Got it! Cancelled!
- Yes yes, it's cancelled...
But what have I done Madam?
Just a little welcoming.
In Lucknow,
we treat a guest like God.
Chauffe r.
Anyway I am not dying
for an appointment with you...
I am busy with appointments
from morning to night.
- And Taru bhai, all well?
- Here you go...
All well?
Tuck your shin in at least...
- It's a style papa...
- Save this style for home.
Mr. Tiwari...
- How are you?
- How are you sir?
All good
Which room is Sania
Habibullah staying in?
Jahapanah suite...
Oh! Suite!
Ateeq, Mateen...
- Yes, Taru Bhai
- Come on, pick up the artillery
Come!
Mr. Abbas and Family
Brothers!
Aren't we all brothers?
Hungry and thirsty...
how long have you been waiting?
And now it's lunch-time.
So on behalf of Haidari Kabab,
banish hunger...
...enjoy our kababs brothers!
Twenty lakhs!
Twenty lakhs?
Ok nineteen lakhs...
but not a penny less.
Colonel Abbas...
Major Abbas...
Madam...
Thank you very much!
So the marriage is fixed!
We have 300 grocery stores
in Dubai. 500 taxis.
5000 employees work under us.
Habibullah Group of Companies'
annual turnover is 200 crores...
...and you're insulting us
by asking for mere 20 lakhs!
How dare you?
- Please get out!
- C'mon son...
- How dare they ask for only 20 lakhs?
- C'mon...we've been insulted enough!
Are we mad that
we'll accept your proposal?
How dare you insult us?
Come on, get out.
Out. Get out from here
I said out
What are you doing...
you're over-acting.
What over-acting...
Father is a Colonel, son's a Major!
My heart was pounding with fear.
How did a Colonel get here?
I had made sure
no IPS or IAS officer...
...no police, no army man
comes in...
I had checked...
But you did well...very well.
What authority!
- Was it good?
- Yes...
Let's call the next one then?
Wait, let me just check
the camera...
I'm really enjoying
being a millionaire...
Until now, we used to be scared
of the boy's families...
...now they are wetting
their pants because of us.
Come, who's the next candidate?
Come on in...we'll make you
wet your pants...
Father-in-law uncle!
You can't barge in like this!
- May I come in?
- Meaning?
Myself Tariq Haidar...
You cannot come in. Your
appointment was cancelled.
Out.
I haven't come for
the appointment Madam.
So then?
For you, with my own hands.
Excuse me... We don't want
to talk to you about anything.
Have you forgotten
yesterday's defeat?
You gate crasher,
I'll send you to jail.
Uncle...
Hello reception...
Yes there is a man...here...
My great-great-grand-father
used to say...
...don't ever break
the customer's heart...
To mend hearts... here are kababs
made from his recipe.
I've come only to serve
these kababs...
There's biryani,
bread, curry, feerni...
...and papa-mummy as well outside.
Want to eat?
Want to meet?
- This one, give me this piece.
- This one.
It's very good...
Where's your fork?
Daddy pick up your fork...
- Shahi tukda
- Thank you!
Hmmmmyummm...
By Allah's grace we have
everything Mr. Habibullah.
But we have to consider
our traditions, customs...
...community, society...
Mr. Haidari... speak openly.
- Sania noting!
- Yes noting!
Noting!
Will you please put
the tiffin-box down...
...aunty's face is getting blocked.
- Anything else?
- No... thank you so much!
What can I say Mr. Habibullah,
I'm sure you understand.
Fridge double door...
...washing machine front loading,
AC split AC...
...such everyday items are a given.
Yes jewellery...
Two gold sets, two silver sets
and one diamond set will do...
And one car... that is
compulsory nowadays.
A Skoda will do.
Anything else?
- And...
- That's all.
Sania total?
Um... forty two lakhs.
Only forty two lakhs?
Round figure, make it forty.
Three lakhs,
forty thousand dirhams...
...you can convert it
and get whatever you want.
By today's conversion rate,
its approximately forty lakhs.
Approximately forty lakhs.
Now the girl's demands.
Of course, today girls are walking
chest to chest with boys.
Shoulder to shoulder papa.
Yes, I meant shoulder to shoulder...
Our country's Prime Minister
was a woman...
...even our President was a woman...
The wedding will be in two days.
Two days?
My heart is eighty percent
blocked... it can fail anytime.
I want to settle my daughter
at the earliest.
Invitation cards, fancy clothes,
relatives... all waste of money.
Waste is a sin...
It will be a simple wedding,
right here in this room...
...bride, groom, you and I.
The bride and groom will solemnize
the wedding themselves...
...according to Islam,
there's no need for a priest...
...only two witnesses are needed.
If you accept my conditions, then
it's a deal. If not, you can leave.
There are others waiting outside.
- But...
- We accept!
We accept all your conditions.
- Day after tomorrow, wedding.
- One minute.
Simple wedding... like!
Okay'
Bride and groom solemnize the
wedding themselvesmlike that too!
Okay'
But make her my wife...
without knowing her...not like!
Meaning?
I need three days...
with your daughter.
Are you crazy?
- What are you saying?
- Have you lost your mind?
One minute please.
We can all see Sania Habibullah
is very beautiful.
But beauty alone is not everything.
I too am a beauty!
She's uptight, she's feisty...
that's all I know about her.
She knows nothing about me either.
To become life-partners
we have to go beyond beauty.
Let's see if we can tolerate
each other for three days.
If we are to get along,
we will in three days...
If we do get along we will
get married, or else bye bye...
Do you agree?
Do not agree!
We're giving forty lakhs in dowry...
...that's all you need to know
about me.
If you want to marry me, you will
have to accept my conditions too.
No way.
As per our customs,
boys and girls...
...don't roam around
openly before marriage.
Then let's meet
behind closed doors...
- How dare you Tariq Haidar?
- Joke madam, joke!
In any case, day after is Holi.
On Holi everyone plays holi here,
nobody gets married.
Day after that is Saturday,
very busy day.
If the wedding can't
happen till Sunday...
...why not spend the
three days with me.
No... This spending time
business is not possible.
Not possible!
Ok, we'll take my cousin sister
Fareeda for safety... My safety...
No, thank you very much. Goodbye.
Ok goodbye!
Thank you very much.
Come on papa-mummy. Let's go.
Listen Tariq,
you're making a big mistake.
- We'll talk in the car.
- Why don't you explain to him...
He's always stubborn...
never listens to others...
Yes please leave...
...far better boys than
your son are lined up outside.
- Oh really? Khuda Hafiz!
- Khuda Hafiz!
Khuda Hafiz!
On the right...the yellow house
is of candidate number 12.
What tall claims he was making...
...that all of Lucknow
eats eggs from his poultry...
One who lives in this ruin will
never have the settlement money.
Cut his name...
That's why I wanted
to see for myself...
...the financial status
of the candidates...
...before choosing the prey.
How do we know who's lying,
can't trust anyone...
Wait, wait...
Tariq Haidar's house.
What an amazing mansion
It is...
They have 3 cars!
Yes! That red one is too sexy Booji.
- It's too amazing
- Yes, sorry
One thing is clear...
A court case will damage
their reputation the most.
They are wealthy too.
They will be able to immediately
pay the cash we demand. What say?
All that is fine...
...but I will have to roam
around Lucknow for three days...
...with that kababster Tariq!
And what if he says
no after three days?
We won't let him... I'll play
negative, you play positive.
Meaning?
Meaning... I will bad mouth
everything he does...
...but you praise him.
He will surely end up liking you.
Yes.
Her father was ready,
your parents were ready...
...even the dowry was enough
to keep our head held high.
What was the need to put
these stupid conditions Taru?
If she likes me even a little bit,
she will agree.
And if she doesn't?
You're getting old...
When will he marry?
I will marry the one who loves me
at least a little bit...
...if not a whole lot.
No chance of you finding
someone who will love you.
Wherever you go,
you put these conditions.
Or tell us where we can
find you a fairy queen...
...we'll go and get her...
So Taru, did she accept
your condition?
She will accept Mr. Chaudhary,
she will.
Did she call?
She will Nanhe miyan...
If she doesn't call,
what will you do Taru bhai?
Then where will you get
a moon-like bride for yourself?
I want not the moon,
Nor the night bird,
Nor a slice of sky.
I want not the light,
Nor a fairy
Nor a fairy-face.
She who walks with me,
She who tastes with me,
Each joy and each sweet sorrow.
I'll wake her from her dreams...
In my arms I'll make her sleep,
I'll pamper her,
I'll feed her all my life,
The heart has laid out a buffet,
it's the feast of love.
If you accept the invitation,
please do come my love.
It's the feast of love.
The heart has laid out a buffet
I have laid out a carpet
of clouds for you...
I have decked out trays
of stars for you...
Why did you trouble
the moon and stars for me?
Wherever I go sunshine follows me
Your words are sugary sweet...
What about your feast?
Is it sweet as your words?
If you come, my bland party
will turn delicious.
If your party is bland,
why should I come?
If you tell me to...
I will fire all the dishes
with the warmth of my heart...
The heart has laid out a buffet,
it is the feast of love.
If you accept the invitation,
please do come my love.
It is the feast of love.
Feast of love,
It's the feast of love.
Love mixed in the drinks
for the feast of love.
That's adulteration
in the feast of love.
Only the fortunate get
invited to the feast of love.
Who has the time to waste,
on the feast of love.
Don't dismiss, just taste.
Don't hyper-ventilate.
Let's get connected
Let's think about it
Not with thought, nor with tact,
I've invited you with my heart.
Ok then...l accept...
I accept your feast of love.
Yes Sir,
I agree to your feast of love.
It's the feast of love...
It's love, it's love,
the feast of love...
It's the feast of love...
It's love!
Come on Farru
Remember, you positive, me negative.
Slalekum! Hope you slept
peacefully last night.
No peace at all...
your hotels are rubbish...
Our Dubai has the best...
Oh daddy, their hotels are fine too.
Hello Fareeda. You've come
to take us sight-seeing?
I have no interest
in being a third wheel!
But Taru bhai promised me a new
phone if I agree to come along.
My phone is too old.
That's the only reason I'm here.
Fareeda and her tall-tales!
Come on Sania. Uncle, Khuda Hafiz.
Uncle will go as well.
Uncle will go as well?
If Fareeda has come with you...
...someone from our side will
have to go as her body guard.
Come on uncle, your daughter
doesn't need a body guard...
...she can bury ten bodies
with one hand.
Come on Sania, he doesn't agree.
No no... come, please come.
If only you had told me...
I would have brought along papa,
mummy, uncles and aunties as well.
You could have set the tuning
with the entire clan. Right?
He is so funny daddy
Let's go!
So Tariq Haider...
- ...we would like to...
- Taru... people call me Taru, sir.
We won't! It's a weird name-Tar...
It's not weird daddy, I like it.
She like it!
- How are you?
- Fine sir.
Where's the car?
Here it is, my Impala.
This red box!
We will go in this jalopy?
Entire Lucknow is crazy
about my Impala.
Entire Lucknow may be crazy
about your Impala...
...but Sania is used to luxury cars.
Get a Mercedes or a Benz,
only then will we go.
Or else, let's go back Sania.
Oh daddy, now that
Tariq is insisting...
I don't mind taking a round
or two in his Impala.
Uncle...
You should get comfortable
in the back seat.
Why?
Oh daddy...now that
Tariq is insisting...
I don't mind sitting
in front for an hour or so.
Rickety Impala!
Uh... Can I drive?
I'll drive?
Stop here...
What's here?
Hazrat Ganj
Saw it, let's go now?
If you're in Lucknow and don't go
'Gunjing' in Hazrat Ganj...
...you've done nothing
father-in-law Uncle.
Sania is allergic
to Gunjing etc, ok?
Daddy...now that Tariq is insisting...
I don't mind doing a round
or so of Gunjing.
The world's best 'Pani Batashe'.
Batashe?
Why, what is it called in Dubai?
'Gol Gappe'?
- Listen
- No.
We won't eat this...
Sania is allergic to chilies,
flies, pot-water...
Oh daddy...now that Tariq is insisting
I don't mind having one or two...
Let's watch a 'Picture'?
Or is she allergic
to 'Pictures' as well?
We don't watch 'Pictures',
we watch 'Movies'.
That too Hollywood.
Oh! Hollywood! I only like Bolly...
Once in awhile I watch Holly,
if it has action.
But every Friday, only Bolly.
Oh daddy...now that
Tariq is insisting...
I don't mind watching a... Bolly!
What a rubbish 'Picture',
even the heroine was so skinny.
But if you ever become roly-poly,
it'll make no difference to me.
What if I get paunch in the future?
Let me know now,
if you want a body-builder type.
That you won't get in Taru.
What's there in the body...
thin today, fat tomorrow.
Beauty should be in the thinking.
Beauty in thinking!
Ok Sania.
For our tuning-setting, there
should be no lies between us. Right?
Yes! No...
In that case... my bio-data posted
on the matrimonial site says...
...I'm a graduate.
- Yes!
- That's a lie.
Oh!
Yes!
Papa-mummy forced me to write that...
...saying now a days no girl is willing
to marry less than a graduate.
The truth is, I failed in the 12th
and you're an MBA. Right?
How will we have tuning-setting?
People from all over the world
come to taste your food.
So what if you didn't go to college
makes no difference.
But we will educate our kids
very well. Right?
Daddy! Can't see daddy anywhere.
Oh, yes.
Hadn't he come along
as your bodyguard?
Must be with Farru somewhere.
Must have been hard
for father-in-law uncle...
...after your mummy's death.
He had to be your mummy
and your daddy.
Waking you up, sending you to
school, must have done everything...
You haven't told me your mummy's
name. What was her name?
- Noorjahan Qadir.
- Noorjahan Qadir...
Qadir?
Her surname was Qadir.
Ok...
...she didn't change
to Habibullah after marriage?
Why? Boys don't change
their name after marriage...
...so why should girls
change their name?
They shouldn't!
Habibullah suit's you best.
Sania Habibullah.
I like it.
So tell me, how many kids?
Daddy will fall ill
if he runs around so much...
- Six, okay?
- Daddy
Twelve-thirteen okay?
Your luscious attitude
makes my intentions snap.
Your enchanting locks entangle
and unravel my promises.
If not the sea of love,
Give me but a drop,
Every bit of my heart, prays to you-
You're my prayer,
I ask you from you,
I believe you are my God,
You're my prayer...
Hey Tarn'.!
You toss your wild hair...
You toss your wild hair
and knock me out.
Your strike bolts with your
glowing eyes, and burn me down.
My youth is a thicket of clouds,
my being is fire
To be imprisoned in my mane,
is every young man's desire.
Yes I burn, but I'm drops
of cool intoxication too
Is it!
I fill a sea within
and let it rain love.
You are Thumﬂ,
I'm Dacha...
We are both exquisite raagas
Tune your notes with mine...
...and let the world sing.
Black, white, my every shade
Prays to you...
You're my prayer...
- Oh Sanﬂu
- Oh Tam
- Did you win the match?
- We lost the match
How many runs did you make Shakeel?
Full century
We lost, we lost, we lost the match
If you lose next time,
no jalebis for you
Thank you aunty!
Uncle, is this your aunty?
She's not aunty, she's uncle's wife.
Uncle's wife, uncle's wife!
My blazing heart is now used to you,
ls now duped by you...
Slowly my desire for you,
ls beginning to cross
my own boundaries.
The heart is not satisfied
with a drop anymore,
It wants your sea of love.
My patience,
is impatient for you.
It prays to you-
You're my prayer,
I ask you from you,
I believe you are my God,
You're my prayer...
Stop stop Taru, stop.
Tarn? Huh?
You know why I asked you
for three days?
So that in three days
you could start loving me...
...at least a little bit,
if not a lot...
...so that you marry me for love.
And if you hadn't
fallen in love with me...
I thought we could become friends.
Facebook-type.
But I do...from Tariq
I've come to Taru.
That's it!
That's all I wanted to confirm.
I am ready. You ready?
Yes ready.
Come on then!
You're my prayer,
I ask you from you,
I believe you are my God,
You're my prayer...
My room!
What is this?
All top heros and heroines
come to Haidari to eat our kababs...
...but my top most heroine is this...
What are you doing Tariq?
Call me Taru.
You said you have come
from Tariq to Taru.
But tell me what you're doing.
I don't want to marry you
for your cash value.
I want to marry you
for your own value.
The value of your friendship...
the value of your beauty...
...the value of your smile
...the value of your brains.
I don't want dowry from your daddy.
I'm not an item for my papa
to sell and your daddy to buy.
Papa doesn't understand.
His heart has attacked him once.
I'm afraid of fighting him...
...what if he passes away
without seeing his grand-children?
He loves me a lot.
But this disease of bowing
before society...
...and It's customs
doesn't leave him.
So, it's like this...
...he will not accept our marriage
without dowry...
So you tell your daddy...
...to give my papa-mummy
this forty lakh rupees as dowry.
Everyone wins!
What happened? Shocked?
Yes... Totally...
I didn't expected this at all...
You love me a lot right?
If I tell you something,
you won't be angry?
No
You'll forgive me at once?
Yes
I'm not Sania...I'm Gullu...
See...
I had come to trap you in a dowry
case and get money out of you
Tarn...
- Taru...
- Gullu...
Gullu save me...
Booji!
- Gullu!
- Booji!
Sania!
What happened? Shocked?
Very shocked...
I didn't expected this at all...
Sania... I never expected...
...that a scrap like me
would get a delicacy like you?
Has anything expected
happened between us so far?
But we're having a good time? Right?
So, get over the shock and smile.
But please don't tell papa-mummy
about this, it's our private secret.
Khuda Hafiz
Khuda Hafiz... Taar...ru.
We have to take care of
law and order as well...
Please get your wife the next time...
- Yes, please do..
- Yes, sure...
- Excuse me Ma'am.
- Yes?
Can I help you with the bag?
No.
- Sure?
- Yes.
He gave you forty lakhs,
just like that?
He has truly
fallen in love with you.
Will you still con him?
Listen to me...
If you tell him the truth even once...
...he will support you
in fulfilling your dreams.
- Don't be childish, Booji!
- How is this being childish?
Booji...he won't support me,
he'll send me tojail.
Fake currency, fake passport,
fake visa... It's very risky.
Now we're deep into this mess...
...there's only one way out...
stick to the plan.
Don't get confused...
...we will do what we have come for
and get out of here.
Aunty...come closer to Taru Bhai.
Yes, closer. That's it.
Ready? And...
- You're glowing aunty...
- Let me see...
Close the button at least.
It's alright papa.
- You should look like a groom.
- Our Taru is looking so handsome...
MY Smarty groom.
WOW!
Allah!
She's so pretty...
Let no evil eye cross
Sania and Taru's pair...
Three lakh forty five
thousand dirhams.
There's no need to count...even
if a hundred here and there is less...
...it's all in the family.
Yes.
I have booked the honeymoon
suite for the bride and groom.
Why? The bride will go home
with us after the wedding.
I'm leaving early tomorrow morning.
It will be easier for me
to say goodbye.
You can take her home tomorrow.
But this is not...
Why not...they can have
a comfortable breakfast...
...and come home by lunch-time.
What will you have for lunch dear?
Lunch? Tomorrow?
Anything would do.
Let's start the wedding.
You're more eager than us
father-in-law uncle.
- Let's start?
- Yes
Do you accept me, Sania Habibullah,
daughter of Shahriyar Habibullah?
I accept you,
accept your stubbornness...
...accept the way you
call my food yummy...
...accept the way you say Holly,
accept your fluent English.
Sania Habibullah,
as a whole and even in pans...
I accept you,
I accept you, I accept you!
That's enough for now.
Now it's your turn.
I accept your daddy,
your daddy's allergies...
Enough!
Yes...for now.
We have our entire lives
to keep accepting each other.
Miss Sania Habibullah,
daughter of Shahriyar Habibullah...
...do you accept me...
Tariq Haider, aka Taru Haider...
...son of Farooq Haider...
...the way you accept
my shahi tukda?
Do you accept me?
- I accept.
- Congratulations!
Come on.
I will have to go
to my beloved's home...
It's okay to cry my dear...
...you must be sad to leave
your father... go on, cry...
- Mummy, papa... Khuda Hafiz
- Khuda Hafiz brother
Now please be quiet aunty...
Why did father-in-law uncle
give dirahams in the suitcase?
He should have given my money.
Well...your papa-mummy
would get suspicious.
But daddy said thanks.
Look, what daddy got for us.
Get well soon... Who is ill?
Poor daddy, in all the wedding
excitement picked up the wrong one.
Father-in-law uncle is too much.
Have some kheer.
I'm not hungry at all Sania.
It's the tradition...
...if you don't eat this
everything will go wrong.
Please, from my hand...one spoon?
One for my beauty...
...one for my mind...
...one for my friendship.
Friendship!
(Sneeze) I'm allergic to roses.
(Sneeze)
Hope he is not dead?
You mixed sleeping pills
in the kheer, did you not?
I obviously wouldn't mix poison...
...you said four, so I mixed four.
Nothing will happen.
In the movie from which I got this
idea, they had put the whole bottle.
Sania
Let's leave before he wakes up.
Come on Gullu
Gullu!
Yeah!
Coming my love...
Tariq Haidar?
Yes
498a, you know what that is?
No.
Your wife has charged you
and your mummy-papa under 498a.
I have the proof... In this DVD...
...that you and your parents
demanded dowry.
Did you or did you not?
Speak up! You did, right?
Yes Taru...
so you are finally married?
Will you invite me to the reception...
...or I will get to meet your wife
at the birth of your child?
Really?
Fridge double door...
Washing machine front-loading...
AC split AC...
Everyday household
items are a given.
Yes, jewellery...
Two gold sets, two silver sets
and one diamond set will do...
And a car...
that is compulsory nowadays.
Skoda will be fine.
- Sania total?
- Forty two lakhs...
Only forty two lakhs?
Round figure, make it forty.
How much is your cut sir?
It's enough.
If we double that?
What do you mean...
...even we have some principles.
I'm the father of two daughters.
When they are of marriageable age...
...nobody will bother about
my uniform or my honesty.
It's because of you dowry-mongers
that we have to take a cut.
I am from the girl's side.
If you want an out
of court settlement...
...leave forty lakhs
at the designated spot...
...or else I'll arrest
all three of you in 498a.
Okay sir, okay...but where's the
guarantee that after the deal...
...this DVD won't reach
the commissioner.
What if they want more?
Did they guarantee they will not ask
for more dowry after the marriage?
Tell me... Did they?
When you didn't give us
any guarantee...
...why should we give you any...
lam from the girl's side,
don't you forget...
498a is a killer.
It takes down heavyweights.
If he files a FIR under 498a,
you will go straight to jail.
No bail.
Case will go straight to court,
and on the basis of this DVD...
...you will get a minimum
of six years in jail.
There's only one way out...
...give them the money
and get out of this mess.
I will not give any money
to give those cheating rogues.
Taru, don't be emotional,
be professional.
If all three of you go to jail, who
will make the biryani and kababs?
125 years old Haidari Kabab
will be ruined in one day.
Neeraj is right... The honour
of our ancestors...
You didn't think of the honour
when you were begging for dowry?
It was a mistake.
I swear on God I will never
even utter the word dowry again.
Just go and drop
the settlement money.
I won't spare that witch so easily.
O the black magic woman,
How she spun a web around me!
Tied me to her braid,
robbed me blind.
A birdie slayed a lion,
and flew away.
While the mustache
studs looked on in dismay.
Hail O brave-heart,
O black magic woman!
Tam bhai...
Here, here... she's here
Hail O strong one,
O black magic woman!
Give the bag...
...and return the dowry money
O the black magic woman,
How she spun a web around me!
Gullu! Gullu...
Come here...here Gullu
Stop you cheat!
Go go go!
She broke the trust of my heart,
She stole the love of my heart,
and flew away.
Cheat!
Damn your affections,
O black magic woman!
Damn your deceitfulness,
O the black magic woman,
How she spun a web around me!
Who is it?
It's me Booji...open the door
- Why didn't you knock in code?
- Oh Sorry.
What do you mean sorry?
Is this something you can forget?
Yuck!
Have gotten used
to Taru's flavours...
...now everything else
will feel tasteless
Bolly...
Lucknow wasn't so bad,
we had fun
Yes, but now you forget
about bonding with Lucknow.
For Lucknow you are an enemy.
Think only of America.
Yes, America
Had a lot of fun?
You cheat!
Slalequm uncle
What did you find out?
Fake names, fake company,
fake passport...
...and only one hundred dirham...
...out of the three lakh
forty five thousand are real?
- Where is Taru?
- On the roof again...
Tarn...
What are you doing at that height?
Even if you chop all the
vegetables in the market...
...your anger won't go away.
It will go only when the father
and daughter will rot in jail.
But if you keep chopping carrots,
how will we find them?
Think Taru, think about her...
We may find a clue...
Her father had called her Gullu...
So?
How can a Sania's pet name be Gullu?
There has to be some story
behind the name Gullu.
Taru bhai!
I found your Gulrez Gullu Qadir...
Come fast...
What have you got?
Just breathe, I'm showing you...
Look at this...
She thinks she's too smart.
She became Sania but forgot
to close Gullu's facebook account.
Damn...
Where will I find this witch?
Hyderabad.
Is Mr. Abdul Qadir at home?
Babu uncle?
Gulrez Qadir?
Yes, come come.
Please sit.
I can't see your father?
He's gone for some important work.
What do you want?
Suppose I have one rupee
as black money.
How do I exchange it into white?
How, is our problem.
All you need to
understand is that...
...you will give me
one rupee in cash,
...and in exchange we will deposit
eighty paise in your bank...
...as white money.
That's it.
Why only eighty?
Twenty paise is our fees,
for turning black into white.
Okay...will it be transferred
by tomorrow?
Soon as you give the cash,
the transfer will be done.
No, first you transfer,
then I will give the cash.
No dear, this business
doesn't work like that.
Ok, then I don't want to do it.
Khuda Hafiz.
How much is it?
Eighty lakhs cash.
Hmmm... You called me uncle...
...your father is a respected
man in the neighbourhood.
Ok, your work will be done.
Had a lot of fun?
You cheat!
But within half an hour
of the money being transferred...
...my man will be here
to collect the cash
Think carefully, because once
the money is deposited in your bank...
...the white money is yours
and the cash is ours.
You will have to give
the entire amount.
I've thought about it...
...transfer it as soon as possible.
- Khuda Hafiz!
Taru bhai, there are
twenty six malls in Hyderabad...
...if we're lucky we will
find her in the first one.
My darned luck has
become a witch too!
Taru, I could only get tickets
for tomorrow morning.
I only have thirty bullets,
will that be enough?
- Have you gone mad?
- Why, won't be enough?
You're not taking a gun.
We will have to take the gun,
who knows how big is her gang?
Yes, but you can't take it
on a flight.
It's licensed.
Put it back.
O the black magic woman,
How she spun a web around me!
She's not a cup of tea,
Nor a cup of wine.
She's not a silver bell,
Nor an aching sore.
She's made of flowers,
But whips so hard.
She's so delicate,
But scrores over brawn.
The hard hitters just look on...
Hail the fire-cracker,
O black magic woman.
Hail the thunder maker,
O black magic woman!
Haizel Naidu,
Rajshekhar Raju,
Venkatesh Raja, G.S. Vijay,
Lakshmi Vijay.
In lots of ten only...
All of you go in please.
Rest of you, wait outside
for your turn.
Not just a bit,
I loved you a whole lot...
...and you cheated me instead...
You cheat!
Gullu... What happened? Let's go.
Abdul Qadir, Gulrez Qadir
Gullu, it's our turn...come on...
What's wrong? Come on...
Gullu!
- Excuse me... excuse me...
- Gullu!
What? You will return Taru's money?
You will go back to Lucknow?
Are you crazy?
I can't courier eighty lakhs.
I will have to go myself...to return
the money... To say sorry.
Are you possessed?
It's our turn...
let's go for the interview...
...take the visa...and go to America.
Booji, if it was any other
dowry mongering low-life...
I wouldn't care...
But I don't want to go to America
with Taru's money.
Just think...
...going back to Lucknow
is so dangerous.
Tariq Haider won't offer
you biryani and kabab.
He will take revenge,
he will send you to jail.
Let him send me
to jail if he wants to.
Let me be imprisoned for life.
Jail is not a joke...
They torture you...
...make you starve,
don't even give you water...
...you have to live like an animal...
I know...
...but I don't want to fulfill
my dreams by breaking Taru's heart.
Please understand. Please.
What are you made of?
You're not scared of anything.
I've spent my entire life
being scared.
I couldn't cheat because of fear...
...now I can't be honest
because of fear.
How did you turn out to be
so fearless, just like your mother.
From my fearless mother's womb.
Come on, sit now.
Sit, quickly.
Hyderabadi biryani is not bad...
It's poison...
“everything here is poison.
Hey Neeraj... that's Gulrez
Qadir's uniform, isn't it?
It's the same...come come...
Madam...
...one second madam...
excuse me...
- One second...
- Is he mad?
Madam...
Walk straight guys...
Why are you walking like cows!
Madam do you know Gulrez Qadir?
Yes, who are you?
Gullu Qadir has been selected
this month's Facebook beauty queen.
We have a gift voucher for her.
Really? I'll just call and tell her.
No, no Madam, if you call her
we will lose our jobs.
Then how will our wives and kids
celebrate Christmas.
You give us the number and address...
We will go and surprise her.
Will you have jalebis?
Please have some...
Ma'am, number?
If your mother was alive...
Booji... Save the sentimental talk.
I'm not being sentimental...
If your mother was alive...
...she would have given you
two slaps for being so stubborn.
You made me lie and run
all over the place...
...and then you didn't
even fulfill your dreams.
Crazy girl!
So what Booji.
It's ok if I didn't go to America,
I'll study Fashion Designing
right here.
There are no jobs in America anyway.
Everyone's coming here.
Booji, when I become
a famous Shoe Designer...
...they will call me themselves.
Not only America.
England, France, Russia
everyone will call my hero.
Not hero. Heroine.
Same thing...
...you never let me feel that
you were a daughter or son.
Come on, pack my pant shin too.
You're not going anywhere.
I'm going alone.
Enough of your stubbornness.
Won't work anymore. Come on, pack.
Hello...
Yes Babu uncle.
Stop stop...
What do you want? Who are you?
They had taken a water-filter
service appointment...
...now they've locked up and left.
Even the bank guys had come...
...they called them home too
and disappeared.
We had to give the cheque.
What happened Bilqees?
They called these poor fellows
for Aquaguard servicing...
...and have now disappeared.
If they're not around,
why don't you do my servicing.
Sure aunty, but at least tell us
where they have gone?
We have to write in our report.
Or we'll lose our jobs.
How will our wives and kids
celebrate Diwali?
They left with luggage...out of town!
Where airport?
Airport they can't afford.
They've gone to the station.
Let's go
Hey good for nothings...
at least do our servicing.
- I will complain to the company...
- Come on, station
Why are you making me
go round in circles?
- Am I a top?
- Come on, quickly
This is an auto not aeroplane.
- Booji, let's get the tickets
- Yes yes
Two tickets, Lucknow. Three tier.
All full.
Only AC 1st class is available.
Eight thousand,
one hundred and eighty.
Hurry up, the train will leave
in ten minutes.
Take it... It's not like
we have to save for your dowry.
We'll go in style.
First Class
Listen...you go that way...yes...
One packet of chips...
No, the big one.
Running away?
Babu Uncle!
Running away with my money?
No, didn't you get the cheque?
Cheque! Your neighbour-aunties
gave the cheque.
So why did you come this far, you
could have said thanks on the phone.
Is this a game? Is it?
Transfer now, withdraw now...
I was very clear, once the money
is transferred into your account...
I will take everything in cash.
Where's the cash?
- With my father...
- Call him then
No, he's gone to get the tickets
and then snacks...
...then magazine...then pillow...
why don't we go to him.
Yes.
Come on.
In case I miss the train...
...let me take the bag,
it has my favourite outfit.
Yes, yes... Come on.
Such a hassle for nothing...
Where is your father?
- Just there...
- Come on.
Hey babu, get some tea here
Hello...yes I'm in a meeting...
...let me get the money
from the party first...
...I will get the curtains then...
Crazy woman, cost me hundred rupees
The girl is getting away...
Catch her
Hey P.T. Usha...stop...
She hits bad...
Sorry 50"'!
Sania...
How slow are you guys...
...see how fast
Gulrez Qadir is running.
Catch her...
What happened brother,
why are you chasing that girl?
She's running away with my money...
Your's too?
You're too?
How much did she dupe you for?
Why should I tell you?
She's made a fool me...
she's made a fool of you,
...we are in the same team brother!
Sania...
Sania come down...
Tarn'.!
You've made a fool of me.
Get down now...
Scoundrel...
You're threatening with a gun...
You'll hit Babu bhai...
You'll insult him
in front of everyone...
- Catch him Rafiq...
- Who are you?
Catch him...break his head...
Hey, not with the can...
Hey wrestler...let go of my boys...
Hey...
Ungrateful girl, you're hitting me?
Sorry... sorry
Tarn...
Tarn... Tarn...
Enough of your drama...
...return my money...
Don't come forward you bully...
Just stop there...
Give my money...
- The police is here Babu bhai!
- Who invited these pests?
Please give my money,
please give it.
Uncle, I gave you the cheque.
You will get the entire amount.
- Come on, run!
- Will I make a curry of the cheque?
I will suffer a huge loss my girl...
Damn the money Babu bhai
let's get out of here...now!
Run...run...
Hey... My money... My money...
- Give me the bag...
- Here, take your money...
Leave me alone...and never
call me a cheat again!
Since the time I've come
you haven't shut up for a second...
Wherever I go, I hear
you calling me a cheat.
Yes I cheated you!
All my life I have faced
dowry seeking boys...
...who have insulted me and Booji
I'm a topper.
But there's no value of my mind.
They hear fifteen lakhs
dowry and reject me
You know how many times
I've been rejected?
I couldn't bear
the insult anymore...
...that's why I decided
never to marry.
I don't want any man in my life.
I made this plan
to fulfill my dreams.
But you ruined the entire plan.
What was the need...
...to make this relationship for the
value of my laughter, my beauty...
...my mind, my friendship?
Why are you so strange?
You never went to college,
you speak in broken English.
You eat paan, you burp,
you wear horrible shins...
...but yet I started liking you
for your sweetness.
I couldn't hurt you
and go to America.
That's why I was coming
to return your money.
It's eighty lakhs. You can count...
Hey Taru, here...
Hey!
Well done Taru, you caught the girl.
Look what I caught?
Leave him... Leave him...
Excuse me.
What do you mean
'see what I caught'?
He's my father, not a thief.
Taru, whatever happened,
it was my doing...
I made the whole plan,
it's not Booji's fault.
Please let him go.
What is this commotion?
Very shrewd criminals they are,
both father and daughter...
They duped my client
of eighty lakhs...
...it's in the bag...
Is this correct uncle?
Yes
Come on then, to the police station
Just wait and watch now Tarn...
I will get the maximum
sentence for her...
So that all the girls of India
will learn a lesson...
...that they shouldn't dare trick
innocent guys into 498a.
If girls trick guys,
they are low-life...
...but boys keep demanding dowry,
they are still considered innocent.
No.
You please leave... Sorry.
Made us run for nothing...
Have you gone mad Tarn'?
You come here...
What?
- If you want to say something...
- Will you shut up for a minute?
Can I say something?
I understood everything else...
...but what did you say in
the middle of that long speech...
...you started liking me?
What? Yes...
Just liking?
I fell in love with you...
Since I've returned from Lucknow,
I just can't forget the flavours
of your talk, of your food...
...of the fun I had with you...
I have gotten addicted
to your flavours.
So the butcher has fallen
in love with the goat?
You are that good...
Why can't all other men
be normal like you...
Then there wouldn't be any problem.
There would have been a big problem.
Then you wouldn't
have come to Lucknow.
Sania would have become
somebody else's in Hyderabad.
Gulrez
Oh yes, Gulrez.
So you have forgiven me?
What to do, you are that good.
You have tricked me
by feeding kheer...
...but I still want to love you
so very much.
Gullu... You hurt me badly.
- You won't again?
- No, no, never ever. Sorry.
What did I do to deserve you?
Something wonderful my dear...
that's why you got my Gullu.
Gullu-Taru, perfect couple.
Now we will have a real wedding.
Enough of fooling around,
shall we begin?
Gulrez dear...
Yes...
Tariq Haider, I mean Taru Haider,
son of Farooq Haider.
Do you accept me, Gulrez Qadir,
daughter of Abdul Qadir?
You accept without
a single penny of dowry?
Not once, a thousand times.
Say you accept son.
I accept...
Do you accept me Tariq Haider,
son of Farooq Haider?
I accept you.
Amju! The girl's father
is ready to help us.
Full help...
One crore.
Say thank you...
Father, I'm not an item for you
to sell and him to buy.
I don't want to go to America
with someone's help...
So sir, thanks but no thanks.
I'm sorry...
Amjad!
- Have you lost your mind?
- Yes, I have...
I wish I had lost it sooner.
Advertised love,
is for strangers.
Tested love,
is for brave-hearts.
Come let's wave the flag
of our crazy love.
Bright and bold and beautiful.
Let's colour love in our colours.
Pull the curtains,
Lift the veils,
Banish the bashfulness of love.
Let's make the whole world speak,
Let's change the language of love.
Calculated love
is for the corrupt.
Committed love
is for the brave-hearts.
With fun, with fervour,
Come let's light
the fireworks of love.
Bright and bold and beautiful.
Let's colour love in our colours.
Everyone eyes your figure,
But I'm crazy about your brains.
Every guy is wild for your looks,
But I'm sold on your thinking.
Body-beauty kind of love,
is for the phonies.
Tuning-setting kind of love
is for the exceptional.
Boldly, Loudly,
Come let's blow the bugle of love.
Bright and bold and beautiful.
Let's colour love in our colours.