Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
What is life?
A subtle harmony of the five elements
What is my?
A mess in these elements
Pandit Brii Narayan Chakbast
Public toilets
A moment.
I have a gift for you.
Thank you.
It's okay?
It's kinda weird.
Open the door !
What is happening here?
Open!
My clothes ?
Open that door!
Good !
So this hotel has turned into a mess?
Well done !
Shall we go wild?
Let's start with you.
Go ahead!
Checked.
Your name?
Your name !
Piyush Agarwal.
- What are you running from?
- Sir, I'm a student.
Where do you come from?
Allahabad.
Is that what you study?
Sir, can we work it out?
Give him a good "arrangement"!
I arrange with Madame.
Your name?
Your name !
- Speak !
- Devi.
So, Devi, you are well fucked!
Superb!
Catch that asshole! Where did he go?
Bring him out!
- Let's see the arrangement you want.
- No sir !
I am a student.
It's the first time.
Are you playing innocent? Open!
Open!
Find his wallet.
Open that damn door!
He's gonna open that motherfucker!
Search well.
Wait, that'll bring him out.
Father's name:Ramdhari Agarwal.
Emergency number:9415257547.
Go out or I call your father.
I want to go to the toilet.
You will shit in prison.
Your father's number is busy.
Please don't call my father!
We will call him back.
Are you from a Madvadi brothel?
Look at the device.
- No.
- From Nepal?
You are wrong !
Is that so ? Are we wrong?
Open,
or we drag you naked in the street!
Open!
What are you waiting for?
Kill that damn door!
Open!
What the hell is he doing?
Open the door !
Are you standing idly by?
Break down the door!
Holy shit!
Sir!
Come to see !
What now?
Pandey! An ambulance !
- Piyush ...
- Quickly !
Slowly.
Be careful, he's bleeding a lot.
Get her dressed, we'll take her on board.
What are you watching?
THE PYRE
My son, are you back home?
I'll bring you a glass of water.
Do not bother,
I will help myself.
I give you some.
Mother, we must light the stove.
Go find the sacred fire of the ghât.
Also wake up Sikandar.
He has to go to work.
Bro
Bro...
Sikandar ...
Hey, brother!
Mom sends me to wake you up.
Standing !
Ram, the name of God
is the eternal truth ...
- I bring fire to mom, I come back.
- What about Sikandar?
He's up, he's coming.
Hey, Motilal!
- Join us.
- I can't leave my shop.
Your shop! We won't steal anything from you!
They brought us this,
they are from the university. Tell him.
Sir, we have
an anthropological project.
They want history and tradition
of our ghats. Enlighten them.
You are the scholar of our ghats!
And you, the one in our alleys!
Shady alleys at night, eh?
You save?
Yes, we forget details
taking notes.
The story...
Formerly, on the banks of the Ganges,
our mother,
stretched the jungle.
The ritual of the pyres was born
on the sacred Ganges.
Many kings
established their ghât here.
Priests from all provinces
settled there.
Each ghât
is allocated according to the regions,
castes and priests.
You see ?
The ghât where we are sitting
is controversial.
- Like Kashmir.
- Yes.
People of Maharashtra
claim it.
Like those of Gudjerat,
What are we going to do with him?
Here is Jhonta, the hero of the ghats,
who wants to become president.
But to bring me customers,
no need to rely on him.
- So what?
- I was going to do it!
Bring my phone. Hurry up !
The neighboring ghât is that of Scindia.
I am going to look for clients.
Kids today are in a hurry.
They don't stop.
The phone doesn't stop either.
Calvary of modern times!
It's me.
They are ingenious.
Madame has put herself in suri
and made herself beautiful.
They hardly know each other,
and forward!
Why?
What did you tell us?
Repeat it.
Explain to your father.
What are you saying
"Out of curiosity".
If I tell a journalist about it go will make the headlines.
What's this ?
A file for another service?
What does it mean?
Are you not paying attention?
Get out !
Can you tell me your name again?
Pathak.
Vidhyadhar Pathak.
I give rituals
at the Nandeshwar ghât.
I used to teach Sanskrit
at University.
I also translate books.
We'll call you back in three days.
For now, pay the deposit,
and take your daughter.
Mr. Mishra ...
What does "for now" mean?
If the boy dies, she is an accomplice
of a suicide, of a crime.
Court
media, you will have to face it all.
Don't beg me! Pay the deposit.
Consider that we are alike ...
Pay the deposit and get out!
Centrifugal force was used,
centripetal force.
And we find ourselves stuck.
So we explore upwards.
And here we are
in the world of civil engineering.
Questions?
How many months of study do you have left?
Two more months, dad.
Then the exams, and the internship.
- The what?
- The internship, for a job.
Do we have to pay to get hired?
Not anymore, mom.
Railways and electricity
hire by competition.
You should not
monitor ash filtering?
What if the kids steal the money?
Uncle Shambhu is there.
Shambhu is still high.
So what ! I have the right to eat?
How much will you earn?
I will find out after my interview.
It's good. Leave here.
The earliest would be best.
Otherwise even you will end your life
among the burning bodies.
A wafer !
I found that, is it in silver?
Hello Master !
I took my bath early!
Weren't you there for 3 days?
Shut up and do your job.
Is your father here?
He is on the ghât.
Call him.
The boy is dead.
Did you offer her some tea?
Sit down.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Mr. Pathak, the boy is dead.
The body is autopsied,
the report will not delay.
Here are the court papers.
Please fill them out.
Wait...
How does the tribunal affect us?
It is a complicity in suicide.
But, sir ... the boy ...
He killed himself in front of your eyes.
Under your intimidation.
Are you lecturing me, professor?
Listen carefully...
Save your sermons for
your client wankers on the ghats.
Including?
Haven't you seen it on TV?
R.K. Puram's sex scandals,
and Jammu and Kashmir.
Now your daughter is part
of a beautiful sex scandal.
Sir, tell us how to do it.
What is your monthly income?
I earn 8-10,000 rupees.
She works too?
Yes, in computer science.
I'll get right to the point.
Complicity,
media, court,
I can take care of everything.
But you have to work it out.
300,000 rupees in 3 installments.
I'll leave you 3 months.
No, you are wrong.
We have principles.
And we wouldn't even have 50,000.
From now on...
Never again...
Never negotiate with me again!
I come to sell a bar of soap
I am here to save your honor.
I have the video of the sex scandal
of your daughter.
Just put it on the Internet,
then no one in Benares
won't let go of your daughter!
Find 100,000 within 2 days.
Don't nod your head
like a horse!
You are going to do what?
Find 100,000 in 2 days.
And in 2 months?
200,000.
Easy to understand, right?
Where are you going?
- At the cremation ghât.
- It's forbidden for women.
You have to hit the skull 5 times.
Piyush!
Deepak, go help him!
Piyush, my son.
The skull must burst
for the soul to escape.
That's 26 rupees.
Where do they come from?
I dived while holding back
my breath very long!
So what?
Let me participate!
Are you asking me to let you bet?
It's not a bet, it's sport.
And I am a pro!
So shut up.
Don't you have a job to do?
You got fucked
by a bull, or what?
It's Pooja with my teddy bear.
Cute, eh?
You can ask him
the name of this girl?
How do I do it?
"Pooja, my mate is crazy
from your girlfriend
"who goes to your poetry reading.
"Tell him his name so that he invites him."
Shall we send a request?
Deepak is quite exhilarated.
As they say ...
All night long the mango was shaken,
but when the time came she fell.
What's the matter with you?
Good listening.
You remember her?
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
Be serious.
Girls' college B.N. Roi.
She must be there.
Will you find it in Pooja's album?
Yes she must be
in his friend list.
It's her?
There it is!
Shaalu Gupta.
Gupta, the class!
Cool, man!
Open a Facebook account,
and let the fireworks begin!
You understand?
Send him a request.
We did it?
Yes.
Come closer, everyone!
Earn lots of money, and fast!
In a few minutes, 10 rupees
bring in 50! And 50 is 200!
These young people will dive
to bring back coins.
Bet on the one who will bring back
the most coins!
20 on Loku, it is noted.
Do not hesitate ! Place your bets!
20 rupees on Netwa.
Let the competition begin!
... 2 ...
Go!
Let's see who brings back the most coins!
Gentlemen, take a good look!
Loku brought back 3 coins.
Netwa! Faster !
Babua only brought back one piece.
Munna had 3 coins at once.
Hold your breath!
- Boss, let me go!
- No, you're watching.
Please I want to go!
What an exciting competition!
Did you bet well?
Those who bet on Munna
see their earnings triple!
Sikandar!
Throw your leg in the stake, asshole!
Looks like the old man is drunk.
A glass,
king of the Dom community!
Another for you prosperity!
Do I look like a king?
Let's see! There are only two kings
in Benares.
One is Kushi Nuresh,
the other the king of the Dom.
One on the other side,
the other on this side.
Look at poor Shambhu.
How many bonus days per year?
Hey ! Shambhu!
Yes sir !
One every ten years.
Shambhu has a bonus day
once every ten years.
So...
That day...
all cremation earnings
comes back to him.
Shambhu's father
was touching his bonus day
once a year.
He was fulfilled and he had ten children.
The bonus has been shared.
His dad had a bonus day
per year,
Shambhu inherited
of the tenth of the bonus.
Today, Shambhu touches
a bonus every ten years.
When will your next one, Shambhu?
I have no more!
I sold my bonus rights to Lulu.
He paid me 100,000 rupees.
I will live on alms the rest of my life.
If I sell my bonus,
I will have a million rupees.
Isn't that right, Lulu?
As if you were going to sell them to me!
Should we sell?
Are you asking your son for advice?
Our ghât does not concern him!
The educated man is an asshole!
Are you insulting my son?
I will never sell you my bonus!
But you never thought about it!
Dad,
I need money
for the Durga Puja party.
Take in my shirt.
300 rupees, will it be okay?
Take what you want.
You are my Everything.
Will you finally explain yourself?
What do you want to hear?
I want to know.
Who was he ? What happened?
I saw him at the computer center.
I was typing his study report.
We became friends, that's it.
And that's all?
Yes.
I liked talking to him.
You didn't think twice
before doing it?
Not even once?
Huh?
Answer!
What?
- You heard?
- I do not know!
A boy has just died.
We have a ransom of 300,000 on our back.
I liquidated my savings of 100,000.
You're on the verge of going to jail.
And you answer:"I don't know."
Friend request sent
You come to the Durga Puja party,
tonight ?
That's 20 rupees.
Put this watch in the hat.
Slowly ! Yes, in the hat.
The watch is in the hat.
Now blow into the hat.
And see now, the watch ...
The watch is gone!
The watch will reappear
in the pocket of someone among you!
She's on him!
The man in the red shirt!
Yes you ! Check your pockets.
We found the watch!
Take the stage, young man!
What is your name?
Deepak.
I will no longer smoke.
Yesterday my friends forced me to do it.
Shaalu agrees to be your friend.
Write to him on his wall.
With my qualifications,
I deserve at least 12000 per month.
Don't negotiate!
He was one of my favorite students.
He was our teacher
all of our schooling.
What we are today
we owe it to him.
Bring some tea.
No thanks. I do not have time.
I have a book translation to finish.
A glass of water?
From the canister.
I have received your CV.
For the moment,
we have no instructor position.
The receptionist is free.
Welcome and advice
to new students.
And a database job
paid in addition.
In all, 5.5K rupees per month.
Perfect !
It starts tomorrow.
Thanks a lot, Sanjay.
Sir, that's the least of it.
Excuse me, I have to answer.
Drink.
The pottery of our bottle
gives it a very good taste.
He gives just 5500.
You saw how he respects me.
Thank you.
Are you in a polytechnic school?
Yes.
Civil engineering. In the last year.
We had a strike for a year,
otherwise I would already have a job.
What are your hobbies?
The music.
- You sing?
- No.
I'm listening to music
on the radio, on CDs.
Only the music?
And I really like poetry!
- Poetry?
- Yes.
Bashir Badr ...
Akbar Allahabadi, Mirza Ghalib ...
Ghalib, do you know?
Yes finally...
Thank you.
Boy! Can we have some sauce?
Szechuan sauce?
Can you bring some?
- Get started.
- No you !
You first.
Well...
We're friends, aren't we?
By the way,
if one day you get into trouble,
say it to me.
What will you do?
I will solve the problem.
If someone bothers you,
laughs, makes you cry ...
There are  bad boys  around here.
Okay.
What if ever ...
What if I cry because of you?
I? No why?
Again, I will solve the problem.
Student's name
in capital letters, please.
Here is our brochure with a free CD.
All the information is there.
Take them and come back tomorrow.
We will register your son.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
You can talk well.
Is this your first job?
No.
What happened?
I didn't like the job.
I know what you were doing.
Enter the face game!
Yes are these actors.
Guess and answer!
Among the correct answers,
a car to win!
Our standard is open.
Internship report
by Piyush Agarwal
Tragic death of Piyush Agarwal,
September 17, 2014
- Do you want to participate?
- Yes !
- Please !
- How many rooms this morning?
More than these old folks will bring back.
Let me  y  go!
Okay, but be careful.
Let's go.
Queue!
Here is Jhonta, a new diver!
Who will bring back the most coins?
Jhonta is doing very well!
Place the pieces here.
Dive over there!
20 rupees on Jhonta?
How many?
This way. Here !
Jhonta brought back 6 pieces!
Piyush Agarwal,
born in Allahabad.
He is dead.
A tragic death.
I heard it say.
I am from the center where he was in training.
These documents were his.
And he owed money.
He also had books to return ...
Could I have his address?
Get out! The contest is over!
four hundred ninety seven
Who has the most coins?
Hey, Munna!
Tell us who is the winner!
Jhonta!
- I told you I would win!
- You were wonderful.
Father of Piyush:Ramdhari Agarwal
Hide these stars in my eyes
May they be safe there
the night will be long to last
travelers like the two of us
Will cross on a path
Maybe in the sailor's light
Then?
How? 'Or' What? That's all.
Sorry,
I am not there.
What I understood is very beautiful!
You are stupid !
And adorable.
What? What?
I said nothing.
But I heard!
You will faint
if I read Chakbast.
Is it going to be your birthday?
I saw it on Facebook.
Is that so?
Facebook doesn't say it all.
What?
A picnic.
Shaalu?
My mother asks me. I will call back.
By the way !
Yes.
You must call me by my first name
and be familiar with each other.
If you remember two poems.
I'll decide after. I have to go.
Hello?
Goodbye.
A poem by Dushyant Kumar.
You are like the train at the misty dawn
I shook like a shaken bridge
In the immense forest of your eyes
Little by little my way is lost
Yes is on the device?
May I speak  to  Mr. Ramdhari Agarwal?
It's me. Yes are you?
I ... I ...
What do you want ?
This is the Kashi Cooperative Bank.
Our new products ...
I don't want anything, thank you!
I'm telling you bluntly.
I want fucker.
Okay?
No one will know.
He was fucking you too.
It's good quality, look.
- It's way too expensive.
- But no !
I'll give you a discount. 320 rupees.
Leave. You think
and come back to buy it.
Okay?
I resigned.
Hey, Pathak!
Your daughter did not come
since a long time.
Hello.
Go away.
What?
Do you want me to die of shame?
Go away !
Indian Railways Recruitment
- What's going through your mind?
- Nothing.
"Nothing", "I am not",
That's all you say !
Have I been hard on you?
Haven't I given you enough freedom?
Answer!
What did i do to you
to deserve such a scandal?
I did not cause a scandal.
So what is it ?
I'm trying to make ends meet.
On the ghât, in the streets,
I'm still scared
tell me about you.
I am not afraid.
I have decided not to live here anymore.
Small town, small vision of the world.
But you live here with dignity.
My vision of the world!
It's very caring, father!
I'll pay the rent if I have to.
Look at me.
What do you want?
Are you looking for revenge?
Look at me. Avenge who?
Mom!
Your mother.
You don't even remember her.
You were only six years old!
Is a six-year-old blind?
I took her to the hospital, didn't I?
For two days she begged
to go  to  the hospital, but nothing.
Your students mattered more.
You didn't do anything.
I thought it was a simple fever.
Afterwards, it was too late.
Have I neglected you?
I left teaching for you!
I sold books
on the ghats for you!
I would have killed you mother?
What about me, would I have killed this boy?
I killed him?
He committed suicide!
You're crazy.
You make false connections.
I do not make any reconciliation.
I will defend my honor.
I won't go to jail.
You decided everything.
Me, poor idiot, I'm looking for the money.
I'll find the ransom.
Now you don't need a father anymore.
Do what you want.
I shook like a shaken bridge
In the immense forest of your eyes
Little by little my way is lost
I never thought about it.
I love them all.
How to love the seasons?
I love the monsoon!
Did you record it?
Yes, on my phone.
And I added an old tube.
Old man, you are surpassing your master!
Great gift!
She is of high caste.
Don't get carried away too quickly.
She follows
that you are of lower caste?
Tell him, and you'll see.
Not everyone
not progressive.
Yes,
I will tell him.
He has time.
A good job will fix it all.
- Ruppan, give him the keys to your motorcycle.
- Why?
He has another surprise for her.
File the keys, he pays for gasoline.
First word.
A plant?
- A lamp?
- A bowl!
Deepak!
No, not the glow of a flame.
Where are we going?
Where you want.
Mounted.
- Your bag?
- Sorry.
- I sit ?
- Yes go ahead.
Do you know what we call your bus?
How? 'Or' What?
The minettes' wagon.
You haven't told me where you live.
Do you see where Bhelupur is?
- Bhelupur?
- Yes. Just after.
My friend Prerna lives there.
I will go to your place
on the pretext of seeing her.
It will be funny, right?
You will come to my place?
Will your parents let you out?
If you do not want to...
No,
I didn't say go.
Here go for a second.
Your birthday present.
Put the.
Can you hear well?
Thank you.
Have you ever been to Sangam?
I have been here often.
In a few days,
we leave by bus for a pilgrimage.
We are all going  there .
Uncle, aunt, grandfather, grandmother.
Will you come too?
- Or?
- With us.
With your family?
I have to think about it.
What?
You're the youngest, aren't you?
Yes.
How do you know?
The little ones are still talking
wrongly and through.
Ouch! Your hand is a real hammer!
It's the ring.
My uncle gave it to me
when I was little.
She's stuck.
My fingers have grown
the ring has not moved.
As I am the youngest,
everyone likes me.
Why are you looking at me like that?
I do not know.
You, the youngest one, I like you.
Shaalu.
You want to marry me?
I do not know.
Will your family accept?
Do you want to see them?
Will you introduce me?
You don't tell me your address,
but do you want to come to my place?
I go.
You live here?
Just around the corner, the house on the left.
And you house?
You said to Bhelupur ...
Shivala?
Kamacha!
Ah, I know.
- Durgakund, right?
- Why?
What's the matter with you?
I told you, near Bhelupur.
Can you talk about something else?
I was joking...
Do you find it funny?
Do you want to see where I live?
I'll take you there.
You will be able to satisfy your curiosity.
Come on, get on.
You want the truth?
Ghat Harishchandra.
I live there and I was born there.
Make the pyres, light them,
this is our job.
Me, my father, my brother, my uncles.
Always.
Have you ever seen a burning body?
Say, have you ever seen one burn?
I see them from morning to night.
I burn bodies, night and day.
In the fire, the skin is consumed.
The bones, the skull remain.
We split the skull with a stick,
the ashes are filtered into the Ganges.
You imagine ? Do you want to come and see?
Are you giving up your friend's pretext?
I don't have a tip?
Why?
A letter of employment from the government
deserves a good tip.
Indian Railways Contract
Are you the new employee?
Yes.
Sit down.
Ah, say ...
If you were out
two minutes later,
I would have given you my water bottle.
By the way, I am Sadhya.
Hello.
Nice guide to ticket sales.
We learned without a guide.
Not easy !
Look.
Mr. Mukherjee.
He worked here before you.
He refused to learn computers.
- Can I use it?
- Of course.
So the company transferred him
deep in Rajasthan.
Now,
he sells the tickets  by  by hand.
Do you know IT?
Yes.
Very well.
A note.
Hello.
- To go where?
- Lalpur.
Shaalu, your aunt is calling you.
You know...
You are different from other boys.
In what ?
There is a certain honesty in you.
Like the one in poetry
by Nida Fazli.
Yes, but who is Nida Fazli?
There it is, your honesty!
It is very good.
Except the onions.
The place is dirty.
It's better if it's good,
the owner is from our caste.
Are you finally calling?
It was you who reacted badly
and you are mad at me?
Sorry.
I'm not waiting for an apology.
- I am stupid !
- That is true.
I can't find the right words.
That is also true.
Where are you ?
We haven't changed state yet.
We're getting there.
Listen...
My parents...
They ... won't accept you.
They live in the past
with backward ideas.
But I am on your side.
Over time, they will change their mind.
Start by finding a good job.
Yes, that's what I'm trying to do.
I will do my best during the internship.
Yes, keep your spirits up!
I take care of the rest.
I will not hesitate  to  run away with you.
Take care of yourself.
Hey, KK! Let's go home!
We just left.
I have my revisions to do.
We turn around!
Other leaves, if Please.
I am in the last year
of civil engineering.
At the polytechnic
Seth Kinaram Agarwal
My goal is
an engineering career,
specialized in industrial design.
- We're going home. I can not wait to see you.
- I'm going to have a job, come quickly.
There are many left
body  to  burn.
Push the skull into the fire.
I'll go get Deepak.
Deepak!
- What?
- Standing!
Dad is still drunk.
There are   lots of bodies.
Get up !
Nobody bumps here!
Hey, Deepak!
Wait, you dirty thief!
The next time,
I throw you on a pyre!
They didn't even cover the bodies.
Hey, Shambhu!
Go up the pyres there.
Yes, I'm going.
Take this body to the ritual bath.
Deepak!
When you are done here
mounts pyres over there.
Over there?
Yes, at the edge. As much as you can.
- Do I end up here first?
- Yes, quickly!
We need more sawdust!
Sikandar needs wood. Go ahead.
Hey, Deepak!
Come help us.
Warning.
Slowly.
Did the cops say something?
The pilgrim bus had an accident,
he fell into the Ganges.
Is that so?
Utilities have left
the bodies here.
Survivors?
No.
You know...
28 trains stop here every day.
And how many do not stop there?
64!
It's easier to come here
than to start again!
- Its very important.
- But it was strong drinks!
They are meant to be.
Can't I drink as much as you?
I do not say that.
Excuse me, could you ...
Is this post confirmed?
It was nice,
but we have to go home.
One more day.
No confirmation.
What about the last minute quota?
A place for two would suit us.
One seat, I like it.
Status:26 places available
I am not going back to this hotel!
No place.
- Cancellations?
- No.
Shit !
What shall we do now?
I am the father of Piyush.
You were at the hotel with him, huh?
- Answer!
- What are you doing? Give me the phone!
It's me speaking, come home!
Were you with Piyush that day?
Answer!
come to see
an exceptional competition,
like you will never see!
Jhonta!
Now ladies and gentlemen
these kids are going to dive.
Jhonta!
He is not there.
Bet on someone else.
Bet on Babua, he's great.
I bet on Babua.
- How many?
- 200 rupees.
The professor bets 200 on Babua!
Get into position.
2 ...
- Do I have something in my mouth?
- No !
I put this bullet in my mouth.
And now, l ... 2 ... and ...
Here you go.
- I deserve at least 500.
- I'll give you more next time.
Professor, how much have you lost?
Is it an hour to go home?
You hear me?
Have you become dumb?
Where were you?
I was having fun!
Are you there to work or have fun?
It's my money, what's the problem?
Shut up !
These other orphans are worthless.
Do you dare to talk to your boss like that?
You won't go anywhere
during a contest!
He takes himself for the king of Benares!
He wastes money!
I'll tell Devi!
Do as you like.
Start by sitting down!
And don't move an inch.
Sit down !
What arrogance.
You will give me your winnings from the contests.
For internships,
the subject of debate is ...
Industrialization and its effects
on the environment,
human life and society.
Hey, Deepak.
Say something.
You've been silent for too long.
Talk to us.
Leash.
Take your time.
"I love poetry."
"You are like the train
at the misty dawn. "
"I shook like a shaken bridge."
"I will not hesitate
to  run away with you. "
This pain will never end?
Deepak, get up!
Hold my motorcycle keys, go where you want.
Shaalu!
The translation was for today.
Printers are twiddling their thumbs.
Mr. Pathak?
Everything is fine?
You will have it in three days.
Three days?
Devi isn't doing well these days.
Mr. Verma ...
an advance would be possible?
You make me hang around.
But I can't refuse.
Hold.
Good.
Excuse me.
I was delayed.
How many are there?
30,000 rupees this time.
Come with me.
Do you see this portal?
Yes.
Opposite, there is  there  a warehouse.
The junkyard Pappu.
Sell ​​that old machine
for 10 or 20,000.
We are really trying.
I think I will be able to pay soon.
It's a joke?
It is not enough.
I have to tell you how?
I'll pay the rest this week.
Take this in the meantime.
The rest this week.
And all of it next month.
- So, you sold us your bonus to Lulu?
- No way!
Sikandar sold it for 300,000.
How would Sikandar sell it
without my consent?
He's not at Mr. Kallu's.
Where the fuck is past Sikandar?
Luxa police station
The cops don't know where he is.
You found it?
What a bastard!
Fucking thief!
You motherfucker!
What constitution forbids me
to buy your bonus?
Bring that damn constitution!
Why talk about the constitution?
It's a private matter.
Find an amicable agreement.
Amicably ? I'll kill that bastard!
Pay 300,000 and I'll give it back to you
your bonus right.
Not a single rupee, you bastard!
Perhaps,
he did not pay Sikandar!
Go get Sikandar.
Ask him if I haven't paid for everything.
Where will I find 300,000?
I am nothing!
Mr. Dubey, you are a witness.
If he pays me 300,000,
I give him back his bonus right.
And thank you for insulting me.
Goodbye.
From all Benares,
you won't get a better deal.
You pay?
Sir, if you could speed up.
- Where are you going?
- Howrah.
With your goddess name,
you should have four arms
on each side.
Eight tickets in record time!
Sir, if you could speed up ...
What's in the rush?
My father says:
"Who doesn't taste kheer,
"ignore the joys of existence!"
Here, take some.
No, this is for you.
Obviously.
My father did it himself.
It is his birthday.
Okay.
- Delicious, isn't it?
- Very good.
You live alone ?
No,
i live with my father.
Father lives alone.
I mean, he's alone during the day.
From kheer?
I haven't done one for a long time,
I thought...
I have just finished dinner.
Keep it, I'll take it tomorrow.
Eat.
One of your favorite desserts.
Its good.
Is there any milk left for tomorrow morning?
What is that?
I have finished my first month of work.
My salary check.
How many?
20,000.
Good.
Sit down next to me.
You didn't tell me anything
of your permanent job.
It is only temporary.
I work to win
the ransom money.
- And after that...
- Then?
I want to go to study
at Allahabad University.
I will work part time
near college.
Do you want to get out of here?
Yes.
Why?
Without this case, I would already have ...
I'm probably better off alone.
It's not far.
I will come from time to time.
And your father?
So I don't count anymore?
If you've got everything ready, then ...
Go.
I didn't kill you mother.
I will go to sleep in the ghats,
silently.
Father, please.
Please don't cry.
Write your address.
There are still narrow ways
in the mountains.
Wide track technology
will replace them in the future.
- You were major of your promotion?
- Yes sir.
We commit you to the 6-month trial,
in Allahabad.
- Thank you sir.
- Well done, congratulations.
Today is the big day!
Dedicate this day to the Almighty!
Long live our god Shiva ...
So everything is fine?
- Take my bet.
- How many ?
- 10,000.
- Noted.
- Do you want to win?
- Of course !
Let's see who will be the winner!
Jhonta, dive in there.
Quickly ! Faster !
Go further.
Jhonta!
Munna, see you there!
Vikram, find Jhonta!
Stand aside all of you!
Make room!
Let it pass!
Jhonta!
I won't make you compete anymore,
my little.
- What?
- Did I make you lose everything?
No.
Want a magic trick?
Something in my hand?
Something in my other hand?
No.
Something in my mouth?
1, 2, 3 ...
Who's is this?
It's for you.
Where is she from?
I found it while diving.
Yes, that's fine with me.
Thank you.
Here, it's hot.
I prepared this for you,
eat it on the train.
Eat, I'll finish.
Its good.
Let's go?
Call me when you arrive.
- Okay, I pure.
- Go ahead.
Don't stay near the door.
- Make yourself comfortable.
- See you soon, dad.
Don't worry, I'll take care of him.
Hello.
I am coming to see Mr. Ramdhari Agarwal.
I am Devi Pathak.
Piyush was my friend.
Let's go home to talk.
- What are you doing ? Have you gone mad?
- Why come now?
Are you alright, my daughter?
Why?
What harm had he done to you?
Here is water.
30 rupees to go to Sangam!
Go up, ma'am.
And you sir?
I'll take you to Sangam.
Come.
You come  to  Sangam
for the first time ?
Yes.
And you?
The second time.
They say you have to come  to  Sangam
twice.
Why?
A first time alone,
and a second time with someone.
Adaptation:Martine Armand
Subtitling:Monal Group