I have reached.
- Sample?
- It's safe.
Where should I come?
You don't have to come Suraj,
you have to go.
"Looking for a reason,
without any reason"
"I lost myself in this world,
looking for the world"
"Looking for an incident"
"Look where I have reached,
searching"
"Everywhere, every lane,
I couldn't find my destination"
"Just holding my breath"
"Confronted by the desert"
"I am a gypsy, what should I do?"
Mister, you cannot park here.
Please make a move.
Sir, I am just leaving now.
One minute! Yes, yes!
Cannot, cannot... You keep
your money... I want you move now...
Look, officer! Look, just come.
Thank you, officer! Thank you!
Here take your money!
I gave 50 to that police officer.
This is 25, count it.
Strange man!
If it's more, he won't take it!
If it's less, he won't say anything.
"The road was always the journey"
"Moments of peace were always short"
"I found a story teller,
looking for a caravan"
"Just holding my breath"
"Confronted by the desert"
"I am a gypsy, what should I do?"
You took so much of time
on the first day, itself?
I'm sorry!
It is very difficult to
do a double shift in this old age.
And you? You do three shifts!
What will you do
with so much money, son?
I have debt that has to be repaid.
Your wish!
Take this key.
My life of double
shifts is now finished.
All the best, son! All the best.
'What a strategy!'
'He ducks,
he misses, and reminds him again.'
'Wow! What a fight!
Oh, another one! What a fight!'
'Oh! He's getting a hold!'
'Woah! And that's a...'
'What a kick! I think,
the match is going to end very soon.'
Hey guard, working or sleeping?
Idiot!
'It's almost a one sided match!'
Hey! Why did you turn it off?
Change the channel!
It must be almost
in 8 o'clock in India.
Please, put on my channel.
What is this?
You still haven't watered this?
I told you,
this has to be watered twice a day.
How many times have I told you?
As soon as it's almost 8 o'clock
in India, turn on my channel.
When will you understand?
Take this!
Take it!
What are you waiting for?
Catch it!
Now, what was the
need to bring all this...
It's your favorite carrot pudding,
uncle Usman.
Now, how many times have
I told you not to play with fire?
But, you?
just blah- blah- blah- blah- blah!
If the lecture is over,
taste it and tell me how it tastes?
Here, come on!
I don't like sweets.
Who are you?
What are you doing
in uncle Usman's cabin?
Uncle Usman has retired
today and I joined in his place.
Oh!
You're a native.
Strange fool you are!
Couldn't you tell me before?
You didn't give me a chance!
I will go to uncle Usman's
house and set him right!
Who just goes away without informing?
First of all, uncle Usman
is not here and to top it...
I don't know whether Bindiya's
mother-in-law will agree or not.
Mother-in-law?
She is very strict!
Poor Bindiya was just
about to apologize.
Now, her fat mother-in-law knows
she was lying to go to the office!
Who is Bindiya?
"I am the Bindiya (ornament)
of your forehead!"
It's the biggest hit
on Indian television.
Don't you watch it?
That's what uncle Usman
and I used to watch together.
Today, he ditched me!
Anyways,
if uncle Usman is not here, then...
I think I should leave, right?
Okay!
I think I should go.
If you wish you can come inside.
No, thanks! I'm fine.
The weather is bad and...
Bindiya should have
reached home by now.
- And her mother-in-law...
- Fat and strict!
I don't know how she's going to react.
What is her mother-in-law's name?
Kalavati!
'Kalavati is the name
of truth and the idol of love.'
'You have cheated Kalavati!'
'Cheated! Cheated!'
'But, you forgot that
Kalavati wears glasses...'
so that if someone tries
to throw dust into her eyes...'
'the dust collides with
the glasses and falls to the ground!'
'The bond of mother-in-law and
daughter-in-law is a fragile wall...'
'but, you have kicked
down the wall of belief!'
'No, mother!
I haven't done anything of the sort.'
'I value the honor of this
family even more than my life!'
'Please forgive me!'
'The Suryavanshi family...'
'...then Kalavati will
not fail even once!'
'I am the Bindiya of your forehead!'
You haven't eaten this!
And one more thing.
I am telling you because
uncle Usman is not here.
This night jasmine has
to be watered twice a day.
Yes.
Can I get the address
for gym Thunderstorm?
Thank you.
Okay! So now, the structure we make,
needs a strong base.
While learning clay modeling,
we need to start with the base...
which is the armature.
So I hope all of you
are ready to learn...
how to make you first armature.
Yes!
Very good!
So, armatures can be
made of different material.
Like PWC pipes, wooden rods.
Just depends on how sturdy
you want the structure to be.
And you know...
You are so good, Jenny!
I mean, you are so hot!
Thank you, Mr. Chang.
I'm really, really impressed with you.
- What's your plan this evening?
- Me?
Yeah! Of course, you!
You definitely deserve a treat!
But today, Bindiya's husband will
take her on a romantic dinner date.
What?
Sorry, Mr. Chang! I'm busy tonight.
8 o'clock, channel 22!
Do watch it!
Come on! Hit me harder!
Come on, punch harder!
Use your body weight!
Stop!
Mercy is the boxer's biggest enemy!
Your opponent will
never do that for you!
So, box me harder now!
Come on! You can do it.
Use you left! Concentrate! Fight!
What happened?
Look here! Concentrate!
- Suraj!
- What?
I knew you would definitely
come here one day.
Come here you!
Forget about the past, Bossy!
You considered Suraj your own son.
He has returned after 3 years.
Let's hug and start all over again.
Trust me,
everything be like the old times.
Come here! What did you do to me?
Let me show you!
Look here! Look!
Look here!
I had to leave that posh locality...
and come and live here in this area!
I had a home which
I built with my hard work.
It got sold.
My wife loved me a lot.
She left me and returned to India.
All because of you!
And you think that
I will hire you again!
I will trust you again.
I did not come here to ask for work.
I have come to apologize.
Sorry.
You've come here to do me a favor.
Omi! He's come here to do me a favor.
Why don't you say it clearly?
You've come to see...
whether Srikant is still alive.
If he is alive, what is his plight?
Omi! Tell him...
Tell him to get out of my sight.
I never want to see his face again.
Get him out from here.
Get him out!
Suraj, you don't worry.
This guy is very haughty!
But, he loves you.
And his wife was going
to leave him anyway.
Now come on,
I will introduce you to the others.
Come on. Let's go.
Come on, boys! Come on! Come here!
Look who's here! This is Suraj.
We used to call him "Storm".
He was the champion in 2012.
There used to be no one left
to face him in the final round.
All the professional
players were defeated by him.
Hey Sikandar, come on here.
Nobody could play until
the last round with him.
That's Storm!
And I was one of them.
He knocked me out in 13 seconds.
Isn't it, Champ?
Sikandar!
Suraj, all these are old stories.
But, he is no less today!
He has worked very hard on himself.
He is the best MMA
fighter in Thunderstorm.
I saw him on TV. Not bad.
Oh, really?
Not bad!
Come on, then! Let's see.
What does good mean
and who is better?
I have given up fighting.
Why?
Have you lost your power?
- Or did you realize your true place?
- Sikander!
This is not the time
for this useless conversation.
He hasn't worn gloves for 3 years.
It will be seen later,
who will win and who will lose.
He gave up winning 3 years ago.
At that time he was the shining sun.
Today, he is the setting sun.
Come on, boss!
Okay, take it. Tell them.
Tell them how much
fire is still left in you.
- Boss, I have given up fighting.
- Boss!
Suraj!
This place is for boxers.
That too, only for winners.
Don't even think of looking this way,
forget about coming here!
Suraj!
'She was looking great!'
'Why dinner tonight?'
'It's nobody's birthday,
nor anniversary!'
'How can you say that, Bindiya?'
'Don't we go out without an occasion?'
If you don't mind,
can you please open the window?
Sorry, but I'm sensitive to smell.
Maybe you've had a work out,
that's why!
What clothes have you worn today?
It's a greenish T- shirt and...
Silly! I'm not talking about you,
I'm asking about Bindiya!
What do her earrings look like?
- Just like you!
- Really?
Wow! Bindiya is wearing
earrings just like mine.
Okay, now look at the TV and
tell me how Bindiya actually looks!
- I'll just be back.
- Okay
'You don't call him a killer,
you call him a murderer!'
'How does it matter whether
he is a killer or a murderer?'
'Will you kill me
now or after dinner?'
'Bindiya! A little romance...'
'My romance is not a joke!'
'I am the bindiya (ornament)
on your forehead'
Thank you! Bye!
Your...
tiffin.
Thanks!
What is inside this?
It's sugar.
What! Why?
- We're equal now.
- Oh, really?
Favor and debt, must be repaid
as soon as possible, Bindiya!
Sometimes, you behave
like Bindiya's husband Jignesh!
Anyway, I'm Jenny!
I'm shaking your hand,
not asking for it!
You are shy like a girl,
but your hand is quite solid.
What do you do?
Okay!
Bye! Thanks for the show.
And thanks for the sugar.
"Sounds! Tell me, what are these
sounds that I can hear nowadays"
"Knocking! Tell me, why are
these strange moments knocking?"
I'm shaking your hand,
not asking for it!
"There is something
that causes less sleep"
that makes the eyes moist"
"There is something,
that if you say so"
"I will lay down
my life with a smile!"
"What can we call that
which exists between us?"
"What is love? It is a wave...
Come, let's flow with it together"
- "Something that makes me lost"
- I'm talking about Bindiya, not you!
"There is something
that you could not sleep!"
"There is something that
both of us laughed until we cried!"
Hi! I'm so late!
Please, put the TV on.
There's water too?
New shoes?
No.
They're pretty old,
bought them quite sometime ago.
Okay.
What is Bindiya going to do today?
She is going to request her husband.
Jignesh is going to leave Bindiya
and go to Singapore for his new job.
Put the TV on, please.
- 'I don't want your money!'
- See? It's already started.
'Why are you crying like this,
darling?'
'I'm doing all this for you.'
'I don't need your money! I need you!'
'No matter what state we are in,
at least we are together.'
'Bindiya will not be able
to live without you, Jignesh!'
'She will die!'
'Bindiya!
Please don't say such things.'
'I will die, before you.'
'My life is tied to yours.'
'Please!'
'What should I do?'
Jignesh is not doing the right thing!
You won't ever do that, right?
'I will be paid twice
as much money in Singapore.'
What does that mean?
That means that you will not
leave your girlfriend for a new job!
'I will work there
and take care of you.'
It depends.
It depends?
What do you mean, it depends?
What is more necessary for you?
Old relationships or a new job?
I will never leave her and go.
Promise?
Promise!
Good!
Your girlfriend is very lucky.
I don't have a girlfriend.
Silly! You don't have one,
but you will one day.
Wherever she is today,
she is very lucky.
Because it's you in her life,
not Jignesh.
Handsome?
Like a typical Gujju guy, tall, fair!
Silly, I'm not talking about Jignesh,
I'm talking about you!
What do you look like?
Tell me.
Don't bluff because I can't see, okay?
People call me rough and tough.
That means you're not very handsome.
Okay, bye!
Ahh! Ouch!
Aww!
Don't move! Are you alright?
Oh no.
How many days since we became friends?
Since Bindiya apologized to
the time Jignesh goes to Singapore.
That means, 6 days.
And you haven't even told
me your name in these 6 days!
Suraj.
Suraj...
Suraj!
Suraj... what?
Suraj Singh Rathore?
Suraj Uday Pratap Chauhan!
What is your full name?
The one who gave me a name,
only gave me this much.
I have never wanted
to have more than that...
nor was it in my destiny
to have more than that.
Wow!
You should be writing the
dialogues of a show like Bindiya.
You narrated your whole
life's history in just one line!
But, don't worry. I don't
know about your life until now...
but from now onwards,
Jenny will never let you...
miss Rathore or Chauhan.
If I have made a friend,
I will be a friend until the end.
Oh, wait, wait, wait!
I cannot walk anymore.
Let me sit down for a while.
There is a bench over there.
You can rest there for some time.
Careful!
- Careful!
- Thanks.
Listen!
If you want you can go home.
I mean, if there is someone
waiting for you at home.
- If you want, I can...
- What can you do?
I mean, I can...
You mean, you will carry me
on your shoulders and drop me home?
Right!
It's not a bad idea.
But, think about it.
You may regret it midway!
Yes, I've thought about it.
Okay!
- Okay.
- Now?
- Have we passed the garage?
Yes.
Now, turn left from here.
Just a little way more.
Have we passed the mosque?
Yes.
Yes, that's gone too.
Then, we've reached.
No, no. I mean almost reached.
See, there is a broken
down beauty parlor on the left.
Yes.
There some stairs just ahead of it.
It's above those stairs.
Upstairs?
If you're tired, I'll manage.
That's it.
Can you see that gate on the left?
- Yes.
- We have to go inside there.
Not here! Just one floor above.
What happened?
Are you tired?
You said, you were a tough guy!
Perfect! Just here.
Ouch!
I'll go.
Just a minute.
Can you just do me one last favor?
Please.
There is a cloth stuck here.
A cloth?
It's an innerwear.
Thanks!
One minute!
Here.
Two tickets to the music concert.
Consider it a gift
for dropping me here.
I don't like music.
And there is no one
to go along with me.
I could have gone with you,
but you don't like music, so.
No!
It's not like that.
We can go.
I'll pick you up.
Thank you.
Hi!
Should we go?
"Playing the guitar with twist melody"
"The youngster become impatient"
"The quick and fast rhythm"
The concert is there.
"Their hearts leap with joy"
"Searching for partners"
"What a beautiful rhythm"
"All are welcome to dance"
I have come to a concert
after a long time.
Thank you, Suraj.
There is an Indian
restaurant close by.
I used to go there
with someone special.
My first love!
I don't know whether
it's still here.
Who was he?
Who?
Your first love?
Silly!
I was talking about my dad.
This was his favorite place.
We came here very often.
Enough about me.
Tell me about yourself.
Were you always like this?
Haughty and speaking very little?
The serious kind?
Or did you have a humorous side?
You know, Bindiya says,
that people who speak less...
have a volcano of
memories in them.
They keep on moving
around in those memories.
Do you have anything like that?
You know, Bindiya also says...
people who speak less
are either very nice...
or very evil.
They can die for somebody
or they can kill for them too.
And I have heard that blind people
talk more than necessary!
We lost track of time
while talking.
I need to leave.
Suraj, now you are our only hope.
Sikandar ditched us to
make more money.
Now, forget everything
and come back to us.
Because, if you're in the race,
we're in the race.
These hands will never
be raised on anybody.
I told you, didn't I?
We're wasting our time with him.
If he was one of my own...
he would come at least once to
check on how I am.
He wouldn't have disappeared
for three years after destroying me.
This is not the man
whom I considered my son!
I was in jail.
I was in a jail in Kuala Lumpur
for 2 years and 7 months.
Winning that fight 3 years ago
was not only your dream.
It was mine too!
The date of the fight
is fixed, Suraj.
Just know that I am taking
the biggest risk of my life.
You are confident, aren't you?
Oh come on, boss! If he wants...
he can break anybody's jaws and
put the teeth on a table before you.
Right, Suraj?
Now that you have taken an advance,
then why be scared?
Hey!
The night before the fight
a woman came to me.
My name is Natasha.
And she asked me to lose the fight.
I have only one daughter, Alisha.
She told me that my opponent
Ali's daughter had cancer.
And that if I won the fight...
he would never be able to
get her medical treatment.
Please save her.
Please.
You have come to the wrong address.
Come on, Suraj!
Yeah!
Suraj!
Dad!
Dad! Dad!
- Come on, Suraj!
- What is he doing!?
Dad!
Hit him more!
One!
I had almost won that fight!
But, when I saw that
little girl's innocent face
I stopped fighting.
I thought, I would have
other fights to win.
But, that little girl had
only one life to live.
Suraj!
Yay! Dad won!
For the first time,
I wasn't sad to lose.
I had saved a life.
Suraj! What was this, Suraj?
Why are you asking him?
He's lost and hiding out here.
You led down the one who
mentored you!
You wanted money, didn't you?
You could have asked me!
I would have given you money.
You have destroyed me!
What are you doing here?
Hey, you!
Don't touch her.
Who are you?
Don't dare touch my kid...
You talk to me,
if you want her, okay?
Then, I realized that all
this was a drama.
Everything inside me
died that day.
I decided, I would
become an evil man.
So evil, that I forgot myself!
After my fighting license
got cancelled...
I started fighting
outside the ring.
I started doing extortion work.
Hey what do you want?
Why did you go to jail?
It was the last night of the year.
Or maybe the first morning of
the new year.
Everybody was welcoming
And I was just doing my work.
Don't come close to me.
I give you money.
That's all I have.
I have no more money.
'Foreign language.'
Open the door!
Police!
We have complaints against you.
Open the door!
I still look after him.
So that the wounds on my heart
heal with the wounds on his body.
Suraj, the handicapped children
of my orphanage have made this.
Do you have a girlfriend?
Go give this to her.
The love between you will double.
God bless!
- Celebrate tonight.
- Who is it?
Who's there?
It's me, Jenny darling!
Mr. Chang!
What are you doing here?
I've been waiting for you.
- Let's go!
- Mr. Chang.
I have got my own juice.
- Mr. Chang, please leave!
- You can forget about your juice.
Let us have fun.
I brought for our
special night tonight.
Please leave.
We'll talk in the office tomorrow.
No!
Tonight, you listen to me!
You must stay here
and drink this.
No!
I'll see to it,
that we will party tonight.
Get out! Mr. Chang,
leave!
How dare you insult me?
You never cared about my feelings.
I'll make sure,
you don't do this to me anymore.
Just leave! Get out!
Son of a...
Get out!
Suraj!
Suraj, no!
No!
- Stop it!
- This time I've broken your fingers.
Next time, I'll break
your freaking neck!
Suraj, please stop!
Why did you do that, Suraj?
He's my boss!
Tomorrow, he will tell
the entire management.
I will lose my job!
Do you still want to work with him?
Then what else should I do?
Is there any place in the world...
where a single girl
is not harassed?
Is there any office where
bosses like him don't exist?
Should I leave my job?
Should I give up living my life?
Who will take care
of my expenses?
- I will look after you.
- Why?
Who are you to me?
Who am I to you?
You cannot do anything, Suraj.
Apart from increasing my troubles.
Please, leave me alone.
Please! Leave me alone.
"Why do I choose you every moment
among all the others?"
"Why do I weave dreams
of you every moment?"
"Why do I choose you every moment
among all the others?"
"Why do I weave dreams of
you every moment?"
"You taught me the art of living"
"Gave me the patience
to silently bear things"
"You are the faith of life"
"You are my courage"
"You taught me the art of
living and dying"
"My loyalty to you
has made me like you"
"You taught me the art of
living and dying"
"My loyalty to you has
made me like you"
"My loneliness is lost
in thoughts of you"
"Now, my soul is
looking after you"
"My loneliness is lost
in thoughts of you"
"Now, my soul is looking
after you"
"You are the faith of life
and you are my courage"
"You taught me the art of
living and dying"
"My loyalty to you
has made me like you"
"Why do I choose you every moment
among all the others?"
"Why do I weave dreams
of you every moment?"
"You taught me the art of living"
"Gave me the patience
to silently bear things"
"You are the faith of life"
"You are my courage"
Hi!
I thought about it
the whole day and left my job.
Good!
Now, I'm not used to sitting at home.
So, I thought I'd ask you...
will you take me out this weekend?
You said,
you would look after me.
Always!
The orphanage where
I grew up was here.
And then one day, a storm came...
and everything
got washed away.
Now, whenever I'm lonely, or...
I am sad,
then I come here.
Are you lonely and sad
today as well?
No!
For the first time today...
I have come to share
my happiness with this place.
Found it?
Umm-hmm.
Carefully!
Perfect!
Now, this is the foundation
of our home.
Okay? Wait.
These pebbles are the symbol
of the foundation.
Always keep them with you.
They will always remind you of me.
And this, I will always keep with me.
I will also come here to share
my happiness and sorrow.
And you will find me here.
But you didn't want to raise
your hand, right?
Now let it go, my friend.
You son is home,
give him your blessings.
Stop asking useless questions!
I want an answer.
He wants to settle down.
He has fallen in love.
But explain to him
very clearly...
his love should not come
in the way of my boxing.
"Rise! Young lad"
"Blood speaks!"
"Filled in each and every vein"
"passion speaks"
"Rise, young lad. The blood speaks,
the passion in your veins speaks"
"Comes let's make up an iron mind,
and say the word"
"Let's fill the cage
with passion of winning..."
"Let's love the pain"
"Become crazy, take courage to a high
and make all our difficulties easy"
"Stay awake the whole night, dream
with open eyes - this is my curse"
"Make all our difficulties disappear"
"The sweat of blood,
my chest swells with my courage"
This is our new home.
There is a sweet little
balcony over here.
From here...
From where the sunshine
comes straight inside.
How do you know?
I have always seen the sun
without my eyes.
But, the sun has never
looked into my eyes.
Look into my eyes, Suraj.
You are looking into them, right?
Yes.
Lies!
I can see everything
even without sight.
And even though
you have eyes...
'Foreign language.'
The one who will look
after me has arrived.
Now, I can come
every day to help you.
"Rise, young lad. The blood speaks,
the passion in your veins speaks"
"Let's die and let's
say the word"
"Like a heart of iron,
a gypsy who loves pain"
"Become crazy, take courage to a high
and make all our difficulties easy"
"Stay awake the whole night, dream
with open eyes, this is my curse"
"Let's break together and make
all our difficulties disappear"
"The sweat of blood, my chest swells
with my courage"
"Let's break together and make
all our difficulties disappear"
"The sweat of blood, my chest swells
with my courage"
Tell me more.
Suraj!
Okay, Stop! Suraj, no!
Okay. Time out! Time out!
Time out! Turn around!
Looks like you didn't find any
patient in the hospital on Sunday.
Just shut up!
You boxers are
are as good as patients.
You know, your back is really weird.
The curve between
your lumbar spine...
and the thoracic spine
is very little.
So, there is a problem
even with my back!
While massaging, you've begun to
imagine yourself as a doctor!
- Doctor Jenny!
- Obviously!
I'm a qualified nurse.
They won't even let me enter
the hospital without this knowledge.
If we collect some money...
then I could open
a little school for you.
How sweet!
So that you can spend
some time with your art...
and not just with your patients.
Oh! And who will you
spend your time with?
Let me think.
What should I say?
You'll think?
Are you serious?
No.
"The threads of a relationship between
us are beginning to take shape"
"My uneasiness has now begun to
find some peacefulness"
"The threads of a relationship between
us are beginning to take shape"
"My uneasiness has now begun
to find some peacefulness"
"You are my faith in life,
you are my courage"
"You taught me how
to live and die"
"My faith has made me like you"
"You taught me how to live and die"
Suraj!
You have done this, right?
How dare you?
Hold this.
I'm sorry!
Silly boy!
We live in Malaysia.
But, we're still Indians.
Who is going to seek permission
from my parents?
Ask them, silly.
I don't speak too much.
I will only say that...
I will keep your
daughter very happy.
You never told me
how they died.
What should I say?
It was the first
night of the New Year.
But for me, that night left behind
a lifetime of darkness.
Dad had stopped all his urgent work
and was with us since two days.
And I was driving.
And then that
fateful accident happened.
But for me, that night left
behind a lifetime of darkness.
My parents always wanted
the best for me.
They worry about me even
though they have gone so far away.
That's why they found you
and sent you to me.
Thanks for coming
in my life, Suraj.
Jenny!
Excuse me, I'm looking
for Jenny Mathias.
Oh! Okay. Ask the doctor.
Okay, thank you, sir.
Excuse me doctor,
I'm with Jenny Mathias.
- Oh, Hi.
- Is she okay?
It was a little cut, not too much.
She was lucky you know,
because the piece didn't dig in.
- Can I take her home?
- Sure!
But remember, next time,
don't leave her alone. Alright?
Okay?
- Thank you, doctor.
- You're welcome.
Oh! Why did you come?
I was about to come home.
It's nothing!
It's just a cut.
It's cornea damage,
causing visual impairment.
But, sight can be restored in
such cases with an operation.
Really?
Yes!
But, you have already
delayed it too much.
What do you mean?
That means, 15 - 20 days.
One month at the maximum.
After that, even this operation
would be useless.
If the operation is done
within a month, then...
can the sight in her eyes
be restored?
Yes, but we will have
to import the cornea from the US.
What will the expenditure be?
Come on, suraj.
Suraj!
Come on.
Come on, breathe!
Breathe!
Defend yourself,
get him on the jaw!
Why don't you elbow him?
Come on! Don't hold back.
Come on!
Suraj!
Yes.
- Well done.
- Good job, my boy.
Until Jenny gets her eyes back...
I will keep thinking
about this, Omi.
I need a lot of money for that.
Suraj, who doesn't need money?
But, Srikant is not
in the right shape.
Neither can he help you, nor can I.
But, you can't let that affect
you, friend.
And you will never get
any money fighting for them.
I saw you fighting, not bad.
One should not be angry with a man
who sells his soul for money...
one should pity him.
I trained him for 2 years.
But, he still left and joined
Gavin's club for money.
Let's see how long
he stays there.
I got what I didn't get in 2 years,
within 2 weeks.
When you are fed up of
fighting this small fights...
and feel like fighting
with a real man...
then come to me.
You will get money.
And all your desires
will also be fulfilled.
Think about it, there will be pain.
Jenny will be more hurt,
if she touches it.
Your wish!
I was thinking about you.
I've told you so many times not to
do all this work when I am not home.
But, I can't get anything done
when you are around.
Suraj! What happened?
Are you alright, Suraj?
What happened?
Nothing.
Oh! I'm absolutely fine.
100%.
If I could see...
would you still lie to me like this?
I knew you would come.
I didn't know
it would be that soon.
Drink.
I need money, Sikandar.
It is need that takes
a man to his destination.
Tell me, what is your need?
300,000.
That's all? If you work
at Gavin's club...
then your needs will be
fulfilled in 3 or 4 months.
Jenny doesn't have
that much time, Sikandar.
I need that money in 15 days.
Gavin never gives such a big advance
even to family!
Sit!
Look, now the matter
is about love.
So Sikandar
will have to do something.
If you need a bigger rate...
then you have to do a bigger job.
I will do it.
Cheers!
Why are you crying?
Okay dear, sorry!
I shouldn't have brought you here.
I'm not crying because
of that, silly!
Then?
I'm crying because you didn't bring
me to such a nice place before!
Come on, let's do it again!
Single ticket, double fun! Come on!
What happened?
The fun would actually have doubled,
if only you were able to see.
You are my eyes!
Come on.
You knew that the operation
would have cured your sight.
What's happened to you?
Come on!
You knew that the cornea
could be imported from the US.
Yes, I knew! But, I also knew...
that it would be impossible to
collect so much money. Let's go.
You could have told me at least.
What's happened to you?
Why are you wasting so much time?
The park will close. Come on!
The doctor has said that...
you have only 15 - 20 days.
- Don't you want...
- No, I don't want.
I don't want to see a world
where my mom and dad don't exist.
Wherever your parents are, they...
will be very sad.
Imagine, how happy they will be,
if you can see again.
And don't you want to
see this silly guy's face?
But where will we get
so much money from?
Work!
Can you take a life?
Sorry!
Can you give your life?
There is freestyle in Langkawi.
Will you play?
That's why I'm here.
But, you have to fight to lose.
And there is no need to tell you
that it is completely illegal!
If you get caught,
the entire responsibility is yours...
and only yours.
I am thinking,
that if I get my sight back...
then we will go to that
lake first.
Where I've laid the
foundation of our home.
Then, I will look at Oscar.
I will look at the sunset,
I will look at the water in the lake.
And me?
I would have already seen you, silly!
- Can I ask you something?
- Yes.
Suppose I don't turn out like you...
How?
- The way you think I am.
- How do I imagine you?
I mean... you know... like...
You mean, the silly
and ugly types?
- You'll be terribly disappointed!
- Really?
Because, neither am I ugly,
nor am I silly!
'One more thing...'
'if you don't want your
family to land in any trouble...'
'then you have to destroy every
identification that you have.'
'Even your family's life can be
endangered in such illegal fights.'
'So destroy every identification
of yours before you leave.'
'So that nobody can trace you.'
'You will get a new name and
passport within two days.'
'You will never leave your
girlfriend for a new job?'
'Promise?'
You've gone out of your mind!
Will you fight for that
ungrateful, Gavin?
- Just this once!
- Oh, really?
And what if you're finished
during that one time?
Suraj, the fight
you're talking about...
has 6 out of 10 fighters dying.
The rest are crippled for life.
Otherwise also, I'm not alive
in the real sense of the word!
I cannot bring
back Jenny's parents.
But, if I can bring back
her sight, perhaps...
my guilt will be a little less.
And about having
broken arms and legs...
I am a cripple now, brother.
Your love has finally
gotten in the way!
Actually, love has saved me, Omi!
Take care of yourself.
Can I say something, Suraj?
When the bandage
on my eyes is opened...
don't come in front
of me immediately.
I don't want to suddenly come face to
face with the biggest joy in my life.
And I also want...
that you should be with me
when my sight is restored.
Will you be there, Suraj?
Promise me!
What are you thinking? Promise!
Sarfaraz Ahmed...
your new name...
Need another ID, the passport.
Your new phone with new sim card.
'Foreign language.'
Cheating with me...
Normally I don't like
to dirty my hands.
But I know when I have to.
Now won't you say,
that's why you came.
To die.
I hope you remember that.
Take him away!
Get him ready for the fight.
7 minutes!
You have 7 minutes to die.
What to do? The rules of
the game are like this.
This fight does not stop until
either man's breath's stops.
And your breath is
mortgaged with me.
From now on each breath of
yours will dance to my tunes.
7 minutes!
You will make this game
interesting for 7 minutes.
And then you can
prepare to lose.
That means, get ready to die!
But you are a very lucky man, Suraj.
Because, your fight
is not with an enemy.
But, with your best friend.
So cheer up, come on!
Soup for you.
Did Suraj call?
No.
Nurse, please check again.
He must have surely called!
Hit me.
Come on, hit me man.
'For 7 minutes you will
make this game interesting.'
'And then you can prepare to lose.'
'Get ready to die!'
What an amazing girl she must be...
if you're ready to
give your life for her.
Your sacrifice and
her youth won't go in vain.
I will take care of her.
Yes!
Wait!
He came here to die anyway.
But, our loss will not be fulfilled...
by his death his life will do it.
And this time you better do it right!
'I give you one more
chance to live your life.'
'And if my goods do not reach intact.'
'Be ready to lose
your life this time.'
- Suraj?
- No!
Take care.
"Nobody knows why God
kept these eyes apart"
"My eyes are brimming
over crying and dying for you"
"They have forgotten
the ways of life"
"Nobody knows why God
kept these eyes apart"
"I am all alone in
this crowded world"
"I have lost myself,
having lost you after finding you"
"I am all alone in
this crowded world"
"I have lost myself,
having lost you after finding you"
"These days are as
dark as kohl without you"
"Even the stars are
dim during the night"
- I have reached.
- Sample?
It's safe.
Where should I come?
I have very little time.
You don't have to come now,
Suraj, you have to go.
Because,
you really have very little time.
Excuse me, Dr. Aakash?
Nurse!
Suraj?
He came for my eye surgery.
You must be remembering him.
Can we get something
for her from CCTV?
We have the CCTV footage.
But it's only for 3 days.
I'm sure you'll be able
to organize it. Please, doctor.
- It's really important for me.
- I'm so sorry.
"My eyes have turned to stone,
looking at the roads and waiting"
"How did pain come
to the lips of happiness?"
"My eyes have turned to stone,
looking at the roads and waiting"
"How did pain come
to the lips of happiness?"
"My dreams sulk, our hearts
joined and then my heart has broken"
"Even the destiny lines
on my palms have broken!"
"Nobody knows why God
kept these eyes apart"
Hi! May I help you?
Hi! I'm Kabir.
I have heard a lot about
you and your creative soldiers.
I have to admit your designs
are just as beautiful as you.
Thank you, but this work is
done by the children of the institute.
- Come inside.
- Someone's trying to be modest.
You are the one teaching these kids.
Anyway, I own a fitness club.
I need some gifts for my staff
for New Year's. Is it possible?
Yes! Absolutely!
Do you just want to
go through the brochure?
When I see you so happy,
I am sure of one thing.
What?
That you are not married!
Sorry!
But, I am married
and very happy.
Anyway, friends?
Friends!
Excuse me.
Hello!
Yes, Dr. Kidwai.
No, I'm much better now.
Thank you, I'm fine.
Yes, it's been really long.
I'll see you this weekend for sure.
- Hello Jenny!
- Hi!
- I haven't seen you for long.
- Been busy.
Dadu... how are you?
'Foreign language.'
Yeah.
My ankle pain still not recovered...
Okay, let me check.
Paining? Don't worry,
I'm here now.
I'll be coming every weekend.
Okay?
- Thank you.
- Don't worry.
And who's here?
Hello!
You're Indian, Pakistani or Malay?
Indian!
Okay!
Hi! I'm Jenny.
Won't you say something?
He has not spoken...
one word until now.
Okay! Let's see your case.
Muscle Spasm.
The recommended treatment...
for your case is a massage.
Let me check.
Your leg muscles are pretty weak.
It looks like you've been
in a very big accident.
Let me see, if you need
traction for your back.
May, I turn you?
Easy. Easy.
Okay.
Your back muscles
have deteriorated!
Sarfaraz Ahmad.
But don't worry,
you'll be fine.
You'll be back running around,
like you were earlier.
Actually you know,
I am not a doctor.
But, I have learnt
physiotherapy.
If destiny had been with me...
I would have had a physiotherapy
centre of my own.
Anyways, I'll be coming
every weekend.
And this is my card.
So call me,
if you need me earlier.
Take care.
Don't worry,
you'll be fine.
Bye!
"So much uncertainty"
"So much loneliness"
"Your stubbornness
twirls in my words"
"I have sunk in the perfume
of your breath"
"I have not been
released from love"
"I found the highs of heaven
in your shelter"
"You are the beauty of this world"
Thank you.
I will have your order delivered
to you by tomorrow. Okay.
Great. Pleasure working with you.
With you as well.
Excuse me.
Can you do me a favor?
There are no favors
in friendship, just order.
I'm getting late. Will you just take
care of my shop for 5 minutes?
- Sure!
- I'll just go across and get some...
medicines for Romeo.
Romeo?
My turtle.
Romeo, Romeo! If only my parents
had given me such a lovely name.
- Then, you would have crawled, too!
- I'd do what you wanted me to.
How stupid!
Come on, Oscar.
Let's go baby, come.
May I help you?
Are you looking out for something?
Night Jasmine.
It only blooms at night.
It's available only at
our shop in this whole area.
Storm?
Should I pack it?
I'll just pack it for you.
Oscar, wait! Oscar!
Oscar!
What are you doing?
Behave yourself. I am sorry.
Really, sorry. He normally
doesn't behave like this.
I don't know what happened to
him! Oscar, come on!
May I help you?
Yeah!
Are you okay?
You are?
Aren't you the same man,
that patient from the hospital?
Should I drop you somewhere?
"You are my winters and
I am like the sun"
"I find peace in your arms"
"Love is like a musical instrument"
"I found bliss in your shelter"
"I found you, found you!"
"You are beauty of this world"
Sit!
You're back so soon.
Here, I have earned 50 ringgits
for you in 5 minutes.
Not bad. One second.
Where's Romeo?
Did somebody come here?
The man with the crutch?
Yes!
He was the one who
bought the night jasmine.
You know what?
I almost mistook him as
one of my favorite boxers.
Storm!
But I felt it was him.
But, he didn't react when
I called him by that name.
You know what?
I'm sure it was him.
I was looking at him,
but he didn't hear me at all.
Silly boy!
Suraj!
Hello!
Dr. Kidwai.
Hi! This is Jenny.
Doctor, I need to know about
that patient on bed number 13.
Yes, Sarfaraz.
What happened?
What happened to Sarfaraz?
What?
He left yesterday?
Suraj!
You done so much
for me quietly.
Now, when it's my turn...
you let go of my hand
and were going away.
It's all the fault of these eyes.
I could read a man
without my eyes, but...
I couldn't recognize him when
I could see him in front of me.
Why?
Why did you do this to me?
Because, I'm silly and ugly.
Jignesh is so much better than you...
he never troubled his
Bindiya as much as this.