Sir, these attacks are
not just on our agents
in fact, it's an attack on RAW.
Dubey, how many of our
agents are still active in China?
Now, 17.
I'm sure they will be attacked, too.
Sir, if our agents keep dying,
then we'll know about
the Chinese army's movement
only after they completely
enter Arunachal Pradesh.
I know this is a matter
of National Security.
Whoever is doing this,
he's trying to weaken RAW.
But who could do this, and why?
Only he can answer this question,
but we have to find him.
How will we catch him, sir?
I'm getting you five acres
of land in the heart of Mumbai.
You can easily make
1,000 to 1,500 apartments.
That's fine, but what about Manohar?
I will deal with Manohar.
Did you come here to buy an apartment?
No... I've come for you.
You've a court hearing today.
Did you forget?
Are you crazy?
You think you can drag me out
in front of my men?
Really? Without your uniform?
You think I would've spared
you if I was in uniform?
-We'll come later.
-No, no.
Go deal with him.
Wait.
My wife died five years ago.
Since then, I've lost my mind.
I tried really hard to die,
but no-one could kill me.
Maybe today is my lucky day.
There are ten to twelve of you...
and I am only one.
Maybe you can kill me.
I forgot to tell you one thing.
I will die. But I will
take a couple of you with me.
Especially you!
Anyone else?
Where are you going?
Wait! Don't be scared!
Hey! Gotya, kill him!
Shoot him, Gotya! Kill him!
Kill him! You're dead, now!
You're a dead man!
Wait, wait!
-Start the car.
-Let's go.
You son of a bitch.
Come on, start the car.
Do something.
Start the car.
Let's go. Let's go.
What are you doing?
Come on, do something. Move it!
What's going on?
-What's this?
-Oh my God!
Drive! Drive!
What are you doing?
Spare me! Let go of the car!
Let go.
Let go of the car.
Shall we?
Sir, what do you have to say
about the people that died in China?
Look, our Intelligence has found out that
the people who died in China
were involved in criminal activities.
And they died due to an internal conflict.
But they were RAW agents, sir.
The media has sensationalized
this news for no reason.
As you heard,
the government clearly states that
India has no connection
with these incidents.
The people killed in Beijing,
Shanghai and Guangzhou
weren't Indian citizens at all.
China has maintained
silence on these incidents,
so commenting on these incidents
will be difficult right now.
Is it done?
Yes, it's done.
How long will this continue?
As long as people like
Niranjan are running free.
Which means forever.
I'm a policeman.
If I don't do something, then who will?
Why? Aren't there other policemen?
Is it your responsibility
to bring all criminals to justice?
One day this heart
Will stop beating
Be with me until then
No matter how long this night is
I will be yours forever
Just give an indication
Where do I go without you?
Try to understand
I will tightly embrace your shadow
Just give an indication
You are watching ABP News.
Mr. Yashwardhan Singh, courier for you.
A newspaper in China
has confirmed that
the people killed in Beijing, Shanghai
and Guangzhou were Indian citizens.
This incident will definitely affect
the relationship between India and China.
One thing is clear. RAW agents
will never be known for their work
even if they sacrifice
their life for the country.
RAW agency functions in complete secrecy,
so it will be very difficult to understand
whether the people
who died were Indian agents.
The question is whether
Harish Chaturvedi, Suraj Rawat
and Arun Gupta died in an accident,
or if there's a mystery behind it.
The CBI is still investigating this case
and we hope to learn more about it soon.
Get up, you drunkard.
Come on.
-Have we arrived?
-We haven't even started yet.
We've been sitting here for 30 minutes.
-I won't drive.
-Why?
And if I do, you would be
the one to arrest me, my cop!
"Cop".
And what are you?
So, tell me, Mr. Bond,
where are you being posted?
Tell me. What if you die?
The way you beat up the bad guys...
I'm sure that you'll be the first to die.
Yeah.
I'm a cop. If I die,
I will be called a martyr.
If anything happens to you...
then the government will say,
"He wasn't an Indian citizen at all."
Then you tell them.
You tell everyone
that I am India's best citizen.
Sir, none of them was an accident.
The Chinese agency learned
that they were RAW agents,
and that got them killed.
Someone is definitely
leaking our identity.
But how can a police
officer have this information?
Yash is not an ordinary officer.
You've been called in.
Come.
Please share whatever
information you have with him.
Harish sent this
book to me, not him.
Do you know what this means?
Harish didn't trust RAW.
There are two people in this room
whom I trust the most.
Harish has written
"2012" in the year 2016.
It's not a mistake. It's a clue.
It's not a date.
It's a page number.
Pages six, eight and twelve.
The first letter on page six is S.
On page eight, it's P.
-And on page 12--
-Y.
We all know there's someone
among us who is a spy for China.
Do you know where he is?
No.
Harish knew.
It takes years to make a spy network.
We must find that man.
Sir, I will find that man.
Let me go to Budapest.
You shouldn't take such complicated
matters personally, Yash.
I'm taking this personally.
That's why I won't turn over.
It's clear that one of your
men is leaking this information.
That is possible.
But please understand, we cannot carry
out such missions on foreign soil.
Times have changed,
and so has the country.
Now, we strike right at the heart.
And you're not trained
for such missions.
Are those who trained alive?
You won't regret sending him there.
Look, Yash, you will go there
with the Eastern European in charge, KK.
They've created quite a network
in the last two years.
Sir. I need your signature on this.
Yash, go and meet KK. I will join you.
Did you counter-check
the information Martinez sent?
Where can I find KK?
Send me the printouts of these, please.
I'm KK. Kamaljeet Kaur.
What was that "oh"?
Were you expecting a male officer?
Yes.
So, you don't think girls are capable?
All I know is that
KK could be a name of a guy.
By the way, who are you?
We've a lead on the China case.
Someone's leaking the identities
of our agents from the Budapest Embassy.
Yash is a police officer.
You two will go together.
I should be accompanied
by a trained RAW agent.
-Why this police officer?
-Because the lead came through him.
This is Brijesh Verma.
Our HRD Minister.
He began his career
in 1988, as an IS officer.
In 2012, he became the cabinet secretary.
He remained in this post for two years.
And entered politics in 2014.
He contested the election
in Meerut and became an MP.
A year later, the HRD minister.
Sir, this is irrelevant information.
We're wasting our time.
It's essential for you
to know about the HRD Minister.
Because he's going to Budapest
for the Indo-Hungarian summit.
You two will go there,
pretending to look after his security.
That's the RAW's way of doing things.
This is Naren Kaushik,
our ambassador for Hungary.
He will assist you with anything you need.
All the details
of the Budapest Embassy staff are in here.
SIM cards, too.
I'm going to Berlin three days later
for a security conference.
If needed, I'll come to Budapest.
-Sir, who is leading this team?
-You will, of course.
-What is RAW's yearly turnover?
-What?
They take good care of their employees.
I bought the business
class ticket myself.
Then you must have booked
a suite for yourself in the hotel.
With your money.
Only film-stars live in hotels.
We're going to the safe house.
This place is called
a safe-house for a reason.
Because no-one knows we're here.
Anyway, the ambassador
will be here in ten to fifteen minutes.
We need to discuss further plans.
How did you get the address to this place?
The ambassador emailed it to me.
Anything else?
Yash, what are you doing?
Come on.
Have you lost your mind, Yash?
This is not the way--
Your job is done. They are dead.
You knew there was a bomb?
If he can hack the agency's system
and get the agents names,
then he can read
the Ambassador's mail, too.
That's the Mumbai Police's
way of doing things.
-Where now?
-Where the film stars stay.
Yes, but whoever it was
thinks we're dead.
I'll check the footage and records
of all the employees
and zero in on the suspects.
After that, we'll keep
surveillance on him and find him.
Where are you going?
You work your way
and I'll work my way.
I've prepared a list of suspects.
And zeroed in on these three.
We're here to work, not to go pub-hopping.
He's your man.
Not possible.
He has a disciplined routine.
He used to work in Belgium.
Never missed office.
Always punctual. Makes good money, too.
No connection with the Chinese.
No alcohol or cigarettes, either.
No girlfriend. He'd go
straight home from the office.
He's too clean.
These are my three suspects.
There's been a considerable change
in his behavior in the last two months.
For someone who never worked overtime,
what made him so hard-working
that he works overtime every day?
He married this girl three months ago.
She's a resident of Hong Kong.
They didn't meet before,
or even go on a date.
So, why did they suddenly get married?
I suspect him the most.
Before Budapest, he worked for three years
at the Indian Embassy in China.
And he handles the Chinese desk over here.
Like you said, he hacked
our entire system from Budapest.
We'll send a coded email
to the Ambassador from a fake ID
stating that a Chinese embassy official
has agreed to be our agent.
And he's coming to meet us
at the Glasshouse Art Gallery.
And whoever our guy is,
he will definitely decode our email.
And if our suspicion is true,
he will show up.
You are right.
He will definitely come there.
Any time now.
Thank you.
I told you he'd come, Yash.
Ma'am, he's making a call.
Hold on.
He's not making a call,
he's taking pictures.
Yash, I...
I'll ask the questions.
Yes, ma'am.
That's my personal phone.
You can't use it.
-Yash, where are you?
-KK, your plan was good,
but you got the wrong guy.
-Let Amit go.
-What? Why?
The right guy never
went inside the gallery.
Who?
You're wasting your time.
I've already arrested Amit.
Check the CCTV footage.
I'm going to Shiv's house.
-What were you doing in the gallery?
-I...
Someone forwarded me an email
which was sent to the Ambassador.
-And it was written--
-Someone forwarded you the mail?
Yes!
-You, show me the CCTV footage.
-Yes, ma'am.
This is your man.
Hello.
Yash, you were right about Shiv.
-Where are you?
-Behind his building.
-I'm right outside his door.
-He's not inside.
But there is someone inside.
It's you.
I was scared for a moment.
What happened?
Where did he go?
I don't know.
Well, he didn't come downstairs.
That means...
You have another opportunity, today.
You can't shoot?
I definitely can.
Want to see?
You're hiding something from me.
What do you want to say?
I feel that Shiv knows you.
Of course you do.
He's my fiancé, after all.
Why did he say that you can't shoot?
It's hard to believe that
this guy could do something like this.
Where did you recruit him from?
We placed an ad for a consultant.
He had all the necessary qualifications.
He's from Belgium. He speaks
Hungarian and French.
Did you notice anything
suspicious about him?
Not at all.
He's hard-working
and good at what he does.
He used to mind his own business.
I thought it was a big plus.
So, he has no family?
He was only three years old
when his parents passed away.
He grew up in an orphanage in Faridabad.
Later, he went to America
for higher studies on a scholarship.
Anyway, we've spoken
to the Hungarian authorities.
The paperwork's complete, too.
You can take him to India tonight.
Postpone our travel.
I want to interrogate him.
Our orders are that we must
immediately take him to India.
He'll be interrogated there.
If we interrogate him now,
we might save someone's life.
You follow orders. I'm going in.
You forget who is leading the team.
Look, I know Harish was your friend.
But the other agents
had friends and family, too.
This is not a personal fight.
We found nothing.
We found this when we checked his clothes,
but there's nothing in here either.
If you're done ogling at me,
can we get to my clothes?
No, no, no. These are...
These clothes can’t be
your choice, Ms. Kaur.
But yes, often people in uniforms
have bad taste in clothes.
Don't talk about uniforms.
Why?
Because I’m a traitor, right?
Let's not argue
over patriotism and treachery.
You will lose.
Are you done? Shall we go?
Wear your clothes.
Or else I will drag you
to India like this.
We've left the embassy.
It will take us almost
an hour to get to the airport.
One hour.
This will be the longest
hour of your life.
We won't get to the airport. Ask me why.
Ask.
Because there is a problem with our team.
What a peculiar team.
A rich brat RAW agent who can't shoot
and a Police Officer
who couldn't save his wife.
How will they save their agents?
You'd better be careful, Ms. Kaur.
Ms. Kaur, anyone who has any kind
of relationship with him ends up dead.
Take Harish, for instance.
That's what he wants.
And as far as relationships are concerned,
Ms. Kaur's were always in a mess.
You know, when she was 18,
her dad was going around
with another 18-year-old girl.
Like this.
She was 18, and so was that girl.
How would Ms. Kaur feel?
Poor thing--
Sir. Sir, please handle her.
Sir, handle her.
I hate violence.
That reminds me. Two more
of your men are going to die.
Shut up. Another word
and you'll regret it.
If you hadn't shut me up, he could've
been saved. This one's on you, ma'am.
There are two bikes.
That's right, there are
two bikes. Go faster!
What are you doing, sir?
One's dead. Can you save the other one?
Unbelievable, one says "shut up",
the says "talk"...
I'm telling you, this team isn't right!
-Tell me.
-Yash! What are you doing?
Where will the next agent be killed?
Yash, pull him inside, now.
Talk!
Thirty minutes. He will die in 30 minutes.
And only you can save him.
Thirty minutes...
-So, he's somewhere in Budapest.
-That's good, that's good.
So what if Ms. Kaur can't shoot?
At least she can use her brain.
Now, use your brain on this.
One angel, four paths.
How will you save your friend?
Take it inside that building.
We'll have to wait here for a while.
KK, there.
Who are you?
We need your help.
I don't have time for 20 questions.
Tell me where they'll kill
the other agent.
Tell me.
They are already scared. Don't!
"One angel, four paths."
"One angel, four paths"!
We still have ten minutes.
We've only ten minutes to save
the next agent, Yash.
Hurry up, Yash!
We don't have much time.
Where is he?
You're at the right place.
But unfortunately, you're 20 feet above.
Heroes' Square is also a metro station.
He's dead.
Poor guy. He was a nice man.
He use to flirt a bit,
but at the end... he was a man.
Yash, what are you doing?
We want him alive.
We wanted our man alive, not him!
Why?
Our men, our country...
Money?
How much money is enough
to let our own men die?
You think I'm doing this for money?
Then why are you doing this?
What do you want?
You two can't give me what I want.
We've already missed one flight.
We can't miss another.
It must be really hard
to tolerate failure, right?
By now, you two must be accustomed...
to failure.
Two losers, here to catch a winner.
RAW should’ve sent someone more capable.
Here comes the cavalry.
First the apartment, now here.
How do they know where we are?
What? Don't look at me.
You have my phone.
And you guys already checked
all the holes in my body.
How could I tell anyone?
I doubt it's one of you.
Someone's dirty.
Where are you going, Yash?
The tunnel is closed.
I know.
Kudos to you two.
I mean, that was good.
But I'll give you a chance
to be impressed by me.
At the airport.
I mean... there were
so many men on the way,
so I'm sure the entire army's
waiting at the airport.
Who says we're going to the airport?
Where are you taking me?
This helicopter will land
directly on the airport's tarmac.
Another agent of ours
was killed in Malaysia.
Bring Shiv to India
as soon as you can.
Now we'll never know how many
names he gave to the Chinese.
Someone was definitely
telling them about our location.
How else did they know we were
coming here, and not to the airport.
But who could it be?
Something's wrong.
You're thinking too much, Yash.
They tried to save him all day.
-So why did they kill him suddenly?
-It's simple.
When they realized they couldn't stop Shiv
from being taken to India,
they killed him.
Why didn't they kill us?
-Did you check his bullet wound?
-No, why?
Sir, nature is just amazing.
Have you heard about the Medusa Spider?
I hadn't, either.
The venom of this spider
can stop a man's heartbeat for 30 minutes.
But next time, your
heartbeat will stop for good.
I mean, you're such a player.
You even have one-liners for your defeat.
How is Ms. Kaur?
She must be upset.
-Take care of her.
-You think about yourself.
How long do you think
they can protect you?
I mean, you won't give up.
This game's gonna be fun.
Killing six people is a game for you?
I didn't start this game, sir.
But I'll definitely finish it.
By the way, don't forget
to thank Ms. Kaur on my behalf.
None of this would've
been possible without her.
Don't be surprised, sir.
Time is a game-changer.
Check Ms. Kaur's watch
when you've got time.
What's wrong?
What are you doing, Yash?
Anjan, Shiv could be anywhere in Europe.
Catching him is impossible right now.
KK, there was a tracker in your watch.
What exactly happened, that day?
It's you.
I was scared for a moment.
Quietly hand over the laptop
and come with me to the embassy.
"Quietly"?
That's one thing I can't do.
And you are three minutes
and 30 seconds late.
-I just deleted everything.
-Stay there.
Do you want to check?
This is all my fault.
KK, we must order an inquiry on you.
Come back. I'm sending a replacement.
No.
What?
KK won't go back.
KK is a capable officer and I trust her.
But that tracker?
He must have slipped it in
when she was unconscious.
It could've happened to anyone.
We will catch him.
What?
One thing's clear.
He's giving them one name after another.
Surely, the Chinese
are giving him something.
Yes, but what?
-Yes, sir.
-KK, there's been a development.
We've been trying to turn Chinese official
for the past six months.
He'll give us Shiv's location in one hour.
Where are you going? Didn't you hear?
We'll get his location soon.
WhatsApp me when you get it.
You think I'm doing this for money?
Then why are you doing this?
What do you want?
-Where are you, sir?
-In your house.
When did you last clean?
Why do you always by unannounced?
If you'd alerted me in advance,
I would've arranged for tea and snacks.
Do you need something,
or did you call to waste my time?
Sir, do you know
the biggest problem with Indians?
So, you did call to waste my time.
We Indians never do our jobs ourselves.
We keep delegating them.
Look. A poor Chinese man ended up dead
trying to give away my location.
Too bad.
How about some advice? For free?
Stop looking for me.
Marry Ms. Kaur and settle down
in some hill-station.
You two are old enough, now.
Here's my advice for you.
Sell your home...
and get used to living
in a room without windows.
Yes, boss.
-I'm listening, boss.
-I've a job for you.
Yash, where are you?
-That Chinese official...
-He's dead.
What? How?
How would a RAW agent find him now?
Through my Hungarian contact, Martinez.
I'll call Anjan, you talk to Martinez.
Martinez never takes calls. Only texts.
This is the address he gave me.
Where is Martinez?
-You want a martini?
-Where is Martinez?
Virai, where's Martinez?
Looking for Martinez?
Upstairs.
Where is Martinez?
There's Martinez.
-What do you mean, "oh"?
-I thought--
You thought it was a man.
So, you don't think girls are capable?
O sweetheart... my eyes
Have been yearning for you
O sweetheart... you weren't here
And I held on to your memories
O sweetheart... my eyes
Have been yearning for you
O sweetheart... you weren't here
And I held on to your memories
How do I explain
The emotions stirring in my heart?
The days and nights are unbearable
I had to tell you
What's in my heart
The days and nights are unbearable
I had to tell you
What's in my heart
So I say this to you,
I love you
As you looked at me,
my heart felt an uproar
Your intoxication
Is slowly growing on me
And stealing my senses
Stealing my senses
The days and nights are unbearable
I had to tell you
What's in my heart
The days and nights are unbearable
I had to tell you
What's in my heart
So I say this to you,
I love you
She doesn't have a clue
about where she is.
How could she tell us about Shiv?
We need to find someone named
Shiv Sharma.
No problem.
I have a condition. I don't want money.
I want to bang him.
What is she saying?
-She'll help us, but in exchange--
-Just say "yes" to whatever she wants.
Finding Shiv is more important.
Yes!
You can bang him.
When?
-She's asking when?
-As soon as she does the job.
As soon as you give us the location.
Tonight.
Something's fishy about her.
She hasn't given us
any wrong information to date.
She'll give us the location tonight.
How do you know?
-She seems to be in a hurry.
-What for?
Ask him to take a shower.
He smells like shit.
What did she say now?
She wants you to take a bath.
Clothes for you.
Why did you do that?
-You want to have sex on this?
-What are you saying?
-I'll take that off--
-What are you doing?
-Don't be shy!
-Go away!
You cheat!
Moron!
I've had enough of you, get lost.
-We had a deal!
-Get lost.
You're a cheat!
Wait!
What's wrong? That was quick.
-So that was her condition?
-Yes. What's wrong?
Didn't anything happen?
Have you lost your mind?
You're a deal-breaker!
Now this will cost you double.
No problem.
-Moron!
-Go away!
Rascal.
Shiv is in Holloko Village.
It's still hot.
He couldn't have gone too far.
He must be somewhere around.
-Yes, Samant.
-Shiv Sharma was in this orphanage,
but he died ten years ago.
Hello?
Balraj, talk to the home
minister if you have to.
Yes, Yash?
Sir, that man is not Shiv Sharma.
He might not even be an orphan.
Whoever he is,
he stole Shiv Sharma's identity.
Use all your resources in India.
Start with the orphanage
and find out everything you
can about this imposter in 24 hours.
Mhatre, assemble a team.
Good job.
Are you crazy?
Why did you stay in the village?
Because if they didn't see me
they wouldn't trust you.
Now, they'll trust whatever you tell them.
Smart!
And hitting those men was a good touch.
See you!
Now what do you want?
He got away. We need his next location.
-More money or get out.
-What is she saying this time?
Will she do the job or not?
She will.
Where do you want me to send them?
Send them to Berlin.
What?
I know you don't drink coffee.
Can I ask you something?
Why did you support me
in front of Anjan the other day?
Because I'm crazy.
Completely insane.
In 2013 we received a tip-off...
that a Naxal-terrorist was
hiding in a lodge in Lajpat Nagar.
We arrived at the scene, he ran for it.
I could've shot him,
but that day, I couldn't.
Two days later, he killed five people.
Since that day, I...
Harish and I were childhood friends.
We even went to school
and college together.
In fact, we even joined
the force together.
He would often joke about
how crazy I am.
Complete lunatic.
I thought I'd definitely get killed
and he would investigate my murder.
Neither he nor I ever imagined
that I'd be investigating his murder.
You were right.
His name isn't Shiv.
His real name is Rudra Pratap Singh.
His father, Karan Pratap Singh,
was an undercover agent for RAW in China.
The Chinese Intelligence Agency
found out that he was a RAW agent.
RAW disowned him
on our cabinet secretary's orders.
That's the world of spying.
If you're caught, we don't know you.
Which is why he assumed the name
and identity of his deceased friend.
So that he could take revenge against RAW.
-When did this happen?
-2012.
I'll call you
as soon as I reach to Berlin.
-He isn't trying to take revenge on RAW.
-What?
He killed four of our agents.
If this isn't revenge, then what is it?
It's not that simple.
He wants to use RAW
to get to someone else.
Who?
-Where are you going now?
-To find the answer to your question.
Yes, dad, I'm just
leaving for the airport.
When are you reaching India?
When is your flight?
Son, it seems like
I won't be able to make it.
Please don't say you're tied up with work.
I... I wanted to come to Seattle, instead.
Stroll into your office,
see how you're working.
Later we could've gone for a walk.
We could've had a beer together.
We never had a beer together, did we?
Yes, dad, but why are you saying this now?
Did something happen?
I hid something from you.
No, I hid something from all of you.
What? Dad, I don't understand
what you're saying.
For the last 30 years...
I've been not been working
for some tech company...
but for RAW.
Please come now. Things will
be fine when we meet again.
What do you mean, "it's too late"?
Why are you saying such things?
Please just come. Everything will be fine.
Look after your mother and sister.
The media has turned this into a farce.
Karan Pratap is not a RAW Agent.
Karan Pratap has no connection
with RAW whatsoever.
But his family claims that he was
working for RAW for the last 30 years.
Look, we even heard
that he was working for China.
He was selling India's secrets to China.
Now, who do we believe?
Are you trying to say
that Karan Pratap was a traitor?
You're all smart people. You know best.
Your father's bank balance
has been transferred in your names.
And the locker, as well.
There isn't much in it.
Just some jewelry.
I guess your father was
too honest, wasn't he?
I met with the Cabinet Secretary.
He said there's nothing that can be done.
I tried to explain that I have two kids.
But he said...
"You'll have to live
with the label of 'traitor'."
You were right.
His name isn't Shiv.
His real name is Rudra Pratap Singh.
His father, Karan Pratap Singh,
was an undercover agent for RAW in China.
Let's not argue
over patriotism and treachery.
You will lose.
The Chinese Intelligence Agency
found out that he was a RAW agent.
RAW disowned him
on our cabinet secretary's orders.
You think I'm doing this for money?
When did this happen?
2012.
2012!
This game's gonna be fun.
Killing six people is a game for you?
I didn't start this game, sir.
2012.
In 2012, he became the cabinet secretary.
He contested the election
in Meerut and became an MP.
A year later, the HRD minister.
This is Brijesh Verma.
Our HRD Minister.
He began his career
in 1988, as an IS officer.
Look, even we heard
that he was working for China.
He was selling India's secrets to China.
Now, who do we believe?
Martinez just called. Rudra is in Berlin.
Anjan is arriving there tomorrow.
He's his next target.
Rudra isn't in Berlin. He's right here.
How do you know?
Because he wants to kill
the HRD Minister, Brijesh Verma.
Right here, in Budapest.
So, Rudra chose to be posted in Budapest
because this summit
was planned almost a year ago?
And sending us to Berlin
was one of his plans.
He knew that Anjan was going there.
That means Martinez...
-We must stop this summit, Yash.
-No.
If we stop this summit,
we'll never catch Rudra.
Are you going to let a minister die
just to catch Rudra?
We're going to save him.
We'll shoot him.
What?
The only difference is,
they will shoot to kill...
and we'll shoot to save.
What's the guarantee
that Rudra will be there?
He just will be.
Yash, finding him
there will be impossible.
When the bullets are fired,
only one man in the hall won't run.
Putting a minister's life
at stake like this is wrong.
Ministers should help their country
when in need.
I can't believe that you're
going to shoot the minister.
Not me. You.
Yash, I can't do it.
-We have no other options.
-Why don't you understand?
-I can't shoot.
-You can.
You cannot fail twice.
Thank you, everyone, for coming.
It gives me great pleasure
to welcome the Indian HRD Minister,
Mr. Brijesh Verma, to Hungary.
I'd like to call upon him to open
the first Indo-Hungarian Summit.
You cannot fail twice.
It's no use. I'm gonna kill
this bloody minister.
What nonsense is this? Who is he?
Karan Pratap's son.
-The one you had killed.
-Killed?
Thirty years.
Father dedicated 30 years
of his life to RAW and his country.
But what did he get in return?
He was labeled a traitor.
And died in disgrace.
Every RAW Agent knows
the consequences of being caught.
-Even your father.
-And my mom?
What was my mother's fault?
My mother killed herself because of you.
What he did to your family was wrong.
But you're doing the same thing.
If I have to ruin 100 more families
to get to him, I--
You're forgetting one thing.
I'm holding the gun.
And you're going to jail.
Do you know how many
undercover RAW agents there are
in China and Hong Kong?
Do you?
Seventeen!
And how many names do I know?
All of them.
All the names are up here.
How many are you going to deem traitors?
I will go to jail...
but I will give all the names
to the Chinese, just so I can kill you.
-Seventeen agents will die, unless--
-No!
Sir, they will die--
No more RAW agents will die, now.
I didn't shoot him to save you.
I saved those 17 RAW agents.
-What do you mean?
-Your life is still in danger.
What are you doing?
You must fix everything
that Rudra's mother
and the rest of the RAW
agent's family had to go through.
What do you mean?
I've done my duty, now. You do yours.
Do it, sir.
He's off the rails. He will kill you.
The government has taken
a very important step today.
Those RAW agents who
were deemed as traitors,
their names are being cleared.
Yes.
We ordered an inquiry
which led us to the understanding
that those RAW agents were not traitors.
In addition to clearing their names,
we will also compensate their families.
Karan Pratap Singh, Harish Chaturvedi,
Suraj Rawat, Arshad Khan, Manjeet Singh,
Rahul Rajput, Mahesh Deshpande,
and many more patriots like them
laid down their lives for this country.
Tonight, their families will be lighting
a lamp in their homes in your name.
Well, those RAW agents did their duty
and I'm just doing mine.
Don't forget, you're watching...
You finally learnt how to use your heart
along with your head.
-By the way, she's nice.
-Who?
Who are you talking to?
You're watching The Voice of Truth,
and with us is the HRD Minister,
Brijesh Verma...
No-one.
...who has raised his voice
in support of our RAW Agents.
And his voice is echoing
all over the country.
So, the Minister finally found a way.
Take care of yourself.
And for the first time, our government
hasn't just restored their honor,
but also their identity.
Our country is really changing.
I don't get it.
Why do only good people die?
Why do bad things happen to the good?
Those who should be crying are laughing.
Those who should be laughing are crying.
I've had enough of this.
I've stayed silent for too long.
Now, listen to the uproar in my heart.
Listen to my intentions.
Obsession is my nature
It's stubborn and I am high on it
And only I know where you belong
The game you just played...
You're going to lose
How long are you going to
Throw stones at
Us thinking we're glass
It's boiling in every vein
Listen up, it's saying...
It's going insane...
The color red... red
The country has changed.
Everything has changed.
If you slap us once...
we'll slap back 1,000 times.
If you try to intimidate us,
we will rip you apart.
We promise you, our force promises you.
Every bullet in my gun
Has your name on it
We won't miss our aim this time
We're determined
We never bow, nor
Can we ever betray
We will blow you away
We are ready
It's boiling in every vein
Listen up, it's saying...
It's going insane...
The color red... red
Force is a persistent feeling.
It's an emotion. It's an obsession.
It's our pride.
Force is a retaliation.
It's insanity.
It's martyrdom. It's a craze.
Force is a voice.
It's your voice. It's my voice.
It's our voice.
If we all scream together...
the world will have to listen.
So, scream.