We've little doubt
the cyclamen scanners at
Dover were attacked and
disabled so that the irradiated
body could be brought into
the country.
- Irradiated body of whom?
- The investigation is ongoing.
But the scale and sophistication
make us certain
that this was
state sponsored.
Russia remaining the prime
suspect -Remaining a suspect.
But there's no smoking gun.
The malware code could viably
point in multiple directions,
and the truck
had been scoured clean
of anything
forensically detectable.
We do, however,
have a cause of death.
He was force fed Polonium 210.
Russia may be behind this.
But with the backlash around
Jaiyou Energy's drilling and the ship
explosion, the Chinese
are furious with us too.
Or it could be misdirection
by another actor entirely.
We don't yet
have anything solid.
Whoever did this could
have brought a nuclear bomb
into this country
right under our noses.
Instead, they dumped the body of a
murdered man they knew we'd find.
- They're sending a message.
- And as soon as
we've identified the dead man,
we can try to decode it.
Maybe deduce who sent
it and for whom.
Then in the meantime
we just sit and wait.
Hoping you get a grip
on something solid
before this country suffers yet
another attack on Christ knows what.
We will continue to investigate
every possible avenue.
In terms of an attack,
we are facing a significantly
escalated domestic threat.
So I've asked Robert to convene
COBRAt 10.
Which I will be doing.
And you will be attending.
Of course people are angry.
After what we heard
about the cyber attack
on Dover last week
it is clear that this country
is under systematic assault
and the public's
lost all trust in this
government's ability to keep us
safe or to tell us the truth.
Well, speaking of the truth, you crossed
the floor to join Robert Sutherland...
Well, cross the floor
is hardly accurate.
I was advising in a policy
unit and I resigned
because I wanted nothing to do with the
government soaked in the blood of its own people.
And the Junction 23 Inquiry with
Lord Singer chosen to conduct it
makes an absolute
mockery of accountability.
So you're suggesting
inherent bias?
I'm suggesting that if
a government wanted to be
exonerated, they couldn't
find someone more reliable to
side with the establishment
against the will of the people,
which makes it hard not to
wonder if Lord Singer's been,
shall we say
singing for his supper.
'Cause I wanted nothing to do
with the government soaked in
the blood of its own people.
An insider blows the whistle.
And the public have lost all
trust in the government's
ability to keep us
safe or to tell us the truth.
We told you the truth,
the government is weak
and venal, a regime
which forced its army
to use live rounds
on its people.
And the Junction 23 inquiry
with Lord Singer
chosen to conduct it,
makes an absolute
mockery of accountability.
They couldn't find someone
more reliable to side with
the establishment against
the will of the people.
- Saving their own skin.
- Makes it hard not to wonder
if Lord Singer has been,
shall we say,
Singing for his supper.
A government which used
its weapons at J23
to send a message to us.
The people of this nation,
that we should be
too afraid to dissent,
to rise up ever again.
But we do not know fear.
Only these corrupt
glutted reptiles
will know fear,
for we shall rise up
for justice for our nation,
and teach it to them.
These enemies of the people.
And where we go,
our brothers will follow.
Francine Bridge.
Scourge of the Tories,
savior of democracy.
- Future of this nation.
- Okay stop it.
Convert to the heady nectar
of pumpkin spice latte.
- You didn't.
- Christ, I'm not a monster, double espresso.
Ever considered you
might have trust issues?
Only with journalists.
Saw you on the television
doing some of that politics.
- What do you think?
- I flipped back to Bake Off.
Hari, I want your opinion,
You were brilliant.
I mean it.
We've been trending.
Even the far right thinks
you're, well, right.
- What?
- Your mentions.
- Hang on.
- Wait, can't you just tell me?
OK, a lot of those accounts
have a St. George's Cross
and I'd stick a monkey
on the owners
enjoying at least two out
of Brexit, real ale and dogging.
Eleanor has provided me with
a report monitoring the rise of
far right online extremism.
Makes clear that in
the wake of recent events,
the rise has become a search.
Escalation of rhetoric,
hate, conspiracy, violence,
calls for insurrection.
We're seeing suspicion
over the Singer Report.
An increasing belief that Jiayou Energy's
sea-bed drilling set off the ship explosion
and the cyber attacks gives these sites at
drum to beat that the UK is weak, defenseless,
We should probably
ask intelligence
to do something about
those attacks.
One site, Firestorm, stands out
in prominence reach, vitriol.
And it's targeting those
it regards as most deserving
of summary justice:
The Home Secretary,
Foreign Secretary, Lord Singer.
The Prime Minister.
And his wife.
Rachel. Why?
Her links to Kostenko,
it doesn't matter
that it's just smoke.
If this is incitement, how does it
not come under the Terrorism Act?
Well, we're navigating a legal
minefield to find out, but um...
For Christ's sake, I've been
a Conservative MP for 30 years.
I've been screamed at,
egged, fruit-pelted, mud-pied.
So I'm afraid I just can't
muster the willies
over some pallid
little bedwetter.
Everyone we consider at risk
will be assigned additional security.
You ought to reconsider
attending
the memorial for the victims
of the Kent disaster.
Now if I need extra security,
so be it, but I'm going.
Prime Minister if I could just
point out...
300 people lost their
lives, I'm going.
This meeting is over and um,
Firestorm, I wanna know
who it is and how we stop it.
Hey I appreciate
you coming in, Hari.
Sorry, it's a bit rushed.
Thanks.
Francine said you
were going to the memorial.
- With Sutherland.
- Yes, Labour and Tory,
hand in hand.
British fortitude
and Blitz spirit, etc.
Oh, hadn't pegged
you as a cynic, Hari.
I'm a believer,
in Francine
and your resuscitation of
the party. That's why I'm here.
And why I'm about to publish another
gut punch to Robert Sutherland?
Any chance for preview on that?
No.
To be clear,
I'm on your side.
- But Morbid Symptoms ain't no Pravda.
- Understood.
- I'm just here to talk about Francine's campaign.
- Yes, let's do that.
- I think you should come with me.
- To the memorial?
To your future constituency.
I think I've filled my quota of
political opportunism this week.
Opportunism, what you don't
mean the Singer interview?
I
O, as it happens.
I'm really not ok
with a strategy
that lets a bunch of far
right assholes use me to
legitimize their bullshit.
Well, we polled after
your appearance.
Overwhelmingly positive
reaction from the members.
And if you've also
broadened your appeal to...
Fascists, Jesus Christ.
I want to announce
that you're contesting in Kent,
and I want you to win.
Because I want
you on my front bench.
If ballot papers then shower
on you like confetti
then I don't really
care who throws them.
Lord Singer, we take this kind of
precautionary measure all the time.
It's just, peace of mind, Allan.
Oh, for God's sake, Robert.
In my entire career of
prosecuting and sentencing,
I've never once
needed a police guard,
but I conduct one
inquiry for your government.
I mean, it's bad enough being
harangued by the press night and day,
but worse than that, that
bloody Francine Bridge woman
is on the news accusing
me of being a stooge.
But to top it all, I'm now
on a fascist hit list.
- Allan, look...
- And you call it peace of mind.
Marjorie and I were
going away next week
to the house in Cyprus.
We'll cancel the flights.
We'll leave tonight.
We'd prefer it if we could
guarantee your security here.
And I would prefer it
if you could guarantee it
til Marjorie and I are
away from this bloody bedlam,
and we return when you can make sure
she's at no further risk of being widowed.
Please, come in.
Sorry to intrude.
I wanted to catch you before.
An unexpected pleasure.
And to which ailing
area of policy do I owe it?
It's a actually
about the by-election,
Clive Turner's seat.
God rest his soul.
Yes, quite, but we'd rather
his seat rested with the Tories.
We've been discussing
potential candidates and...
one mooted is Roger Hawkins.
Is he Robert's choice?
The discussion is ongoing.
Roger's name cropped up and I...
If Robert were to end up
leaning towards him.
I wondered how comfortably
that would sit with you.
Because Roger has some...
eccentric views.
Because he has a widely
documented history
of inflammatory rabble rousing
and barely veiled racism.
Well. Nobody's perfect.
Look, I have no desire
to break bread
with Roger Hawkins, but.
I assume he's Robert's choice
'cause Robert thinks he can win.
And, given the demographic,
he probably can.
That demographic being
a white working class
whom a populist like Hawkins
will do his best to whip up.
I would have thought that would have
been more troubling to Home Secretary.
A Home Secretary or a black man?
I'm frankly curious as to why it
doesn't trouble you as either.
Whether or not it
troubles me is irrelevant.
We need to hold the seat.
And I trust Robert's judgment.
So... I'm afraid...
I cannot lend authentic
ethnic ballast
to your struggles
in dissuading him.
And if his judgment's wrong?
Well...
We learn from
the mistakes of others.
As much as from our own.
Shall we?
We don't want to miss our lift.
Rachel, the car will
be here shortly. You ready?
Darling, what's the matter?
That website that tried to make out that lad
something to do with kickbacks to Kostenko.
They've just tried even harder.
Oh... it's going to be all over the
news and I'm so sorry but it's lies.
I swear it's lies.
Rachel, I don't know
what you're talking about.
Hari Misra from Morbid Symptoms
has interviewed a former colleague
of mine claiming
I knew about the bribes.
He's saying it's impossible
I didn't know what was going on.
On what grounds,
you were a junior.
Yeah I was but you know,
right home to the senior and
I didn't know my senior
was breaking the law of course
I fucking didn't but Nigel
Raine's saying either Ine new
and turned a blind eye
or I was part of it.
Surely that's defamation.
He's too slick to do
anything actionable.
He's lying,
but I can't prove it.
I don't think he's going
public to grind to an old axe,
so maybe it's money,
maybe it's blackmail,
but somebody's got their
hand up the puppet
and it's the same
someone I imagine
who gave the documents
to Morbid Symptoms,
and then you know the dots
just joined themselves.
- Dots?
- Oh Rob come on.
This assault on me
amid the cyber attacks
isn't happening by unfortunate
fucking coincidence.
It's your integrity, your job,
they're trying to capsize.
And I'm just.
Mine are just collateral damage.
So our dead man has a name.
The body found in
the truck was Edward Price.
U.S. citizen.
He was abducted on
a holiday in Bordeaux.
Have the Americans been
informed?
Not yet, but the NSA are
breathing down our necks.
The NSA, why?
Price was a scientist at DARPA.
- The military lab.
- Military technology, yes
but Price's field of research
was heavily classified.
Last time Ihecked the Americans
were still our key allies, hecked
so they may be able to tell us
why one of theirs
ended up glowing like Chernobyl
in the back of the lorry.
Speak to their intelligence as
a matter of immediate urgency.
Understood and I'll pass on
your gratitude to my team, shall I?
Why don't we just file it
under better late than never?
I would like to
clarify one last thing.
- Yes?
- I am keen for us to work together
as productively as possible.
Despite your pitiful animosity.
But when I am briefing COBRA,
please keep your snide little
peashooter in your pencil case.
Just a little levity
between colleagues.
You never struck me as the type
to feel so needled.
And you always struck me
as knowing better
than to pull an Oxbridge
Rapier on a serrated machete.
I'd never pull a rapier.
I was in the Pistol Club.
And I Foreign Secretary,
am the Royal fucking Artillery.
- Pencil case it is there.
- Hm.
While we the people starve,
these corrupt gluttons
continue to gorge
at the troth of power.
More proof from Hari Misra
of the corruption in no. 10.
Rachel Sutherland was at the
heart of the Kostenko bribery scandal.
My brothers, we must take action
and stamp on these cockroaches.
Let's rise up for justice
and our nation.
On the same bench for once.
Well, if ever there
was a place for miracles.
I shall begin with a reading
from Philippians 4, verse 8.
Whatever is true,
whatever is honorable, whatever
is just, whatever is pure.
Whatever is pleasing,
whatever is commendable,
if there is any
excellence in it.
If there is anything
worthy of praise.
We are here today.
In the memory of these
people who have perished.
I want you to consider
these thoughts.
No recriminations,
no guilt.
Just the memory of
good things in their life.
Keep away!
Thank you!
Pleasant journey here?
Apart from being told I'm now
a target for Nazi terrorists.
I'm sorry Rachel. We are doing
everything we can to mitigate.
You sound just
like a politician.
No comment!
- ...the truth?
- Step back sir!
How many times do I
have to say no comment!
Step back.
Can you just leave us alone?
Mr. Singer? Did you
sing for your supper?
What?
Eleanor, can't this wait?
He's what?
No, no he's what?
Oh my God.
Police and ambulance crews
attended the scene
where the killing took place.
The suspect has
been apprehended.
A message has been recovered
from his recording equipment.
A warning. This report
contains images that some
people may find disturbing.
I have stamped on a cockroach.
Great Britain has one less
instrument of corruption.
Where I've gone,
me and my brothers follow.
He don't sing for
his supper no more.
There'll be
a statement from the police
shortly regarding the murder
of Lord Allan Singer.
What's happened?
A statement of sympathy has been
issued for Lord Singer's family.
And the protection officer?
Critical but stable.
Our next move
needs to be robust.
- This cannot stand.
- She's bloody right.
Look at this.
The killer,
this Thompson bastard,
now a hero
to the nutter factions.
His disgusting footage
all over social bloody media.
I'm aware and the companies have
said they'll be cooperative,
but every time they stamp it
out, it pops up somewhere else.
Meanwhile, we are
monitoring a worrying
traction with certain conspiracy
theories that Thompson was put
up to the murder by MI 5
which is now being tide to theories
that the Prime Minister ordered
the Kostenko assassination.
To protect his wife
from prosecution.
Firestorm.
Firestorm incited Thompson.
And now Allan Singer is dead.
There will be another Thompson.
And another.
Ore dead.
As long as Firestorm
is spewing its poison.
And this government
will not tolerate that.
I don't doubt that we could
prosecute whoever's behind.
Firestorm under the Terrorism
Act. The issue is finding them.
You said the internet companies
were being cooperative.
To the usual limits,
but if we demand records,
we're looking down the barrel
of an enormous legal fight.
That's not good.
We won't look strong,
we'll look draconian.
Then what do we do about this?
Then we don't go through
these bloody companies.
We tell GCHQ to go around.
Underneath.
Is that legal?
It's um... somewhat gray.
I don't give a shit
if it's jet black, do it.
Understood.
And then deal with Hari Misra.
His site's adding fuel
to all of this.
So now we're
arresting journalists,
Finding out who
pulls his strings.
The investigation is
progressing, Prime Minister.
Well, I'm sure that inspires
us all with confidence.
Thank you Elena. Racine.
Joseph didn't seem happy
with our strategy.
I'm sure he'll come on board.
If it puts at least one hateful
bastard under lock and key.
Since you mention him.
I wouldn't mind your opinion on
something if you got a moment.
It's what I'm here for.
What do you think of him?
Who?
Joseph, Anna.
I think...
Why?
Because I'm asking.
Bright.
Charismatic.
Ambitious.
Do you want an essay?
No, I just thought you might say
someone was recruiting.
To harangue me over
my choice of Roger Hawkins
for the by-election.
Robert...
- Before we discuss you going behind my back.
Roger Hawkins may
be to the right of us
may even be a reactionary,
but I will tell
you something he hasn't done.
He hasn't accused a respected
judge of corruption
shortly before
he was butchered and even
supplied the fucking
hashtag for it.
You brought Francine Bridge in,
vouch for her.
I
Ear you're even pals again.
And yet you have the temerity
to question my judgment.
You think Francine
is the problem,
you're going to blame
a black woman for feeding
far right extremism while
you shove your weight behind
a dog whistling jingoist.
And yes, I spoke
to Joseph because my job
is to make sure you make
the best possible decision.
But maybe that's something
overdue for reappraisal.
Robert...
Get a fucking grip.
I say this with kindness.
But you're mental, thinking
you played a part in it.
Any fucking part.
Scumbag who killed
Singer was a Nazi incel,
you think a prick like
that listens to a black woman?
All you did was speak
truth to power and...
Christ knows that's
what this country
needs from its politicians.
You did your job.
Like I do mine.
Maybe you've just
had more practice.
- At truth?
- At collateral damage.
I mean, when you run pieces
that, like with Rachel Sutherland,
Oh Jesus, seriously?
Next you'll ask me how I sleep,
how do you sleep?
Like a baby, curled up and
crying all night for my mum.
I'm being serious Harry,
a man is dead.
I'm being serious too.
About truth.
And truth is the only blade
that draws blood from liars.
However deep the lie,
however high the liar.
Your sources must find
that very comforting.
I couldn't tell you, lately,
I don't even know who they are.
Doesn't that bother you?
Nothing I've been sent is illegal and I
don't run anything without due diligence.
Yeah but if you don't
know who, you don't know why.
I mean, the Rachel Sutherland
stuff for example,
somebody has got an agenda.
I don't care when it's my story,
it's my agenda.
Remind me not to come to you
for emotional support again.
Look, here's an idea.
We do an interview for the site.
You can be front footed
with your reaction to Singer.
Denounce all extremism.
State in all caps,
how we must cleave to truth,
but also peace.
And then we can have dinner.
You just don't quit, do you?
Nope.
Jesus Christ.
Lab's this way and just before
the ship blew,
we had a reconnaissance boat
over it scanning, gathering data.
The condition of the hull, the
munitions, seabed seismology
all got bloody obliterated.
Along with 300 people.
Audrey.
I'm here. I'm here.
Like I said, obliterated.
The dive team have been
searching the wreckage
and this morning
we found our video.
Heard of a black box on a
plane? Well, it's that. For boats.
All data up until the moment of
destination is backed up here.
Well that's, that's
excellent news, isn't it?
Well force of the blast
damaged the unit,
we've only just managing to
pull the readings from it now.
Look spectrogram.
Taken moments
before the explosion.
These lines represent
the noise made
from the boats' engines
and down here.
We'd expect to see a low seismic
frequency from the tremor
that set off the blast.
This is what a tremor
should look like.
This was taken 17 hours
prior to the explosion,
but when the boat went off.
There's nothing.
So the scanner was bust.
Or, there was no tremor at all,
- but hang on what's this?
- Ah.
Something extremely low
frequency but high decibel.
Let me show you more detail.
Starts here 32 minutes,
then stops.
3.7 seconds later... boom.
If that's not a tremor,
what could it be?
Most likely a faulty sensor.
But just supposing
it wasn't faulty,
I have no idea, But I can
tell you
there's no natural phenomena
which explains this wave pattern.
We're still analyzing.
Bored of your office?
Just thought we'd come
face to say. Take the air.
New hobby.
14 years since I quit.
That's plenty.
I'm worried about Robert.
He's...
I think this thing with Rachel
might be pushing him over the edge.
Yeah, about that.
I didn't move this meeting
out of my office for fresh air.
I'm here because I'm doing
you a favor I shouldn't be.
Francine Bridge. Are you still
friends? Or friends again?
Yeah, -She's due to give Hari
Misra an interview this afternoon,
but he won't be able to make it.
There's been an escalation
and our hand's been forced.
If you value Francine,
and she values anything
resembling a political future,
tell her to cut Misra loose.
And do it now.
Holy fucking hell.
What the...
Grip it or what?
Fuck this.
It isn't fucking on.
Hey Anna, can I call you back? I'm about to...
-No.
- Yeah, I'm about to do an interview.
- I know.
- Wait, how do you know?
- I need you to meet me, now.
Yeah, I can't like I said
I'm about to do this interview.
- Hari is not someone you should associate with.
- What?
Please listen, I don't
want to speak on the phone,
but I... I need you...
- OK, Anna, I will call you back, all right? Bye.
Alright, bye.
He's on the move, follow or...
Take him.
Who the fuck are they?
Passenger on board?
Boss, someone else
snatched him.
What do you mean someone else?
The car came out of nowhere
and they grabbed him.
What fucking car?
Follow!
- Eleanor?
- What?
Firestorm, we've traced it.
- We know who he is.
- Who?
Gavin Beadle,
currently at his residence
in Old Trafford,
Everything is in
place for the raid.
I need your permission
to proceed.
Do it now.
Pop his hat off.
- Hello, Hari.
- Who are you?
I'm Tommy.
So's he.
Yard? MI5?
We're Tommy.
Let's talk about you.
Two units: I will proceed with Unit
Alpha to the front of the building.
Sierra five will proceed with Unit
Bravo to the rear of the building.
Then all units hold position and
await my command to breach.
May 22nd to 27th, 2015.
You took a trip to Moscow.
Is that when you
were taped up by the SVR?
I was reporting
a gay pride rally.
Sierra five trojan three-seven. That's
a go. Proceed to breaching position.
Trojan three-seven
zero five moving now.
Sierra five confirm
when you're in position.
Let's talk about
another report, then.
The one you were due
to publish tomorrow.
The one you were instructed
to run by your masters.
To disseminate egregious
untruths about the United States.
You work for the yanks.
You're mercs?
Get back inside.
Sierra five trojan three seven.
Front position held.
No sign of movement,
confirm your status.
Trojan three-seven zero five. In
position. Awaiting breach signal.
Who gave you
the American documents?
Who is your fucking handler?
Trojan three seven stand by,
unit bravo on the move.
Armed police! Armed police!
Armed police!
Down down, now!
Gavin Beadle, where is he?
Trojan three-seven, unit alpha
proceeding with search upstairs.
Two rooms, checking room one.
Clear, clear, clear.
Proceeding to room two.
Contact, contact, contact!
Down, down, down, get down.
Hands behind your back,
hands behind your back.
All units, all units. Trojan three-seven,
positive contact with suspect in room two.
Hold position. Awaiting visual
confirmation of suspect ID.
We actually got him.
- Trojan three seven.
- Suspect apprehended.
Repeat, trojan three seven,
suspect apprehended.
N-PAS six-zero to control.
Suspect en route to secure
location Delta Seven-Three.
Over and out.
Well that's one
fire snuffed out.
Or have we stoked it?
How many more Firestorms
are out there?
And who's pulling the strings?
It's Hari, you know what to do.
Not even the basic
courtesy of a text.
You made me look a twat
this afternoon Hari.
See, we don't have
much choice here, Hari.
See our business is
just like yours, really.
We're only after the truth.
I told the truth, I told you,
no, no, wait, please, don't, no.
Wait, wait, wait, wait! I told you the
truth, I don't know who my source is.
Please don't...
You just said useful bloody
idiot, really, aren't you pal?
No hard feelings.
Ride home?
It is believed to be
a firebomb attack.
It's not yet known if anybody was
inside the offices of the left-leaning
online political site
Morbid Symptoms.
There are claims a far right
group is behind the attack.