A firestorm is caused by
baskets of incendiaries,
and not a single bomb.
Neither the silencing
of a lone patriot,
nor the disappearance
of one truth-telling journalist
will stop the flames
of truth from spreading.
Water may douse the flames,
but who controls the water?
Think before you drink.
Oh, my God, she has made me
sound like a complete and utter idiot.
Well, I'm sure it's just...
"Seemingly cloth-eared
to current debates
on privilege
and racial justice,
she moans about the size
of the Downing Street flat,
and claims that
her infamous comment
that posh white girls
do not belong in prison
was not understood
'in context'...
I made a joke
about the flat
because the cameraman
banged his head.
Oh. Come on,
this is just newspapers.
It's an absolute
bloody disaster.
Look, uh,
Firestorm is back.
I have to, uh...
Well, are they messing
with our water now?
Fraser's looking into it,
Prime Minister.
And who snatched Hari Misra?
- Ask the people he pissed off with his scoops.
- What, including us?
Contrary to popular myth
and social media...
Maybe my wife's had him snatched
and is overseeing his torture somewhere.
That's what they'll be saying,
I imagine.
Well, Misra's recent output certainly
means the finger will point at us
- to make us look bad.
- And you're sure that wasn't your objective as well?
A little strategic own-goal?
Because I'm getting a bit doubtful
to whose side anyone is on right now.
We have done nothing
to Hari Misra.
Not to make you look bad,
or for any other reason.
We failed to pick him up, and
even if we had got there first,
we don't have an
assassination program,
as you know perfectly well.
Well, I'm beginning
to question merits of that.
Especially when it comes
to journalists.
We can announce a change of policy
on the Number 10 Twitter feed if you like?
Okay, keep me informed.
Thanks.
Problems with the water
down in Kent.
Oh, yeah, my brother
mentioned that to me.
Been on and off
for a while now,
but the water company's saying
that the pressure's completely normal.
Well, now, there's stuff
flying all over social media
- saying that it isn't safe to drink.
- Really?
Do you think
it might be another...
Water systems would be a
prime target for a cyber-attack.
I'll speak to the
Intelligence Chief.
They haven't flagged any
malware in the system yet.
We are clearly under attack
from a coalition
of powerful state actors,
and they seem to be taking
turns to occupy the driving seat.
Foreign Secretary is not wrong.
But first things first,
my counterpart
at the American Embassy
has assured me that the Misra
story we intercepted from his computer
about their involvement
in the ship explosion in Kent
was fake news
planted by the Chinese.
- And what do you think?
- We're still looking at the evidence.
Well, early evidence suggests that
something odd went on down there.
Fraser mentioned
some kind of sonic event.
And tension's very high between the
Yanks and the Chinese at the moment.
Would the Americans really...
Well, not deliberately.
But they could be making
a point to the Chinese
about their
underwater capacities.
Especially with everything so
on edge in the South China Sea.
And they did make it
very clear
that they were unhappy
with the drilling permissions
that we granted
to the Jiayou Corporation.
I want reprisals.
- What, against the Americans?
- No.
Not them for now
until the facts are clearer.
But identify some targets
from the other two who we know
are behind Ruin Britannia.
- Yeah, the problem with that...
- I know the problems.
Keep it largely symbolic,
but not entirely pain-free.
A few surgical strikes that will
make both Russia and China jump.
A central bank,
TV network.
Use your imagination.
I am not gonna sit here
and take this.
Did you, um, ask the
government about Hari Misra?
Yeah, they claimed they don't
know anything. Maybe they don't.
All right, I will say a few
words, announce your candidacy
- and then hand over to you.
- What's all this about?
No idea. What's wrong
with the tap water?
Nothing, as far as I know.
What's a quantum algorithm?
No idea.
But I do know that
you can put the word "quantum"
in front of any other bullshit and
all of a sudden it looks high status.
Good morning, everybody,
and thank you for coming.
As you can see with me
is Francine Bridge.
Uh, we'll take a few questions.
Maybe five minutes,
and then we really
will have to move on, okay?
But I really
appreciate you coming.
Over to Francine.
Hey.
Who's drunk all the water?
There's water
in the kettle still.
You know I'm not
drinking that.
You don't really
believe all that crap
that they're poisoning us
with equations, do you?
Algorithms.
And Lin says it's actually
quite dangerous.
Lin listens to Michael Buble,
refused to get
her kids vaccinated,
and is voting for that
racist's nonce.
Yeah, she's also my best mate
and Danny's godmother.
So...
I'm gonna go and get
some bottled stuff,
just so we're sure.
Bring me back a Kit-Kat then.
Shut up. "Kit-Kat."
You're meant to be on a diet.
I've got a naturally high
metabolism, I don't need to diet.
Oh! Be nice to be able to see
your cock again, though, right?
You tell me. It fell off last
week through lack of use.
Danny!
Gonna go to the shops.
You really
gonna drink that?
Yeah.
You're an idiot.
Don't be a mean ol' Jezebel.
- Get me a Kit-Kat.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Danny?
- I'm coming.
First they came with their
pills and vaccinations,
now it's the water.
Ask yourselves this:
Why was the water supply
suspended for emergency work
on the water main
a month ago?
To carry out an emergency
work on a water main?
And why has the pressure
been so weird recently?
Probably because someone's
using buried malware to manipulate it.
They're making the data in the water
plants look normal to the technicians,
while lowering the pressure
to consumers.
They're going for slow drip
rather than a drought,
which is even more frustrating.
As any man over 50 knows.
No coincidence, I suppose,
they've chosen an area
where a bitter election
is taking place.
Well, what's worrying me
is that they've teamed up
to hit back for this week's
symbolic reprisals.
Ganging up and showing off?
Player one, world leaders
and sophisticated malware.
Player two, world leaders
and misinformation and chaos.
Others turning in the chips
in their pockets,
waiting for the next
spin of the wheel.
Why did it start though?
Because that's what happens
when you have the weapons
and the conditions are right.
Spark becomes flame,
becomes inferno.
First World War could have
been Prussian railway timetables.
On a happier note,
you know how scientists
can develop weapons
that can immobilize you
purely through a vile stench?
I am familiar
with the concept.
They would struggle to
find one that has an impact
as strong as our new candidate
from Kent House.
On Anna Marshall's
delicate little schnoz.
Have you ever actually
been to Kent?
As opposed to figuratively?
Of course
I've actually been to Kent.
I'm not talking about
a pint of prawns in Deal.
I'm talking about the Medway
towns and the real people.
Oh, bad news, Deal residents,
you don't actually exist.
Okay, I think it's given
that you two
aren't going to be sharing
a picnic in Glyndebourne.
Can we just focus
on the issues in hand?
Good call.
The opposition will attack us
if they have any sense.
On the housing issue.
Yeah, plus the water issue, which
has suddenly emerged from nowhere.
I'm not gonna talk about
housing plans or water.
You didn't put me in this seat
to fight clean and you know it.
So, stop being hypocrites.
You put me in it
to defeat
a resurgent opposition
from winning a seat
you can ill-afford to lose.
This election's gonna be
about one thing for me.
And that's stopping
Francine Bridge
from representing a constituency
totally at odds with her values.
- Which values are those then?
- -Oh, what, you don't know?
- Mimsy, lefty.
- Feminine.
Chuck it in
if you like, Archie.
But I'll certainly be appealing
to the female vote.
One of the mistakes
you make is to assume
that everybody agrees
with your values
when it's just a handful
of media lovies
posting photos of their
negronis on Instagram.
Negronis.
It's all about the skinny
bitches now, Rodger.
They had an open goal,
but they gambled
with her selection.
- Fresh lime not cordial...
- Anna.
And they're so desperate to
get her back into parliament.
It could be their undoing.
She's gonna be... soft
on all kinds of issues,
which I intend to hit her with
again and again and again.
And that's how we're
gonna win that seat.
No need to make it
about race, Rodger.
Do not target that.
Oh, don't worry, Joseph, I
have no intention of doing so.
I won't need to.
Hi, Anna, I've just...
- Don't dwell on it.
- She made me look like a complete idiot.
I trusted her.
Okay. Beginner's error.
It's happened to us all.
I did an interview once,
they used everything I said,
but made me look like
a simpering idiot.
Which I'm not.
Every joke,
every suggestion of irony...
I'm funny, Anna.
I know, you're a hoot.
I'm a harpy, a racist.
The wicked witch
pulling her husband's strings,
when everybody knows
that's you.
You'd be surprised.
Well, he's a bit jealous,
isn't he?
Of whom?
Francine Bridge.
He worries you prefer her
to Hawkins.
News flash: I do.
Yeah, but to Rob that's like
saying you prefer her to him.
It's ridiculous.
Listen, don't worry about
the response to the article.
Well, I'm just
never gonna be enough.
You know, the...
the way I dress,
the way I speak, my body.
The fact that I'm Jewish.
Yeah, Jewish lawyer to boot.
Come on, you must be
pulling strings somewhere.
Well, I had a
Ukrainian oligarch murdered
to spare my blushes over
some bullshit
that wasn't even my fault.
So, you know,
join the dots, sheeple.
Maybe you need a break
or something.
I don't know,
go and visit Ellie?
I don't think I can live in this
bloody flat for much longer.
Well, it's little more than
a matchbox after all.
I literally feel
like I'm going insane.
Talk to Robert.
I can't, he's got
too much on his plate.
Talk to him now.
It's not fair
what they're doing to you.
Thank you.
Thank you, thank you.
Thank you. Thanks.
Uh, can I ask you a personal
question? So, don't be offended,
but, uh, anything happening
between you and Misra?
No.
Had to ask.
But something really
bad's happened, Chris.
The fire at his office,
his disappearance, I just...
- Get back to London, you northern monkey.
- Poisoning our water.
Ah, it's like Burnley-on-Sea.
Spoken like a true woman
of the people.
They're having a hard time
deciding if I'm a metropolitan elitist,
- or Moss-Side drug dealer.
- Bit of both, actually.
Chorlton, mate.
Creative hub of Manchester.
There's a very ugly mood
in this town.
And it's only gonna get worse.
Yes?
I'm afraid I have some
disturbing news
linked to the water in Kent,
Prime Minister.
And I was on such
a winning streak.
A child in Rochester
called Simon Drake
has developed
amoebic meningitis.
And that's different from...
Yeah, it's caused by a
bacteria called Naegleria fowleri,
that attacks the brain
and is always almost fatal.
How did he catch it?
Well, you normally get it by
breathing contaminated water
through the nose.
- And had he?
- They're investigating.
It's very rare,
especially in the UK.
- They wouldn't...
- It could be a coincidence,
but it's been picked up on
by the trolls and the bots,
and they're exploiting it
to the maximum effect.
Prepare the Cobra room.
Children are dying for this
government's experiments.
Luckily, we will soon
have an opportunity
to tell them what we
think of them at the polls.
Justice for Simon.
Vote nobody.
What's that symbol they use?
It's similar to an image used
by a Chilean fascist group
called Patria y Libertad in the
1970s, but they're long gone.
Chile?
I recently reviewed
Ellie's security.
How's the child doing?
ICU, very poorly.
What's the water company saying?
That the water
is completely safe,
but if people are worried, they
should boil it and avoid inhaling it.
- Who inhales water?
- Showers, etc.
The bacteria can't actually
be spread by drinking
- because stomach acid neutralizes it.
- Uh.
Let me get this straight.
First, they fooled around
with the water supply.
Then they started
a blizzard of rumor,
and now they're telling people
not to vote in the election.
Get our bloody candidate
to drink a big glass of water.
Now, there's a
win-win scenario.
I'll get down there
as soon as I can.
Is that such a good idea?
Well, it worked during the solar
storm. You can't run from the people.
As Mussolini discovered from
the wrong end of a meat hook.
Enough with the wise cracks
and smart alec replies.
- Does anybody see what's happening here?
- We do see...
One thing after another.
Death by a thousand cuts.
I mean, they're not
even asking for anything.
It's like we've just become
fucking game-board for them.
That's exactly what
it's like, Prime Minister.
Problem is,
now that it's started,
I'm not sure anyone knows
how this game ends.
Yeah, well, I'm not gonna hide
behind a punch of useless pawns.
- Hit back hard.
- We've just done that.
Then try again, harder.
It's like bloody Nuremberg,
down this close.
All these swastika things.
Nobody around here
is gonna vote.
- I am.
- Good.
They're kids dying in hospital because
of what they're doing to the water.
- There's one case.
- Ah, believe what you want to believe.
I've got more beliefs,
in case you're interested.
Vaccinations are a triumph
of medical science.
Our dad died before one
had a chance to save him.
And there's nothing in the water
apart from hydrogen, oxygen,
and a little bit of fluoride to
stop your teeth from falling out.
I'm not interested,
Audrey.
- Just 'cos you went to college.
- Yeah, I did go to college, Tina. Yeah.
Because my dad wasn't a moron, and
he thought education was a good thing.
I'm proud I went
to college, actually.
It stopped me turning into some
two-bob conspiracy-peddling...
Well, go on, love,
say it.
I know what you've
always thought of me.
Moppet.
You stuck-up little cow.
And give it a rest
about your dad.
Like he's the only person
who ever died,
- and you're the only person who cares.
- Fuck you.
A lot of people
think like she does.
Can you blame her,
with this lot in power?
The boat going up like that
all of a sudden
and now this shit
with the water.
There is no shit
Well, something's going on.
How did that kid get that...
Nigeria.
Naegleria fowleri.
I don't know, Cary.
Maybe...
maybe jumped off a locke
into a filthy canal
like you were wasted
when you were 15.
Remember that kid who ripped his
bullocks off on the submerged bicycle?
God.
Was that actually true, or did
they just say that to scare us?
I don't know.
Worked though.
Well, there you are then.
Well...
Hello. You from
the local Labor Party?
- Thank you.
- Cheers.
What do you think?
Yeah, I think she'll win.
She got a better smile
than that Tory doughnut.
You just fancy her.
I'm not gonna lie,
I've got the ragin' horn, mate.
Oh. Yuck.
It's disgusting.
You sure there's nothing up
with the water?
The water is safe.
It's my department,
I really would know.
Tina's just worried. She's
got a big heart, that's all.
And that kid with all 'em tubes
has really upset her.
Okay. Okay.
Big-hearted moppet.
Well,
here comes a Tory moppet.
Good evening, sir.
Reckon I can keep these bastards
here for an hour at least.
So, I'm very undecided in this
election, and I was wondering...
Mr. Hawkins?
Do you know if the water
in Kent is safe to drink?
I've been assured
that it is.
That's not the same as saying
it actually is though.
I mean, we're all
assured that it is.
Francine Bridge made a categoric
statement saying that she...
Well, to be fair,
it's probably cleaner
than the water
where she comes from.
Hard as nails, that water
in the inner cities.
I doubt she's even
tasted our Kent water.
Cheers.
He said what?
No, tell me exactly.
Right. I'll raise it
directly with the PM.
Drinking unclean water
is an obvious trope
that she's not
really British.
- Yes, but he said...
- Oh, come on, Robert!
One thing to be an opportunist,
but another to be willfully dense.
- Willfully what?
- This is an absolute disgrace!
It's clear enough
what he was doing.
It's completely unacceptable.
Also, what's with "I'm assured
the water is safe to drink"?
- Okay.
- Okay, what?
- Okay, point taken.
- Okay, point taken, and what?
We'll make sure he doesn't
overstep the mark like that again.
That's it?
If you book a ride on a tiger you
cannot then complain about its stripes.
I don't believe it.
- I can't believe you don't have a problem.
- Don't go there, Anna.
I don't really
take kindly to lectures
about what my reaction
should be to anything.
The fact is, this is a hard
fight and he's our dog.
A dog whistle, you mean.
Look, he's fighting a battle
based on social conservatism.
I agree with much of that.
I don't support
the identity extremists either,
but where he crosses a line,
we rein him in.
I would say
he is over the line,
- but it's still in earshot.
- Bullocks!
And that's what passes
for debate at St Paul's, is it?
Oh, spare me the self-made
salt of the earth patter, Joseph.
You can keep the speech about your
hardworking mum for party conferences.
A bit envious,
because I actually have
an audience bigger than one.
Joseph, could you
excuse us for a moment?
Sure.
- How much of this is because it's Francine?
- What?
How much would you be
complaining if it wasn't your friend?
Because I think you'd rather
see her back in parliament
than our candidate.
In fact...
if you lived in Kent,
I suspect you'd secretly
vote for her as well.
I think it's been well established
that I don't live in Kent,
I live in a box at the Opera,
sneering at the proletariat with
the rest of the toffee-nosed crew.
- This is so totally not the issue.
- Isn't it?
We cannot lose this seat, Anna.
Not now.
We're living through some
crazy undeclared war
where we don't even know
what the enemy wants.
The whole country is bubbling
with rumors and suspicions
fed by an Internet that we
cannot even begin to compete with.
So, I'm sorry,
I'm really fucking sorry
if your liberal sensibilities
have been offended
by a heat of the battle remark
about your precious little friend.
But this is politics,
it's tough.
- And it's gonna get tougher.
- They were your sensibilities once, Robert.
Tough shit.
This is now.
If you can't get in line with that...
- Then what?
Then what?
Hello, Anna.
He died?
Lin!
Don't bother going in, Tina,
there's none left.
You can have a couple
of bottles of mine.
- You okay?
- Yeah, thanks.
I'm still drinking tap water, as you
can probably tell by my lizard tail.
Oh, same old Cary.
Everything's a joke.
Same old Linda, believe any old
shit she reads on the World Wide Web.
- There are kids dying, Cary.
- One kid has died.
- Well, that makes it okay?
- Of course it's not okay.
We weren't always this crazy.
What the hell are we all coming to?
Come on, let's go.
He's not in a good place.
I've never seen him
so paranoid.
Or tetchy.
His wife?
Both his marriages
are looking shaky.
So...
I've been speaking to my
equivalent at the American Embassy.
The imagination boggles.
What's he like?
She is a female John Bolton,
who also has a PhD
in geopolitical balancing.
The Americans are very keen
we don't escalate things further.
Maybe we should blow up
half of Kentucky in revenge.
Things are extremely delicate
in the South China Sea.
They think Beijing is about to
make a big, aggressive move.
And you think this may be
connected to all that?
I don't know.
But I think a cyber war
on a weak country
might not even be connected to any
specific thing we did or could control.
And that's the terrifying part.
We are not weak.
We are significant,
but not sovereign.
In their eyes, sovereign
is being able to survive
without a bigger boy looking
after you, and we can't.
Better go eat worms.
Look, this water situation
is terrifying.
That they can confect
such panic out of nothing.
- The kid died.
- One kid, though.
And God knows
how he actually got it.
The rest is all
smoke and mirrors.
We think an outsourced rogue
nation hit the water supply.
And a Russian hand is
pulling the Firestorm strings.
If we are on our own,
attacked by all sides now,
we need a strong figure
on the bridge.
Not someone
beset by paranoia.
- You never fall out with him.
- I mean, we squabble a bit, but not like this.
Not where he threatens to...
How's everything else?
Everything else?
Well...
Hot flashes.
Absolute torment.
They should call it
something far worse.
But even that's
not the main thing.
What's the main thing?
This just isn't how I
thought I would get old.
I thought it would be graceful.
Dignified.
They keep...
mocking me for being this...
sneering, elitist Brahmin,
and I feel...
I sometimes feel as if I'm
looking at myself and thinking,
"The absolute state
of you, love."
And now, Robert says I
would rather you were elected
than our candidate.
And you know what?
He's right.
You would.
I mean, good.
Because Rodger Hawkins
is a weapons-grade prick.
A prick that might lead
to me losing my job.
Come and work for me then.
I saw this thing.
It said that Joseph Obasi was
gonna be the first black Prime Minister.
Yeah, he's a piece of work.
Yeah, he is what he is.
But I thought...
Not on my watch, mate.
I'm taking this all the way.
First black Minister
isn't gonna be a man.
- Just one problem.
- Hmm?
You've got to get your party
to accept a woman
as leader first.
You asked me to come
and work for you once.
Change your life, Anna.
That party doesn't have room
for people like you any more.
Come work with me.
Do not say
you were not warned.
They are poisoning the children
with modified water.
The sick children have
suffered a rare side effect,
and are collateral damage.
Something has been placed
in the water supply
to adjust the minds
of young people
- and make them more susceptible...
- -Oh, God!
This will get
my sister-in-law going.
You know what you have to do.
Fight fire with fire.
You know what the targets are.
A thousand sparks
create a firestorm.
Yeah, that's it!
We don't want
your fake drugs.
Burn it down!
Burn it down, burn it down.
Burn it down.
Don't do this.
It's madness.
Please, come home.
For fuck's sake,
stop it, Lin.
Tina, stop it.
This has to stop. Now!
I'm scared.
I know.
I'm so sick of it.
I'm so sick of being scared.
I don't want Danny to die.
He's at home in his bedroom,
on his PlayStation.
He's not going to die.
Your hands.
I love you.
That's all we need,
isn't it?
B side “Baby you're a Rich Man”"
I told you
not to drink that water.
Take me home.
Have you seen the TV? They're
burning things down in Kent.
It's like anarchy.
It's really scary.
What the fuck
you even doing?
One:
Don't swear at me.
Two: Don't say
"even" in that context.
Three: Don't put crap
like this in the window.
- Wait, wait, wait.
- Don't you "wait" me.
Quantum fucking algorithm.
It doesn't mean anything!
They've burned down
Francine's election offices in Kent.
So what? The planet's
been burning for long enough.
All the political parties
are the same.
Maybe people
will listen for a change.
This is completely insane.
Serious arson attacks
in Kent overnight.
Shops, especially chemists',
and a couple of GP surgeries.
Local government buildings.
Even a few police stations.
Phone masts
were also attacked.
The casualties, largely in flats
above properties, stand at five.
And all this was achieved with
lies about Quantum Algorithm?
All the main news outlets
have carried reports that
the water is safe, but, uh...
people are still
burning things.
There's something deep rooted
in the national psyche
when it comes to arson.
I'm sure it gets
the dopamine flying.
There's a Firestorm meme
doing the rounds.
I've seen it.
Our candidate in Kent
has retreated it.
In an attempt...
- Tell him to delete that immediately.
We have.
He's, so far,
failed to respond.
That tiger ride's
going smoothly then.
Seriously, he's posting stuff
probably spread by a hostile force.
Not very local, is it?
She's right.
It's definitely an attack line.
I'll deal with it.
Can I posit a scenario?
What happens if he goes so
far that we have to suspend him?
It's too late
to nominate another candidate.
This is the masterplan,
then, is it?
We have to stop this.
But no more revenge attacks
on banks and assets though.
That, clearly,
has just fed the beast.
The Americans have made it clear...
- Fuck the Americans.
They're probably watching this shit
show with as much interest as anyone else.
Organize a press conference
for 4:00 p.m.
Time to go public with who we think is
behind this. We present a collegiate face.
I think the Home Secretary would
be better in the circumstances.
Fine, we'll do
a joint conference.
Rodger.
- Ever been in the Foreign Office, Rog?
- Can't say I have.
Splendid, isn't it?
Fruitier than
Carmen Miranda hat.
Now I need you to do me
a bit of a favor.
- What's that?
- Stop being a cunt.
- I'm sorry.
- Big ask, I know.
You see, it doesn't matter
if a crypto-communist
like Anna Marshall doesn't
care for you. That's a given.
But if you lose Jo Obasi,
you're on shaky ground.
I think I can handle him.
- Do you now?
- I do.
Yes, but thanks for the advice,
Archie, all the same.
Well, look, let me float
a different scenario.
What do you think happens
if you lose me?
The Home Secretary asked
you to delete the meme.
So, delete the meme.
It's not an endorsement,
I just like it.
It's garbage, but that's
neither here nor there.
Delete the meme
and apologize.
No wonder people say
you're a spent force.
People say that, eh?
Have you ever heard that
when you're racing the
dawn back to the crypt, Motty?
No. I mean, I've heard you called
lots of things, Archie, but not that.
Be sure to tell me if you do.
Would you care
to put it to the test?
What's your game, Rodger?
My game?
I would really advise you not
to play with matches, my friend.
But I'm not your friend,
Archie.
He's not going to delete it.
- Maybe Anna is right.
- What?
Call Division 45.
Archie's been hacked.
Why did you forgo
the opportunity
to appear on the podium
alongside the PM later?
I have to go to Scotland.
It's not like you
to shun the limelight.
What are you scheming at now,
you crafty old...
It is the anniversary
of my son's death.
Marianne and I always go
to the site to lay a wreath.
- I didn't know.
- Because I don't talk about it much.
He was on a Royal Marines
live-fire training exercise.
Nobody's fault.
But anyway... Stephen died.
I'm very sorry.
Yes, it was sad.
Keep an eye on his social media
because I can
definitely smell smoke
rising from under
Rodger Hawkins' feet.
What's going on?
- Security says you're...
- I have to go.
- I can't stay or I will go insane.
- Go where?
I'm going to go
and visit Ellie in Chile.
- No, no, no. Chile's not safe.
- Why not?
Rob, some of those arsonists were
wearing masks with my face on them.
Wicked Witch T-shirts, it...
We're gonna go horse-riding in
the Andes, and, you know, just...
You, Ellie
and the Anarchist.
It's like the High Chaparral.
The Anarchist
is ancient history.
And nobody remembers
the High Chaparral.
I do.
It was...
Anna's suggestion, actually.
And suddenly I thought...
You spoke to Anna?
- Yeah. She suggested going to visit Ellie just to...
- What?
What?
It's a sensible idea...
You talked to Anna
before me?
- Yeah, but it wasn't like that.
- Oh, this is great.
This really is revenge.
Well, you got to hand it to her,
she knows how to stab
from every direction.
Rob, no, we were
just talking, and...
I've lost her loyalty.
It's gone.
All because I reinstated Archie
and overruled her on Hawkins.
She's a fucking mole.
She's working for them.
For the opposition.
So, as we await
government press conference
on the wave
of arson attacks last night,
I can confirm that Rodger Hawkins,
the Conservative candidate in Kent,
has not deleted a tweet associated
with the Firestorm campaign.
And in a move likely to deeply
embarrass the Prime Minister,
he has also said he will not be
drinking tap water as a precaution.
- Hawkins is going to flip on us.
- I think you're right.
That was a good point earlier.
About the opposition using
the attack line against us.
Anyone might think that was
something you did in your spare time.
Don't worry,
if I were going to do that,
I would make sure that
I was handsomely paid for it.
- Don't ever speak to my wife again.
- What?
Um, shall we discuss
how we parcel this out?
- I think you need to lead...
- No, no, it's okay, Anna, we have this.
Why don't you just go off
and leak to Francine...
- What?
- Fidelity.
It never was your
strong suit, was it?
Fuck you, Robert.
- You're fired.
- No, I resign.
Cerberus.
You know what that means,
don't you?
The multi-headed dog that
stands at the gates of hell.
Get me the Prime Minister
immediately.
He's about to do
the news conference.
Stop him.
Get the Prime Minister.
Good afternoon, everyone.
Justice for Simon.
Vote nobody.
Hit back harder.
I have to go,
or I will go insane.
She's a fucking mole.
- Fuck you, Robert!
- I resign!