What's happening, Audrey?
What's the Naval Commander said?
Nothing, because I'm a girl and
he doesn't see the point of me.
But I'm sensing
they're really worried
the bad weather might be moving
the wreck about even more.
- Okay, keep me informed.
- Fraser?
Yeah?
I just want you to know that I will never
forgive you for sending me out here.
Bring it up
at your next appraisal.
I'll be bringing up my breakfast
into the North Sea first.
Okay, take care.
We are evacuating this town
as a precaution.
Please report to one
of our information points.
We are evacuating this town
as a precaution.
Please report to one
of our information points.
Okay, so our problem
remains the elderly
who insist on staying
in their homes
because the wreck
hasn't blown up
for 50 years etcetera, etcetera.
Someone should remind them Leicester
City didn't win the league until 2016...
The Prime Minister wishes me to thank you
for your efforts in evacuating the town.
I'd like to think that everybody
but the most hard-line refusniks
will be out of here
by the evening.
And when we have received the
proper analysis from the Naval team
then we can plan the next steps.
Thank you.
Bailout tested and clear.
We've got 2-8-0 in the bailout,
requesting mains.
Copy that. 2-8-0 in the bailout.
Bailout checked and complete.
Ready for mains.
Okay, standbys on
mains, ready to go.
Hi, madam, good morning.
I'm not sure if you're aware
but there's currently an urgent
evacuation taking place at the moment,
so I'm going to have to ask you
to leave the property right now.
Mum,
they're coming round again.
Ridiculous.
What's that?
No idea.
I'm getting some...
it might be another tremor?
Bring him up.
Command to Dive Team Alpha,
prepare to surface.
Bring him up. Bring him up!
Get him up now.
Get him up, get him up!
Command to Dive team Alpha,
mission abort.
Surface now.
These are
the scenes from Kent
after the significant
earth tremor
that took place
on Tuesday afternoon.
Following inspections of a
sunken World War II munitions ship
lying just offshore,
the government is considering the
evacuation of towns along the coast
and we understand
that the Prime Minister
has convened a full COBRA
to take place later in the day
to discuss the possibility of a mandatory
evacuation of the areas most at risk.
That's fracking.
What's fracking?
Causing all the earthquakes.
Problem is Greta,
they've stopped fracking...
Oh, too little too late.
Thanks, boomers.
Er, Gen X
and proud of it actually.
What are you actually proud of?
Oh, I dunno. Better music,
high-status reading habits,
and not having
all my predictable
and socially-conforming views
given to me by Twitter mobs.
You still murdered the planet.
Put the milk back in the fridge
or there will be hate speech.
He's impressive.
- Who is?
- Joseph.
Big change from Archie.
You have reservations?
I would have told you
if I had reservations.
Well, as a person then...
I don't really have an opinion
one way or another.
That's what worries me.
He's fine.
We're different
which is also fine.
The party base likes him.
Socially conservative,
working class, self-made...
Which is why I agree
he's a good appointment
because any more defections
and we're fucked.
Archie's on maneuvers
by the way.
Wants the whip back.
You wouldn't...
I most certainly would
if I deemed it necessary.
Look, none of these bastards
are my friends, Anna.
It's purely strategic.
How's Ellie
getting on in Santiago?
Well, the trial took
a lot out of her.
She has a new boyfriend.
A Chilean anarchist
who sets fire to tube stations.
Take that, neo-liberals.
Home Secretary.
Congratulations, Joseph.
If you were a drinking man, I
would offer you a nip of something.
Thank you, Prime Minister.
For the time being, I am
enjoying reading people online
announcing that I am no longer
a black man.
Well, real rebels join
the establishment, I guess.
Real rebels follow the truth.
Like Paul.
- Paul?
- Saint Paul.
Oh, yes.
Wasn't so great on women
as I recall.
Especially short-haired ones.
Yes, he did give the Corinthians
some grief on coiffure as I recall.
Paul's most important message
was love.
Without love there is nothing
and only His love
can save us all.
Well, amen to that.
Now that you have been sworn in,
you can attend the COBRA we
have called on the earthquakes in Kent
which starts in, uh...
Five minutes ago.
Well it's briefing room J
actually but don't tell anyone.
It destroys the mystique.
Good morning, everyone.
Most of you know
Joseph Obasi, of course.
This is his first COBRA
as Home Secretary,
so I'll let him take the
chair...
Thank you, Prime Minister.
I believe, Fraser,
you will be updating us on the situation
in Kent and the sunken munition ship.
The naval teams
are down there now.
There was some concern that the hull
was damaged by these earth tremors.
Am I correct in thinking that some reports
suggest that the long immersion in water
will mean that there is nothing
to detonate the explosives.
Yes, that is correct.
But there is also speculation that
copper azide could be produced
which might be sufficient
to detonate the munitions.
So do we evacuate?
Huge resistance to that.
So we make it mandatory.
I think
that's the only option
given the reluctance of the
elderly to leave their homes.
Okay, so let's say the tremor
has shifted the wreck
and damaged
the hull significantly.
Let's say it does blow up...
- The damage would be enormous.
- How enormous?
Reshaping the Kent
coastline enormous.
I'd refer you to the Nova
Scotia incident in 1917
where the Mont Blanc explosion
took out Halifax
at the cost of 2,000 lives.
And as we saw in Beirut,
catastrophic damage to buildings
and infrastructure and terrible injuries.
We are also very concerned
about subsequent flooding.
But it's been so long
since the ship went down,
and I know you hate it
when I say this...
Uh, don't tell me...
we just don't really know?
It probably won't blow up.
Why haven't we dealt
with this wreck before?
Too hard.
More danger of setting
it off by prodding it.
If the earthquake
has damaged the hull,
then I would say we have to go
for mandatory evacuation.
Get things moving immediately.
Right, lads, at the back,
come on, move to the front.
Those tables are set up
for tonight.
So don't be messing about
on the coach to Chertsey.
Remember you gotta bring ID with the
age on it or you won't be allowed to play.
Oi, sir, what's happening?
Sorry, did I say
I had finished, lads?
But, sir, it's the helicopter.
I don't care if it's
the International Space Station,
sit down and listen
while I'm talking
or I'll be using you to demonstrate
how to do a spear tackle.
Come on, that's it,
sit down, sit down!
Alright, we've all seen a
helicopter before lads, come on.
Down you get,
come on, there we go.
- Sir...
- Lads, get down... lads!
Mr. Hadleigh!
Sir? Mr. Hadleigh!
And speaking
of dangerous old wrecks...
Ah, Peter, thanks for coming.
What's this about?
Oh, you know. How's tricks?
What's the story?
- Thought you might want to congratulate me.
- On what?
On holding my seat
at the election
in spite of everything
they threw at me.
Seventeen votes.
Made it all the sweeter.
Imagine his face watching
that second recount!
He still won. Which after
everything they had been through...
A majority of nine
is a tricky thing.
Especially now the opposition
has a grown-up in charge.
- Maybe.
- Anyway...
I still haven't had the chance
to congratulate you
on somehow walking
out of court a free man.
I really don't have time
for the badinage, Archie.
Debatable because you
may be free
but you are also unemployable.
- Always a pleasure to see you, Archie...
- Okay, okay!
Let's cut to the chase.
First, they restore the whip.
Then I get a seat in Cabinet.
And I want you to help me.
I know what you're going to say
to me, "This is just trolling Robert."
This is just trolling Robert.
Well,
of course partly, yes,
and quite a big part
to be fair, but also...
say what you like about him
but he has an eye for talent.
And what's the price,
Mephistopheles?
I think you've just answered
your own question.
We're gonna start
as we always do
on the Morbid Symptoms podcast
and jump straight in, so Francine Bridge...
Why did you do it?
Why did I do what?
Join the Tories.
After so many "comrades" ordering me to
fuck off and do precisely that, you mean?
And I didn't join the Tories
of course, I took a job.
And resigned from it.
Yes.
So we know that Sutherland has
that difficult majority of nine.
But, what about
his other problems?
The Singer inquiry into
the shootings at Junction 23
during the solar storm
will report soon.
That's right. I just hope
that it brings justice
and some closure for the innocent
photographer that was shot.
What was your view of the collapse
of the Rachel Sutherland trial?
Well, the jury heard the evidence.
They couldn't reach a verdict...
Because posh white mums
don't belong in prison?
Well, that depends
if they've committed a crime.
How about
their drug-dealing daughters?
I think the sentence
for Ellie Sutherland
was appropriate
under the circumstances,
but I don't know enough about
the case to have an opinion on it.
Francine Bridge demonstrating
that whatever her other virtues,
she has absolutely no
understanding of the Zeitgeist.
Uh, okay. Ask me another one.
Ever kissed a Tory?
Oh, please.
So that's where
you draw the line?
Oligarch plus helicopter
crash normally equals...
Investigations are underway.
What about the teacher?
A rugby coach
whose name was Graham Hadleigh.
Wife and two kids.
He was killed instantly
by shrapnel from the crash.
His poor children.
Mikael Kostenko had
just attended the varsity match.
Our Ukrainian sources say
he was en route to Brazil
to sort out a land contract
in the Amazon.
Pretty sure Archie's been
on his yacht.
Along with politicians of many different
stripes from Tony Blair to Bill Clinton.
That's just one stripe actually.
If it was sabotage
or something like that,
then I'm guessing
it's not down to the Norwegians.
Well, it would be
easier to list those
who didn't have
a grudge against him.
He pissed off both the Ukrainian
and Russian governments
and had several powerful rivals.
He is heavily implicated
in recent corruption cases
involving both the Israeli Prime
Minister and the Brazilian President,
with whom he is good friends.
Why was a helicopter
taking off from...
The school next door lets
VIP helicopters use the land
during rugby games
to raise funds.
There had apparently
been some complaints
from parents
worried about safety.
You can expect
blow-back on that.
School forced
to rent out playing fields
for oligarch's helicopter
equals blood on our hands.
I will keep you informed.
We are evacuating
this town as a precaution.
The hull is very corroded.
Any movement is problematic.
- Is it going to blow up?
- It's very hard to say.
Okay.
You're evacuating the town,
which is sensible.
Leave the ship to us.
I've booked us a B&amp;B outside
the evacuation area, down in Margate...
Oh, great. I can pay a visit
to Olby's Studio One.
What's that?
The old Dugout.
Mod weekenders...
Ah, I didn't know
you were a Mod.
I'm not gonna come to work
just in a parka, am I?
What's your thing then?
Outside of planning
for national emergencies.
I don't really have
any interests.
Just work, work, work.
Weren't you seeing
that Francine Bridge?
- Sort of, but it didn't... it didn't really...
- It didn't...
I'm not really good
with relationships.
My ex-wife called me
a slow puncture.
That's not very nice.
She might have a point though.
Well, never mind,
not everybody can say
that they're top dog
when it comes
to civil contingencies planning.
I mean, I dunno, my default position
is usually to support the woman.
Rightly, so probably.
Usually the man's fault.
Yeah. Not always though.
My dad was one of the softest
people you could've ever met.
All he wanted to do was go
down the boozer with his mates,
listen to The Faces,
and watch the Wall.
The what?
No one likes us?
- Millwall Football Club.
- Oh.
He was a school caretaker
and he wore the same hat every
year at Christmas that lit up for the kids.
But he was also fat
and unhealthy so...
he died alone in hospital,
we couldn't go and see him,
say goodbye.
- That's pretty fucked up.
- Yep.
Good evening,
ladies and gentlemen,
we are Tiny Flaws and our first
tune is called Wrong Kind of Blue.
Yeah?
Never underestimate a Mod.
Expel a few
"diplomats," right?
That's usually the format.
That man was a volunteer, Anna.
He gave up his free time
to coach disadvantaged kids.
I know.
But can we really afford a
major diplomatic incident right now
when there's all this shit
going on around us?
Let's sleep on it.
Discuss it tomorrow.
Sleep.
What's that again?
Are you still having trouble
with that?
Yes, and please don't tell me...
As soon as my head
hits the pillow I'm gone!
What's happening with Sam?
He's still shacked up
with his 16-year-old.
- Sixteen!
- Oh, okay, 36. Same difference though.
Worse possibly.
Do you think you might
be a little bit depressed?
No.
Good.
I think I'm tired, stressed
and a bit down in the dumps
for reasons I don't really need
a shrink to explain.
I just had to ask.
Mental Health is...
- No laughing matter?
- It's important.
I don't want you thinking it's all
about me and my needs the whole time.
Duty done.
You were really close
to Anna Marshall though?
I was and I still think
she's brilliant...
But...
Elite schools,
elite university, elite values.
Same.
What's wrong with that?
You'll be telling me punctuality
and the written word
are all part
of white privilege next.
Alright, well, I'll tell you what I'll
be telling you, thank you very much.
Which is that you have
to at least contemplate the idea
that yours isn't
the only angle of view.
Sure but you have to think it's the best
one or you would presumably change it?
Anyway, I didn't belong there.
You don't believe
in white privilege?
Just look at a COBRA meeting.
I never said
I didn't believe in it...
Confirmation that I'm on
the Breakfast Show tomorrow.
Discussing the Kostenko case.
You think it was a hit?
Oligarch plus helicopter crash?
Nah,
nothing suspicious there.
You better get
an early night, then.
Oh, I'm not an early night
kind of person really.
I am.
Shame.
Have you got my mobile?
Don't think so.
Hold on. I've got yours,
so I'll just ping it over.
Why?
In case you ever want to use it.
Got it.
- Bye.
- So... working.
- Mmm.
I didn't know if I'd be able
to do my job again.
Yeah, I know.
Still, work is good.
But I've also been thinking
about holidays.
- Oh, right...
- You hate them, I know.
But I've been looking
at places in the Atacama
and I thought maybe we could go
and see Ellie.
We'll head up there together. Stars
are meant to be amazing apparently.
No, it would be good.
To be together as a family.
Eleanor...
It was a hit.
We're almost certain they used an
armored drone to shoot down the helicopter.
It's a complicated situation.
It might be a boat
we don't want to rock.
I'll be right down.
Who's this, then?
This has just come in
from our investigation.
Klara Lechkova
is a Russian citizen.
She's picked up a couple of
times on CCTV walking the tow-path
which adjoins the school where
the helicopter was due to take off.
Where was
the drone controlled from?
She also purchased a scooter,
which we believe may have been
used to leave the scene afterwards.
And she's vanished
off the face of the earth.
Klara is the niece of a member of
the Duma with links to the President.
Her uncle is
a decorated GRU member
and also has close links
to separatists
operating out of
the Donetsk People's Republic.
Who's the sidekick?
Rodrigo Lenin Araya. Colombian.
His father was a senior commandant
of the FARC guerrilla movement
murdered by
right-wing paramilitaries.
Araya studied at the People's
Friendship University in Moscow.
We believe he is an SVR asset.
Well, this is all
an enormous relief.
I thought things
might get complicated.
Bottom line:
It was a Russian hit.
They couldn't get close to
Kostenko so they used a drone.
And killed an innocent man.
I don't think
that was part of the plan.
So I assume
they're out of the country?
Well, you assume wrong.
They sprayed out a bunch of decoys
first to see if we tried to pick them up.
They are at a safe house still.
We can arrest them?
Oh, we can.
Question is...
Do we want to?
A nice dilemma
for a new Home Secretary.
Okay, perfect. It is about
two hours wait, I'm afraid.
But you will be on the next bus.
Have you had breakfast? No?
Help yourself to breakfast,
sit wherever you like.
Can you make sure
that first bus is gone by 12:00?
Good morning. Now look, I wasn't
expecting Egyptian cotton or anything
but those sheets
were like sandpaper.
Some nice tinned tomatoes and
bacon fat for breakfast, though.
Are you sure you want
to come out with us?
It's pretty choppy out there.
It's me coming out.
I know.
Why are you looking
at him, then?
Okay, if you insist,
I'll see you down there.
He reminds me of an Action Man
I used to have.
- You had an Action Man?
- I had about six.
You don't have to go out
if you don't want to, you know?
I don't want to.
- Okay...
- But I do have to.
Otherwise, I'll sit around
thinking of how I should have gone
and I'll just drive myself mad.
You might even enjoy it.
Okay.
Okay, targets are on the move.
Leaving early morning
with little traffic.
Easier to spot a trail.
What's happening?
They're moving.
We think it's Stansted, though.
So what are we going to do?
If we let them go,
everything will be a lot easier.
Impunity often is.
There could be consequences
that go beyond diplomatic exchanges.
I know that.
But if we just let them go,
they will know that, too,
and that will also have
consequences down the line.
Okay, then. It's your call.
Yes, it is.
Okay. And over.
So there was another
earth tremor last night.
Yeah.
Any idea of the impact...
That's what we're going
out to take a look at.
- Okay but...
- Sorry and no offense,
but I'm not entirely sure
what the point of you is.
- What the point of me is?
- I meant being here.
Why don't you guys just do your
job and let me do mine, yeah?
No, fair play, it's a question I
do ask myself from time to time.
Okay, well,
the point of me right now is
I am the eyes and ears of the
Civil Contingencies Secretariat.
Now that may not mean
much to you, Captain Pugwash,
but it makes me the eyes and
ears of Number 10 Downing Street,
and hence,
the British Prime Minister.
So if you've got a problem, then I
suggest you take it up directly with him.
Suspects are through security,
Terminal 1.
Okay. Keep eyes on.
Do you want to put
Lightfingers into play?
What's Lightfingers?
A world of pain
for very little reward.
- What?
- -There's still time to abort the mission.
- And it won't bring Graham Hadleigh back.
- -No, no.
You don't get to kill an innocent British
citizen and then just waltz off home
with a new handbag
and a bottle of Johnnie Walker.
Take the bastards in.
Do what he says.
- Again. What's Lightfingers?
- Watch.
Excuse me, Madam.
Would you mind stepping back
into the store for a moment, please?
Yes, I would mind.
They've called my flight,
I haven't done anything.
If you could just show me the
receipt for the item in your bag.
There is no item
in my bag.
What's going on?
Target on the move...
Oi! You! Stop!
Out the way! Move.
Move to the side!
Stop!
Armed Police! Show me your
hands! Get down on the floor!
I am Rodrigo Araya.
I am a Colombian
human rights activist.
They are trying
to make me disappear.
I am a human rights activist!
A human rights activist.
Target in custody.
All officers stand down.
Pull their files for me.
So what now?
Now we charge her with shoplifting
and him with resisting arrest.
- But those are minor...
- -We remand them in custody
on the basis that they are
suspected of other unspecified crimes
and-or the possible commission
of future crimes.
And we...
what, we just wait now?
Yep.
Well, we've chosen
to prod the snake.
Now let's see if it bites
or just rattles a bit.
Update me in an hour.
Please report to one
of our information points.
Jesus.
You all need to make
your way to the buses, now.
The evacuation is mandatory.
What's that?
No idea. I'm getting some...
It might be another tremor?
What the hell
is going on down there?
That's not a tremor.
Bring him up.
Command to Dive Team Alpha,
prepare to surface.
Bring him up!
Run, now! Get to higher ground!
Come on!
Go! Go! Go!
First reports suggest heavy
casualties among emergency teams.
- Have you heard from Fraser?
- No, we can't reach him.
He was down there
with his entire team.
There are mass casualties
on the seafront.
Glass, scalding water,
collapsed masonry.
Have we got a live link yet?
There have been problems
connecting to the feed.
We need to get that link up.
Will someone please tell me what's
going on with our communication system?
SRT to Control, we seem to be
experiencing comms malfunction.
SRT to Control,
are you receiving?
This is SRT, come in, Control.
GCHQ are reporting
a massive cyber-attack.
It's taken out ECON. The new
Emergency Services comms Network.
It means they can't talk to
each other or send us live links.
You know what this is,
don't you?
This is their bloody answer
to the arrests.
No, we can't have this. Not now.
Not in the middle
of a natural disaster.
There's a message embedded in the
malware they've used to crash the system.
- What kind of message?
- Ruin Brittania.
National Cyber Defense have seen
nothing like this before.
Is it Russian?
They have no idea. The signature
coding is like nothing we've seen before.
Is it connected to the
assassination? Who's behind this?
Honestly, we don't have
any information...
Then find out and bring me
some fucking answers!