Grow up.
Sing a song that starts
with the letter 'M'.
- Hey, Insia has got her guitar out.
Quiet, everyone.
- Quiet, everyone.
Secretly, quietly and with care
Patiently I picked a twig here
And a straw there
And built myself a dream
With a stitch here and some knitting there
Collecting little patches
I quilted myself a dream
Oh dream, my dream
Come alive, my dream
Insia...
Is this a new song?
It's really nice. You wrote it?
What are you doing here?
I have an announcement to make.
These are the flyers of an inter-school
cultural competition.
In every category,
the winner gets a laptop
and one year of free internet!
Let me see!
And one more thing, all the best everyone.
Did you have fun, dear?
How was your trip?
I missed you so much.
Let me carry the bag.
You know, on the show Singing Idol,
a little boy auditioned.
Shakti Kumaarr was so hard on him...
it was terrible!
What happened to your eyes?
It's nothing.
I opened the kitchen cabinet,
and the door hit my eye.
You're right.
I'm really stupid.
So, I was saying,
Shakti Kumaarr was so mean
that the poor kid broke down.
I am right.
You really are stupid.
Insu!
Get away!
- Hello!
Hello.
- How was your outing?
Be quiet.
- Did you get me any gifts?
What gifts?
Two chocolates?
No.
- One chocolate?
Shut up.
- Not even one?
No!
- Insia!
Don't you have manners?
You didn't even greet me.
Greetings, Grand-aunt.
Greetings.
Why didn't you get me a gift?
- Get out of here!
Gift... gift. Go!
Why are you screaming at Guddu?
- Guddu...
Up to no good, this mother and daughter!
This one. No, this one.
So, judges, what's your verdict?
Ten points just for cuteness.
Are we judging cuteness?
This is a singing show, Monali. Singing.
I know my job. I'm a judge, too.
You are useless.
He can't sing to save his life.
Kiddo, you're an insult to talent!
You're an insult to talent!
What do you know about talent?
What are you looking at?
Now, get out!
Friends, Mr. Shakti is well knownfor his anger.
And now it is rumoredthat his wife left him last month.
Obviously he's under stress
And frustrated.
Well, his marriage seems to be over,
after the break
our astrologer will predict,
whether Salman will finallyget married this year.
Oh, I completely forgot,
Glamour Awards is on TV tonight.
I remembered.
Who do you think will win Best Singer?
I don't know. It's a tough one.
Best Music Composer?
Anyone... but Shakti Kumaarr.
He has never won an award in any case.
Earlier, he made such good songs.
But nowadays, when I listen to his songs,
it feels like he has remixed
some really nice song,
and that nice song never got made.
Mom...
Potty.
Wait for sometime.
Come.
Let's proceed to the next award,
which isthe 'Best Female Playback Singer'.
And the nominees for this award are:
Monali Thakur...
Sudha Venkat will definitely win.
No, Monali Thakur.
Bet?
- Bet!
Done.
- If I win, I can ask for anything.
Okay.
Mom, I'm done.
He's done.
I am coming.
Push some more. There maybe some left.
Shakti Kummarr!
I'm tired of receiving awards.
I'm tired.
He'll blabber on now.
So, this time I called
Glamour Awards and said,
"Glamour Award, this year Shakti
won't receive the award, he'll give it."
Mom!
- Yes?
I'm done.
So, here I am to give the award
for the Best Singer...
female.
To my protégé, whom I launched.
Monali Thakur.
Come, Mona. Come, babes.
Keep loving me this way
and I'll keep singing such lovely songs.
Thank you so much.
Babes, you're singing
quite well these days.
But, you've been only screaming
at little children nowadays.
Why don't you write some songs?
Who are you to tell me what to do?
I've won the award, haven't I?
I think I've earned the right to speak.
Why are you giving a speech?
Have you won an award?
You used to sing jingles
for toothpaste ads,
I groomed you.
They are arguing on television.
They have no shame.
By the way, I won the bet.
Yes.
So, what do you want?
There's an inter-school
singing competition.
Can I participate?
Okay. But, don't tell your father.
But, if I get selected for the finals
I will have to go to Mumbai.
No, Insu.
Then let it go.
Your father threatens to break
your guitar every now and then!
He'll never allow it.
You said I could ask for anything.
Insu, I said you can ask anything from me.
Not from life.
Listen, I have an idea.
What?
- Come here.
Stop being so gloomy.
Tell me.
Your father will be home late.
- So?
He'll be tired and hungry.
Ask him this question, when he's eating.
He may agree.
Good idea, Mom.
Which song should I sing?
Song...
- Do you know what the first prize is?
A laptop and a year of free internet.
So, think of a good song.
Sing any song.
You'll win for sure.
You're my favorite singer.
Even better than Monali Thakur.
Really.
Go to sleep.
Salam, father.
Can I expect to get some water
in this house?
Yes, Father.
How was your trip?
It was good, Father.
Did you learn anything
or did you just waste your time?
No, Father. It was good.
How are you?
Salam.
Father, there's this...
Father, there is a...
There's less salt.
What?
Come here.
Just coming.
Should I fill my stomach
with your apology?
Can a man not expect a decent meal
after working 17 hours?
Father...
Najma... Have you packed my bag?
- Yes?
Bag?
Are you Najma?
- I'm sorry, Father.
You are leaving day after, right?
What did I say? When was I leaving?
On the third.
What's the date today?
Today is the second.
What does that make tomorrow?
I'm sorry.
- You forget the salt. You forget to pack.
Is there anything you remember?
I'm fed up of you.
Say sorry once more,,
and it won't be the plate, it'll be you.
You go inside, I'll clean it.
Mom, I think you should leave father.
He's not the right husband for you.
Then who is?
Shah Rukh Khan?
Mom, why don't you get it?
I'm not joking.
Insu, I've told you a million times.
Who will take care of us?
There's your school fees...
We can't be depen on your grandfather.
Why grandfather?
Mom, trust me. I'll take care of us.
Really?
What's your plan?
Just trust me, Mom.
Tell me, isn't the destination
decided first and then the route later?
Did the chicken come first or the egg?
What?
It depends on the situation.
Meaning?
Meaning, if you want to eat chicken,
the egg comes first,
it hatches into a chicken, which you cook.
But, if you want to have an omelet,
the chicken comes first,
it lays the egg,
which you make into an omelet.
Oh God, Insu! You have
the answer to every question.
No, Mom.
But, we'll find it, won't we?
Insu, it's impossible to argue with you.
- Then, don't.
Promise me.
What?
If I make a good plan,
you will leave Father.
Insu...
Don't Insu me. Promise me.
Mom, promise me.
Okay... fine...
Go to sleep now. I promise.
-Like a definite promise?
-All right, I promise.
A real promise?
Yes!
Bye.
Come on... quick.
What about our journey?
I am afraid.
Insia.
Insia!
Give me one example of irony.
Did this witch have to ask me
a question right now?
I have just got a tune, If I think
about the answer I'll forget it.
Are you deaf?
Give me one example of irony.
Should I answer or stay with the tune?
Give me our hand.
I said, give me your hand!
Go on, hit me.
You are most welcome.
Guddu, open the door.
How long do you take to open the door?
Sorry... sorry.
Give it to me!
What's this?!
Mom, what's this?!
What?
I have no idea.
Where did it come from, Guddu?
Drama queen!
Mom, how much did it cost?
Thousand rupees per kilo.
Your laptop is more expensive
than mangoes.
Tell me. Where did you get the money from?
It doesn't matter.
Last night if I had added
salt in the food,
then perhaps you would've won this
in the competition.
But, I forgot.
Tell me honestly.
Did you borrow the money?
I can't accept it. Let's return it.
Are you crazy, Insu?
There are so many things in life,
I have not been able to give you,
and nor will I be able to.
Don't rob me of the joy
of seeing you smile.
It comes rarely.
Mom!
Yes?
Look, the world is so big,
and our Baroda is so small.
Is this Baroda?!
Suddenly my eyes have learnt to dance
Suddenly my teeth have learnt to sparkle
It feels like this heart of mine
Has just learnt to laugh
Laugh from the depths of my soul
Suddenly, my hair has learnt to bounce
Suddenly my stains have learnt to vanish
It feels like this heart of mine
Has just learnt to laugh
Laugh from the depths of my soul
Suddenly the windows
Have begun to tickle me
Suddenly the chairs
Suddenly every little thing
Is bringing me joy
Suddenly the curries
Have begun to tickle me
Suddenly the flatbreads
Suddenly every little thing
Is bringing me joy
Who is this?
- No idea, Mom!
Really?
Suddenly every little thing
Is bringing me joy
Why are you still awake at this hour?
Mom, I want to upload
my videos on YouTube.
How wonderful.
Upload your videos on YouTube,
and send it to your father in Riyadh.
You know what will happen next.
I know, Mom.
Insu, it's 3 am.
Stop dreaming and go to sleep.
How is that possible, Mom?
First you tell me to sleep,
then you ask me not to dream?
When I sleep won't I end up dreaming?
You tell me, why do we
wake up every morning?
So that we can realize our dreams.
Otherwise, what's the point
of waking up every day?
Mom, there is no point
to anything without dreams.
Neither to sleep, nor to wake up.
Neither to live, nor to die.
Mom, to dream is a basic right!
Everyone should be allowed this much.
- Insu, how much you talk!
Tell me in one line, what do you want?
Tell me, what is your dream?
What do I want?
Mom, I want the whole world
to hear my voice.
Not just school, or Baroda, or India.
The whole world should know me
as the best singer.
Not just you.
That's my dream, too.
And I'm sure it will come true.
Go to sleep now.
Let it be, Mom.
It's useless talking to you.
Insu.
I have an idea.
What?
What are you doing?
Wait.
Here.
What's this?
An idea.
It's not an idea, it's a burqa.
Exactly!
What do you mean?
I should wear this and make videos?
- Yes.
You want the entire world
to hear you, right?
Why do they have to see your face?
They should hear you.
It does matter, Mom. How absurd?
It's a horrible idea.
I want to be famous
and you tell me to hide my face?
No. You don't understand.
Listen to me.
I'm not telling you
to change your destination.
Just change your route.
You should allow that much.
No, Mom. It's a stupid idea.
It will never work.
To all those who are watching me,
this is my first YouTube video.
My name is...
I can't tell you all my name.
But if you like this video
please click 'like'.
Can someone tell me, where am I?
Can someone tell me, where I stand?
Have I chosen the correct path?
Should I embark on this journey?
I fear my dreams
Will they destroy me?
I fear those close to me
Will they betray me?
Am I the moon?
Or the shadows in it?
Am I the ashes?
Or the raging fire?
Am I the drop?
Or the mighty wave?
Do I bring tranquility?
Or do I unleash a storm?
Can someone tell me, who am I?
Do I have a purpose?
A reason to be? Who am I?
Do I believe in myself?
Does my existence even matter?
Whose shoulder do I cry onShould I falter?
Who will guide me
Should I lose my way?
Am I the moon?
Or the shadows in it?
Am I the ashes?
Or the raging fire?
Am I the drop?
Or the mighty wave?
Do I bring tranquility?
Or do I unleash a storm?
Should I live my truth?
Or remain silent?
Should I bear my soul?
Or break my heart?
Should I cross all boundaries?
Or rein myself in?
Should I keep fighting?
Or just give up?
Am I the moon?
Or the shadows in it?
Am I the ashes?
Or the raging fire?
Am I the drop?
Or the mighty wave?
Do I bring tranquility?
Or do I unleash a storm?
Who am I?
I knew it was a stupid idea.
Your mother put me in a fix.
I already have so many children.
I shouldn't have taken you in.
Everyone knows that I don't take
more than 45 children.
I'm sorry, ma'am. It won't happen again.
Come, now.
Find a place.
Yes, ma'am.
- It's 1173K.
And 1973K.
Ma'am, there's no other place to sit.
What is it?
You came late to class.
So, if you want notes,
I can share them with you.
Okay.
Hey, Insia.
I added you on Facebook.
You didn't respond.
Are we friends?
- Are we not?
Chintan.
Tell me.
Do you have the trigonometry sums solved?
Yes, I do.
You can copy them.
I'll wait outside your house.
Are you a watchman?
No.
You can come inside.
Okay.
Insu.
Lay the table.
Mom!
Mom.
Insu. Easy.
- Come here.
Calm down.
Look, Mom.
This is your video!
Yes, and guess how many people
have watched it?
11,470 people!
Seriously?
- Yes.
I have never even met
so many people in my life.
All thanks to this laptop.
Your idea worked, Mom.
I told you, didn't I?
Now I'll be a superstar, too!
Insu, listen...
everyone knows a superstar.
You'll have to remain a secret.
Or your father will throw us
out of the house along with this laptop.
Try to understand.
- Don't worry, Mom.
Insu.
I mean it.
Your father shouldn't get to know.
How will Father know?
Father doesn't watch YouTube.
Promise. Nothing will happen.
Alright.
Before your grand-aunt yells,
I'll serve dinner.
Listen. Come here.
What is it now, Mom?
- Your father will be back tomorrow.
He's going to be home all day.
Please keep this thing shut.
Mom, when will Father
get that job in Riyadh?
Once he does, he will be
out of our lives for 11 months, right?
Yes, and during Ramadan,
he'll be in the house 24 hours.
Only one month, right? We'll bear with it.
It's not a bad deal.
Hey, what's your name?
You are so talented.
Your videos are damn good.
Do you have a Twitter account
or a Facebook page?
So sad!
You can't show your face?
How does it matter
if she shows her face or not?
What an amazing voice this child has!
Otherwise, videos nowadays are short
on both talent and clothes.
You have such an amazing voice.
When do we get to see your next video?
Thank you.
You are not sleepy either?
It's 3 am.
I'm in New York.
It's 5.30 in the evening here.
Mom.
Mom, people in New York
are watching my video, too.
Mom.
Salam.
All well?
Yes.
How's Guddu?
He's fine.
What's this?
Where did it come from?
Brother sent it.
No one was using it at his house.
Has your brother ever sent anything new?
He likes dumping his trash here.
Aunt.
Shah Rukh Khan's film is showing.
Do you want to watch it?
- Since your uncle passed away,
I haven't gone to the theater.
Shall we go, then?
- That's a great idea.
Insu, too, has been wanting
to watch a film.
Doesn't Insia have assignments to do?
Aren't the 10th grade exams important?
Films, television, guitar...
Stop everything this year.
And now this laptop...
What use is it?
Come here.
It is very difficult to find a match
for an illiterate, uneducated girl.
I got stuck. Not everyone will.
I'm sorry.
Be careful, Aunt.
Hello, everyone.
Thank you for your likes and comments.
Here's my second video.
This song is for my mom.
She's a little cute
And a little stern too
She's a little cool
And a little old school too
She's like a sweet, chilled juice
On a hot summer day
She's like a warm blanket
On a freezing winter night
My dearest mom
She's my dearestMy mom
When I'm troubled
She's all tears
In my joy, too
Her tears make her scarf wet
With every tear drop
She weaves blessings
Will someone tell me
Are all moms are like this?
Sometimes she's practical
And sometimes she's emotional
Her one smile
Dispels all my worries
She's like a master key
Which opens all the locks to my fortunes
I've placed in her care
All my trunks, full of dreams
My dearest mom
She's my dearestMy mom
Chintan.
Does ma'am yell at you?
Yes.
She yells at me more.
Hey!
Ma'am, I'm done.
So fast?
- Yes.
Show it to me.
Wait a minute, Insia.
What's this?
Teacher, I'll come prepared tomorrow
and take the test again.
Get your mom to sign this.
Your mom pleaded with me
to take you in this class.
Taking you in was a waste of my time.
It wasn't the pleading,
it was double the fees that worked on you!
Oh, really?
Your father is the one
paying me 'double fees'.
My fees come from his hard earned money.
So, get his signature too.
I'm so sorry, ma'am. I didn't mean...
Go, get the signatures.
I'm sorry, ma'am. Please...
Go or I will call your home.
Get the signatures.
Ma'am, I'm done too.
Insia, what happened?
I'm sorry.
Hey, this is you, isn't it?
What? What rubbish?
And what are you doing here?
I've seen all your videos.
I had a feeling it's you.
Because I recognize your voice.
Everyone at school watches your videos.
Who else knows?
I don't think anyone else knows. Only me.
Hey, just a minute!
You don't want anyone to know,
that's why you wear a burqa, right?
Insu?
Chintan, please take this newspaper
and leave.
And don't tell anyone about this, please.
Okay. Don't worry.
I keep everyone's secrets.
I never reveal anyone's secrets.
Thanks, Chintan.
By the way,
can I tell you one of my secrets?
Sure.
Well...
What?
- Not because you are a superstar.
I swear to God!
I've loved you way before that.
You must have felt it too?
Leave. I have to go home.
Should I go?
Go.
Najma.
- Yes?
Have you taken the newspaper?
The newspaper hasn't come today.
Welcome back, guys.
Bollywood's news...
Be sure to deduct his money.
Today's not a holiday.
Sure.
- Secret Superstar.
- Anonymous, yet famous.
- Who is this mysterious girl
who won't show us her face?
- Is this a marketing strategy?
- If not, then who is this person,
who has taken the Internet by storm
in barely four months?
- Friends... you must've heard...
Father, look at this dinosaur...
I'm sorry, Father.
Why are you always in a hurry, Guddu?
- Coco Money Singh's song
has got one million views.
But our Secret Superstar
has got thirty million views!
Not just that,
her song 'Who Am I?' is trending
on number one on YouTube.
- And Superstar Amitabh Bachchan himself
has tweeted about this song.
This afternoon the All India committee
of the Singers' Association,
has boycotted music composer
Mr. Shakti Kumaarr.
The committee is deeply upset
with the way he yelled at a small child,
on the Singing Idol show.
The situation is such
that no singer is ready to singfor Shakti Kumaarr's new film.
- Now, the producer will have no choice
but to replace him.
By the way,
it's Zahir's daughter's wedding tomorrow.
You have to come, too.
And there's no need to wear a burqa there.
They are very modern. They won't like it.
Guddu, you come with us too.
Hi, ma'am
I'm in love with you.
I haven't seen your face,
but I love your voice.
Bye!
Babes, I saw your video.
Hiding your face, eh?
Naughty... naughty!
You have a pretty good voice.
Not bad. You have potential.
If you want to make your future,
then call Shakti.
Yuck!
- My number is 98200...
Couldn't A.R. Rahman have emailed instead?
Go on, talk to him.
What happened?
Father, we had a science test.
The same? 50 percent again?
No, Father, this was just a test
at the private tuition.
I will study harder for the school exams.
How much did you score?
-Thirty.
-Out of?
Hundred.
You failed?
Yes, Father.
But this was a surprise test.
I was totally unprepared.
Had I known earlier,
I would've gone prepared.
I need your signature on this.
Father, look how strictly
she has assessed it.
Get me your guitar.
What?
Father, I'm sorry.
I'll study well for the school exams.
I will score 70 percent.
70 percent? You can't even pass!
I said, bring me your guitar.
I'm sorry, Father.
Don't make me ask you again.
Don't restring it till I tell you to.
How is this connected to my exams?
Even if I don't play, I could still fail!
Insu! Is this how you talk to your father?
Apologize to him. Listen.
- What did you say?
I'm sorry.
She's just a child. Let her go.
Are you doing me a favor by apologizing?
I'm sorry.
- Let her go.
Insu.
Why are you irritating me, Chintan?
Go away.
I'm sorry. Take care.
Say 'Who's there'.
I have a great 'knock, knock' joke.
Why are you bugging me, Chintan?
"Hi, Insia!"
"I see you're in a bad mood."
"I'm a lollipop."
"Why don't you eat me?"
Are you a pet dog?
Why do you always follow me?
Why are you so obsessed with me?
What's your problem?
I've told you off
four times since morning.
But you don't understand.
Because you have no self-respect.
I'm sorry.
I'm extremely sorry.
You're looking like a star.
Come on... hurry up.
How much longer?
I'm coming. Just a minute longer.
Insu, eat your food.
And serve grand-aunt, too.
We'll be late.
Shall we go?
- Yes.
Will you come like this?
What's wrong?
Something's missing.
Wear that gold necklace
your father gave you, the cheap one.
Otherwise, people will think
that this engineer husband
can't even buy his wife a necklace.
I don't know where I've kept it.
If I start looking for it now,
it'll get very late.
Let's go.
- It's not like we live in a palace!
It's a small house.
Look for it. I'll wait.
I remember now.
It's in the bank locker.
Have you taken sleeping pills?
We gave up the locker four months ago.
Don't waste time. Go... find it.
Actually, I forgot to tell you.
I left it at my brother's house.
You had worn it on Eid.
We haven't met your brother after that.
Don't bullshit me!
Go inside.
I said, find it. That's it!
Nonsense!
- Come, I'll help you find it.
I'll wait here.
Mom, you sold the necklace
to buy the laptop?
What else could I do?
There was nothing else to sell.
Why did you sell the gold necklace?
What should we tell Father now?
I don't know, Insu.
What should we do?
I'll say that I've kept it somewhere.
I can't find it.
Will Father believe you?
I don't know, Insu.
I don't know what to say.
I'll have to say something.
There's no other way out.
I'll say I've misplaced it.
Let's try that.
I'm looking for it. I'll find it.
Insu, look there in that box.
I must've kept it there.
Look in that box below.
Can't find it.
Sell the house next without asking me.
Father, listen...
- Did I speak to you?
Father, but...
I was going to tell you.
Father... listen...
Father, I had insisted... Listen, Father.
Stand here.
Father, listen to me.
I'll definitely sell the laptop tomorrow.
And we will buy a similar necklace.
Father, it's my fault, not hers.
Insia, take Guddu and go inside.
I'm telling you the truth.
Mom had nothing to do with this.
Didn't you hear me?
Take Guddu and go inside.
Father, it's not her fault.
I'm responsible for this.
Do you want your brother to see this?
Do you?
You should definitely be seeing this
because it's all your fault.
She really had nothing to do with this.
Father...
Insu.
Take Guddu inside.
Go. Go inside.
- Tell me, what else you have sold.
- Don't tell me later, you sold this
and that and forgot to tell me.
- What are you looking down for?
- Look at me. I'm asking you something.
- Yes? I'm asking you.
- Answer me.
- Tell me.
- Who am I? Am I a dog?
- Am I your servant?
- Put a leash around my neck
and tie me outside.
- Is this what I'm worth?
- Who do you think I am?
- Will you say something?
- Or have you gone mute? Mistake? How?
- How? Did it happen on its own?
- You must've planned it.
- So you didn't plan it?
- Was it involuntary?
- Tell me.
Father, stop it, please.
I don't want the laptop. You can sell it.
I'm admitting that it's my fault.
Right. The laptop.
Where is it?
Najma. Go and get the laptop.
Laptop.
Hurry up.
Throw it out.
Why are you looking at her?
Oh, right! It's your laptop.
And you are the one who wanted it.
So, you should throw it out.
Today, let's turn to page number 22
of our Gujarati textbooks.
We shall recite this beautiful poem called
Mane Joine Udi Jata Pakshi.
Which means,
the birds who fly at my sight.
You are angry, right? Because you
insulted me in front of everyone?
You are the one who should be angry.
I'm sorry.
Actually, that was my trick.
Yes, I do the same thing with my mom.
When she's in a bad mood,
I try to cheer her up.
Instead, she yells at me.
And when she does that,
she releases her anger.
Then she's back to normal.
So, I thought I should use
the same trick on you.
No problem. It's okay.
Flatbread?
It's the best flatbread in the universe.
Then I'll have to eat it.
You both are friends now, right?
You read his tweet?
I read all your tweets.
And the ones by your fans, too.
That music composer, Shakti Kumaarr,
has also sent you a tweet.
Call him.
You can be a playback singer in his film.
I won't call him.
Why?
- He's not a nice man.
Do you know him?
No!
Then how do you know
that he's not a nice person?
I've seen it on the news.
And his wife left him, too.
So, he must not be a nice man.
My mom left my dad, too.
But he is not a bad man.
My mom told me.
I'm sorry, Chintan... I didn't know.
It's not your fault.
Mom tells me, it's nobody's fault.
Will you do me a favor?
Sure, tell me.
My laptop broke.
Will you check my email?
And post on Facebook and Twitter
that I won't be uploading videos
for some time.
Due to some personal problem.
And, do you want to say anything
to Shakti Kumaarr?
Insia, what's your password?
Give me a pen.
Go... sit!
Chintan.
Chintan!
- Yes?
Your stop.
Oh... I see.
I'll get off at the next stop.
Next stop... for sure.
What's your mom like?
Mom is like a child.
What do you mean?
You know how children are cute
but so naive.
Always scared.
And very stupid.
You have to always explain
what's right for them, and what's not.
Yet they never get it.
Mom is exactly like that.
Absolutely stupid.
How do you know?
Know what?
About children.
Do you have any?
I'm sorry. I'm just joking.
There are two boys.
This one beats the other.
And he falls into the water...
Salam, Father.
Salam.
How are you, child?
I'm fine. Guddu, open your mouth.
What are we celebrating?
Aunt, I've got that job in Riyadh.
In one of the Sheikh's oil rigs.
As a senior engineer.
Very good.
Did you hear?
- Yes.
Here, have some.
That's such good news.
I'll make a thanks-giving prayer
tomorrow at the mausoleum.
Why not?
And tonight, we'll all eat out.
You come too.
Okay, Father.
Here, take it.
You've grown up so much.
In these last few months,
enjoy your freedom.
Then you'll have to start a new life
in a new country.
Right?
Did you know, Zahir's friend lives there?
He's the vice president
of the company I'll be working for.
He has a son.
Razzaq.
He has a travel agency.
He also has a license for Hajj tours.
He's a good boy. You will like him.
Look. He has also sent some photographs.
You knew all along, didn't you?
That if Father got this job, we'll all
have to move with him to Saudi Arabia.
I didn't think he'd get the job, Insu.
Forget it, Mom.
I don't want to talk to you.
At least listen to me...
- Mom, please.
Insu.
Everything will be okay.
What will be okay?
How?
Mom, I'm telling you let's run away.
Where will we go, Insu?
How does it matter?
Anyway, in this house,
no one cares about us.
He just cares about Guddu, doesn't he?
We'll leave Guddu behind.
What rubbish, Insu!
If we leave Guddu here,
he will grow up to be
exactly like his father.
So what's the point of our lives?
That we make Guddu
two percent better than him?
What about our lives?
Insu.
Some things are beyond our control.
Wrong, Mom. Wrong!
Everything is in our control.
There's nothing that we can't do.
I'm telling you, Mom.
I'm not going to Saudi Arabia.
I'll run away.
And you shouldn't go either.
Mom, I'll plan something.
Insu...
- Insu... Insu... Insu!
It's useless talking to you.
Shakti Kumaarr's lifehas taken a new twist.
The Mumbai Family Court
has ruled against him.
And his wife has won the case.
His wife's lawyer, Sheena Sabavala,
has proved in the court,
that he has not one,
not two, but three affairs!
And that too, simultaneously!
Here's what Shakti Kumaarr had to say.
Sir, you lost the case. How do you feel?
Bullshit. It's all rubbish.
My wife's lawyer, Sheena Sabavala,has lied in court.
I will appeal to the Supreme court.
But are the rumors
about your affairs true?
Shut up, you...
- Sir, please, sir.
Now, let's meet the enemy
of such men, Sheena Sabavala.
Ma'am, tell us aboutShakti Kumaarr's case.
Shakti Kumaarr is an ill-mannered
and disgusting man.
I'm very happy with the court's decision.
It's important to teach a lesson
to men like Shakti.
If I'm not mistaken
this is Advocate Sheena Sabavala's11th victory this year.
Which means, she has ruined the lives
of 11 men in this one year alone.
Sheena Sabavala has a perfect
track record in family court.
Whether she's up against
a music composer or a mafia don,
So, all the menwho are watching this show...
Chintan.
Come.
I have some work. You carry on.
Okay.
I've saved it. It's in 'contacts'.
But... there's a problem.
What's the problem?
I recharge the phone with my allowance.
There's no money left
on the phone, and I'm broke.
So, I can't call?
No. You can give him a missed call.
- A missed call?
Why will he call me back?
He will. Give it a try.
How do you know he will call back?
I have my fingers crossed!
Try once more, please.
I'm sorry. Tomorrow I'll take an advance
on my allowance.
It's okay. Forget it.
Chintan, go home.
Don't irritate me. I want to be alone.
I'm headed to your building.
My friend stays there.
Which friend?
Jignesh.
There's no Jignesh in my building.
Oh, sorry.
I thought every building in Baroda
would have at least one Jignesh.
Chintan, please don't try
your tricks on me again.
Go home.
- I'm sorry.
Insia... Insu...
He called back. Come quickly!
Hello. Mr. Shakti?
Insia Mallik...
My videos are on the internet
by the name of Secret Superstar.
Yes sir, the girl in the burqa.
Sorry, it's my friend's phone.
There's no calling balance on his phone.
So...
Sir, Baroda.
Today?
Not today, sir.
Tomorrow?
Yes, sir. Tomorrow.
But sir, I have one condition.
If the recording goes well,
then you have to help me.
That I'll tell you tomorrow.
Promise, sir?
A real promise?
Thank you, sir.
Sir, can I... can you call me back
in two minutes, please?
Thank you, sir.
He wants me to go to Mumbai
tomorrow, to record a song.
Chintan, how will I go?
By aeroplane.
Yes, I know.
He said he'll book the flight
and send an airport pickup.
You'll have to skip school tomorrow.
I'll give you the class notes.
And anyway, you don't do your assignments.
By the time school finishes,
you come back.
What if someone sees me?
You are the 'Secret Superstar'. 'Secret!'
There's one more problem.
I've never flown before.
- I'll make a plan by tomorrow.
Insu, wait...
- Mom, I'm getting late.
Bye, Insu.
- Wait for two minutes.
Hang on.
At least take your lunch box.
- Your mom drops you off at the bus stop.
So, you have to get on it.
- Don't worry about the ticket.
- Here's your ticket.
- I'll get its printout.
Come on, Insu. Hurry up!
- The bus drops us off
inside the school gate.
- So, you'll have to make
your escape from school.
- As soon as you reach school,
go to the girls toilet.
- And, jump out from there.
Oh, no!
- I know an escape route.
- I figured in case of a terrorist attack,
I must have an escape plan.
Chintan, there's a lock on this!
- Lock?
Now what?
I'll think of something.
I'll be late for the flight.
It won't break!
What are you doing?
Wait.
You'll have to jump the wall.
Have you lost it?
Do you have a better idea?
How will I get back inside?
I have eight hours to figure that out.
I'll think of something.
Come on, give me your bag.
Put one foot here.
And one foot there.
Yes.
Land on your feet
or else you will hurt yourself.
Are you okay?
Yes, and you?
I'm fine.
Listen...
Yes?
The airport, please.
Please drive faster.
- At the airport,
show your school ID and ticket.
Stop!
- If questioned,
say that your grandfather is unwell.
Are you traveling alone?
My grandfather is unwell.
Okay.
- At the airline counter,
ask for a window seat.
Mister, that's my seat.
It's a short flight.
Sit anywhere you want.
But the window seat is mine.
How does it matter?
I'm already sitting here. You sit there.
Mister, that's my seat. Get up!
- Don't forget to fasten your seat belt.
- When the plane takes off, you'll see...
- how big the world is
and how small Baroda is.
- Your bad mood, your father,
Ms. Sheetal...
- leaving everyone behind,
you will fly away.
- I'll wave to you from down here,
but you won't be able to see me.
Do you need an auto-rickshaw?
A taxi?
A hotel?
Where do you want to go?
Secret Superstar?
No.
I'm the airport pickup.
I'm Ranjeet.
Come.
Has Shakti Kumaarr sent you?
Yes, ma'am. Shakti Kumaarr has sent me.
Now, shall we? Or else we'll be late.
Come on.
Unions don't operate on relationships,
but money.
Give as much as you want.
I'll call you back.
What a voice!
My pleasure to meet you, kiddo.
What an interesting journey!
Baroda, Burqa, YouTube,
Shakti Kumaarr and then...
Superstar!
I'll host a launch event for you.
At a five-star hotel. Big time!
Industry, media, trade.
I'll buy the front page
of Mumbai Times for you.
Babes, don't mind,
but your name is low on glamour.
What does it mean? Your name? Insia?
It means 'woman'.
Oh! Woman...
Woman.
It sounds awful and it's meaning is worse.
What about Shabnam?
Too old fashioned.
Sunny?
- That name has been taken.
Natashha!
Natashha with a double H.
N-A-T-A-S-S-H-A. Natashha.
Sir.
I'm sorry but my identity
needs to remain a secret.
If my dad finds out, I'll be dead meat.
Look, sooner or later
the media will find out.
Whether I tell them or not.
Anyway, we are short on time.
The shoot for the song is in two days.
The album releases in two weeks.
And the film, in two months.
And you have to get back
to school in six hours.
Ali, play the song.
I'll speak your words
I'll sing your praises
I'll adorn myselfWith the colors of your love
Oh, I dance wild and free
For you, my sexy lover!
My sexy lover!
It's a superhit, kiddo.
Everything is by the grace of God.
On the mic, kiddo.
Ranjeet, take her to the mic.
- Okay.
Come on.
Ali, is everything ready?
- Yes, sir.
Okay, well done.
It's definitely a hit, kiddo. A superhit!
Just sing it.
Come on, go for it.
Sir, I need two minutes.
Let's start. Ready. Come on.
Go for it, kiddo.
Not like this, kiddo.
Don't you get it?
Do one thing. Start from the verse.
We'll patch the moaning later.
- Yes, sir.
I'll speak your words
I'll sing your praises
I'll adorn myself with...
This is not a hymn, kiddo.
Sing it with feeling.
Get the feeling of the song.
I'll speak your words
I'll sing your praises
You are making a mistake.
You are singing from your head.
Do you know where
you should be singing from?
Heart, sir. From the heart.
Doomed!
She wants to sing from the heart.
You don't have to sing
from your heart, kiddo.
You have to sing with your body.
Meaning?
- Body language.
Body language.
Okay?
You know what, you need
to loosen up. Open up a little.
Try jogging.
Jogging?
- Yes.
Where?
- Right there. Spot jogging.
Come on, I'll show you.
Yes, go for it. Knees up.
Yes, well done. Very good.
Come on. Very good, kiddo.
Buck up, India... buck up, India.
I'll praise your words
I'll word your song
Come on. Go for it.
I'll...
I'll sing your praises
I'll adorn myself
Listen, you won't be able to do it.
Ranjeet will drop you off to the airport.
There's a huge difference
between singing at home,
and singing in front of the mic.
It's not everyone's cup of tea.
You... go back to school.
Sir, I need to use the toilet.
- You know Insu, earlier,
he made such good songs.
- But nowadays,
when I listen to his songs,
- it feels like he has remixed
some really nice song,
- and that nice song never got made.
I told you, she's not good enough.
But you didn't listen.
As it is, no one wants to work with you.
Why are you trying to destroy my film?
I'll find someone.
- Who are you going to find?
Should I sing it by myself?
Please leave this film. Spare me.
- Sir.
Sir, can you step out
for a minute, please?
What is it?
I want to talk to you in private.
What's up? What's the problem?
Sir, I feel the problem is not with me,
it's with your song.
I see.
You mean there's no problem with you.
The problem is with my song.
Wow... wow! Amazing! I like it!
That's a new one. Amazing!
Sir, I'm not a professional singer.
- I can see that.
Sir, actually I'm a listener.
Ever since I was born...
my mom made me listen
to Bollywood songs... new, old, all!
So?
What am I supposed to do?
I've no interest in your nonsense.
But you should be interested
in my nonsense!
I read in the news,
that the Singers' Association
has boycotted you.
Who are they to boycott me?
I boycott them. Scram! Boycott!
Sir, let me finish.
Your song is a romantic song,
but the tune is upbeat.
The lyrics are good,
but you've ruined them with innuendos.
It feels like a remixed version
of a great song, which never got made!
My mom says that, too.
This song should be one
from the heart...
- 2007.
What?
I made this song ten years ago in 2007.
This is the remix version.
The producer kept asking for a party song.
I spun it around.
This isn't the original.
Your words and thoughtsWill flow from me
In your praise and devotionWill I always sing
In robes weaved of your love
I'll dress myself
And merge into your colors
With ornaments bejeweled with your love
I'll decorate myself
And merge into your radiance
I dance wild and free
Adorned in you, my love!
Sir, this is what I will sing.
Exactly this way.
Nowadays, everyone wants a fast song.
Sir, that's not true.
Have you heard the songs of Aashiqui 2?
There are no fast songs in the album.
Yet it was a super hit.
So sir, let me try it once.
I'll sing it just the way you did.
The producer won't agree.
Sir, let me try once.
Not with 'body language',
but from the heart.
Just once. For my sake?
I see.
For your sake?
Sir, it's a lovely song.
But can I remove the word 'sexy', please?
Shakti had added that word.
Remove it.
Ali, cancel this session.
Load the one from 2007. The old one.
I'm trying a new version. Check it out.
Sir, the slow version?
Why? Do you have a problem?
Your words and thoughts
Will flow from me
In your praise and devotion
Will I always sing
In robes weaved of your love
I'll dress myself
And merge into your colors
With ornaments bejeweled with your love
I'll decorate myself
And merge into your radiance
I dance wild and free
Adorned in you, my love
Resonating with you, my love
I've lost my bearings
The world taunts
I'm beyond consciousness, beyond reason
I've lost myself, they say
I've lost my identity to you
They scorn me
But what do they know
The mysteries of this heart?
By losing myself
And realizing you
I've found myself, I'm complete
I'm one with myself.
I'll abandon all ties
And come to you
All evil aimed at you
Let it befall me
In robes weaved of your love
I'll dress myself
And merge into your colors
With ornaments bejeweled with your love
I'll decorate myself
And merge into your radiance
I dance wild and free
Adorned in you, my love
Resonating with you, my love
I dance wild and free
Adorned in you, my love
Resonating with you, my love
Wow!
You have no idea
how I'm feeling right now.
I feel as though
this was the first recording of my life.
You won't understand.
Sir, actually this really was
the first recording of my life.
With ornaments bejeweled with your love
I'll decorate myself
Sir, I want to discuss something with you.
Yes, tell me. What is it?
Sir, I want your help.
Your fees, yes. Sorry.
Your friend's name is... Yes, Chintan.
Should I send him your check?
- No, sir. I don't want money.
I just need your help.
Kiddo, once this song releases,
you won't need anyone's help.
Producers and music composers
will line up outside your house.
Sir, aren't you divorced?
What do you mean?
Your wife left you.
She's taken your kids, too.
Yes, so?
I want to meet your wife's lawyer.
I want to get my parents divorced.
What? Why?
I'm sorry. I can understand.
Don't worry. I'll help you.
I'll call my lawyer right away.
Kamlesh is a fantastic lawyer.
No, sir. Not your lawyer.
But your wife's lawyer.
Who? Sheena Sabavala?
She's crazy.
Sir, you promised.
Yes, and I'm not refusing you.
I'm helping you.
Hi, Kamlesh.
- Your 'fantastic' lawyer lost your case.
Kamlesh... listen... I'll...
I'll call you back.
What do you mean by 'Who?'
Don't pretend you don't know. Hello!
I know you're busy. I'm not free either.
I haven't called for small talk.
I have important work. Need to meet.
We'll talk when we meet.
No, this isn't about my divorce.
It's another matter.
It's about a girl...
Age? What's your age?
- I'm 15.
She's 15 years old.
How can you even think like that?
You've gone crazy. You're mad!
I will take you to the Supreme Court.
I tried. You saw me.
You saw what happened.
Hello, Sheena.
Listen to me.
I'm an ill-mannered person. You're right.
Listen to me, babes! I'm begging you.
Not for me. It's for this little girl.
This innocent child.
Please.
She just needs half an hour. That's all.
Can we come now?
Next month?
No, babes, that's too late.
Next week? It's an emergency.
Next week?
Next week, good.
Witch!
So, see you next week.
I'll send your ticket to your boyfriend.
What's his name? Yes, Chintan.
Sir, he's not my boyfriend.
- What?
He's not your boyfriend?
Then why are you blushing?
Chintan!
Mom, the materials I need
for my project are missing.
Insu. We bought it just a few days ago.
Where can it disappear?
Did you leave it in school?
Mom, how will I complete
my school project now?
Guddu, get ready for bed.
Guddu...
Have you seen my glue bottle?
And my brown tape?
No?
Do you want me to slap you?
Mom, tell him not to touch my stuff.
Guddu, how many times have I told you
not to touch her things?
I was making a gift for Insu.
There's no need to make me a gift.
Airport, please.
Come, kiddo.
Babe, tell Sheena that Shakti is here.
She's busy.
Please wait.
- Oh. Busy?
"Please wait."
Come, kiddo.
Oh my... I'm heart broken.
No, thanks.
I'm better off "thirsty".
You go.
Ma'am.
My dad...
he beats my mother...
for every little thing.
Once, Mom forgot to turn on
the water heater.
He fractured her bone.
Babes, have you heard my new song?
Which one, 'Soft and Tender'?
No, that's old now.
The new song is...
'Rough and Ready'.
Look, Insia. This is a difficult case.
Firstly, Guddu and you are minors.
Furthermore, your mom's
financial situation isn't strong.
Anyway, I will prepare a file for you.
Take it home.
Read it to your mom
and tell her what's written in it.
Explain it to her. Okay?
And then get her to sign on it.
Alright, ma'am.
The lines on your palm tells me
that there's a new love in your life.
Here.
Ma'am, I can't afford your fees...
Don't worry. She's a very cheap lawyer.
I'll handle it. Come.
Listen.
No, dear. I was talking to him.
Perhaps you are not as bad as you seem.
Sir, may I ask you something?
Why are you helping me?
Kiddo, actually...
Our stories are very similar.
How's that?
You know, in the past ten years,
I've been divorced twice.
My brother sued me.
I pretty much have no family.
This film industry is my family.
It's my mom, sister., family..
And, this film industry too,
has never given me an ounce of love.
They nominate me every year,
but have never given me an award.
How does this make our stories similar?
Anyways...
how did you learn to play the guitar?
I was six years old.
My mom got me a guitar.
Sir, I want to relocate to Mumbai.
With my mom.
I want proper training in music.
Then, maybe I can be
a part of Singing Idol, too.
Kids like you don't need Singing Idol.
Then how will I become a superstar?
You will become one anyway.
Talented kids like you are...
How do I explain?
You are like bubbles in soda.
You see these bubbles?
It's rising one by one, right?
So?
Talented kids are like that.
They rise like this. On their own.
Nothing can stop them.
No problem, kiddo.
Just call me
if you have any problems, okay?
Tell Chintan to give me a missed call
once you've reached home safely.
Take care, kiddo.
Mom, get down, I want to talk to you.
Not now, Insu.
Hurry up and start chopping
the vegetables.
Mom, get down.
Not now. Later...
- Mom, it's very important. Get down.
Goodness.
What is it?
Sit.
Mom, I... I had gone to Mumbai.
Shakti Kumaarr, the composer,
had sent me an email.
He called me to Mumbai to record a song.
The recording went very well.
After that Mr. Shakti got me
to meet a lawyer.
She's a famous lawyer in Mumbai.
She has given me these divorce papers.
Please take a look at them.
Mom, please leave Dad.
Then we won't have to go to Saudi Arabia.
I'll become a famous singer.
And Mr. Shakti said that he would help.
You went to Mumbai?
When?
Last week. And today.
Mom, the plan is ready.
In a plane?
Alone?
And school?
Mom, I was going to tell you, but...
- Have you grown up so much,
that you'll go to Mumbai alone?
You'll get your parents divorced?
But Mom, I told you that I had a plan.
What were you thinking?
If something had happened to you,
how would I know?
You met a lawyer, too!
What were you thinking?
You thought,
you'll get your parents divorced?
Did you ask me
whether I want a divorce or not?
And what is this nonsense about divorce?
What has your dad done?
Don't you know what he has done?
He beats you up all the time.
He has a bad temper.
-He doesn't have control. Which man...
-Please, Mom!
What sort of a life are we living?
We aren't even allowed to breathe.
Now, he will take us to Saudi.
Marry me off to someone like him.
Without even asking me.
-I'll suffer the same fate as you.
-Insu.
Everyone has their limitations.
- But I don't, Mom.
Mom, trust me. I'll make everything okay.
What will you do?
My father didn't ask me
before getting me married.
My daughter didn't ask me
if I want a divorce.
No one cares about what I want.
Whatever, Mom!
I won't go to Saudi.
- That's it, Insu.
This is my world.
And this is your world, too!
And in our reality, I've given you
as much freedom as I could.
But, don't dream of flying beyond this.
Don't!
We are going to Saudi with your dad.
I won't let your education stop,
I promise.
But my dream of becoming a singer
will never come true.
Don't argue with me.
We are going to Saudi with your dad.
I won't go to Saudi.
I can't believe how you can be so stupid.
Doesn't it make any difference to you?
My life will be wasted, Mom.
You are such a coward that
you can't do anything for your daughter!
The gift?
It isn't ready yet.
Give it to me. It's not done yet.
Insia.
Now apologize to your mom.
I won't apologize to mom.
It's her fault. Not mine.
Her biggest mistake
is that she gave birth to you.
Your dad had said,
"What will you do with a girl?"
"Abort her."
Najma was adamant.
Everyone beat her up.
They dragged her to the doctor.
Then?
The doctor said, "It's late today."
"We will operate on her tomorrow."
They kept her in the hospital all night.
Didn't you say anything?
I constantly wonder
why my mother didn't abort me?
What good has my life been?
And mom? The operation?
The next day,
when we went to the hospital,
your mom had escaped.
Ten months later,
when she returned with you,
she said, "Next time if it's a girl,
we could abort."
"Let's keep her."
"This is my Insia."
Where was I born?
And where was Mom?
How does it matter?
After all, it's your mom's fault,
not yours. Right?
Why should you apologize?
Listen.
Najma never wanted you to know all this.
Don't tell her you know.
Do you understand?
But...
The joy I'm having in telling you this
is nothing compared to the joy
your mom gets in keeping this from you.
This great big world
Suddenly seems so small
I took flight only to crash
Into a glass ceiling
O my heart, stop insisting
Lock your cage from within
Along with your dreams
O my heart, stop insisting
Lock your cage from within
Along with your dreams
I've spoken to Sheena.
There are many ways.
You can lodge a police complaint.
A children's organization here
can help you.
There's Sheena.
There's me.
You don't need to waste your life.
Sir, my mom didn't give up on me.
It's my turn now.
How can I desert her?
But...
What about you, Insia?
Why are you wasting your talent?
O my heart, stop insisting
Lock your cage from within
Along with your dreams
Secret Superstar!
Friends, a few months ago,
a mystery girl wearing a burqa,
uploaded her songs
on her YouTube channel.
These videos became so popular
that even celebrities and politicians
appreciated and shared them.
But a few weeks ago,
this YouTube channel went dormant.
No more songs!
There was silence on her
YouTube, Facebook, Twitter pages.
'Come Back Secret Superstar' pages
began trending,
and all her fans were upset.
But today, there is reason to rejoice.
Because our Secret Superstar
has set foot into the world of Bollywood.
Let's talk to Shakti Kumaarr about her.
- Sir, tell us something
about the Secret Superstar.
There's a pain in her voice
that stems from her heart.
Her eyes have a passion
that transcends into her voice.
She's blessed by Jesus.
She's a gifted child... gifted!
What's her real name?
How does it matter?
Her voice is real!
Will she sing more songs for you?
God willing!
'I dance!'
Your words and thoughts
Will flow from me
In your praise and devotion
Will I always sing
In robes weaved of your love
I'll dress myself
And merge into your colors
Insu...
Mom, I don't want to dream any more.
Isn't school over?
No, Dad.
Today is the last day.
When are your exams starting?
From the fifth of the next month.
And when do they end?
On the 20th.
Alright, I'll book the tickets for 20th.
Start packing.
Don't leave anything for the last minute.
Okay?
I'll write it.
You wrote even the last time.
It's my turn now.
-My turn.
-No.
Shall I write something?
Are your tickets booked?
Insu.
Shall we go?
Ma'am, just a minute.
I'm Chintan.
Insia's friend.
The 'pav bhaji' that you sent
for lunch the other day was amazing.
I didn't let Insia have it.
I finished everything.
Will you have ice cream?
No.
Ma'am, today is the last day of school.
So, if you don't mind,
can Insia and I go for ice cream?
We'll be back in ten minutes.
Promise. Please?
Please?
Go.
- Thank you, ma'am. Let's go.
- Come.
Go!
- Come on.
Listen.
Your dad has gone to Ahmedabad.
He'll return late at night.
You can stay out longer,
but come back by evening.
Come.
Babes, your song has become a superhit.
Yes, sir. I've seen it.
It's always shown on TV.
And Mom has bought its CD.
- There's more good news.
What?
- Glamour Awards has nominated you.
Best Singer.
What? Really?
And me, too.
- Wow, sir.
I can't believe it.
When is it?
On the 20th. In Mumbai.
You should come.
No, sir. I won't be able to come.
You know that.
But you will surely win the award.
Fat chance.
No, sir. Don't say that.
I'm sure, you will win it this time.
Listen.
Don't forget me when you go to Saudi.
Keep in touch.
How can I forget you?
You have done so much for me.
God bless, kiddo.
Don't be sad.
You are anyway the best singer.
And you, a best friend.
Let's celebrate today.
What?
I read on twitter...
"Don't cry it's over, smile it happened."
You read this on Twitter?
- Yes.
Who tweeted it?
Break up Quotations.
At 7.30 in the morning
At 4.45 in the evening
When the first rains fall
When the summer holidays
Come to an end
Sometimes in joy
Sometimes in sorrow
And sometimes for no reason at all
I love you
Whenever I pass by your house
I'll wait a little for you
I know, I won't see you there
I know, I'll end up getting delayed
When I have tea and cookies
In the morning
When I have cold coffee
In the evening
When it is your birthday
When it is my birthday
31st December, 14th February,
Festival of Nine Nights
I love you
How did your exam go?
Good.
I'm going to Mumbai.
To attend the Glamour Awards.
Mr. Shakti has arranged a pass for me.
I love you
Sir, load this too.
Careful.
I need to use the toilet.
Hold this.
Watch the luggage.
I...
Ma'am, my husband has gone to the toilet.
He'll be back in two minutes.
No problem. Please step out of the queue.
No... please check these.
Mom, don't worry. I'll take care of it.
From here to Mumbai,
then Mumbai to Riyadh.
You'll get the boarding passes to Riyadh
at the Mumbai International airport.
You'll have to check in your bags
again at Mumbai airport.
I have another request.
These three seats together.
And these two seats behind them.
Okay, ma'am.
Done?
Come on, then.
It happens every time.
Someone takes my window seat.
That's my seat.
Come, take the window seat.
Monali Thakur, Sudha Venkat, Geet Singhal,
have been joined this time,
by our first-time nominee,
Secret Superstar.
For her beautiful song...
Secret Superstar sings really well.
- Yes.
She'll definitely win the award.
Yes, she should win the award.
Where are the rest of the passengers?
Hello!
- Yes.
Why don't you dive into the television?
Come on.
Guddu, move to the side.
Stand here or you'll get hurt.
Sir, this needs a fragile tag.
- Okay.
On these two as well.
- I'll do it. Don't worry.
Sir, you have extra baggage.
You'll have to pay for it.
What rubbish!
Every bag is under 25kg.
I weighed them myself.
Sir, it is not about the weight.
You have an extra bag.
You are allowed to check in ten bags,
but you've checked in eleven bags.
How much will I have to pay?
Sir, 4,500 rupees.
What's this?
Where has this come from?
Tell me.
- It's Insu's guitar.
So? Are we taking her there
to play the guitar?
When will you both stop obsessing
over the guitar?
Insia.
Pick up the guitar.
Yes... and dump it in the dustbin.
Over there.
There is no need for a guitar there.
Do you think I'll pay 5,000 rupees
for that junk?
Listen...
Insu has nothing but her guitar.
There's so much luggage anyway,
so let's take her guitar too.
It's not a guitar, it's junk.
The same junk that's in both your heads.
It's not junk.
It's Insu's guitar.
If you say the word 'guitar' once more,
you have no idea,
how hard I'll slap you right here.
Get it?
In fact, it's not even a guitar.
It's Insia's dream.
And without dreams
there's no point to anything.
Neither to sleep, nor to wake up.
Neither to live, nor to die.
To dream is a basic right.
Everyone should be allowed this much.
- Hey!
Have you lost it?
I've told you once that
the guitar will stay here. That's it!
Alright.
The guitar will stay here.
Along with Insu,
Guddu,
and me.
We are not coming to Riyadh with you.
Hold it!
There are cameras everywhere.
If you hit me,
we'll take the footage from security
and upload it on YouTube.
Insu has a channel on it.
Haven't you seen it on TV?
The burqa clad girl.
The one who sings and plays the guitar.
She has millions of fans.
They'll all see you.
Before any of this happens,
it's best that you go to Riyadh.
Enough is enough! Stop this nonsense.
I'm your husband.
You can't move from here
without my permission.
Hold this, Insu.
What's happening? Can't you hear me?
Can't you hear or have you gone deaf?
Why are you opening this bag?
What's this?
What file is this?
Can't you hear me?
I'm talking to you. Look here.
What are you doing?
What file is this?
What are you signing on?
What's this?
I can't read.
You can.
It's written here
that if I complain to the police,
you'll be arrested.
You'll definitely lose the children.
I might get your house, too.
If you get arrested,
you'll lose your job in Riyadh.
And your life will be ruined.
Why take the risk?
It's best you go from here
and leave us alone.
Come on, Insu.
- Sir, are you checking in?
- Shall I give your boarding passes?
- You are blocking the queue.
Are you going to board the flight?
Excuse me, sir. I'm talking to you.
I can hear you!
I'm not deaf!
Najma!
Where are you going? Listen to me.
The passports and luggage are lying there.
Insia, explain to your mom.
It's all about the guitar, right?
We'll take the guitar along.
Listen, I'm ready to take the guitar.
Ma'am, once you step out,
you won't be allowed back in.
Nothing could be better than that.
Najma!
Listen to me!
But Mom...
What will we do now?
Where will we go?
Ma'am, may I use your cell phone
to make a call?
It's urgent, please. Just one call.
Thank you so much.
Insu.
Call Shakti Kumaarr.
It's the night of the awards, right?
Let's just go there for now.
We'll figure the rest later.
When will they be here?
Any minute.
How are you?
Insia's mom, I'm very happy to meet you.
Fantastic!
Shakti's entry.
Hold it.
Where are your passes?
Don't you recognize her?
No.
Wait.
She's the YouTube singer.
- If you are done with your nonsense,
can we do some important work?
- Yes, of course. Let's get on
with what we've been paid for.
Monali Thakur.
What rubbish!
It's all rubbish.
Ever since I was a little girl
and used to sing on stage,
I had just one dream.
To win these awards.
And every time I'm in the audience
and the nominations were announced,
I always wish that I win, not anyone else.
But, this time...
something didn't feel right.
Today,
amongst us,
there's a new star.
And compared to her voice,
my voice seems to pale.
Secret Superstar...
If you're here amongst us today,
please come up,
and collect your award.
Because I...
I can't accept this award.
Go on.
Go. They're calling you.
Insu, go.
Secret Superstar, are you here?
Is Secret Superstar there?
Secret Superstar...
Are you here?
The Secret Superstar is here.
Put a spotlight on her.
Give her a big hand.
Move the jib! Cameras on her!
Insu, go.
- Insu, go.
You should go.
- They're calling you. Go.
Go.
Claim your window seat.
You all think
that I'm the 'Secret Superstar'.
But I'm not.
I was six years old
when mom got me a guitar.
How?
She stole money from my dad's wallet.
She had a necklace.
Her last ornament.
She sold that and bought me a laptop.
Dad wanted to end my story
when I was in my mom's womb.
But she didn't let it happen.
My mom has written my story.
And she continues to write it.
Singing songs and winning awards,
have always been my dream.
But some people aren't allowed to dream.
The freedom to dream...
Well, my mom gave me that, too.
So, who's the superstar here?
Me?
Or my mom?
Mom...
You are not stupid.
You're a genius.
You are not a coward.
You're a fighter.
You aren't childish at all, Mom.
You are the world's best mom.
She's my dearestMy mom
Friends, this is Shakti Kumaarr's
first YouTube video.
And I dedicate it to the Secret Superstar,
whom I launched!
So, presenting my new song,
fresh off the block,
recorded just yesterday.
I'll speak your words
I'll sing your praises
I'll adorn myself
With the colors of your love
I'll dance like you
I'll sway like you
I'll adorn myself
With the jewels of your love
I dance wild and free
For you, my sexy lover
Oh, my sexy lover
Go for it!
Let's go
Everybody in the house
Very hot, whiskey shot
Got me high without a sip
I'm doomed now
Left to lay in the fields
I've got cash, you have beautiful lips
Let's meet and party hard
Chicken roast, manchurian
I'll have a go at them both
I search for you
I search for you everywhere
My sexy lover
Oh, my sexy lover
O, my sexy lover
Give it to me!
Come on! Come on!
Superhit! It's a superhit!
If you enjoyed the video, click on 'like'.
And if you didn't then change your taste!