"The monkey looks for taste
of ginger in the democracy."
"They say and we hear
that nobody killed Jessica."
"The monkey looks for taste
of ginger in the democracy."
"They say and we hear
that nobody killed Jessica."
"The buffalo says that play
the organ and I shall dance."
"I sell off for votes
but I still curse my fate."
"Look how the fox has
ventured into the city."
"The ominous one
looks out for a curse.."
They say there's a reason
behind everything
in this world.
But, can you think of a reason
behind what's going on here?
This place is beyond reason.
This is Bakrapur.
O' Lord!
May the Lord bless you
with his grace.
How are you?
May the Lord bless you
with his grace.
How is business?
- Good.
My Lord!
May the Lord bless you
with his grace.
O' Lord!
Don't hoard.
Share what you have.
You can't take it to your grave.
You brought nothing.
You'll take back nothing.
Right?
Let's drink to it.
May the Lord bless you!
Not a penny more.
But the deal was for 3000!
3000 bucks for incense?
No. I was talking
about Shahrukh.
Suraiyya finalized
everything with Mr. Usman.
Fine, take a seat.
Come on, boy.
Zulfi, are you dreaming again?
Memorize the entire
lesson by tomorrow.
Yes, teacher.
Concentrate.
No more mischief!
Keep studying..
Suraiyya!
Greetings, Ms. Nooran.
- Greetings.
I was on my way to the city.
Did you arrange for the money?
He left for the city just this
morning, along with his uncle.
I will somehow get the
money to you by evening.
I guess you aren't
tired of making excuses.
But I am tired of
listening to them.
I bought imported
shoes for myself.
I'll elope with you in a trice.
I see.
- What?
I've things to do here.
That's why I say
talk to your father.
I'll treat you
like a movie star.
Star!
This cheap mobile
that you bought me
can't even take
decent pictures.
Forget the mobile.
I'll bring you a
laptop this time.
The big one.
One with a camera.
Listen.
- What?
Naaz.
How about a kiss?
Don't laugh.
Have you seen yourself
in the mirror?
Asking for a kiss!
- I have. I look nice.
Naaz. What are you doing?
- Who was that?
Listen, I need to get going.
I am not done yet.
Are you still there?
- Coming, mother.
Cut your crap, I have to go.
Mother's here. Goodbye.
- Naaz..
Why don't you all just kill me?
I was working, mother.
I hope you didn't get blisters.
An incompetent husband
and two good-for-nothing
children.
There's just no end
to my problems.
What the heck is that?
- Mother, must be a bee..
Please go inside,
I'll be with you.
Come soon.
- Yes, mother.
Naaz!
Zulfi!
Hey, hot shot!
What's wrong with you?
Zulfi!
Why so sad?
Say something.
- It's nothing, Mr. Jaffer.
Nothing?
Then why do you look
like a sacrificial lamb?
Zulfi!
I was looking for you.
Wait.
Get on my bike.
How can a man be so stupid?
Suraiyya. Is it my fault
that Usman's mother-in-law
broke her back?
No, it's entirely my fault!
It's my father's fault!
For getting me married
to a penniless man.
And what was the point
of you going along?
You two are just useless.
Teach her some manners.
If she continues
yelling this way
we'll soon rot in inferno.
Right. Just sit here and rant
about heaven and inferno.
A woman has to do the chores
as well as amass money
by selling eggs and hens.
The men of this family,
lazy to the core!
Arrange for the money somehow.
Otherwise, I'm going
back to my mother's.
I won't stay here
a minute longer.
Come in, Mr. Munna.
I am free.
Come in.
I want to style my hair.
Is Mr. Jaffer in?
Greetings.
- See you later.
Go on in.
- Take a seat.
Ever since you returned from the
city, business has been slow.
Everyone asks for Jaffer.
And for free.
Father, why be sad?
They come here
because they've faith in me
as I've learnt
new techniques.
How can I charge them money?
In fact,
I should be paying them.
I'm getting a chance to practice.
Look at this new style.
Shall I teach you?
- Shut up! What faith?
A beggar asking for alms
is happy with what he gets.
They are here for freebies.
- Father.
Yes.
- Chill, dude.
How about I thrash you..
- No, no, remain seated.
Haven't you finished yet?
Just a little longer.
I see.
- Yes.
What are you doing here?
I was running an errand
for my mother.
You know,
I soaked henna yesterday.
Come tomorrow,
and we'll apply it together.
And, is everything okay?
Naaz.
What are you doing here?
Come on, go home.
Your mother's looking for you.
Didn't you hear it?
Go home.
I am going, there's no need to yell.
Go on. Go home.
Did he have to drop in now?
Greetings.
- Greetings.
No, no.. Leave.
Majid,
you were really brave today.
Give me a smoke.
Zulfi. What do we do
with your hair today?
What style would you like?
Aamir? Salman?
Or Shahrukh.
- The children these days..
What can a poor mother
do all alone?
Majid wants to get romantic.
But his wife's just
not playing along.
Go ahead, make fun of me.
Can't help it when
I'm ill-fated.
Are you Majid?
Yes. Is something wrong?
Is Suraiyya home?
Suraiyya..
She is.
Let's go.
Mother.
- Yes.
Mother. They are here!
- Who?
Them! - Them?
- Yes.
Your father didn't exactly
leave behind a fortune!
Tell them I'm not at home.
Go on.
But, mother.
They met father on the way.
Oh God! I'm tired of this man!
Go on, I'm coming.
Yes.
Is everyone here?
Start collecting.
Shakuntala!
Vidyavati.
Saraswati.
I hope you're making
sure their payment's right.
Mallika.
Yes.
- Is it all there?
Greetings, ma'am.
- I see.
So, you're finally here.
That's not it, ma'am.
Why wouldn't I come to meet you?
I won't be fooled
by you anymore.
And your leader, Nooran..
She's been taking your side.
- No, ma'am.
I visit her on your behalf.
Ma'am, my circumstances
are such that..
It's no secret, everyone
knows about my situation.
Zulfi's father's aunt, who
lives in Sultanpur, fell ill.
I wonder what sort of
an outbreak it was
and half my poultry
succumbed to it.
And then..
- Stop.
In the last three months
you haven't paid the
loan or the interest.
Ma'am, try to understand.
I swear on my child.
I'm not lying.
The circumstances..
Just give me a little more time!
Look, Suraiyya. All these
women have repaid their loan.
If you don't repay
the money in a week
I will stop everyone's
loan in this group.
No one will get anything.
See that. Helping you has
landed all of us in trouble.
What do I say?
I was honestly coming
to the office to pay you.
But just then, Mr. Usman's
mother-in-law broke her back.
We're in a lot of trouble..
You should've thought
about it before.
I explained the rules
in the beginning.
Didn't I?
- Yes.
Look, Suraiyya.
If you don't return the money
in a week, then be ready
to face legal procedures.
Everyone!
Let's go!
Hocus-Pocus!
Abracadabra!
Run away!
Leave this kid alone!
Go!
Go away!
Ma'am, the kid's being
haunted by a spirit.
But don't you worry.
I've chanted a strong mantra
and got rid of it.
Here.
Make him wear this
in the morning, after bath.
Everything will be okay.
May the Lord bless you!
What's wrong?
Why are you upset?
Have you eaten
or are you fasting?
No..
Why would he fast?
All the villagers
are humiliating me.
And all you two care
about is stuffing your mouths.
I want the money
before Thursday..
Otherwise, I won't
stay here a moment.
Spare me!
How can we get
the money so soon?
Who will lend us the money,
uncle?
Of course.
Who will lend you the money?
The only one who could,
gave you his daughter instead.
Mother, I am hungry.
- Why did you bring him inside?
Naaz, take him outside.
- Come in.
Don't worry, I know a way.
What is it, uncle?
Tell me.
Don't worry,
we'll get the money.
Where will we get it from?
Is there a lottery running
for mendicants now?
Stop taunting me.
I was talking about Shahrukh.
- Shahrukh?
I can never make
sense of what you say.
The animal fair of Malshapur
is quite popular.
We'll take Shahrukh there.
Many buyers come there.
We'll get a good price.
Usman offered better
than that, for sure.
You're right, uncle.
Zulfi, catch the ball.
Zulfi. Could you not have
caught the ball?
Oh God!
The Lord had
answered my prayers
and blessed me with a son.
And now, he's gone as well.
Uncle. I looked everywhere,
but Zulfi's nowhere.
Oh God! My son.
He's just a child.
Where can he possibly go?
He didn't go alone,
he took Shahrukh along.
What were you doing?
Uncle, they left quietly.
Even that animal
didn't make a sound.
Stop crying like a girl!
My son!
I told you not to call.
Everyone's so worried.
Sweetheart, I'm worried too.
In your love.
Listen. I had a wonderful
dream this morning.
You and me, by the seaside.
It was beautiful.
Naaz..
Naaz. Why are you crying?
What's the matter. - Zulfi ran away
from home.. - What?
What are you saying?
When did this happen?
And, with Shahrukh.
Hey!
Wonderful.
Everyone's worried back home
while you two
are having a ball.
And, with biscuits.
I knew this is where
I would find you.
You know,
when father would beat me
I too would hide here.
It's a nice place, right?
Listen, let's go home.
No, I don't want to go home.
Where else do you want to go?
- Take us to the city.
We will work with you too.
Come along,
and bring Shahrukh too.
He will make for a great barber.
Shahrukh that is..
Let's go.
We'll go to the city later,
let's now go home.
Can't we stay here until Sunday?
What's on Sunday?
They're taking Shahrukh
to the Malshapur fair that day.
So, you want to hide
here till Sunday? - Yes.
Great.
What will you do next Sunday?
The fair's just once a month.
- You're smart.
What will you do next month?
I don't know, Mr. Jaffer!
Just take us along.
I don't know, Mr. Jaffer.
Come along with me.
You've my word
that nothing will go wrong.
We'll go to the city too
tagging Shahrukh and you along.
Let's go home now.
- Why did you run away?
Do you know how worried we were?
If you ever do it again,
I'll break your limbs.
That's great, ma'am.
That's a nice way
to teach him a lesson.
Break his legs.
- I don't like saying it either.
A child never understands
a mother's heart.
May the Lord bless you
with progress in your work.
Work's good, ma'am.
Just bless me so that
I find a nice bride.
That's it.
- Of course.
Any girl would be
fortunate to marry you.
I see.
So, sir..
Are you sure about
the Malshapur fair?
Yes, I..
- There's no other choice.
These children have
never had to starve
so, they will never
understand our condition.
They will have to understand,
ma'am.
The food's begging to be eaten.
But, the boy's still stubborn.
Fine. You want to starve,
don't you? Then go ahead.
Zulfi. Don't infuriate me.
Mother. Leave him alone.
I'll console him.
Oh my!
You never cared so much
about your mother before.
Why, mother?
Can't I console him?
He's my brother after all.
Yes, he is.
I am the only enemy
in this house.
You two can do anything
you want to. Just spare me.
I don't have the will anymore.
Mother's just impossible!
Zulfi. Get up.
Come with your sister.
- No. I don't want to go.
Hear me out.
Let's go sit outside.
- Leave me alone, sister.
I said, don't be stubborn.
Come along. Come on..
Come on.
Mother's always scolding him.
And he isn't eating either.
Talk to him.
Who is it?
- Here.
Zulfi.
- Mr. Jaffer!
So, why aren't you eating?
No, I don't want to eat?
Why?
They are taking Shahrukh away.
Don't you want to save him?
Yes.
Then do as I say.
Go inside and finish your meal.
And come, meet me an hour later..
At the old fort,
along with Shahrukh.
And, don't tell anyone about it.
Understood?
Do you attend school?
Yes.
Why?
Read this aloud.
What's written..
Alif..
Laam..
Zulfi!
Are you going to take
that long to read it?
Tell me now.
What's written in it?
Lord!
It says Lord.
That's it.
Now,
only Lord can save Shahrukh.
How?
Like this.
"A mighty goat escorted
by two courtiers."
"Appreciate the irony.
Indulge in the ruckus.."
"Be it the household merchandise,
the prices have gone sky high."
He won't even give 10 kilos of meat.
What are you saying?
Nothing less than 4500..
- That's too much.
2500 is all we can give.
2500 is too less.
Go find someone else.
11,000!
- 11,000!
How about 3000?
4000 is too much!
That's not possible.
It's a fine goat.
Take a look.
How much?
- 5000!
Quote reasonably!
He's stuck at 5000!
How much did you offer?
- Leave him.
- 2500.
Let's settle for 3500.
That's it.
Give me at least 4000.
- No, 4000 is too much.
Hear me out!
Just 500 more.
We've brought him from far.
Even I have to go a long way.
Let's settle for 3500.
That's it.
Fine. How much are
you willing to offer?
3500, that's it. Nothing more.
Greetings, sir.
Greetings, lad.
What brings you here?
Nothing, sir.
A friend of mine from the city,
lives here.
So I came here with him.
That's good, lad.
How are you?
How are you, Shahrukh?
So, you're leaving us
today, right?
Fine, hand over the rope to me.
I've got to leave.
Just 500 more.
I'm offering you
a reasonable price.
Okay, like you say.
Sir.
How much did you sell him for?
3500. He's sold, at least.
What do you mean?
You sold an animal worth
3 to 4 lakhs for few thousands.
3 lakhs?
- He's a prankster.
Always playing pranks.
- I see.
Don't listen to him.
He's not covered with gold.
- Right.
He's better than that,
sir.
He's blessed with
the grace of the Lord.
Don't joke about this.
What? What are you saying?
Be clear, what are you saying?
You're a mendicant.
How could you miss this?
- What?
Look here. Carefully.
Here.
This. Take a good look.
Look at the crescent shape.
Have you seen the
Mecca-Medina calendar?
You must have.
The crescent shining,
on top of the dome.
It's the same thing.
You're a wise man.
And you didn't see it either.
You didn't go on Haj, but
you've a world of experience.
Don't you?
It's true.
- Yes.
Child, it says Lord.
Hail the Lord!
My service has been accepted.
He's an angel, child.
Don't sell it.
- This is no ordinary goat!
I don't care.
Just handover the animal to me.
I'll be on my way.
Don't call him an animal.
He's an angel.
Apologize to him.
We didn't take any
money from you.
So, I am not refusing to pay.
Take it.
Didn't we make a deal?
Look.
My nephew's not so wise.
Look. We don't want to sell it.
Just leave. - Leave..
But, uncle..
- Dear, didn't you see that?
It's Lord written on him.
We cannot sell him.
But, uncle,
what will we tell Suraiyya?
We cannot set foot in
the house without the money.
Henpecked husband!
Don't you understand
what Jaffer's saying?
Lord is written on him.
- Yes.
And, a Sheikh from Saudi
paid 52 lakhs
for a similar goat.
52 lakhs!
52 lakhs.
- 52 lakhs?
He took it home on an airplane.
Airplane?
Of course.
It requires special permission
from the government.
But, how do you know?
I read the newspaper.
And I can show you
the news as well.
Even the kids from
Delhi's Jamma Masjid area
know about it.
Do you want to read it?
Child, even I've heard
the Jamma Masjid story.
Indeed.
- Let's take him back.
He's been blessed
by the Lord!
How could I trust that man?
He's good for nothing.
I wonder how father spent
so many years with you.
Yes. We'll see.
How your husband tolerates you!
Mother. Father's back.
Didn't I tell you?
This man isn't
capable of anything.
Stop.
Stop right there.
Listen. Listen to me..
Why don't you try
telling our creditors?
Maybe, they will listen to you.
I'm trying to speak.
Let me speak!
Look, dear.
Shahrukh' s no ordinary goat.
He's blessed by the Lord!
He's special.
He's our golden goose.
Are you two drunk?
You could've brought
me some poison.
God forbid.
Explain it to her.
Suraiyya.. You tell her.
He's right, ma'am.
Jaffer says Shahrukh' s
not worth a few thousands
but he's worth millions.
And,
if we can find an Arab merchant
he will definitely
pay millions for him.
And, the story about 52 lakhs is
famous in Jamma Masjid. - Right.
Even the kids know about it.
Right?
I see.
Tell her.
- Yes, tell her.
He's right.
- But, what is he saying?
Child, you're the educated one.
Why don't you explain it
to me?
Ma'am, an angel
has descended in your home.
Take a look.
Look at the crescent formation.
Have you seen the
Mecca-Medina calendar?
You must have. The crescent
moon, shines atop the dome.
It's the same thing.
Right?
- Yes.
Yes.. It's something.
What do you mean by something,
ma'am?
It's time to celebrate.
That's alright, child.
But, what about the creditors?
Loan!
Stop worrying about them, ma'am.
What's the amount?
- 3000!
3000! Come on now, ma'am.
Here you go.
What's he doing?
How can I borrow from him?
Take it. But..
- I.. I'm family too.
I mean.. I am not an outsider.
Just take it..
- What!
Ma'am. You can return it once
you find an Arab buyer.
With interest.
- Yes..
Let's get him some water.
- Let's get him some water.
Ma'am, a golden goose.
Come.
Brother,
you'll get a chance too.
Don't worry.
Everyone will get a chance.
God's watching over everyone.
What's going on here?
Yes, come forward.
Get the blessings.
Keep the money.
Yes.
O' Lord!
Wear this talisman, in the
morning after your bath. Okay.
Goodbye.
Keep moving.
All in line.
- What's going on?
Don't interfere.
Come on. Keep moving.
Put your money in this.
Take the blessings..
- What's this?
It's the grace of God.
Let us work, leave.
The Lord will bless you!
O' Lord!
Keep coming.
This way.
Come on.
Slowly.
Put the money in here.
My beautiful, gorgeous Suraiyya.
Each time she decks up,
my heart skips a beat.
I'm totally fed up!
I should..
Listen to me. I'll just
wait for five more minutes.
I see.
Five for you and five for me.
How about me coming
in 10 minutes?
10 minutes?
I'll grow old in 10 minutes.
Would you still love me
if I get grey hair?
I will still love you.
And, if your hair turns grey,
I'll paint it black.
I'm an expert at it.
Right, painter.
By the way, painters command
more respect than barbers.
I see.
- Of course.
Just imagine,
Jaffer Super Barber.
Hair-cutting, massage,
and all that.. All free.
I see. You've been getting
too bold these days.
Aren't you scared of
your mother any longer
that you're being so audacious?
Wait, I'll come right now
and teach you a lesson.
I..
- Okay.
Who do you think you are?
- Sorry.
By the way,
where's your mother?
Doesn't she ask you..
Naaz, where are you?
Naaz, where were you?
Only if she gets some
time off from Shahrukh.
By the way, Shahrukh' s a little angel.
- I see.
Tell me something.
Don't you think
we should get blessed by
Shahrukh' s grace as well?
Why?
Don't you think,
the mark on Shahrukh
is a stamp of Lord's
approval for our love.
Right?
Isn't it?
You see..
We meet so freely these days.
What are you thinking about?
- No. Nothing.
Right?
- Yes. You're right.
There's a dialogue from actor
Shahrukh' s movie..
If you want something
from your heart..
The entire universe conspires
to unite you with it.
Or something like that.
Shahrukh' s a part
of our world too.
So what if he's a goat.
Right?
Universe.
You're talking about the universe!
- You touch me a lot these days.
You're getting audacious.
"Meeting secretly."
"And hiding again."
"The heart's missing a beat.."
"In love.."
"The heart risks everything."
"Since my heart.."
"Since my heart fell"
"prey to your love."
"Meeting secretly."
"And hiding again."
"We can convey everything"
"with our eyes."
"The heart can communicate"
"without any means."
"We can convey everything"
"with our eyes."
"The heart can communicate"
"without any means."
"The call of love"
"is no longer on hold."
"Nor is"
"there a single day without you."
"Since my heart.."
"Since my heart fell"
"prey to your love."
Greetings, Majid.
Greetings.
You look really nice.
I guess sister Suraiyya's really
pleased with you these days.
It's the grace of God
that he sent Shahrukh to us.
With a little contribution
from Suraiyya as well.
Mr. Jamal, you should get a share too.
- How?
Because your son
spotted the goat first.
Mr. Sohail
my son can spot
all the problems in the world.
Except those of his father.
Don't say that, Mr. Jamal.
- It's true, Majid.
Not at all.
Mr. Majid,
the police is at your home.
Police?
- Yes.
Go on.
- Let's go, child.
Suraiyya. Are they here
to take Shahrukh away?
Can't you ever think positively?
Better be ready for
what's going to follow.
Whose goat is it?
- Who made the money?
Tell him.
Whose goat is it?
We never cheated anyone.
Please don't arrest us.
- Yes.
I never said
that I'm arresting you.
We thought so,
looking at your uniform.
He is Legislator
Syed Suleiman's brother-in-law.
He's opening a new showroom
in the city.
He was really impressed
by your goat.
Send him over on the
day of the inauguration.
Lotan.
- Yes.
Send the jeep in the morning.
- Yes, sir.
Greetings, sir.
Are you on your way?
Of course, we've made
all the arrangements.
Okay.
I think the minister's tied up
with something important.
No, that's not it.
He's on his way.
And,
I don't see your brother-in-law.
He's with the minister as well.
They will be here.
I see, so Mr. Suleiman's
with the minister? - Yes.
That's good.
This is the right opportunity to show
brotherly love. - Are they here?
They were held up
by a punctured tire.
I don't want to hear anything.
Arrange for another car.
He should be here before
the minister arrives.
Yes. Yes, sir.
Is there another guest of honor
other than the minister?
No, that's it.
Long live..
- Minister.
Congratulations, Mr. Rizwan.
How are you? - It's all
your grace, Minister.
Hello, Minister.
You too, Singhania.
You never like this ambience.
Things change with time, sir.
And, when you're personally
visiting my area
then, it's my duty to attend.
Rizwan, hurry up. The minister's
got other engagements. - Yes.
I was supposed to attend
a cabinet meeting.
But I made it clear.
I am committed to Mr. Suleiman.
I can't attend the meeting.
Of course, you've to please
the alliance partners.
It's the law of
coalition politics.
Pass me the scissors.
Let's not delay this
auspicious event.
Just a few more minutes.
Is it the auspicious hour?
- No, no, just..
Here they are.
- Them?
Come..
You've planned a sacrifice.
Honestly, Mr. Suleiman
I don't get the
time anymore
but I really miss your
homemade kebabs.
No.. That isn't the case.
It's for warding off the evil eye.
- I see.
Come.
Please..
Look.
You're taking the Lord's
angel out for a stroll.
You sneaked him out, didn't you?
People keep coming to see him.
No one lets me play with him.
That's a problem.
You should be thankful
that he's still alive.
We haven't yet been exposed.
Can you believe it?
I am waiting in a shady village.
For a bloody goat!
I swear.
I'm going to blow a fuse.
But you can't argue
with your boss, right?
Can you?
Hello! Hello?
Are you there?
Darn! Network!
Icing on the cake.
Ma'am, please sit down.
Be patient, he'll be here soon.
Get some cold sherbet for ma'am.
Yes.
- No, it's okay. Thanks.
Can I tell you something?
It's about Shahrukh.
You know, he was born
right before our eyes.
It was a peculiar night.
Strong winds blowing..
Storm..
Heavy rains..
Lightning struck
in our courtyard.
And right then,
Shahrukh was born.
He's the angel of God.
A miracle of nature.
Wow! Sounds straight as
if from the twilight zone.
See, he..
They are here.
Ma'am. They are here.
- Come quickly.
Come on.
Come, Zulfi.
Bring Shahrukh.
Come on, son.
You've been playing in the mud.
Madam. This is Shahrukh.
Look at this.
He is Jaffer. Jaffer.
You can tell him too. He lives
in the city, just like you do.
Child, what was that..
That cup..
- World cup.
Yes.
- Cricket World Cup.
Cricket.
She's here to pray for them.
Yes, ma'am.
I understood everything.
Myself Jaffer, hair-stylist.
In town.
Hi!
The texture of your
hair is really nice.
Thanks.
Sachin. I'm a huge fan of him.
Sachin's a client of our agency.
- I see.
In fact, our agency handles
half the Indian team.
What are you saying?
Minister Rawat spoke with
our boss, about Shahrukh.
So, our boss decided that
Shahrukh' s going
to bless all the jerseys
and kits of all the players.
That's great.
He's the lucky charm
of the Indian team.
Right. Of course.
By the way,
Shahrukh' s got scope.
In fact, he can endorse
local brands. Right?
Money's money after all.
Yes. Money's money after all.
Yes, ma'am.
Money's money after all.
"The game begins"
"We met a man by
the ghat of Ganges.."
"Upon inquiring,
it said it's India."
"Waiting with patience.."
"Waiting for the opportunity.."
It is not going to
be easy this time.
We need to play the
communal card carefully.
They have also chosen
a candidate from our own.
Votes are bound to be split.
So be prepared.
It will be tough. All of you
will have to work hard.
Mujibur Rehman has a good hold
on this area. - Indeed!
We will have to do
something to ensure
that our votes
don't go to them.
Mr. Suleiman,
do you have any solution?
Yes. I have.
Here it is.
Hello.
- Hello.
How is your goat?
"Waiting for the opportunity.."
"The votes are being asked for
in the name of the Lord.."
"The goat shall reign
and that the destiny.."
"It's time for the sacrifice.."
"Waiting for the opportunity.."
"Be it the sage or the politician..
This is a strange game.."
"What sort of amalgamation is this?"
"This smells like trouble.."
"Waiting for the opportunity.."
You kept insisting on coming.
Jaffer is here.
Jaffer. Jaffer.
Hello, ma'am.
- Hello.
Ma'am,
how did you come here today?
She wanted to go shopping.
You know I hardly have the time
to spare, from household chores.
She kept pushing me.
And now it's raining.
It's raining, ma'am.
I'd come for some salon work.
It was raining,
so I thought of shopping.
Yes. Why not? It's your
age to enjoy. Let's go.
Ma'am, are you hungry?
Let's eat something.
No. No. Do you get any
hygienic stuff in this city?
No. No. Let's go.
- No. No, ma'am.
What are you saying?
Of course, you get.
Tea. Tea is not unhygienic.
We can drink tea.
I will take your word for it.
Let's drink tea.
Hurry up. Come on.
Ma'am, can I come under the umbrella?
It's raining. - Yes. Come on.
"We can communicate
through our eyes."
If not for you
we wouldn't be
where we are today.
What are you saying, ma'am?
God has done all of this.
I am just a medium.
That's true. The tea is still
not here. - Hey! Bring tea!
You know what they have come from the village.
They are my close acquaintances.
They have journeyed for 1.5
hours to taste your strong tea.
Isn't it good?
God should fulfill
one more wish of mine.
I should find a suitable,
employed boy.
He should always
keep my daughter happy.
Is that so?
You know what ma'am
my father is also
worried about this.
That we should find a girl.
You are right.
Yes. But he worries
without a reason.
I have told father many times,
ma'am
to look in the village.
That there is no shortage of girls.
That we will find someone.
Ma'am, you also look around.
You will find a boy.
Right?
- Yes. We will see.
The party won the elections
because of Shahrukh.
Mother.
How do I look, mother?
- Very pretty.
My sweet mother.
Mother, will you buy me
gold bangles on Eid?
I have been telling you
for so long. - Yes. Fine.
Save some money for
the motorcycle too.
Motorcycle?
- Yes.
We have to take
Shahrukh to the city.
A motorcycle would save time.
And we will earn more.
Right, Majid?
Yes.
No. It's not important.
Why?
- Okay. Fine.
Don't be so greedy.
Be patient.
Let's finalize the soap and
biscuit deals for Shahrukh.
Then we will see.
Motorcycles and airplanes.
Suraiyya!
Two-wheeler or three-wheeler?
- What?
Let's buy a bicycle.
Not in front of the kids.
- Henpecked husband.
Hello.
Everything is fine?
- Hello.
Yes. We are
managing somehow.
My Shabbo is getting
engaged next Friday.
I need some money.
Ask the lady at the NGO.
Now we don't owe them anything.
Where do I go
when I am in debt?
You have never differentiated
between Naaz and Shabbo.
Help us out.
That is fine. But you can
see that we barely manage
to make both ends meet.
It's difficult to
spare anything.
Tea.
Here. A 500 rupee note.
Give me the change early morning.
What is this Rs. 500 for?
Should I tear it?
I should have the change to
give you. Right, Jamaal?
Go and check.
- Pay me later. It's okay.
Why are you inviting
my curse early morning?
Have I ever had tea on credit?
- Let it be, priest.
He does not know how to speak
to a person of your stature.
Here, take this.
Get going.
God will bless you.
What will the Lord bless me with,
priest?
Our goats are hardly messiahs.
Only fit to be cooked and eaten.
- You always joke.
Whose car is this?
Jamaal, seems like a big shot.
Is it the real Shahrukh?
Maybe, he wants to get
clicked with our Shahrukh.
It happens before the
release of a new movie.
Where does Shahrukh live?
- Yes.
Yes. Come.
Who is it?
Can someone tell me
where Shahrukh lives?
Shahrukh?
- Who are you?
Everyone calls me the priest.
Shahrukh belongs to our family.
My name is Rayeez Ahmed.
- Okay.
I am Saudi Sheikh Abdul
Rehman Bakhtiyar's PA.
Saudi?
Praise the Lord!
O' Lord, thanks a lot.
Come..
Another treasure-trove.
- Come.
Have tea.
- No. I don't drink tea.
So shall I get something
cold instead?
Go and get a cold drink. - Yes.
- No. Thank you.
Do you know Mr. Pandey?
- Mr. Pandey?
Mr. Pandey.
His company PML Consultants
manages your
Indian cricket team.
The lady with the kit.
- Yes.
Yes. We know her very well.
We were discussing our
new company logo with him.
What logo?
- Nothing.
Actually, Mr. Pandey advised
Sheikh to use
Shahrukh' s photograph
for the logo.
Yes. - Mr. Sheikh said,
not just the photograph
he would buy Shahrukh.
- It's good.
Can I see him?
- Sure. Look. Come. Look.
Zulfi.
Zulfi, move.
Zulfi,
show it to Mr. Sheikh yourself.
Wow! Wonderful.
Good.
He is an angel.
We were facing tough times.
But now, we earn no less
than Rs.20,000 a month.
Sheikh is coming
to India in a month or two.
We will finalize everything
when he arrives.
A month or two?
- Will it take so long?
A month or two.
A merchant paid 52 lakhs for
a goat in Delhi. - 52 lakhs.
If the Lord wills,
our merchant will pay more.
Yes.
You see,
there is only one angel.
If there is another buyer, the
price can increase too. - Yes.
No. I am just telling you.
You talk to him.
Yes.
Will you see him off
from the door?
Invite him in.
Come, let us go in.
Come.
- Please come.
Come on.
- Come on.
We will talk inside.
- Let's have tea.
What a change in two weeks,
sir!
What prosperity!
- It's a boon. - Here. Eat.
Ma'am, I was thinking..
- Don't think.
Majid, I was thinking..
I will ask Mr. Sheikh
to book my ticket for Saudi
along with that of Shahrukh.
He is used to this place.
Who will look after him there?
I thought I would accompany him.
- Can't my husband do that?
I am thinking about
earning 50 lakhs.
But if my husband also
accompanies Shahrukh
I am sure they pay goatherds
not less than the officers here.
Am I right?
And when you go there, find
a suitable groom for the girl.
After that, we will go on Haj.
Did you hear that?
You will go abroad.
All thanks to this kind fellow.
Yes, ma'am.
Hello, Mr. Swaran.
- Hello.
Where were you?
I haven't seen you in a while.
I had gone on a pilgrimage
with my wife.
Okay.
What did you ask from God?
No need to ask.
- Why?
I found out on my return.
It's his divine play.
I will leave now.
- Okay.
Take this, Shanti.
She is working so hard.
Let Sheikh come.
She will go to Saudi
and live like a queen.
Wear this after a bath.
Everything will be fine.
How are you?
- Sir?
All is well.
How is the boy doing?
Come on, go.
Go!
God made my
pilgrimage successful.
Great!
Where were you for so long, sir?
You were not to be seen.
I returned yesterday.
- Okay. - From my pilgrimage.
As soon as we came back,
my wife urged me
to check on my grandson's
wellbeing.
What is the news?
When is the Sheikh coming?
What?
- 55 lakhs is not a small amount.
Since a long time,
I wanted to buy some land.
But you know.
Property prices are rising.
And our earnings
are at rock bottom.
Now all my hopes
are pinned on the child.
What is this about your child?
As if you begot the goat.
His mother might belong to you.
But his father is
from our family.
We have a right.
We do have it.
Am I right?
What father? What right
are you talking about?
My Kalia is Shahrukh' s father.
- Kalia?
What new story is this?
Majid. - Yes.
- You were there.
When Kalia and your goat..
What is her name? - Salma.
Yes. Salma.
When Kalia and Salma united.
Disgusting. Even after
undertaking a pilgrimage
you don't have the sense
to talk in front of women.
Why? What did I say? All of
you were at the vet's clinic.
When Kalia and Salma united..
- Stop it.
Both of you just keep
listening like useless fellows.
He is talking nonsense in
front of your wife and daughter.
And both of you just keep quiet.
Nobody came when we
were cleaning the goat feces.
Now everyone wants
a share in the 55 lakhs.
She is right. Mind your tongue.
Fine. Fine.
Let's settle the money issue..
Look, Shahrukh is ours.
- His father is ours.
And 55 lakhs are ours.
- Yes.
Hello.
- Come. Come, Shyama Prasad.
God bless you.
Come. Take the offering.
Come, Shyama Prasad. Come.
How are you?
- Fine.
Everything is fine? - Yes.
I have some good news for you.
Is it that you have become
a father for the sixth time?
You always tease me.
- Tell me. What is it?
I have brought
someone to meet you.
He could be our trump
card in the elections.
Sir, touch his feet.
He is my elder brother.
It's okay. It's okay.
Whom have you brought,
Shyama Prasad?
Sir. Sir, it's enough.
- Shyama Prasad, you are..
Come. Stand up.
He is Swaran Singh.
He is from my village Sirauni.
Mangori and Sirauni are in the
vicinity. He is like my uncle.
Come to the point,
Shyama Prasad.
The thing is that
magical goat Shahrukh..
The one that cost us
the municipal body elections.
The father of the goat..
It's Kalia, right?
- Yes, Kalia.
His name is Kalia.
He belongs to Swaran.
How is this relevant?
Sir,
if the father is a Hindu..
How can the diabolic
lay claim on the goat?
Now you see the relevance?
What about the Arabic
lettering on his body?
What about the Arabic lettering?
Sir,
so what if there is no symbol?
But his blood is of a Hindu.
You can get the
medical test done
in front of the whole village.
- We can do that as well.
The child will clear the exams.
Make the offering. Leave!
How are you, priest?
- I am fine. Hello.
Hello. Is Suraiyya at home?
- Yes.
Shall I call her? Suraiyya. Suraiyya.
How are you, Suraiyya?
- Fine.
With God's grace, we've
repaid all your money.
What brings you here?
Isn't this Shahrukh?
- Yes.
It is so adorable.
Ask, sir. You can ask
for whatever you want.
Come. Come.
- Yes.
Don't be scared.
He is God's messiah.
Give whatever you want.
Keep it.
Suraiyya, he is the bank manager.
Gupta sir.
All the accounts of
our NGO are with his bank.
He has come especially
to meet you guys.
Hello.
Pleased to meet you.
These..
These are the account
and fixed deposit forms.
You can't keep 50 lakhs at home,
can you?
We don't have 50 lakhs.
No. You will get it.
Look, ATM
locker, fixed deposits,
net banking
phone banking..
You will get all the facilities.
Without charges.
How are you, Majid?
- Fine.
He is Suraiyya's husband.
Hello, sir. Pleased to meet you.
Myself Vibhuti Bhushan Gupta.
Manager of BMZ bank.
Why are you panting?
The village council
has summoned us.
With Shahrukh.
- Oh Lord! Why?
I don't know.
Chief, we are waiting
for your decision.
It's a clear-cut case.
How come?
We raised him like a child.
And today,
people are laying claim on him.
You did it for your benefit.
Otherwise, you guys
would have sacrificed
him on Eid.
- Sir, hold on.
Chief, understand one thing.
It's the question
of our religion's honor.
If the need arises,
we will move the Parliament
leave alone the Supreme Court.
Get that straight.
So what are we here for?
So what are you waiting for?
As far as the truth of
Shahrukh' s birth is concerned
Majid has also confirmed it.
Why don't you speak up, Majid?
What? - If you need more proof,
if you want more truth..
Check with the Sirauni
veterinary hospital
about Shahrukh' s bloodline.
We don't know about
Kalia and Salma's ancestors.
If a Catholic comes
in the future
and we get to know that
they are Christian by birth
it will complicate
the matter further.
Another thing.
There is no greed in us.
Because Mr. Swaran
has promised
that he will donate more
than half the money he gets
to the Goddess's temple.
Glory to the Goddess!
- Yes. So what's the big deal?
On the first day itself,
Majid had said
that he will give more than half
the money to the
mosque and school.
You are behind all this?
Look, chief and gentlemen.
This sacred symbol
is the proof of our claim.
So the money earned from him
will be used in the
name of the Lord. - Yes.
Our Gods will have
to go empty-handed?
Because of a symbol..
Lord! Lord!
Lord!
Glory to Lord Shiv Shambhu!
Lord Bholenath.
It's Lord Bholenath himself.
What happened?
- What are you doing?
I will offer my head to Goddess.
If anyone swears
on Lord Bholenath
and says that this symbol
is not Bholenath' s trident.
What nonsense!
- Glory to Lord Shiva!
Glory to Mahadev!
Say, glory to Mahadev!
- Glory to Allah! Glory to Mahadev!
Glory to Allah!
- Allah is great!
Silence. Silence.
What is this?
Is this a council or a joke?
Glory to Allah!
Glory to Mahadev!
It's a complicated matter.
So the decision can't
be taken in haste.
So..
The council has decided that
until the Sheikh comes here
or some other
decision is taken
Shahrukh will remain
in the council's custody.
Chief.
- And neither of the parties
will exercise
their right on him.
This is the council's decision. Enough.
- Chief, he is our child.
We don't accept it.
- It is the council's decision.
Silence.
The council ends here.
All of you go. Go home.
We don't accept your decision.
- It is our goat.
It is our goat. - It is ours.
Allah is written on it.
Come on. We won't leave.
We won't accept it.
- Silence.
Naaz,
I have told you so many times.
Don't call me
while I am working.
What is going on?
Nothing.
Everything will be fine.
When?
And how will it be alright?
Such things happen
in the council meeting.
Don't be afraid.
Nothing will happen.
Nothing will happen?
This betrayer also
had to show his color now.
We don't even know whether
he is a Hindu or a Muslim.
That's not true.
He is a messiah.
The entire village
accepts his powers. Right?
So what do we do?
Nothing will happen.
Don't worry.
I will do something.
Look,
you will have to do something,
Jaffer. You don't understand.
Or else..
What will happen of us?
Everyone is burning
with jealousy.
The things they said
in the council meeting.
What happened?
The shopkeeper has
refused to take eggs. - Why?
He says these are infernal eggs.
- What?
He said those who eat
them will incur a curse.
They will be born as
Muslims in their next birth.
All are scoundrels.
Let it be. Don't worry.
We have made the arrangement.
We have found a solution.
Got it?
We are trying to
call up the Sheikh.
Once he finds out, everything
will be resolved. - What?
What? Are you crazy?
You want to ruin everything.
- Give the phone back.
We have to call up Mr. Sheikh.
What are you doing?
Get the phone out. Get it out.
You have burned the phone.
Majid! Majid!
Majid!
Hello, Majid.
- Hello.
You know that assembly elections
are round the corner.
The party has
always stood by you.
This time you have got a chance
to show your loyalty.
If you had got money
from the Sheikh
and the people had
not been confused
by the trident symbol claims
we would have had
great expectations from you.
But seeing your situation
we have fixed the
amount of Rs. 25,000.
Rs.25,000? - Rizwan has
especially instructed that
Shahrukh' s absence
doesn't matter.
The priest's hands are blessed.
So we are to take
the money from him.
Chief, I was saying that you
have still not found a solution.
We have to pay for
Shahrukh' s upkeep every day.
So.. - Why?
Until now you have enjoyed
Shahrukh' s earnings.
Swaran Singh is waiting
with cash in hand.
He is ready to pay
for Shahrukh' s maintenance.
If that weakens your case..
- No, chief.
Our child is not a burden on us.
We can afford to
take care of him. Yes.
Chief,
don't worry about the money.
Feed him well. Feed him well.
Majid, there is a call
for you at Shastri's place.
What?
- Call for you.
Okay.
- Bye. Bye. - Come on.
Pick it up..
Hello.
Yes..
This is the priest.
Yes.
Who?
Give it to Majid?
Majid is unwell.
He has diarrhea.
Yes.
Mobile?
It got burned.
Yes. Okay.
What? Yes.
Bye.
Hello.
Junior Sheikh was very angry.
With great difficulty he got
the number from
the telephone exchange.
What did he say?
Sheikh is coming next week.
What?
- Yes.
The council members
will have to be quick.
To heck with them!
Even if they declare
Shahrukh to be a Hindu
Sheikh would still not care.
Who better than
Sheikh to spot a messiah?
The Quran originated from there.
Am I right, priest?
Let's go home.
- Yes.
Come on. Come on.
- Let's go.
Hello, ma'am.
Sir..
I am also there.
Hello, priest.
- Hello.
Are you going somewhere, ma'am?
Yes, child.
I am going to my mother's place.
It's better than
going to prison.
Prison?
What are you saying, ma'am?
I have brought sweets
for all of you.
I have got a job in
a big salon in Mumbai.
That's great news, child!
Child, take me along with you.
- Yes. Everyone can go.
I am here to get
beaten by the police.
Police?
What's the matter?
Sir, what is the matter?
Mr. Sheikh is coming.
Now what to do?
We can't stay here.
But why to leave the village?
What if he finds out
Shahrukh' s truth?
That his father Kalia
is a non-Muslim.
Now they are saying, he is
the incarnation of Lord Shiva.
Trident. God forbid.
Who knows what decision
the council will take, and when?
Priest, that's a good thing.
What's the worse
that will happen?
Mr. Sheikh won't take
Shahrukh with him.
The matter will end.
It's good.
Yes. And then we
will go to prison.
Why prison?
Sir, the claim not being
proven is not an offense.
But not returning 50,000
is a crime, isn't it?
You took money?
We asked for an advance.
And he immediately agreed.
Ask them where the money went.
Ma'am, where is the money?
Only Rs. 5,000 is left.
- What?
Forget that.
No one cared for me here.
You hardly will, when
I go to my mother's place.
But where did such
a hefty sum go?
The party workers took
away half as donation.
Okay. I am going.
I won't stay here.
Come on. Pick up the bags.
Pack your bags.
Yes. Go to the city.
Fine. If this is the matter
let's leave together.
What?
- What?
Yes. Come on.
Why is it taking so long?
Where are they?
Did that boy run away again?
Where will he go?
As it is, Shahrukh is not..
Don't take that wretch's name.
We are in trouble
because of him.
I am sure something is wrong.
- Yes.
Why are you worried?
He will come.
What do you mean?
We need to get away.
You don't understand. - We will
leave. Everything will be fine.
With God's grace everything
will be fine. Don't worry.
Look, a vehicle is coming.
- They are there.
Stop. Pull over.
- Look. Get up.
See whose vehicle it is?
It's ours!
Come on. Let's go.
Pick up the bags.
Pick it up.
- Has everyone come?
Come on.
- Let's go.
The luggage.. Ma'am,
all of you get into the vehicle.
I will load the bags.
Okay.
- All of you sit comfortably.
- Sit. Sit. Come on. Let's go.
Wait. - Why are you sitting
in the front? Let him sit.
Priest.
- Come on.
You sit.
Ma'am, I am there.
Let him sit. We youngsters
will sit in the rear.
He will manage. Let's go.
- Hurry up. Come on.
Get in. Get in.
- Sit comfortably.
Sit. Come on.
Come. Come, lad. Very good.
May God bless you
with prosperity, lad.
Not prosperity.
Just a beautiful girl. Yes.
Get that bag too.
Okay. Come on.
Come on. Let's go.
Murli, what happened?
I don't know. The vehicle is not
starting. I need the tool box.
Is that so? I will give you.
I know where the tool box is.
Wait.
Take this.
The goat has also come along?
What happened?
- What's going on?
Repair the vehicle. Repair
the vehicle. Repair the vehicle.
Why did you bring him?
Say something.
What have you done?
Oh, God!
Zulfi, are you crazy?
- Don't scold Zulfi.
You have put us
in serious trouble.
People think he is God.
We had to flee at night
because of this wretch.
Don't scold Shahrukh.
- Beware!
If he had not been there,
we wouldn't have been slandered.
He didn't do anything.
We did it.
What?
- What did you do?
Zulfi is right.
We made this symbol on Shahrukh.
I made it.
- What?
You made this symbol?
Yes. I wrote 'Lord' on him.
Oh God!
What else could I do?
You wanted to sell Shahrukh.
Zulfi didn't want him
to go anywhere.
Zulfi wanted Shahrukh.
All of you wanted money.
Why didn't both of you tell us
for so many days?
What will happen now?
Nothing will happen.
Everyone knows the truth.
Let's return to the village.
Shut up!
- What? You are a fool!
What do we do now?
- What else?
We will do what we were doing.
Let's flee.
Murli, did you fix the vehicle?
Yes, sir. The vehicle has been fixed.
Come on. Sit in the vehicle.
Let's go. Hurry up.
Zulfi, come on.
Come on. Sit in the vehicle.
Ma'am.
- Come on. - Sir.
Get him in.
- Yes, priest. You sit as well.
Let's go.
- Hurry up.
Murli.
"O' Prince.. You'll not be spared."
"Forget the wedding or love.
It's all in ruins now."
"You lost your way.
Love has made you blind."
"Look, who has come."
"He has captured the world."
"Everyone's eyes are on him."
"Arms have opened for him."
"Recognize me. I am Don."
Sir.
Let us pass, sir.
What?
- Let us pass.
Show the papers.
- They are in the car.
So bring them.
What do you think?
Can we extract something?
We will.
Looks like the police
have found out everything.
What nonsense! Keep quiet.
You don't have any brains.
You just keep talking nonsense.
Keep quiet. They are coming.
- Keep quiet.
From where?
- Who?
From which village
is your father from?
Mangori.
Where are you going?
We are going to Mumbai, sir.
Come on. Come out.
Hello, sir.
Sir, there are women.
We will check who are behind
the veil. Men or women.
Hurry up.
- Sir, I am from Mumbai.
I work in Mumbai. Hair stylist.
They are my relatives.
They are coming
to Mumbai with me.
I see. So you are the leader.
Where do you work in Mumbai?
You make bombs?
- Barber.
You make bombs,
acid and its likes in Mumbai.
What is in the vehicle?
- Nothing, sir. Household stuff.
Move. Show us. Show us. Show us.
RDX?
- No, sir.
Provisions. Clothes.
Nothing else.
What if there is
really a bomb inside?
What if it explodes?
What are you saying, sir?
Is that possible?
Anything can happen.
Didn't you see the old man?
He looks like Osama
Bin Laden's brother.
That Osama?
- Yes. That very Osama.
What do we do?
Hero. Come here.
Open the door.
Open it.
- Open it. Open it.
I am opening it, sir.
- Shall I hit you? No.
Open it.
Sir, it is a goat.
- What?
There is a goat and a child.
Tell me. Tell me.
Who is behind this? No.
Sir, are they going
to create trouble? No.
Whatever it is.
We can't take a chance.
The minister's function
is not far from here.
The minister is expected
to stay there for two hours.
Meanwhile, let them remain here.
They will stay here until
the function is over.
Arrest everyone
whom you suspect.
We will verify later who is
innocent and who is guilty.
Provide them with all the treatment.
- Sir. Sir, he has fever.
Look, how he is reclining. If
you could give him some drug..
I mean, medicine.
That's the medicine we offer.
Look. Take a good look.
This man is a smart chap.
He has gone to sleep.
Listen, find yourself a corner.
Come on.
Something is fishy.
I have an experience
of 30 years.
I can sense it.
No, sir.
- Sir
we had a doubt when
we opened the door.
We thought we would
find RDX, bombs.
Instead, we found a goat.
All are fools.
If they are fools,
we will let them go
once the minister leaves.
We have got orders
from our superiors.
Can't afford to take risk.
That's it.
Sir, we need to frisk the goat.
Frisk the goat?
- Of course.
Oh my!
Must weigh 15 kgs.
What is the market rate?
I don't know.
I asked my wife to make
'biryani' once.
She said, she would
break my bones.
We can't afford eggs
with our salary.
Mutton is beyond our reach.
Here is your chance.
Biryani. Kebab. Curry.
First, frisk the goat.
You don't know,
they fit it anywhere.
You are right.
Shinde, shove the stick inside.
See if it explodes.
Hold him.
- It is running.
Yes. - Wait. Come here.
- Stop.
What is this?
Oh my! Seems to be
some secret code. - Yes.
What is going on?
- See this.
Can you crack this code?
Code?
Oh God!
You all will be cursed.
Whom have you tied?
Why? Any problem?
Have all of you gone blind?
You have tied the Lord.
The Lord?
- What nonsense!
Not nonsense. A manifestation
of the Lord himself.
Look. Look carefully.
Yes. There is something.
- Yes.
Really.
- Oh God!
And you wanted to eat biryani?
O' Lord, I made a mistake.
I didn't know God
would come here like this.
How did you not see
such a big trident?
Oh God! All will be cursed.
God, forgive us this time.
We won't do this again.
Glory to the Lord!
Iqbal, untie him quickly.
- Glory to the Lord!
Praise the Lord!
Keep this Hindu-Muslim unity
for later. First, untie him.
Glory to the Lord!
- Glory to the Lord!
Why reverse circumambulation?
We do reverse circumambulation
for atonement.
This is how we will
get rid of the sin.
Glory to the Lord!
- Glory to the Lord!
The chaos continues.
Wonder what Shahrukh
thinks about all of this.
Human logic is beyond reason.
Shahrukh is just Shahrukh.
Roll camera..
And action!
"You are both alien and
acquaintance to me.."
"You are both alien
and acquaintance to me.."
"Your boon transforms
coal into a diamond."
"When it comes to the Lord.."
"When it comes to the Lord,
you're the messenger."
"Om Shanti Om.."
"You're the talk of the town.
You're a miracle."
"Even the sun
salutes you."
"I love you with all my heart."
"I love you with all my heart,
my beloved.."
"Om Shanti Om."
"Shahrukh, never bid adieu..
- Never bid adieu.."
"Stay in the hearts
till you thrive."
till you thrive.."
"I haven't seen a player like you."
"I see you never backing out."
"Everyone calls you their own.."
"You reign supreme.."
- "Yes, you do.."
"You're the love
of the hearts.."
"You personify prayers
and affection alike.."
"I'm grateful to you.."
"I'm grateful to you.
"I offer my gratitude.."
"Never bid us adieu.."
"Om Shanti Om.."