The tune..
You remember the tune?
Hey baby. I'm on the way.
Shall we meet directly
at the restaurant?
Sanjana, I am sorry. We'll have
to cancel today's dinner plan.
I have an important meeting
with a client.
I can't miss it.
Baby, it's my birthday.
We can at least
have dinner together.
Sanjana, we can celebrate
your birthday tomorrow.
This meeting is important.
I really need to go.
I'll see you at home.
And yeah.. Happy birthday.
Happy birthday to me.
Happy birthday!
Surprise!
- Anu! Oh my, God!
"Happy birthday to you!"
"Happy birthday, dear Sanjana."
- Thank you.
Thank you so much, Anu.
It's so sweet of you.
Don't thank me,
thank your husband.
He's organized all this.
Kabir?
But he's busy with some client..
- He knew he'll be late.
That's why
he organized this party
and called us all here.
Come on. Cut the cake before
your birthday gets over.
Cut my birthday cake
without Kabir?
Never.
Sanjana! It's hard to say
who loves whom the most?
You both are mad.
Absolutely crazy.
Honestly, you two
make me really jealous.
By the way, Sanju,
meet my cousin Chitra.
Hi.
- Happy birthday.
Thank you.
I am sorry for coming
here uninvited..
Are you mad?
You're most welcome.
- Thank you.
Sanju, she's an expert
tarot card reader.
If there's anything you want
to know anything about yourself.
Here she is.
She knows everything.
I hope you don't mind.
I don't believe in these things.
Why learn about
yourself from others?
And I've got everything.
And I'm doing good.
Of course you are.
But don't you want to know
whether you'll have
the fortune forever?
You always end up losing
everyone you love
or is close to your heart.
Do you agree?
Right or wrong?
A bit of both.
Have you lost something?
Strange, because
this card indicates that
you're going to find
what you lost.
Maybe someone's coming back.
"The moon's missing
from the sky."
"And descended in my home."
"I am so fortunate"
"like my wish has
been fulfilled."
"My love, I can't live
a moment without you."
"Desire to have you
has made me crazy."
Kabir, I want us
to spend time together.
I've told you
a thousand times before.
I don't want nothing
and no one between us.
Just you and me.
But you can't live with me.
There's always some surprise,
or party or people..
And then there's your career,
your meetings, your job.
Sanjana, you wanted
to flee from Kerala, right?
You wanted to come here.
To start a new life.
A better life, better lifestyle.
Isn't that what we
needed to be happy, right?
But for that, one has to work,
stay apart for a while.
I don't want to stay apart.
I don't want this.
I just want you.
Your time, your company.
Am I asking for too much?
Fleeing from Kerala didn't
mean that we grow apart too.
What do you want me
to do, Sanjana?
Quit my job and stay at home to
assure you nothing has changed.
Everything...
Everything is still the same.
Or let's go to Kerala?
Would you like that?
No.
The root of this problem is
this place. Let's just go back.
No.
Neither that city
nor that house.
That place is littered
with Anjana's memories.
Everywhere.
I won't go back to Kerala.
No.
Hello.
Okay.
What happened?
Mom's in the hospital.
We'll have to go to Kerala.
You okay?
Yes.
I cannot forgive myself.
I am really selfish,
right, Kabir?
Not at all.
If I hadn't insisted
for an operation
then Anjana would've been..
- Sanjana.
It wasn't you,
it was the operation.
No one wants
to be born like that.
No one wants a life like that.
It was an accident. A mishap.
Not selfishness.
Look, she suffered
a serious blow to her head.
She's paralyzed neck down.
She can't speak or walk.
Also, there's a blood clot
in her brain.
We found it in her MRI scan.
We may need to operate her.
Thank you, Doctor.
Sanjana.
Come on, Leo.
Yes, I'll take that.
Thank you. - Okay.
Shall we?
- Yes.
Five!
Anjana.
Sanjana?
Are you Mangala?
Yes, I..
How are you?
I'm okay. And you?
I am fine.
It's all right.
Some ups and downs.
How's madam?
She's being treated.
It's serious.
Who's she?
She's my daughter-in-law, Jaya.
- Hello.
My son's biggest mistake.
They got married
three months ago.
So I brought her here,
to work with me.
I see.
Do you know
what happened that day?
That accident?
I have no clue.
But there was a big storm
that night.
It was such a fierce storm
that the ceiling
of the outhouse collapsed.
Madam was lying outside
the outhouse, unconscious.
Outhouse?
Why do you always
keep it locked?
Why don't you open it?
How can we, sir?
It's been closed
for seven years.
I've been working here
since five years.
I asked madam once, and she said
this was Sanjana
and Anjana's playroom.
After Anjana's death,
Sanjana locked this place.
She said, this place is
filled with Anjana's memories.
Her toys, and..
And Anjana too.
- Mother!
What nonsense! Anjana too!
Please open it.
Sir..
- Get the key, please.
Thank you.
- Let's go.
Who is it?
Kabir!
Oh, God! You scared me.
And you amaze me.
What are you doing here
at 2 o'clock in the night?
Kabir, I.. I heard some noises.
What noise? Are you crazy?
Really, Kabir.
I heard some noises
and came to inspect.. - Sanjana.
If there were any sounds,
I'd have heard them too, right?
You didn't hear anything?
- No.
Come on.
- Kabir, trust me.
I heard some noises.
It must be coming
from some other house.
Come on. Let's go back
to sleep, come on.
Mr. Kabir.
- Yeah.
There have been
some complications.
We need to operate
on her immediately.
I think you should get her
as quick as you can.
What?
'Paging for Sister Parvati.'
'Sister Parvati please report
to ward 5.'
'Sister Parvati please
report to ward 5.'
Yes, Mohit, go ahead.
What?
No, Mohit,
you can't take a leave.
Kabir!
Sorry.
Buddy..
Mohit, firstly I am
not in the office.
And now you want a leave too.
Those are very
important clients.
Somebody has to be
there to handle them.
Who will do it?
I don't know. I am stuck
in this goddamn place.
Why did all the mothers have to
fall ill at the same time?
I just don't understand..
I'll call you back.
Sanjana, I am sorry.
I didn't mean that.
Sanjana.
I am sorry.
Actually, I am quite
stressed because of the work..
Just go, Kabir.
Don't worry about me.
I'll handle everything
here, alone.
And anyway,
what will you do here?
Just go.
I wanted your support,
not your favor.
Come on, Sanjana. You're making
a big deal out of this.
I am not going anywhere.
And I won't go until
mom doesn't recover.
But I will stay distracted..
I can't help that.
I know that.
I am used to dealing
with my problems alone.
To keep my emotions to myself.
For God's sake Sanjana,
all I said was..
Excuse me.
The operation was successful.
But you can't meet
your mom right now.
In the meantime,
you can complete
some hospital formalities.
Please. Thank you.
- Okay.
Thank you.
I'll take care of it.
It's all right. I'll do it.
Sanjana,
I said I'll take care of it.
Kabir!
Namit sir? You?
It's..
I can't believe it.
How are you?
- Good, sir. Good.
But you tell me this.
You just disappeared for years.
No contact or anything.
What are you doing here?
I mean what are you doing here?
- Hey!
Catch your breath first.
Well.. After seeing you,
I feel perfectly all right.
You haven't changed at all.
Still the same.
Looks and wits.
What are you doing here
at this hour?
Well, sir, my mother-in-law's
admitted in this hospital.
You don't worry,
she is in safe hands.
This is a very good hospital.
And then I am there.
Let me know if I can
be of some help. I'll do it.
Thank you so much, sir.
I know.
But first tell me
what are you doing here?
I am a psychologist
in this hospital.
And I also run a Healing
Institute in Kottayam.
Healing Institute?
- Yeah!
These days I do everything.
Spiritual healing, etcetera.
I have students, I also teach.
Keep my card.
- Thank you, sir.
I.. I will call you, sir.
Sure?
- We'll definitely meet.
Yeah! Okay.
You take care.
Okay?
It was nice seeing you, sir.
- Same here, Kabir.
Kabir. Kabir.
I saw her in the lift.
- Saw who?
She's there.
- Who? Who's there?
Can I say something?
Will you believe me?
What is it?
She's here, Kabir.
I can feel her.
Feel who?
Anjana.
Sanjana, please.
We're educated people.
Don't talk like
an illiterate woman.
Kabir.
How long will it
take to fix this?
Three to four days.
Excuse me.
Oh! Maximum three to four days.
Oh.. Okay.
Please get the work started.
- Okay.
Leo!
Where did he go?
Statue!
I am sorry to say
but your wife
has had a miscarriage.
Kabir.
I told you.. I had told you,
she's in this house.
Kabir, she's trying to harm me.
Kabir, please believe me.
I saw her last night.
Kabir.
Last night,
in the courtyard downstairs..
We've had a miscarriage!
We lost our child!
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
I wanted to.
But I was scared.
I didn't want to nurture
a deformed baby.
Like Anjana and Me.
Whether deformed or abnormal
but it would still have
been our baby.
You hid such a
big truth from me. Why?
You were drifting away from me.
After the child, you would've
drifted further away from me.
Kabir, the truth is that
I can't stay away from you.
I can't let anyone
come between us.
Between us?
What madness is this?
And children don't create rifts.
They fill the void, Sanjana!
You could've done it too.
You've totally lost it, Sanjana.
And it's all in your head,
not in this house.
Because it's completely empty.
It's filled with negative
thoughts, fear and illusions.
There's.. There's nothing here.
- Kabir.
And look at the consequences.
We lost our baby.
- Kabir.
Sanjana dear..
My mother once said to me
if you keep a knife
under your pillow
you won't see dream
about ghosts and evil spirits.
Will you try that?
Yes.
Here.
Kabir.
Kabir, I..
- What?
You're bleeding.
Kabir, I..
- Who, Sanjana?
There's no one here.
You've lost your mind.
She..
I am sorry.
- Yeah whatever.
I am going crazy.
I am sorry.
Okay.
I am going crazy.
- I'm sorry. Okay?
Kabir.
Help me. Please help me.
So Sanjana, tell me something
about your childhood.
What do I say?
I have so many
childhood memories.
So many untold stories.
Who were you closer
to in your childhood?
Your mother or father?
My sister, Anjana.
Anjana.
- What?
We'll never separate.
Promise?
- Promise!
So why did you
two decide to separate?
That..
Okay, okay, okay.
Stop.
Enough for today.
We'll continue in
the next session. Okay?
Now, relax.
- Okay.
Kabir.
It is a very delicate case.
We need to handle
it sensitively.
She's been through a lot.
Sister's death,
her miscarriage.
Mother's accident.
For sometime
believe what she says.
But, sir..
- Listen to me, Kabir.
Just agree to what she says,
what she thinks.
Don't fight with her.
Even if you don't believe.
Get it?
Yes.
Another thing.
I think she needs a break.
Take her out, in the open air.
Let's see if staying away from
this house makes a difference.
Where have you brought me?
Ready?
- Ready.
Kabir, this..
This is a dream,
where there is you, me
and no one else.
This is your time.
Not even mine.
I am really sorry, Sanjana.
I didn't try to understand you
and left you alone.
Please. It was my fault too.
I wanted to impart love
instead I just became
a burden on you.
I always thought about myself.
I should say sorry, Kabir.
- Enough.
We're done apologizing.
Please forget everything.
Kabir, what about mom?
If there's an emergency,
the doctors will call us.
I've taken care of it.
Trust me.
And your trip to Mumbai?
Changed your mind?
Yes.
- "It says.."
I changed my mind
about going back
and returning to you.
"Let's spend those days again."
"Brought me close to you,
made me restless."
"Made me crave for you!"
"Lost control.."
"My heart's lost control."
"Gives rise to desires
in the first rain."
"Makes the heart beat faster."
"Restless by nature,
calls out to you."
"Makes me cry when you're away."
"And no matter how I try"
"it's impossible to pacify."
"Brought me close to you,
made me restless."
"Made me crave for you!"
"Lost control.."
"My heart's lost control."
"Let's wander
in those lanes again."
"Where the breeze
of love always flew."
"Why don't we meet
like strangers again?"
"And introduce
each other once again."
"And lose my heart again,
after meeting you."
"Brought me close to you,
made me restless."
"Made me crave for you!"
"Lost control.."
"My heart's lost control."
What happened?
- Kabir..
That hand..
It was a hand..
Kabir.. Kabir..
- There's nothing.
It's nothing.
'It didn't make a difference,
sir.'
'She thinks Anjana's
following her everywhere.'
Sir, it's said that,
if one of conjoined twins die
the other doesn't live
for too long. I know..
I know this is all a..
- Hold on.
You will have to understand
that Anjana and Sanjana
were connected together
even by soul,
not just physically.
Don't you see?
Maybe due to fear,
but they're still together.
They haven't separated.
Sir, I agree you're right.
But Sanjana's problems started
after we came to Kerala.
Do one thing.
Consult the doctor and see
if Sanjana's mother can be
shifted to a hospital in Mumbai.
Yeah, I can do that.
Did you fix the roof?
- Yes.
Have you done it properly?
- Yes, madam. I've done it.
Mangla. Lock the doors.
Sorry, madam. I forgot.
I'll lock the door.
How could I forget?
Doc, I just want to know
if we can shift her to Mumbai.
It's important for me to go.
And I'll get her treated.
Mr. Kabir, forget treating
her at Mumbai
she is not in a condition
to travel.
Sorry. I can't take that risk.
- I understand.
When was the first time
you met Kabir?
Sanjana, I'm going to
London for higher studies.
London? But why didn't
you tell me this earlier?
And now suddenly..
- After my parent's divorce
dad shifted to London.
He got me admission
in the Leigh University.
So I have to go.
- But for how many days?
Not days, but years.
Won't you come to the airport,
to see me off?
Of course I will.
I will see you there.
Okay, bye.
- Bye.
Kabir's going to London,
for years.
He's called me to the airport.
I don't want to go anywhere.
Anjana, let's go please.
- No.
Anjana, please.
- No!
'Anjana, let's go please.
- No.'
After that it was difficult
for us to stay in touch.
'I could neither write
a letter or an email.'
'Nor call him.'
Anjana!
Anjana, please give it to me.
'Even mom didn't want us
to be together.'
'So she would hide
the letters he wrote to me.'
'Maybe.'
'Time went on.'
'Kabir had been away
for 10 years.'
And one day.
Hello.
- Hi.
Kabir, is that you?
Guess what?
I am coming back.
To you.
You're coming back. When?
I can't believe this.
I am coming back soon, Sanjana.
And this time you'll have to
come to the airport
to receive me.
I don't know how,
but you will have to come. Okay?
Yes, I will come.
I definitely will.
No one can stop me this time.
Good.
Okay, I'll have to go now.
I'll.. I'll see you soon.
Okay.
- Bye.
Kabir is coming back.
And he wants us to receive him.
Meet him.
You can meet him, not me.
Anjana, stop being so obstinate.
We're no longer kids.
I want to meet him, Anjana.
He loves me
and I love him so much.
This time I will meet him,
Anjana.
Even if it means
separating from you.
And that's when you decided
to separate from Anjana.
'Yes, it was my decision.'
And I blame myself
for her death.
Yes, I killed her.
If that's true
then you still have no reason
to feel so guilty.
It's not wrong to
think about yourself.
Sometimes it's not a crime
to be selfish either.
You're human being, not God.
I was trying to be God.
Made a decision about
someone else's life.
She could've lived her life,
still be alive
but I took away her life.
But she's back now.
She's following me.
She wants to take me with her.
Sanjana. Sanjana.
Please try and understand.
It's the after-effect
of her death
which you're still
carrying along.
Your fear
is nothing but the burden
on your heart.
The day you stop
blaming yourself
you will stop seeing
Anjana as well.
Kabir!
Sanjana!
Sanja..
Sanjana, wake up.
Wake up.
Sanjana,
what are you doing here?
Kabir!
- W-Why are you here?
I don't know, Kabir.
I don't know.
Kabir, I am scared.
Enough, Sanjana. Stop crying.
- Please help me.
That's enough.
Enough.
Calm down. Calm down.
Stop it.
Isn't one ghost enough
in this house?
Oh mother-in-law! Does your
TV only air horror movies?
I told you a thousand times
there's no such thing as ghost.
But you..
Madam said it for
the sake of her child.
The sister said for
the sake of her sister.
So why won't you believe it?
Mother-in-law,
everyone has a soul
in their body.
Once the body perishes
the soul won't come back.
Oh God! You confuse me
if I'm inside
or outside the body?
Oh God! Forget it. Go make some
breakfast and serve it to them.
Go.
Inside or outside the body?
What are you looking at?
- You.
Because I want to.
So I am looking at you.
What else do you
feel like doing?
I feel affectionate.
There are so many things
in my heart.
I want to say everything.
So then what's stopping you?
Stay with me forever.
Sanjana, I have to go.
Go
but come back soon.
I promise.
Mother-in-law! Mother-in-law!
What is it?
- Mother-in-law!
I saw Sanjana madam.
She was lying on the floor
in the outhouse
clutching on to her
sister's clothes and toys.
And when I went closer
she stared back at me
as if she was possessed.
Enough about ghosts and spirits.
Hold this.
Mother-in-law..
Mother-in-law. Believe me,
I'm telling you the truth.
Keep quiet, keep this plate.
Take a look.
Please come take a look.
Why did you drop
the plate on seeing her?
What were you thinking?
Sorry, madam, I..
- It's all right.
It happens.
Next time, focus on your job
and not the people
in this house.
Okay.
You..
Sanjana.
This..
No one can love you
as much as I do.
And no matter how
many times I say this
it's not enough.
No matter how much
I express my love
it's never enough.
Sanjana.
No one will come between us now.
It's just you
and me.
What's the matter, Sanjana?
Something's different about you.
What?
Don't know.
There's something different
but whatever it is
I don't want to go
away from it.
"Embrace me in you."
"Don't leave any
part of me in me."
"You don't remember
who you are."
"I don't remember who am I?"
"Come embrace me."
"And let me hide you
in my arms."
"I'll trickle drop by drop."
"And stay on your body."
"And stay in you."
"Empty the river"
"fill me with it."
"Let me drink you up."
"Quench my thirst."
"Bring some clouds."
"And make them shower on me."
"Let me drench you with drops."
"You don't remember
who you are."
"I don't remember who am I?"
"Come embrace me."
"And let me hide you
in my arms."
"I'll trickle drop by drop."
"And stay on your body."
"And stay in you."
"I'll trickle drop by drop."
"And stay on your body."
"And stay in you."
I'll go see the doctor, okay?
Okay.
Mom.
What happened?
I don't know.
She was trying to say something.
I don't know what happened.
Yes, everything is fine.
I mean, is there
anything to worry about?
No, there's nothing
to worry about.
Thank God we reached on time
otherwise anything
could've happened.
So, how's Sanjana now?
- She's much better now, sir.
What do you mean?
- I mean..
The guilt about Anjana.
The nightmares, depression.
It's..
It's all gone.
Disappeared.
And I just want
to thank you, sir.
You're the reason
I found my old Sanjana back.
Thank you so much.
Coffee.
Hi, Sanjana.
- Hi.
Sorry, excuse me.
Yeah, Mohit. Tell me.
Divya was talking about you.
She said, 'We must invite
Kabir and Sanjana for lunch'.
Well, that's not
my bloody problem.
I said, 'Good idea,
let's plan it out today'.
Just send them
the logistical plan and..
She was also planning
on watching a film.
But..
But, there must
be an alternative.
I am sure there's
something you can do.
Your husband is a busy man.
Tell them, we are..
You must feel lonely, right?
Seriously, Mohit,
I can't handle it.
I know.
I know your mother's ill,
but until I come back..
Hello.
- You must handle it.
You know this project
is very important for us.
We cannot afford to
make any more mistakes.
Sanjana.
And the requirements from their
company, please update..
Sanjana!
I am sorry.
I'll make the coffee.
- No. I'll make it.
And, did the customs
release the shipment?
Are you okay?
- Yes.
I'm absolutely fine.
After a decade,
I am finally happy.
Thank you.
Sorry, sir, it was an important
call. Couldn't avoid it.
Leo, shut up.
Shut up!
I wonder what's wrong with Leo.
He suddenly got violent.
He barked at Sanjana.
I think he needs
counseling as well.
Kabir, this is serious.
Animals can see
what humans can't.
It's called
Extra Sensory Perception.
It's weird that he
got violent like this
on seeing Sanjana.
Maybe he sees
the change that you did.
Something isn't right.
Sir..
Such drastic change in
such a short time is not normal.
Such people hide things.
They have too many things
on their mind
but they don't reveal it.
They want people to
consider them normal.
but, they are actually not.
Sir..
Sir, I don't understand.
Watch her.
Keep an eye on her.
And keep this between us.
Help.
Help! Kabir!
- Sanjana.
Kabir, help me!
Help me.
- Leo!
Leo, stop it.
Leo. No, Leo.
- Help me, Kabir.
No, Leo.
Mother-in-law! Mother-in-law!
Mother-in-law!
Mother-in-law.. - Why are
you shivering in this weather?
Are you sick?
- I won't work in this house.
You won't work here? Why?
Mother-in-law,
I am scared of Sanjana madam.
Scared of Sanjana madam? Why?
I was collecting my purse
and that's when looked
out the window..
Help!
Help. Kabir, help me!
Kabir, help me! Help me!
Help!
Kabir, help me!
Kabir!
Leo!
- Leo!
Leo, stop it.
Leo! Leo! No, Leo!
Help me, Kabir!
I don't know, sir.
I don't understand.
I mean..
There's always something
happening in this house.
One thing's over
and another spring's up.
I just don't know what to do.
Sir..
Yes, Mangla. Tell me.
Sir, I don't know
if you'd believe me.
But someone's cast
an evil eye on this house.
With your permission
I'll conduct veneration
in this house.
And everything will
be fine after that.
Okay.
Sanjana.
Just like there are
two kinds of human beings.
Similarly,
there are two kinds of spirits.
Good and bad.
Bad spirits often
possess weak bodies.
Trouble them.
And later, kills them.
The way your wife's getting weak
she's getting seriously ill
it proves that she's possessed
by her sister's spirit.
But she won't
posses her for long.
Soon, she will kill her.
We have very little time.
Hail the Bhoot Puran
(Book of evil)!
Lord have mercy on us.
This Bhoot Puran was
been written by ascetics
thousands of years ago.
We can use the chants written
in them to control the spirit.
Destroy all the
belongings of her sister.
Cover every glass in this house.
Mirrors, photographs,
everything.
Because, as soon as
I start chanting
the spirit will leave her body
and try to hide in these things.
And this shouldn't happen.
I've covered all the
corners of this house
so that the spirit
doesn't leave.
The spirit has to be
destroyed right here.
Once I start chanting,
it will lie, try to distract us.
She'll try to scare us.
But we'll have to be brave.
Cover her face.
Kabir!
Kabir, help me!
Kabir, they are hurting me!
Kabir!
Leave me.
Help me!
Kabir, help me!
No one can stop me!
Let her go.
You don't belong to this world.
Go back to wherever
you came from.
I didn't go there
but I was sent there.
She killed me.
Now I will kill her.
I will kill her!
Shut up!
Go away or else
I'll turn you to ashes.
Go!
Find the truth.
You'll get me out of her body
but, how will you get me out
of this house?
She killed me!
Killed me!
She killed me. Took my life.
Try to find the truth.
The truth.
The spirit is out of her body
but, she's not in my control.
She's still somewhere
in this house.
You okay?
My head's aching.
The effect won't
wear off so soon.
What happened with me, Kabir?
What happened?
Sanjana's returned
to me after a long time.
Let me you in my arms first.
Then I'll tell you
what Anjana did to us.
'She killed me. Killed me.'
'She took my life.'
Did Anjana's truth scare you
or Sanjana's lie?
What do you mean?
What's all this?
All I got was lies, so I thought
I must lie to know the truth.
Stop talking in riddles.
Be clear.
Even I am trying
to solve the puzzle.
Tell me what you did?
Who did you kill?
What was the lie
you always told me?
Tell me, Sanjana!
I never lied to you.
You didn't lie to me, but you
didn't tell me the truth either.
Anjana's spirit is
still in this house.
And she won't leave you alone
until you don't speak the truth.
Sanjana,
I don't want to argue with you
or raise my voice.
It's even your responsibility
to keep this relation intact.
Now the choice is over.
The truth might not
keep us together
but a lie will
definitely shatter it.
Okay, Sanjana.
Your silence has
conveyed your decision.
But Sanjana, everyone
has to pay for their deeds.
You'll have to pay for yours
and I will repent
for loving you.
Kabir, stop.
I will tell you the truth.
Please don't leave me.
I love you very much.
Please don't go.
I will tell you everything.
Please don't leave me.
Please.
Kabir is coming back,
and he wants us to receive him.
Meet him.
- You can go, not me.
I will meet him
this time, Anjana.
Even if I have
to separate from you.
Kabir doesn't love you.
He just wants to separate us.
So he's pretending to love you.
Otherwise,
what else could be the reason
that he loves you instead of me.
What's wrong with you, Anjana?
Have you lost your mind?
He only loves me.
He thinks of you
as a good friend.
You snatched Kabir from me.
You came between us.
Because I know he loves me!
And I love him!
That's not true.
Kabir loves me, not you.
No? Then I'll make sure,
he only loves me.
Anjana!
Mom!
'That day mom saved me'
'because it was an accident.'
I didn't want to kill her.
I was only trying
to save my life.
Sanjana, why didn't
you tell me this before?
Because I didn't
want to lose you.
I'm so sorry, Sanjana.
I didn't know
that my love for one sister
would be the cause
of death for the other sister.
Remember this.
Anjana loved you very much.
And I love you.
So sorry, Sanjana.
This means Anjana's spirit
is here to take revenge
and, she won't leave
without doing so.
There's something Anjana's
spirit is tethered to.
Before she attacks Sanjana again
you'll have to find
that thing and burn it.
What happened?
Sanjana, he says
something in the house..
Come.
It's coming from here.
Anjana!
Mother-in-law..
We'll have to burn
this body right now.
Go get kerosene.
Walk faster.
Mother-in-law..
Come on.
Let's go.
Mother-in-law.
Jaya! Jaya!
Mother-in-law!
Mother-in-law! Mother-in-law!
Why are they taking so long?
I'll take a look.
Thank God you're here, sir.
We found Anjana's dead body.
We just need kerosene..
- Here.
You have the kerosene?
I found this when I went
in the house. I.. - Okay.
You should never
try to fool spirits.
Kabir!
Hide and seek?
Sanjana! Burn her body.
Go! Go!
Kabir..
Kabir!
Kabir, are you okay?
What do I call you?
Sanjana or Anjana?
Kabir, what are you saying?
What do I call you?
That's Sanjana's body, isn't it?
No, Kabir.
I am Sanjana.
That's a lie!
How many times
are you going to lie?
Please, tell me the truth now.
Tell me the truth.
Kabir..
- Tell me the truth.
Tell me the truth.
No? Then I'll make sure
that he only loves me.
Mom, please.
From now, I am Sanjana.
I could not help it, Kabir.
I loved you like crazy.
I wanted you.
I couldn't live without you.
You couldn't live without me..
but, you could kill your sister.
- No.
Our relationship, our marriage,
it was all a lie. - No.
All these years I was deceived
because, it was all a lie.
- No.
Your whole existence
is nothing but a lie.
- No, Kabir.
Don't say that.
What's the difference
between me and her?
We were both the same.
Then why didn't you love me?
Having the same face doesn't
make you the same person.
People are always different.
Kabir.
And like you said
no one can replace anyone.
Kabir. Kabir..
That moment, that day,
that year.
All the time that
we spent together.
Don't they have any importance?
Every time you said you love me.
Isn't that worth anything?
Say it, Kabir.
- No.
It's worth nothing.
Because I always loved Sanjana.
When I was close to you, I was
not with you. And you knew
that you had taken
Sanjana's place.
Not yours.
Fine, then give me my place.
Forget her and accept me.
This locket.
Adorn this locket on me,
like you did to Sanjana.
Do it.
- Anjana.
Do it, please.
There's place for only
one person in the heart.
And no one else can take it.
Nor the moments together or
the nuptial rounds.. - Please.
Kabir.
- Nor did we breathe together.
So just let it go.
Because this..
Kabir.
...and me
belong to someone else.
Kabir!
You can't leave.
I won't let you go.
Say you love me.
Say you love me!
Say you love me, Kabir.
It was always about Sanjana.
You never knew how much
I loved you.
If you can't be mine
then no one else
can have you either.
You can't be anybody else's!
Kabir!
Sanjana!
"I conveyed my feelings"
"to you, through my eyes."
"You gestured your love"
"and I unhooked my tresses."
"Touch me,
slowly-slowly feel me."
"Don't tease me anymore"
"I could take it no more."
"I just want to,
feel your body."
"Touch my body."
"Don't be shy, my honey."
"Feel my body."
"I just want to,
feel your body."
"Touch my body."
"Don't be shy, my honey."
"Feel my body."
"Touch your lips with mine"
"and leave an impression."
"I want to stay in your arms"
"until tomorrow morning."
"I'm going crazy
looking at you."
"Give me a place in your heart."
"I could take it no more."
"I just want to feel your body."
"Touch my body."
"Don't be shy, my honey."
"Feel my body."
"I just want to feel your body."
"Touch my body."
"Don't be shy, my honey."
"Feel my body."
"You're so intoxicating"
"I want to drink all of it."
"You can do anything you want."
"I am all yours.
I wouldn't mind."
"I conveyed my feelings"
"to you, through my eyes."
"I could take it no more."
"I just want to feel your body."
"Touch my body."
"Don't be shy, my honey."
"Feel my body."
"I just want to feel your body."
"Touch my body."
"Don't be shy, my honey."
"Feel my body."