We're standing outside
the Pune Tennis stadium.
Elderbaum All India Tennis
Final Match is going to be played.
In this final there is
one side Indian number one...
...and winner from 3
years Mr. Mahesh Singh.
And on the other side is
up coming tennis star...
...Chirag Mehra.
This noise, this crowd and
the moments before the game...
...is very
exciting for every player.
Today's match might
just be a game for viewers.
But I know...
...today my
competition is with my own fate.
I can not win till my aim
comes true related to this game...
...which I've started 16 years ago.
Chirag! You didn't sleep yet.
Come on, come on.
- Good shot.
Chirag, you come and stand
here after school?
You've a lot of
interest in this game.
Yes, sir.
Want to learn?
- Yes, sir.
Good. Get your racquet.
It's kid's nature...
...if you stop them from
something they'll insist to do that...
And maybe that was
happening with me too.
Chirag, very good.
Back hand swing.
Very good.
After each day my
game was improving.
Everyone was happy, but my
destination was very far.
What's the big deal?
If I'll try 10-15 times then
I'll make 8-10 shots, correct.
Okay, come.
What?
- Quiet. Stand straight.
Chirag! You're being
serious, I was just joking.
But I'm serious.
If you'll hit the ball
somewhere else then I'll be in trouble.
Do you understand?
- Shut up and don't move.
It's just a game for you
but it's a matter of my life.
Stand straight.
Okay. Aim at that can.
Good shot!
Mumbai's and Surat's consignment
of grapes...
...should be deliver by tonight.
Consignment will
be delivered on time,
Good.
And I need report on my
table in just two hours.
I've already kept that.
Okay!
Vangi, I told you many times
to check every thing by your self.
I've checked by myself.
But in 2 box there is...
- What did you check?
See it's still raw?
I'm sorry.
Father.
Hey...
I hope you didn't get
hurt. Are you alright?
Get aside.
Let him breathe.
- Did you get hurt?
Somebody fetch some water for
him, You guys get back to work.
Pratik, handle it.
- Okay.
How did it happen?
He didn't sleep well nor
he take his meals on time...
If he'll work in 2
shifts then it will happen.
It's not his age
to work for 2 shifts...
Then what else he'll do?
He's doing because he want
to get his daughter married.
I just want to my
get daughter married...
...then I'll go back to my village.
Everything will be fine.
Take him to shelter.
Come, father.
- Take care.
Come on. Load this.
And keep these bad grapes aside.
Pick up this.
- What is happening?
Who the hell is done this?
Who did it all?
Sir, that just...
- What just? Who did it?
I dropped them all.
You?
That's how you fulfil your
duty, So irresponsible.
You're are free now.
Now you'll load
these boxes in the truck.
And nobody will help him.
You all go.
- Sir, should I help him?
Shut up! Follow me.
Disgraceful! Sinful!
He thinks it's a joke.
Come on, let's get
back to the work.
Come on, start.
Nice reprimand!
I'm tired.
- Really?
I'm helpless.
I don't have anyone except you...
...but I don't understand why
do you tolerate all these things.
Why don't you go
away from this Hitler?
You know why I can't do it.
I'm going to Mumbai for some days.
Make sure that everything
should be perfect in my absence.
Yes.
I don't need any trouble.
Good.
Bye.
Come on. Do your work.
When will you clean this well?
We'll have to
drain the water first.
I've to stop the water
flow after that I'll clean it.
Aunt, is this the
same pickle which...
...you cook with red
chilly? - Yes. - Chirag!
Yes, uncle.
One minute son.
You guys eat it.
Thank you.
- Greeting.
Aunt, even bring jaggery tomorrow.
- Okay, son.
Yes, uncle?
Boss is gone.
- He went to Bombay for a few days. Why?
Actually that...
I've to make many arrangements...
...and I want to
go for 7 days leave.
Why?
- Tomorrow is my daughter's wedding.
You didn't tell me.
You need leave, So you can go.
And if you're worried about
the arrangements then... Venky!
Just coming.
Yes! - Tomorrow is his
daughter's wedding...
You'll make all
arrangements. Nothing should be lacking.
Okay, uncle?
- Thank you very much, Chirag.
C'mon.
- Will you come?
I'll come and celebrate.
The marriage will
look like the celebration.
Listen, beloved! Buy a
golden ear ring for me.
O young damsel! First
show me your dance.
My heart longs for you.
If you listen to
me, I'll agree with you.
Oh my sweetheart...
Oh my sweetheart... don't
make your lover crave.
Don't make your lover crave.
Oh my sweetheart...
I'll make you crave.
You walk with a swagger.
Your intentions aren't good.
I won't be wooed by you.
Oh my sweetheart...
Oh my sweetheart... don't
make your lover crave.
I know everything. Don't
think I'm naive.
Everyone calls you flirt.
I know everything. Don't
think I'm naive.
Everyone calls you flirt.
Don't break my heart.
I will never leave your hand.
Why do you hold my hand?
Oh my sweetheart...
I'll make you crave.
Oh my sweetheart... don't
make your lover crave.
Sweetheart...
She'll become Pratik's queen.
Oh my sweetheart...
Stand properly.
I'm standing straight only.
The ground is shaking.
Where you coming from?
That...
Uncle you don't know...
It was Birju Uncle's daughter's wedding.
- Yes.
It was a great party.
From whose permission you
sent all workers on leave.
Dehli's consigment
is about to deliver...
How we'll send it, You
didn't think about it.
Consignment is ready and
it will be deliver tomorrow.
I see, okay.
Then tomorrow
you'll go to Hyderabad...
...to finalize Cold Harvest Project,
You'll meet Mr. Bedi there,
And when Bedi will...
- Tomorrow but.
How could I go tomorrow?
- Why?
Tomorrow is 1st of month.
Hi.
- Hi mother.
Hi son.
How are you?
- I'm fine.
Hi Pratik. - Greeting aunty.
- Greeting.
Mom! I've told you
many times that...
...don't send chopper to pick me up.
I can come from the car.
My son comes to me for one month...
I don't want to
miss a single second.
You're crazy mother.
- That I'm.
Can we go?
- Come.
Hello sir. - Hi.
How are you? - Fine.
Thanks.
- I'll come from here.
Okay.
You must be hungry,
How was the food?
Great food mother.
Give him some Biryani,
- I'll take it by myself.
Eat properly, I've made
your favourite food.
I know what my son eats there.
Except food everything
is fantastic there.
Right, Pratik.
Yes yes.
Mother, come to our vineyard once.
You're going to
love the place and...
...even dad has
taken 4sqe land more.
That place down
the mountain is now...
Thanks for reminding me.
The place of panvel is deal now.
The land is of 200 Acre.
I've thought to make an
elite township in your name.
When you'll come to the office
tomorrow we'll decide its sale.
Even you've to sigh so
many contract and tender.
What is this?
- Madam, Chirag has brought.
Mother, that is for you.
Chirag, except you I don't
have interest in any thing.
Excuse me.
Hello yes.
Chirag every children is playing.
What you're
thinking and sitting alone.
Sister I'm thinking that...
...who is more important
among mother and father.
For a child both mother
and father is important.
Then why my mother and
father don't understand this.
I know your mother and
father both love you a lot.
But I want to know that
with whom you want to leave?
With both.
Chirag, who is child
now and there should...
...not be any
disturbance in his education...
...so his mother
and father has the...
...responsibility of his education.
During holiday of
boding school he'II...
...be with his
father for one month...
And one month with her mother.
But I decided till the time mother
and father become one...
I'll continue this distribution.
Dad is really handsome. Right?
Sorry, did I scare you?
What are you doing?
- Sorry.
When will you grow up, Chirag?
- Mom, I'm fine.
This is fine. Everything
is proper. Chill.
Why did you stop it? Didn't
you like my childhood?
Naughty! Stop it.
Oh... I got it.
Dad has ruined your mood.
Chirag.
- Okay. Chill.
But mom, night isn't so
boring at dad's vineyard.
Ah...
What I mean is that so
many people are there...
And dad...
Don't ask about him.
If you had been
there, it would've been fun.
You wouldn't miss me there.
I miss you. I don't know about dad.
Even if he misses,
he won't show it.
Let it be.
I know him very well.
If you knew him well, you
would've been together.
You know, mom...
...when I'm with you,
dad gets alone there.
And when I'm with dad...
...I feel the pain
of your Ioneliness.
I'm in no pain, Chirag.
Even of separation from dad?
No.
I'm only hurt...
...because of that man...
...my son was divided.
Chirag.
Oh God.
You're still sleeping.
Wake up. It's late.
You're sleeping in the same clothes.
- Mom.
I came yesterday.
Let me sleep for more time. Please.
I told you there is work in office.
I'll come.
I've brought your favourite thing.
Cone and see when you get up.
My favourite thing.
Wow mother, what a
machine I love it.
It's like flaying.
Thanks mother.
I told you, you can
always count on me.
Mother, look whose phone is there?
Yes.
Receive it.
Put on a speaker.
Hello.
Why you look that much
time to pick up the phone.
Is your mother there near you?
No she's in office.
Why you phone me?
I'm not getting the
presentation of golden harvest.
That is in my
folder on the desk stop.
But the file isn't opening.
What is the password.
Shalini.
Ji Shalani or only Shalani?
Only Shalini.
You dint get any other password?
Why what is the problem in Shalani?
Does it open?
Typing.
Chirag take care...
Talking during drive.
If I would be
with you then I want...
...allow you to do this mistake.
What's that?
Mother, sorry.
Mother.
Good morning madam.
- Good morning.
Mr. Makhija please have a set.
Gentle man after so much
affect I brought Chirag here.
Make him sigh the
document and contract.
Is the other busy man.
Madam, we got the papers read.
Sir.
- All right.
Good morning madam good morning sir.
- Good morning.
Madam, some Important document
has come. Will you've a look?
Take them to my chamber I'll
just joint you okay. - Yes madam.
Okay you take care
I'll see you later. - Okay.
Bye.
- Bye madam.
Mr. Makhija, please give.
Hi Ourni.
So long time. How are you?
I'm absolutely fine.
What really, that's good
news. When you're coming?
So Chirag, how is going on?
All done mother, let's go.
Done?
- Yes.
Excuse me sir you
forgot to sine this document.
I've not forgot Mr. Makhija.
I've not sine this
document purposely.
I didn't understood sir.
From last two
weak there is strike...
...of indefinite chemical supply.
And the time of delivery
that you mention is so less.
If a delivery not on time
we'll lost around 3to5 million.
Just inform me before
any commitment.
Okay.
- Yes sir.
Mother, can we go?
Chirag, I was thinking
that you're not...
...interested in
business but you're...
Mother, when I take the
calculation of father's...
...vane ward of
each and every grape...
Then how can I do lose of
millions rupees of mother?
Thank you.
Congratulation Mr. Bajaj.
I'm shore your product
will absolutely success.
Thank you Chirag, we're
happy to see you here.
My pleasure.
- Enjoy your self.
Anishka, have you come?
Okay I'm coming.
But where are you?
- Oh madam, pay my charge.
Oh sorry.
How much money?
- 190 rupees.
To come here it make
80 rupees how come 190?
Madam, you must be travailing
in a rickshaw it's a cool cab.
If it's a cool cap then why
you switch off the air condition.
And even you increase your meter.
It's not right.
- Give how much he says.
But this people.
- Let it be we're getting late.
Yes give it.
Take it.
- I'll complain it to the police.
This money will definitely harm you.
- Do complain...
but go by rickshaw.
It's Atul Bajaj's party.
There are so many people who are
connected with advertise agency.
Such a big party?
- Yes.
I'll try to introduce you with all.
But you don't give
your number to any one.
If some one say
something extra them...
...say him to talk to my manager.
- Yes.
Anishka.
Red wine!
- Yes.
Don't drink just do acting.
I'm going to hello them.
Where are you going?
- Relax I'm coming.
Hi.
Omeji.
My... my Avnit.
Wate hold on, come on
give me a tight hug. - Yes.
Give a tight hug.
Hi Anishka, you're here?
- Hi.
As you're here.
Okay...
Hi how are you.
- And this is Kavita.
Okay.
Omiji, I want to introduce
you to some one.
Hi see you girl.
Bealive me she's a stuning girl.
She's very beautiful girl.
Do you like to meet her?
Sure why not.
I think so she has drunk more.
God know from where they come from.
Anishka.
Hi.
- Anishka come.
Anishka this is Omeji.
- Omeji this is Anishka.
Omeji nice to meet you.
- Same hare.
Anishka nice name I like it.
You both carry on I'm just coming.
- Yes.
Where are you going?
- Coming.
I've seen the small
commercial which you've done.
Thanks. - Should I give a satiation.
- Yes sir.
Don't do all that crab.
- Crab?
Yes it's crab you know.
Good face and even good figure.
Why don't you do one thing?
You just come to my
office we'll plan something.
Yes sir.
- Yes.
She'll send you the photographs.
- Oh sure that's nice.
You don't have glass in your hand?
Actually that...
- Let's have some champion?
You like?
- No I'll eat something.
You want to eat something all right.
- Yes thank you.
Waiter, come here.
Yeah have some fishy!
Even you'll eat this?
Ladies first.
- Yeah.
This is raw fish.
Yes I'm coming.
Excuse me.
- I'm coming.
Come on.
Go go.
Oh no...
Sorry.
- That's all right.
The ladies wash room is there.
Hello, yes dad.
I'll go for the
practice after this.
Pratik, I'm ready
you just come inside.
What I'll in the tennis club?
You don't practise
with girls in frock.
Come down with in five
minute other wise I'm coming up.
Chirag, it's very
enjoyable in aunty's place.
But your practice
at night make trouble.
What I'm saying you just
abject your time of doing practice.
Let me do the practice, hi friends.
- Hi Chirag.
What's up Pratik?
- What...
Chirag.
Did you slap?
Come on Chirag focus.
Very good Chirag.
Good good very good Chirag.
Thank you sir.
- Well done.
Yes tanishka I'm
living for the office.
And listen make all the appointment
of Chirag after lunch.
I don't think he'll be
able to reach there before.
Okay I'm leaving.
Good morning mother.
You're ready.
Yes why?
Yesterday night I didn't see you so
I thought you were doing party
with your friend and slap late.
Right.
But you got ready in
the morning that's great.
Actually I'm
going to the panchgani.
Panchgani?
Because of some project.
But which project?
First let me complete after
that I'll give you the details.
Okay just wish me luck.
Wish you all the best son.
Take this. Is wadi
and wadiya's papers ready?
Yes madam the papers are ready.
Give I'll sine it. - But Chirag
was going to sign this papers.
Chirag has gone to the panchgani.
So I'll sigh this papers
Panchagani? But match
is in the Bangalore madam.
Match!
Today Chirag Sir's
tennis caughter final is...
...there and ever
there is live in t. Very
Okay thank you.
Good shot.
Yes.
Yes well done.
Yes my boy.
This isn't the tennis.
This the much biger game
which Siddharth is playing with me.
But I want let you wine Siddharth.
Check mother, your
king is in danger.
By the way you're playing nice.
You put your mother in problem.
Take this.
How was the trip of Panchgani?
Panchgani? Yes good all on track.
Check again.
Okay.
You don't have to go outside
tomorrow for some project.
Not at all, Why?
Surprise.
Hi aunty.
- Hey Kamiya.
My goodness you
become a beautiful girl.
Thank you aunty and
you're looking stunning.
Oh thanks.
Aunty where is Chirag?
I see.
So that's my surprise.
How are you?
- Good.
You're so mean.
Can't you come to
airport to pick me up.
He didn't know that you are coming,
I wanted to give him a surprise.
But don't worry I'll
must come to drop you,
Aunty.
- Don't be rude.
She has just arrived and
you started bothering her,
I'm joking,
She must be tired,
Why don't you show her the room?
Show why not, come.
- By aunty.
So how was the flight? Not bad.
My toys, clothes, books and
everything are on two places...
But why you've my tennis trophies.
Because your mom hates this game.
But why dad?
Because when you
were getting birth...
I was playing a match,
Your mom felt that...
I don't care for
anyone except my career,
So! Why don't you explain the mom,
I tried alot.
But dad where will I
stay in my vaccations,
One month with your mom...
And one month with your dad.
But I want to
stay with both of you.
Madam.
- Thank you.
So what were you saying?
Prateek is also like my son.
After his parent's death we
took his all responsibilites.
I see. Prateek is along with Chirag.
Something is like that,
Absolutely.
We're always
together, and that's our story.
You tell how come you're here.
Dad is opening a
boutique in london.
And after a long
discussion he decided...
...that I'll keep
only Indian dresses.
Because they've great
demand in western market.
So...
And Chirag you'll help me out.
I?
Come of show me the best stores.
Come on chirag.
I've no idea
about all these things.
Chirag come on you've to help her.
I'm in the mall, helping
to do shoping. I'm very well.
Yes this is nice.
Superb! Very good bye it.
Yes...
Chirag see this.
Both are nice bye it.
- Let's go from here.
I don't understand what
you're exactly looking for?
If patern is nice then
thread work isn't nice.
If thread work is nice
then fabric isn't nice.
If both are nice then there
is problem in colour combination.
I don't understand what to do?
Creat something new your
own brand, make your own name.
You're right.
I've not thought this.
- Then think now.
Hello.
Hi
I was going for evening walk.
Walk in late night?
By doing jump I see.
Actually I'm going to party.
Wearing track suit and carrying...
...a racket you're going to party.
Wow.
Theme party, its a theme party.
Someone is bringing bat and someone
is bringing hockey stick...
And few people are
also bringing football.
So, I'm also coming with you,
Should I bring skiping roof?
No girls aren't allow.
Girls aren't allow in party.
Its a gay party.
Aunty.
- Just listen.
Listen...
How could I say you.
Actually! I was going for practise.
And you know
mother she hates tennis.
That is why I'm going like this.
And If you'll tell the
mom then she'll be upset.
That's why.
I won't tell her but
only on one condition.
You've to take me out and show me...
...the night live and that is today.
Today?
- Yes.
Okay.
Wake up now.
Come on. Dear.
I like you among
all these fairies.
Come close to me.
The heart goes astray.
Your charm is enticing.
Come into my arms.
Wake up now.
Come to the party.
Let's party now.
There is beauty
and the night is young.
We are only aware of each other.
The sky is under my feet.
There is aroma all around.
When I saw you, my heart is lost.
Your charm is enticing.
Come into my arms.
Wake up now.
Come to the party.
Uncle, look. It got infested.
Show them.
- Yes
Yes. That was...
What's going on here?
Sir that...
What are you hiding?
It's Chirag's photo...
Sir that Kamiya manhotara...
...I meam madam's
frirnd's daughter from London.
Hello. - You've so much
to make your son happy.
But this time you cross the limit.
- What do you mean?
Don't try to force
the girl you called...
...from London enter my son's life.
I'm not interested to
see replay of my life.
Mr. Siddharth Mehra...
...our views weren't
one and never it will be.
And you listen to me.
I know what's good and bad
for my son better than you.
You listen to me.
Hip, hip, hurray!
Your phone, sir.
Just a minute.
Hello. Hello...
Mehra speaking.
- Deaf...
How will you listen if you're deaf?
Not deaf... it's Siddharth Mehra.
Sidhu! My dear friend.
How are you?
I'm fine. You tell me,
what's the commotion?
Manjit's alliance got fixed.
- What?
The boy is from London.
He has to go back tomorrow so
his family came here with proposal.
Okay.
Congratulations.
Sidhu. Such a quiet response!
Why did you phone?
Never mind. Just like that.
Sidhu, you can't hide
your lie. Tell me.
Dharam, I wanted your
daughter and my son Chirag...
Let it be.
My wishes are with your daughter.
Give my love to Manjit.
Bye now. We'll talk later.
My friend wanted this
but he never mentioned.
Never mind.
Friends hold it.
I said hold it.
I said stop it!!
No one is ready to listen.
What happen Dharmpal.
Sir this party is canceled now.
Have you drink more?
Are you concious?
Yes I'm saying it after
thinking a lot...
this engagement is canceled.
How can you canceled? Have
you called us here to insult?
Do you know there will be fight.
Don't give me threat otherwise.
- Otherwise?
Otherwise what you'll do?
You don't know who are we?
Do you want to see what we can do?
Hey...
Don't think my father Ione.
Don't you listen
what my father said?
Engagement is cancel means cancel.
Manjit you don't know
what will be the result.
Is there was any problem when
father fixed the engagement? - No.
Then what is the problem
when he's canceling it?
What nonsense.
How can you do
this at the movement?
Thanks God
because your time is good.
Otherwise the way
you talk to my father...
...I would talk to you very badly.
You've not done nice.
We'll fix it.
Hey... don't even dream
or you'll be in trouble.
Come son, they both
daughter and father are mad.
We're safe from the mad family.
Father, you don't worry.
I know after thinking a
lot you've taken this decision.
What ever you'll say
that will only happen.
I'm with you.
My brave daughter.
No I'm not dating Kamiya.
And please don't phone
me because of this.
What happen?
- That only Kamiya and I.
This man keep on
printing what ever they like.
Chirag, look such a
nice photo of you and Kamiya.
What Kamiya will
think after looking at this.
I don't look any problem in it.
But...
Look nice?
Nice aunty.
- Hello.
Yes, Venky say.
- Hi... hello.
Chirag, your dady
isn't feeling well.
Not feeling well,
what happen to him?
It's very difficult
to say in phone.
But I know he'll be fine
when you'll come here.
Okay I'm coming there.
Pratik we need to go.
Chirag you...
I know yet two days is left,
I'll manage it to next month.
Pratik.
Oh franki.
- Sir, Venky.
What ever it's, you
don't take care of sir?
What you're doing?
Is daiting going on?
Eat chicken.
I'm full now.
- Eat it.
Dad.
Chirag has come.
Wow... thank God.
What a colour and body you made.
Give me a hug.
What a emotion movement sir.
Why you're looking like this?
I'm your uncle Rampal.
Greeting.
You go and have food
I'm coming by washing hand.
Good man.
- Father.
Who is he? And...
And you said that
you're not feeling well.
Vankey phone me but...
- Sir, we've talked too much...
I'm going to the kitchen.
I wasn't feeling well...
but I eat food cooked by
Manjit and now I'm well.
Manjit? Who Manjit?
Manjit? Just calling her.
Manjit.
She has come. She's wonderful girl.
The time she come
every thing is changed.
Manjit he's my son Chirag.
Hi hello.
And he's his friend...
- Pratik. Sit and have food.
You must be angry?
Father, you're not eating.
Enough daughter.
- Have some chicken.
How much I can eat.
- Take one more.
Chirag eat food made by
Manjit. She cook very well.
Not only in cooking my daughter
is also number one in studies.
She's proud of Punjab.
She's very nice and
tradition girl and even...
...she respect the
traditional value.
How did you like food
made by daughter-in-law?
What happen?
Daughter-in-law?
Feeling very nice over here.
Father. We've lands
in Punjab too but...
...I never saw such
beautiful orchards.
Then also why do you
always look so tense?
No, daughter, I'm just upset...
Why?
You know the reason.
Just win Chirag's heart anyhow.
But uncle, what if
this doesn't happen?
Why not? There is
victory in your name.
Manjit (winner of heart).
It's true.
Be quiet.
What's this trouble, Venky?
Her name is Manjit Aluwaliya.
What ever her name
is but what about him?
Why you don't like it?
She's such a nice girl.
Even aunty has called
a sweet girl from London.
But Sir has already
recognise her has a daughter-in-law.
So what can I do.
- Even you've to.
Why?
Come?
Listen it's like that.
Okay.
Sir, she has come.
I am your Juliet, you're my Romeo.
We've love each other.
O darling! Everyone knows this.
I am neither your
Romeo nor are you my Juliet.
O darling! Everyone knows this.
The family and priest is ready.
Forget this. I won't marry you.
Don't lie to me. You've
given your heart to me.
You have loved me. Accept it.
I am neither your
Romeo nor are you my Juliet.
O darling! Everyone knows this.
Destiny has brought
me between two valleyes.
If you marry me, you'll
enjoy day and night.
I break this ties.
I leave this town too.
I beg you. Don't ruin my life.
I am your Juliet, you're my Romeo.
We've love each other.
O darling! Everyone knows this.
Yes, come in.
Oh...
How do you feeling now?
How am I feeling? Superb!
I've flu, I've headache...
I'm screwed up and you're
asking me how am I feeling.
That's why I've brought this soup...
...I don't want to drink your soup.
At least try it.
My grandma said
that after drinking...
...this soup your flu will be gone.
Keep it over there, I'll drink it.
- No! No!
You must have to drink it hot.
I've made it for you,
Please drink it.
You're back to me.
Hello.
- Who is this.
Yes, I'm Manjit speaking.
Who Manjit? Are you house maid?
I'm not a maid
I'm suppose to be Chirag's wife.
Chirag's wife?
What are you talking about?
Give phone to Chirag,
- He's in washroom.
Tell me what do you want?
What happen?
Some Manjit is on the phone,
she's saying she's Chirag's wife.
What?
- I've no idea.
Hello, who is speaking.
I think I'll have to give
you my complete introduction.
I'm Manjit Aluwaliya from bathinda.
Daughter of Mr Dharampal Aluwaliya.
Would be daughter-in-law
of Mr. Siddharth Mehra.
Have you listen everything.
Who you're talking to? Hello.
So your dad called
you there for this reason.
You'll marry with
that illeterate girl.
Chirag! If it will
happen then I'll kill myself.
But there is nothing like that.
What the...
Mom. Dad.
Why did you call me here?
If you wanted to talk to me
then you could talk to me at home.
No! Because I wanted to
talk both of you together.
And it's not possible at your
banglow nor at your farm house.
You can keep any guest in
your house for the lifetime...
I've no problem with that.
But please don't
attach them with my life.
I don't want to get married now.
I've to make my career first...
...as a tennis player.
I know everything...
You supposed to go for practise...
You went to play the
match, You lied to me.
I was helpless.
I can understand
what problem has occured...
...between you because of tennis
But I love this game.
I want to play tennis.
Fine. On one condition.
Say yes for Kamya.
What?!
- Not at all.
He'll only marry with Manjit.
My son will take this decision.
Don't listen to her.
She'll ruin your life.
Don't spoil your life like this.
I didn't come
here to insult myself.
And even I've not
come to see sunset.
Will you both stop
and listen to me.
To make both of you happy
I can't marry with both of them.
I would've some
girl in my life whom...
Whom I loved.
Do you love someone?
There is some girl in your life.
Who is she?
That...
She's that girl.
I love this girl.
You've created a nice blunder.
Do you think your problem will
be solved if you shit in hotel?
I don't know.
But at least we'll be rid
of Kamya and Manjit's matter.
I can't handle this anymore.
Chirag, suppose if for your
happiness your parents...
...agree to let you
marry the girl you love...
...what will you do?
Where will you find that girl?
Forget address, you don't even
know the name of that girl.
First of all, it won't happen.
Do you think they'll
agree for something?
You can keep anyone as guest
in your house all your life...
...but don't try to
link them to my life.
There can be a girl
in my life whom I love.
Good evening, madam.
Take this. It has all the details.
I think it's a game plan.
She has purposely wooed our sir.
It's no match.
Fine. You may go, Desai.
- Okay, madam.
Yeah that's nice.
I think we'll go for take.
- Yeah.
Anishka. Come a little upward.
Anishka. A little up, you know.
I mean... will you go little up.
What's sort of an attitude is this!
I'll manage.
Anishka! What are you doing?
Director is shouting for long.
Don't you understand?
Come up! I won't go more up.
Then stay in rented
single room house for life.
It's not a face cream ad.
It's a soap ad.
Come up.
- Fine.
You shud show off. That's better.
Sir, okay now?
You're looking good.
See...
What!
Yeah, Anishka. That's nice.
Roll camera.
- Rolling.
Action!
Cut. Cut. Cut it.
Hello. Madam. What is this?
Desai, just sort him out.
- Yes, madam.
What is this?
- She's our Shalini Ma'am.
She wants to talk to her.
We'll reimburse you.
It's an important
that's why she came here,
What important?
Isn't our work important?
So it's you.
Beauty with brains.
Anishka Shrivastav.
What?
You're from Nainital.
Daughter of Head Constable
Ashwin Shrivastav.
You left your college
and came to Mumbai.
And since that day you're
working in small ad films.
Excuse me?
Either it's modeling
or film industry...
...here girl's careers
are very short.
That's why they keep trying
to have relationship...
...with a successful man...
...that's why you've chosen Chirag.
Chirag?
Shalini Mehra's son Chirag Mehra.
He's the only heir of
Multi Millionaire Empire.
You already know that.
What are you saying?
Cut the crap, young lady.
I'm giving you an advice...
Stay away from my son's life.
Or else you and your career...
I'll wipe it off like this.
Okay?
Who was she?
Shalini Mehra!
- Who is Shalini Mehra?
I don't know.
- And why was she scolding you?
And who is this Chirag Mehra?
- How would I know that?
Madam, we're out of gas.
- Get it filled.
But money...
- Does money grow on tree?
My mood is ruined.
I'll phone later. Yes, I'm home.
Madam, some sir came to meet you.
Sir? Who?
I don't know. He said he
has important work with you.
Give me water.
- Okay.
He didn't tell you his name.
- I forgot to ask.
But he's waiting
for you in the lobby.
Excuse me.
Yes.
- You're here to see me?
Please. Sit.
Tell me.
I don't know how to start...
...actually I learnt
about Chirag and you...
...when decision of
his life was made.
Hmm!
Chirag?
Chirag is my son.
Oh... okay. Okay.
So what were you
saying about Chirag?
I've fixed Chirag's marriage
with my friend's daughter.
He won't go against my decision.
So I came to request you...
To get out of his life. Right?
I won't...
I won't get out of Chirag's life.
You can do what you want!
Chirag.
Good Chirag! Very good.
- Thank you, sir.
I'm playing but you're panting.
Play... play more...
Look at the result of your game!
Aunt created a commotion
on Anishka's set.
And media published
the news adding gossips.
You're stuck! Mr. Chirag!
Why are you smiling?
Tara.
No. I don't know
anything and you won't...
...phone me about this. Please.
Great.
You're on laptop and I'm
tired of answering the phone.
It's becoming a big scandal.
This Chirag and Shalini
Mehra... who are they?
This is just the half story.
- Meaning?
I mean his father reached home.
- What?
Mother is threatening
and father is requesting...
...to get out of his son's life.
When I'm not in his
life, how can I get out?
Point.
Hello.
- Hello, Anishka.
Chirag Mehra speaking.
I wanted to meet you.
I see. So now you want to meet me.
- Yes, why?
I've met your parents and I'm
not interesting in meeting you.
But Anishka...
- Listen carefully, Chirag Mehra.
If you try to harass me,
I'll be severe on you.
What do we do now?
I don't understand.
We're homeless because
of Kamya and Manjit.
How can do you intend
to stay in this hotel?
I don't know.
Master...
What's the next move?
It's the same.
I've to meet Anishka.
It's his phone.
- Wait. Listen. Relax.
Listen to me carefully.
Just meet him once. Talk to him.
You should know the real story.
Come on now...
Papa, my birthday cake.
Oh no...
Hi.
Whenever we meet something
goes wrong. Right?
And you're the reason for it.
Can I know why you and
your parents after my life?
I'm sorry, Anishka.
It wasn't deliberate.
But now I feel everything
is happening is fine.
Meaning?
I mean...
...I don't know how to say.
Okay, I'll say it straight.
What will you take to spend 15
- 20 days with me?
Anishka. What happened?
Will you tell me?
What does he think of himself?
He might be rich but...
Anishka. Listen.
What's the problem?
It's a matter of 15-20 days.
He's ready to pay you price.
I think it's a very good deal.
You should make some money.
Page 3 for women.
Cut it. Fantastic. Very good.
Next shot, Anishka.
Make up.
I don't need any white spots.
Sir. Sir.
Sir has phoned to
pack up the shooting.
I'm ready for the shot.
Anishka, shooting is cancelled.
Why is the shooting cancelled?
What's the problem?
Shalini Mehra.
What does she has to do with my shoot?
- Anishka.
Shalini Mehra gives us business...
...of 200 Crore rupees every year.
We campaign for her 12 products.
You got involved in a
controversy with her son.
Sir, media writes anything. They...
Anishka. I'll have to replace
you from all my ad campaign.
You can not do that.
Your agency has a
legal contract with me.
Mr. Batra, you can't do this to me.
I'll drag your agency to court.
I won't spare you and
that Shalini Mehra.
Answer the phone.
No use. Some shoot must
have been cancelled again...
...or some agency must've
phoned to cancel your agreement.
Anishka. All this is happening
because of that Chirag.
You've no choice.
So listen to me and
accept his offer.
Yes. He said he's very rich.
He's ready to pay any price.
So let's fleece him.
Ah...
What happened?
Nothing. I'm tense.
Don't be tense. I'm here
to handle everything.
Really?
She's here.
Hi. Nice to see you again.
Hi. I'm Avnit.
Her business manager.
Hi.
- So you can talk to me.
Okay.
Please.
So what's your proposal?
Actually...
Proposal is that for 2-3 weeks
she has to be with Chirag.
Meaning?
I'll tell you...
For a few days she
has to do a drama...
...to pretend that we're
lovers. That's all.
But why?
There are two problems.
Okay. How many days for the days?
I think...
Be precise.
20 days. From tomorrow.
What will be your fees?
20 Lakh rupees.
- 20 Lakh...
...for 20 days.
Per day.
It's okay.
No problem.
I've to get used to it.
Anyways, I agree.
Often we get oblivious.
The heart shouldn't be lost.
Who knows when desires
will be kindled?
Who knows when
seasons will change?
Hearts knows not
how love happens.
When eyes are locked...
dreams are woven.
When someone accompanies us,
he seems to be a dear one.
When eyes are locked...
dreams are woven.
When someone accompanies us,
he seems to be a dear one.
We've reached your house.
Thank you for the lift.
- You're welcome.
See you tomorrow.
- Okay. Anishka, I forgot...
This is a gift for you.
You got a gift for me.
Band aids.
You keep needing them.
It happens only
when you're with me.
But I'll keep it.
I didn't do anything.
I'm fine.
When we keep talking
of each other...
...the aura is filled with bliss.
When you'll be in love,
you'll be restless.
Who knows when desires
will be kindled?
Who knows when
seasons will change?
Hearts knows not
how love happens.
When eyes are locked...
dreams are woven.
When someone accompanies us,
he seems to be a dear one.
He'll come closer
one day, believe it.
The heart is crazy
and unrestrained.
Trust it.
Who knows when desires
will be kindled?
Who knows when
seasons will change?
Hearts knows not
how love happens.
When eyes are locked...
dreams are woven.
When someone accompanies us,
he seems to be a dear one.
Are you fine, Anishka?
Be careful!
- I'm already careful!
Did I get astray?
I didn't know that...
...I'll enjoy this affair act.
I even forgot that there
is an end of this drama...
But there is a problem.
- What?
I practised with you.
Now where can I
find a boy like you?
Yeah...
- Anishka.
Mom.
The work for which
I was here is over.
Yes, mom. I'm all set to leave.
I'll call you when my return
ticket will be confirmed.
No, mom. I'm absolutely all right.
Just missing you. That's all.
I love you, mom. Okay. Bye.
You've decided to go back.
And you didn't even tell me.
There is no more
reason to stay here.
What are you doing?
I've applied in Multi
National Company for a job.
So I got my appointment letter.
Which address you've told them?
It was my mistake
that I thought that...
...this house will
be your new address.
I really don't want to...
But I'm staying for that friend...
Whose own son left the house.
I can't leave him alone like this...
And I won't left my dad alone...
And won't go anywhere.
Hey... let's celebrate.
Come on.
Oh... relax, Pratik. Take it easy.
No. Today is the celebration day...
Today we've booked
the entire hotel.
Our friend got freedom today,
Kamia and Manjeet's
chapter is closed.
Your all problems are
solved, Congratulations!
Why you're sitting so quite?
Please smile.
Cheers.
Anishka, the credit goes to you.
You've done great acting
of being his girlfriend,
Superb.
Once I felt she's
actually in love with him.
Nobody could think
she was only acting.
Everything looked so
real. Everyone got fooled.
You both looked so much in love.
What a performance!
That's a good performance.
You're great. Superb!
Excuse me.
Why did you come here?
Just like that.
Pratik is a crazy guy.
He says anything.
By the way, only I know the truth.
I know. You've tolerated me a lot.
I'm feeling addicted to you
after living so long with you.
I really enjoyed your company.
Anyways...
Can I call you sometime?
Will you come with me
for coffee or dinner?
Can't we extend this agreement?
Till the end of this life!
The one I found... the one
who dwells in my eyes...
...she has come in my arms.
Slowly and slowly it
happens, this is love.
Maybe we had to meet.
We had to write this
exciting love saga.
Wait and watch what
will happen now...
When you're with me,
we can reach the sky.
Your words are magical.
Slowly and slowly it
happens, this is love.
Songs echo in the air.
The season is romantic
and the world seems new.
This is the effect of love.
When heart is in love,
everything looks beautiful.
In moonlit night...
Slowly and slowly it
happens, this is love.
What are you thinking?
First time my parent's
fight gave me something.
And that's you Anishka.
So that means I should
be thankful to them.
Yeah.
But it's my bad luck...
...I can't share my
happiness with them.
Next week I'm going to
play my final match...
I'm very close to my life goal.
But this time my family won't
be with me to appreciate me.
Will you listen to me, Chirag?
Sidhu.
- Pal.
Ask him what he came to prove?
I didn't come to prove anything.
I just came to apologize
to uncle Dharam and Manjit.
You all are responsibility
for all this.
Anishka.
The girl I didn't even
know is everything for me.
I love Anishka.
I want to marry her.
But I won't do it
without your wish.
I don't want after marriage...
...we should have only
court's marriage certificate.
I want blessings of
my dad and mom too.
I'm sure you won't refuse.
I want to share my
happiness with both of you.
With my mom and dad.
For me... for your son...
...will you make mom agree.
Please.
Friend, where are you going?
In life your son has asked for
something for the first time.
Won't you listen to him?
You don't have to
go to any stranger.
She's your wife.
Please go, friend.
It's possible, this is the
way for estranged to unite.
Friend, don't worry about us.
We don't choose
destiny and matches.
It's made in heaven.
Correct, father.
Anyway, they look so nice.
Made for each other.
Come.
Come, son.
Don't look like this.
Won't you bless them?
Enough.
Come, son.
Thank you, Dharampal.
Come in.
- Madam, it's sir.
Who?
Your sir...
Make him sit. I'm coming.
Okay.
Please. Sit down.
Shalini. Didn't I
disturb you at this hour?
The reason for your arrival
can disturb, not you.
Shalini, we've passed our lives,
whether it was good or bad.
But now it's question of our son.
Chirag came to me...
...with Anishka.
He loves Anishka and wants
to spend his life with her.
She's a nice girl.
I'm glad to hear that.
So go ahead.
You don't mind?
Sidharth, will you use
my son to win against me?
I never thought that.
What?
Are you the same who brought his...
...friend's daughter seeing Kamya.
And when Chirag rejected her too...
...now you've accepted
that soap called...
...model your
daughter- in- law.
Great.
Actually you're favoring my
son to make him go against me.
You're getting me wrong.
Absolutely not. I'm not wrong.
I know my son, his
nature better than you.
And that girl doesn't
deserve my son.
But Chirag...
- I've given my decision.
Would you please excuse me now.
Chirag.
I tried my best.
But your mother...
didn't agree for it.
Don't worry, son. I'm with you.
Chirag.
Chirag, everyone
is looking for you.
Why won't you answer my phone?
Chirag. Phone me urgent.
Call me back.
Chirag, where are you?
You won't answer any
phone or reply my message.
Everyone is worried. Where are you?
Please phone me.
I'm waiting for your call.
Sidharth, where is Chirag?
He won't come for practice.
Only 2 days are
left for Final match.
All the formalities are left.
Doesn't he want to play the match?
Do you hear me?
I don't know anything.
What are you saying?
The truth. Chirag
isn't to be found.
He won't answer mine,
Anishka or uncle's phone.
He didn't go for
practice for a week.
Aunt, he did everything
to reach this Final.
And today when it's the time...
Aunt, please. Do something.
Chirag.
Yes. Why did you call me?
Chirag, you know everyone
is worried for you.
Why are you doing this?
I don't know.
You've the right to take
the decision of your life.
If your happiness
lies with Anishka...
...so be it.
I don't mind, Chirag.
But how can you take the credit
by giving what's not yours?
Chirag.
Of course. I'm tired.
I'm tired of thinking
who is right or...
...who is wrong between my parents.
Who loves me more
and who loves me less.
Chirag.
What are you saying?
Yes, mom. This is the truth.
But you never realized it.
You're happy thinking you've
given everything to your son.
Dad was always worried that
your luxuries will ruin me.
I've lived two different
lives because of you.
But it's enough.
Let's end it.
I want nothing.
Neither you nor dad nor tennis.
Just think that dad
lost in the arena...
...and your son lost before.
I won't tell you to sit, Shalini.
Because I'm sure that
our meeting won't be long.
Don't waste time.
Sidharth, what's time...
...we've ruined our lives.
But today our son is on
the verge of destruction.
Our son... you're saying this.
You've fought a battle all
your life to make him yours.
What is lacking that only a
father can provide not a mother?
Talkin Cinema with Karan Adarsh.
People of India and UK...
Chirag.
If you'll play and lose
so you'll be a winner,
But if you'll give up and lose...
Then you'll never
forgive your self.
Do you know Anishka?
Why did I play Tennis?
Because my dad give up.
And I've decided that...
I'll make him win from my victory.
And I'll show my
victory trophy to my mom.
Now for who I'll play.
Chirag! For those people with
whom you've no relationship.
But they still came
to watch your game...
They feel happy,
they applause for you...
In those viewers where
your parents aren't there...
But there are many
parents over there...
...who are watching you playing...
And told their kids...
That play like Chirag.
Good evening to you,
ladies and gentlemen.
Welcome to the Pune Tennis stadium.
You're about to witness
the final of the...
Yes, Vikram. Audience are
impatient for this match.
It's between defending
champion Mahesh...
...and upcoming star Chirag Mehra.
Vikram, this match has
been in controversy...
...because of Chirag Mehra.
Before the match there were
questions is he'll play or not.
Ladies and gentlemen
the wait is finally over...
and the players make their way
from the dressing room to the court.
And listen to the crowd as
they cheer for both the players.
We see the first sign of
competition as Mahesh Singh...
...and Chirag Mehra give
each other a cold flare.
Players come on the
court for the toss.
Just look at Mahesh not taking
the eyes of the opponent.
Telling Chirag Mehra the
challenger to the crown that...
...you've to bring out your
best game or you're done.
Chirag wins the toss
and choses to serve.
What should Chirag
do to win the match?
I think Chirag will have
to be more aggressive...
...take his chances
and hope for the best.
Most important, he should be
confident and mentally strong.
And Chirag ready to serve.
Mahesh smashes the ball
into Chirag's body...
...and Chirag is unable
to handle the ball.
First blood! Champion Mahesh
Singh gets love 15.Iove
What a good passing shot!
Mahesh looking come to the net.
And finish the point... Chirag...
The Chirag comes out with
answer with his own.
The first game goes
to Chirag Mehra.
Again Chirag changes
the direction of...
...the ball and Mahesh
can't return it.
Chirag Mehra is playing with
innovative and aggressiveness...
...and leading the first set by 52.
Chirag has started
strongly and he has...
...to maintain his momentum through.
A great passing shot by
Chirag of his back hand.
Chirag Mehra. 60. 15.
That's a commendable job.
And I think if he
continues in this spirit...
...there is nothing stopping
him from winning this match.
We got a nice set to watch...
Chirag had an answer
of every short...
And Chirag won the
first set of the match.
And here it begins the second set...
Mahesh Singh serves.
What a serve!
Mahesh Singh has started
the set aggressively.
Chirag. Focus.
Chirag has to do something
or else he'll lose this set.
He's not able to
concentrate the way he...
...was concentrating
in the first set.
Why we felt that something
is bothering Chirag...
It seems he's losing his focus.
I think he needs to get
his focus back again.
And he's already trailing 1-4
in the second set.
One more...
What are we seeing here?
I think this is
absolutely uncalled...
...for in the good game of tennis.
It reminds me of John McNore when...
...he used to argue with the umpire.
It's not like him.
Chirag is very calm by nature.
It's not good to argue with umpire.
I think he should just
focus of his game...
...take control of himself
and just move on with it.
That's double fault. The
second set goes to Mahesh Singh.
And we're not level
with one set a piece.
If Chirag plays with the
form of his first set...
...things can turn.
Maybe the change of racket
will bring him some luck.
Chirag is lagging in
the third set as well.
Never double fault.
Chirag needs to improve on his serve
which has gone from bad to worse.
Chirag!
You can do it, son.
Oh God! Chirag can't handle
Mahesh's forehand pace.
Third set is 4-2 to Mahesh Singh.
And Chirag is making
come back in the match.
Everybody is looking for a
fight and a competitive match.
Quiet please.
That was a bad ball.
I think Chirag was wrong footed
and he has twisted his ankle.
We hope that won't be very serious.
Physio is there at such an
interesting point in the game...
...you know I mean...
- The score is levelled at 6 all.
Injury is on the
deciding tie break.
Chirag is up. He'll
begin the tie break.
7 points will win. The tie
break will decide the match.
Quiet please.
1 to Mahesh Singh.
One more body shot. Mahesh
started aggressively in tie break.
Exciting match. Chirag is
making a comeback in this game.
That's another second hand by
Chirag. Match point to Chirag.
What an amazing turn
around to the game!
It's a nail biting finish.
Now we've reached to
that moment where...
...we'll get our next champion.
Ladies and gentlemen,
the match point.
I understand the
differences between...
...you and dad because of tennis.
But I love this game.
I want to play tennis.
I'll make them win with my win.
I'll show the trophy to mom.
We've a new champion
ladies and gentlemen.
Our new all India tennis
champion. Chirag Mehra.
Well done, son.
Mom...
I love you, son.
Congratulations.
Anishka!
Congratulation!
Chirag won the match.
I've won both the games.
I have found the one
who dwells in my eyes.
...she has come in my arms.
Slowly and slowly it
happens, this is love.
Maybe we had to meet.
We had to write this
exciting love saga.
Wait and watch what
will happen now...
When you're with me,
we can reach the sky.
Your words are magical.
Slowly and slowly it
happens, this is love.
Songs echo in the air.
The season is romantic
and the world seems new.
This is the effect of love.
When heart is in love,
everything looks beautiful.
In moonlit night...
Slowly and slowly it
happens, this is love.