I can't imagine the
face of the idiot...
who once said...
OPPOSITES ATTRACT!!
I guess some of you out
there did fall for that logic
But we didn't...
and this is our story.
"Each moment is young and
beautiful."
"There is no sorrow when I am
there."
"Life is filled with joy."
"This is how I live."
"Each morning brings light."
"Each evening brings beauty."
"Life is awakened."
"This is the song that life
sings."
"Everyday life is awakened."
"There are showers of colors.
There are graces."
"There are showers
of colors every day."
"My heart feels like
smiling all the time."
"And humming a tune slowly."
"Whomever I met I
considered him my friend."
"Life is a celebration."
"Whatever I heard I
considered it good news."
"I recognized joy every day."
"Each morning brings light."
"Each evening brings beauty."
"This is my story. This is my
life."
"This is my story every day."
"There are showers of colors.
There are graces."
"There are showers
of colors every day."
Boss has given it.
He wants light effect.
Shit! Govind, how could I
forget!
Forget what?
Today is Valentine's Day.
Relax, bro... she
doesn't know that you forgot.
You have enough time.
Plan something special for her.
Good idea!
What should I do?
Jai you know very well that
I have been divorced twice
I've been on three dates
in the past three months!
They've all been pretty boring.
Do I look like the guy with
a special plan up his sleeve?
Govind, you know how she is!
Come on, you're my friend!
You have to help me think
of something... anything.
No, no
Great. Some help.
"Like fragrance in flowers.
And colors in buds."
"I have the zest to live."
"There is resonance of hopes."
"There is a zest in my
heart all the time."
"The world of dreams is
familiar."
"I weave a new dream every day."
"Each morning brings light."
"Each evening brings beauty."
"This is the spectacle."
"Each moment is filled with
hope."
"This is the spectacle every
day."
"There are showers of colors."
"There are graces."
"There are showers
of colors every day."
Hi. Happy Valentine's Day.
Same to you.
This is for you.
Thank you.
This is for me?
- Yes!
Happy Valentine..
Hello.
- How are you, Jai?
Hi mom!
Well... do you like it?
It's a guitar.
Yes!
Naina you know I cant even
sing happy birthday in tune
I don't know how to
play the guitar, love.
I have ingestion today.
Mom, why aren't you having
those organic vegetables?
It's not available.
- At least wash it in potassium.
Nowadays it is very chlorine.
- Yes.
Listen, will you talk to your
aunt?
- Surely.
I have to take this.
As if you have the
time to teach me to play.
Hello. Yes..
Oh no, we're having dinner at
home.
Listen, talk to your aunty.
- Okay.
Sorry!
It's okay. Greetings aunty-ji.
How are you?
Very well, how are you?
What's the special gift?
Well... he has
prepared a fabulous dinner.
I almost forgot.
Your gift.
Oh my God! They are beautiful.
Next time you can expect a
necklace.
as soon as this deal comes
through.
But these must be very
expensive.
So? You're worth it.
Thank you.
- You're welcome.
You've been saying it for
months.
Okay, I will talk to
you about this next time.
Put aunty on line, mom.
Hello aunty-ji, how are you?
You find it amusing, huh?
You know it's quite logical.
I don't think your mom is wrong.
Tell me, why aren't
you getting married?
You want the truth...
I haven't heard that
loud bell in my heart
Bell? What's a bell
got to do with marriage?
I know Radhika is great...
she is beautiful, smart,
intelligent.
And I guess successful too.
Actually, she is a lot
more successful than you.
Anyway.
- I don't know, man!
It takes a few years of
marriage
for couples to get to where we are.
You know what I mean.
Well... I mean...
for example, you and Nandini.
Remember that life?
What's the word for it...
it's...
boring?
- Boring!
Bland, regular,
like a routine, you know!
I understand.
But why do you understand?
It's because you did
things differently.
You priorities were different.
God forbid, Govind if...
I get... I get it, Jai.
It was my marriage,
I was there, I get it.
Sorry!
- That's fine.
That's not what I meant.
But just imagine. And trust me.
Its good she left you
I mean you left her
It's fine, dude.
It didn't work.
How does it matter who left
whom?
Well sometimes even I forget.
I miss the energy, the good
times...
The college days, the
single and ready to mingle days.
I wonder if I will
ever feel that way again.
The excitement, the magic
that fills up your heart.
Bell! Ding dong Bell bro!
Relax bro... You'll hear it
But when?
But Jai, it's your fault.
Why don't you talk to Radhika?
Talk to Radhika?
There is no talking to radhika.
There is only listening to
Radhika
And a discussion about this?
She could kill me.
She is quite psycho.
- Yeah, a bit.
What? Power failure in Mumbai?
Oh no! The rest of my
ice-cream will melt!
If the ice-cream melts
you will die, right?
Trust me, Naina. Ice cream is
the best cure for a break-up.
The best cure for a
break-up is also a patch up,
Ritu.
Why don't you speak with Kunal?
He has apologised a million
times.
Saying sorry comes easy but
being faithful is the difficult
part.
But what did he do?
One silly sms...
He did nothing
because I had read his sms.
I can't imagine what he
would've done otherwise.
And you tell me...
How long does it take these
days for an SMS to become an
MMS ?
The point is there is no mms.
You are overacting... a little
bit.
Don't you worry, Jai.
I tell you honestly, our
generation's
number 1 problem is this.
Radhika?
Relationships, man. - Yes.
- Relationships. - Right.
Everyone's in a mess. You know
that.
Now you want to smoke this?
No!
Throw it away. You'll die
if you continue smoking.
Come on. Let's go now.
Come on, our manager
must be waiting for us.
To hell with him! Project
report!
You know... can't live with
them...
Hello. - Hi. - Can't live
without them. - Correct. -
Let's go!
You know, yesterday she was
checking my nails. - Please.
You miss him, don't you?
A lot.
Well... it is said that
time heals everything.
Perhaps one day you will
forgive him.
Until then you have
ice cream. Indulge in it!
I hope I don't run out of
flavours!
Naughty! Stupid!
Are you taking guitar lessons?
It was a gift meant for Dhruv..
.. but I guess now
I'll have to take lessons.
Men are the same everywhere.
Yet we dream of
spending our lives with them.
That reminds me
Gayatri is getting married.
Really? Wow! What is
the name of the guy?
Arjun, really nice guy.
She is very happy.
Are you going for it?
- Of course!
You should come along.
Apparently you meet some
good guys at weddings.
Chandigarh. For marriage?
Come on, Jai.
I thought if you don't come
along,
it won't be half as fun.
Actually it won't be any fun.
Please Jai! Can you see how
much work I have on my head?
Tomorrow morning is the
seminar,
it's going to be very hard.
You mean you really can't...
you swear you can't?
Are you really going
to miss me that much?
I swear.
Fine, I'll figure something.
It won't be easy but
I'll try to make it.
Radhika, I think I'm putting
you under a lot of pressure.
You are so honest and hard
working and I'm plain selfish.
It's ridiculous.
No, Jai, it's fine. I'll sort
it out.
No, it's okay. I'll go alone.
Jai, listen to me...
No, Radhika, I
shouldn't bear on your work.
Please, I swear.
Really?
Yeah.
That's so sweet of you.
So, what is it?
Govind, Radhika is...
Damn! Here we go again.
Radhika-isn't-coming...
What are you talking...
you are joking?
You know I get stressed very
easily.
Keep it down or she'll hear us.
Touchwood! This is great news,
pal.
I was craving a vacation.
I need a break, it's too much.
We're taking a vacation,
brother!
What are you doing?
- I don't know. - Let's go!
I still need to pack the
magazines!
Good morning, ma'am. Your
flight
to Delhi is on time. - Thank you.
You expect me to carry
this bag? It's so heavy!
Naina?
Yeah!
How did you know?
Magic.
Just kidding!
Arjun said you'll be
travelling with us.
So he asked me to look out for
you.
And I've been asking every
single girl the same thing!
Naina?
The bus isn't here yet?
The bus is here and so are the
guests.
We were waiting for you.
It's over there.
Okay. Phone!
Yeah!
I am sorry, Dhruv.
You have to make it.
You can't miss the "sangeet"
ceremony.
Okay, bye!
Sorry, they're heavy.
No, no, not at all. It's fine.
Come on.
"We don't start a fight."
"Every day and night
we try to fight."
Jai, would you please
look over my bag for me?
I will just come.
- Yes, sure.
Now we also know
each other very well.
I mean, your bags are
quite heavy... quite some time.
We spent quite some time
together.
Do you always crack such jokes?
Yes. Why? Would you
prefer some other type?
You could try.
Really? Any particular type?
For example, jokes
people can actually laugh at.
Dude! Beautiful girl-one,
Jai-zero!
By the way did you hear a bell?
Just sit down! Nobody
asked for your expert advice.
But your jokes sure
were a class apart!
"Look, the paths are
calling out to us."
"We are walking without
thinking."
"I am thinking this is
where I want to be."
"Beloved, meet me someday."
I can't wait to get
to Chandigarh, man.
Sir, the engine needs to cool
down.
We'll go and some water. Let's
go.
Why is he yelling?
Forget it. Here, everybody
yells.
What's wrong?
Nothing, the engine needs to
cool
down. Should take a few minutes.
Okay, I'll be right back.
Hello... where do
you think you're going?
The restroom in the bus is a
mess
So don't go alone.
We'll come along. Right?
No, it's okay. I am fine,
really!
Naina, it's a jungle.
It's not safe out here.
What say, Govind?
I mean... it's safe but...
we should go.
We should go!
Then you hold onto this.
Thanks!
What?
- Look at you...
matching!
- So?
It's amazing.
She made you a
porter as soon as you met.
And now both of us are
standing here as security
guards.
By the time we get to
Chandigarh...
Then what?
Come on...
You know Govind, I
just realised something.
You have become very negative.
Be positive, brother!
We are on a vacation,
remember the trip has just
begun.
There's lots of good
stuff in store for us.
Really? Good stuff... like what?
Guys, can please sing a song?
This is really weird!
Sing!
"Life is a beautiful journey."
"Nobody knows what will
happen in the future." - Louder!
"Understand what the gestures
say."
"Listen. Everybody is
calling to us from the heart."
"I am thinking this is
where I want to be."
"Beloved, meet me someday."
Start.
Come on.
Gayatri.
Great, you can take
them to the hotel.
If you need something call me,
okay?
Don't worry. I am there.
Arjun, I still can't believe
that..
..you and Gayatri
are getting married.
It's amazing! Time flies, man!
You know actually she's quite
hot.
Govind, have some respect.
What's disrespectful about that?
She is hot, so she is!
Shut up man, don't
talk nonsense. Keep quiet.
What's wrong with you?
If a girl is gorgeous you
can use other adjectives too...
like hot, sexy, cute... you
know.
Just shut up!
Are you mad? Have you lost it?
I'd rather not talk to you.
Let me ask Arjun. You
don't have a problem..
..if I refer to her as
hot and sexy, do you?
I mean, in a nice way.
But actually,
Govind, there is a problem.
Yeah! She is quite reserved.
You don't know her very well.
You know... besides Gayatri
is like your sister-in-law.
- Correct! - Gayatri?
Where did she come from? I
wasn't talking about her.
I was talking about her friend
..
..and Mr. Ding Dong
Bell here sang for her.
Drat! You mean Naina?
-Naina!
- She is hot.
That's what I said.
- Brother, she is hot!
- I told you so! - She is hot!
Guys... what do you
think of Gayatri? I mean...
Jai, tell him.
She's good, very sweet.
Aunty and uncle will
love her. Right, Govind?
Of course! Can I get some
water...
my throat's parched.
I know that. But do
you think she is hot?
I mean 'hot'?
Answer him, Jai.
She is sweet, she is nice.
What say, Govind?
Oh no, nice won't do.
What's his question?
Arjun asked if she is hot.
Do you think Gayatri is hot?
- Hot!
God Gayatri! We've been
discussing
your marriage for ages now.
We haven't, you have been.
You've been discussing my
marriage
since you were in the 6th grade.
So cute!
But just imagine.
Now each day will begin
and end with Arjun for you.
It's perfect.
I know!
So we've decided that
Naina is hot, right?
And Gayatri isn't
that what you're saying?
- Answer him! - Yeah!
He is speechless.
- Speechless.
Alok, how're you doing?
You look very smart!
Hello.
- Hello.
Where's Biji?
Sexy.
Bloody Mary.
Arjun, I want to see Biji.
Hurry up.
- Quick. - Thank you.
Nice, huh?
The combo is unbelievable.
Greetings Biji, guess who is
here.
How are you, Biji?
- Greetings to you. - Bless you!
I hope you are ready with a
sizzling
performance for the "sangeet".
Like the 'Infamous Munni'!
Idiot! This Munni isn't
infamous,
she is sick.
You are shameless. On the phone
you keep saying you'll visit me.
I got caught up with work, Biji.
Is it work or a beautiful girl?
Greetings Biji!
I can't help it. You helped
your grandson Arjun find a girl.
You don't care about me.
Well that's because I am sure
that
you will find a girl for yourself.
So, how's the lady of the house?
Have you'll decided on
something?
Well the thing is... you see...
I, what do you say?
- Biji, he hasn't heard the
bell yet!
That's good. There's still some
hope.
You are so naughty! Can't
wait for your performance.
I'd love to dance but the
doctor's advice is, 'Just
Chill'.
To hell with the doctor!
I would only if he
weren't Arjun's dad.
Arjun, my sweetie pie!
You look happy, Biji,
finally you are smiling.
This is Naina, Gayatri's best
friend.
She is gorgeous, just like
Gayatri.
Are you married?
No.
What's wrong with
the boys these days!
Such a beautiful girl
and she isn't married yet.
Biji, Naina has a boyfriend.
His name is Dhruv.
Is he here with you?
No, he is caught up with work.
What's the use of such a
boyfriend?
That's just like Jai.
I suggest you keep your eyes
open..
..you will find
someone as sweet as Naina.
Okay then! I think
you should rest now.
Let's freshen up, Arjun?
Let me show you to your room.
Bye, Biji.
- Yes, son.
Love you, sexy.
- Go and rest.
Fritters are ready.
Thanks.
- There is some..
You haven't changed a bit!
That's true.
Thanks pal for waking me up!
It gives me joy to wake you up,
to bring you tea in bed...
Obviously. - And probably
even massage your feet.
Correct!
- No problem, come on.
I'm starving.
Too late! Buffet is over,
but there's lots of beer.
Of course, I can see that
but it's also good to share.
What have you all decided
for the pre wedding party?
It's simple, dude
Vodka, Bacardi, some wine,
if you insist. That's all, bro.
Drinks apart other things are
necessary for an entertainment
value.
But thanks.
- Very well!
From the outside you are Dr.
Jekyll but you really are Mr.
Hyde!
What?
- What a pleasant surprise!
So, what do you have
in mind, like Russians?
Russians at home? Jai,
do something, please!
Ignore him! So what were you
saying?
Well, we were thinking that ..
..the 'boys versus
girls' competition is passé.
I agree! But the boys'
side is always the best.
- Right, Arjun? - Absolutely!
What rubbish! You don't
stand a chance against us!
I see.
- What say, Naina?
Absolutely! You can
try us out anytime.
Probably another day.
And it's our favourite song.
No, no, Gayatri!
How filmy can you be! Come on!
I think it's rather sweet.
Exactly. - It's their
wedding and their performance.
I think we should do it. Let's
do it.
I think you should
call for some more vodka.
This is turning into
a "Hum Aapke Hain Kaun" sequel.
That's jasmine! Do you smell
jasmine?
It must be aunt Sheila.
Hi aunt Sheila.
Hello...
Welcome!
- How are you? - Great!
Nice to see you. Hello...
How nice of you to show up.
You're a day late!
About time you got married.
She's been waiting for years.
Anyway, you know how I
love weddings. I just love it.
The questions fielded by
the aunts and uncles...
it takes a while to prepare
yourself.
Everyone present here knows you
don't want to marry. So relax.
Where's uncle?
He needs even more time to
prepare himself, you know!
Now come on, I have to
show you something. - What?
- Let's go. - Okay.
Hello Soniaji, this is Sheila.
Hi.
- Hi. Very close to the family.
She's like a younger sister to
me.
Nice to meet you.
You teach Urdu, don't you?
- Yes. Yes.
I have heard a lot about you.
- Shall we go?
I'm really sorry.
I suppose you are
inconvenienced by my arrival.
Sorry? Of course.
Everyone's excited since
they are meeting after ages.
Govind.
- Sheila.
Aren't you performing with
the others at the "sangeet"?
Dancing is fun.
Well... nobody asked.
Really? That's shocking!
Alright, this stuff is very
simple.
Everyone will take a
chit from this bowl.
Boys will take yellow and girls
red.
And what about green?
There is no green here.
- Okay.
People with the same number..
.. will be partners at
the "sangeet" ceremony.
Boys... girls... are you ready?
Yes, of course!
- Cool.
Good luck. Now pick up the chit.
Ladies first.
Yeah, what is this?
Oh, no.
- Oh, no.
These chits are scary.
I hoping for the right partner.
- I agree.
Boys.
- Come on. - What a masculine
colour!
Great, Pinku has taken two!
Two.
Now open your chits and
say the number out loud.
Nikki, we will start with you.
It's two...
Two.
- Two. - Tow. I've got two!
I'm a... four.
-Oh... I'm a...
- I'm four!
And that means you are three.
Correct! I am three.
Don't know what I was thinking.
I'm three.
Just imagine... partners!
Yeah.
- Naina, that means you are
three.
Yes.
- You are three. - Yes. - Okay.
How surprising... just imagine.
Yes, partners. Let's
begin the rehearsal.
No, that's for tomorrow.
It's all planned.
It will be fun.
- Okay. And now?
Now all of you can quickly
freshen up for dinner. Don't be
late!
Yes.
- Alright. - Yes. - Bye, aunt.
Dad, come on! Let's go.
"Your kohl eyes look beautiful."
"An innocent boy got enticed."
"When you turned and looked
behind."
"I fell in love with you."
Naina... Naina, wait up!
- Hey partner! - Hi Jai.
You are looking very nice.
I know!
Where's Govind?
Getting dressed I guess.
Nice guy.
Since when do you know Gayatri.
We went to boarding school
together.
Best friends then.
And now?
We're still very
close but as you know...
- she's a Delhi girl. - And
soon to be a Chandigarh girl.
Right. And I live in Bombay.
So are you a Maharashtrian?
My dad was.
Sorry.
No, not about being
Maharashtrian,
of course. The "was" part.
It's okay.
Actually, you and me
have that in common.
Really? Your father
is also Maharashtrian?
No, dad was a Punjabi.
Was being the common part
I am sorry.
It's okay.
Hey... Jai wait!
- Hi... - There you are!
Are we practicing today?
The engagement isn't today?
- Let's go. - Yes, let's!
There are so many functions,
it's difficult to keep track.
Oh wow!
- Wow!
Wow! This is so beautiful.
I'm sure Arjun has nothing to
do
with this. He is colour blind.
We're going to have a great
time.
- Naina. Naina, come here.
Look. Okay, I'll see you later.
Bye.
- Hi... - Hello..
This one?
Tonight is going to be a good
night.
It's going to be a great night.
Which one do you think?
- I think this one.
Hi.
- Hold on.
Govind, she said hi.
Show me.
- See this.
Usually people wave back.
I should say hi...
Yes, I should reply.
Yes. I will have to see
when I find out. - Yes.
You like to..
Hello Sheila.
Hi.
How are you?
- I'm fine.
- Good.
You're wearing a jasmine
perfume?
- Yes...
It's really nice.
- Thank you.
Okay.
- Okay...
Cool? Happy?
- I'm sure auntie Sheila is.
It's Sheila!
Auntie Sheila.
Are you and Arjun brothers?
- No.
Are you cousins?
Are you a distant relative?
- Of course not!
So then She is Arjun's aunt.
Why
should we call her auntie Sheila?
Have some respect
for her feelings, dude.
Will you like it if
everyone called you uncle?
Well no... not if I'm 40.
- She is 38. Thirty eight!
- What 38?
Sheila is 38.
Wow! Big difference.
It is a big difference, Jai.
A lot can happen in two years.
Two years ago, I was married...
while you were fluttering
around like a butterfly.
Two years later, I'm single...
Bro, according to your mom,
you should be married!
Radhika misses you. Think about
it.
Why are you getting personal?
- Thanks, uncle!
Asshole.
Ladies and gentlemen, may I
have you attention please.
Woo-hoo!
Thank you, thank you...
Thanks dad... sorry, dads!
No, go ahead Arjun,
this is your day.
I'd like to say something...
to Gayatri.
It was during my 7th grade
vacation..
..that I went to my
grandmother's place and...
..that's when I saw
Gayatri for the very first time.
She was in the home
opposite ours and...
..along with her friends she
was trying to steal ice cream.
I don't think she was
successful
and I know this sounds very filmy...
..but that day in her little
pink frock, she stole my heart.
Wow!
And, today after 14 years of
innumerable breakups and
patch-ups...
I'm going to return the favour!
I am finally stealing Gayatri
away from all of you. Forever.
Sorry everyone!
Congratulations!
"Lord is the savior."
"This ambiance of joy."
"Clarion is resonating in my
heart."
"This ambiance of joy."
"Clarion is resonating in my
heart."
"This beautiful beloved."
"It's the story of love."
"Lord is the savior."
"Celebrate the feeling."
"For a day and evening."
"Beautiful hearts are beating.
Love is in the air."
"Celebrate the feeling."
"For a day and evening."
"Beautiful hearts are beating.
Love is in the air."
"Celebrate the feeling."
"For a day and evening."
"Beautiful hearts are beating.
Love is in the air."
"Somebody ask what the
eyes spoke to each other."
"And what did they hear?"
"Say quietly."
"Both have chosen their
life partner."
"This velvety moment."
"This soft fervor."
"These clouds of dream.
Lord is the savior."
"This beautiful beloved."
"It's the story of love."
"Lord is the savior.
Lord is the savior."
"Lord is the savior."
"Lord is the savior.
Lord is the savior."
"Lord is the savior."
Thank you. Thank you.
Teach. Please.
One, two, three, four, five,
six...
Three, four, five, six.
Seven, eight.
Well done!
- And jump.
This is not a step. I can't do
this.
Govind, why aren't you
rehearsing?
You are dancing, who will watch
us?
Are you sure about this?
- Right!
Think about it.
I already did!
I think I hear the bell.
Bell?
Jai has this strange
theory but it's amazing.
What's the worst that could
happen?
Probably a slap or two!
Right! Life keeps slapping us...
We were slapped almost daily
when in college. - You mean you!
You know this is very special,
bro!
I can tell... she is special.
Do you know she is a
professor in a college.
No! I think this is too sweet.
Naina, you are very sweet.
- You're so sweet.
You are sweeter! - Shut up. -
Gayatri, here are some more
outfits.
You better decide what you
want to wear. It's too much now.
Mom, I can't decide, I
want you to do it, please.
I can't do it.
- This is beautiful.
Arjun, don't keep your
feet on the coffee-table.
Dad is calling you, come on!
Come on.
- Arjun!
Where does Sheila teach?
At "Jamia Milia". But why?
What does she teach?
- Urdu.
Urdu.
- Sheila teaches Urdu.
Good. But in which language?
English!
Great... now you should learn
Urdu.
Just a second...
Govind and Urdu, why?
Correct!
- To hell with correct!
It's my wedding and you
want to hog the limelight!
"We celebrate
an auspicious occasion."
"Drums and clarions are
playing."
"I have found my beloved."
"Lord, protect me."
Congratulations.
"My heart wants to dance.
My heart wants to dance."
"I just want your company. O
damsel,
I just want your company."
"Come with me."
"And dance."
"My heart wants to dance.
My heart wants to dance."
"When I see you."
"I don't know why my
heart beats fast, beloved."
"I am fragrant,
unnerved, afraid, beloved."
"What have you done?"
"This beauty and you.
This fragrance today."
"This beauty and magic.
Lord is the savior."
"This beautiful beloved."
"It's the story of love."
"Lord is the savior.
Lord is the savior."
"Lord is the savior."
"Savior."
- "Lord is the savior."
"Lord is the savior."
This stinks... it's pretty
but...see?
No, no I trust you.
- Me too, I think.
You can smell.
- No, he can smell. Smell...
Smell...
- Okay, just smell it.
It's horrible.
It's gross.
- Sort of.. - One second.
Hello.
- Hi, Naina.
One second. Hi Dhruv.
What?
- Nothing.
We're having so much fun.
That's great love.
When is the "sangeet"?
Tomorrow night. And you have
no idea what we have planned.
I wish you were here.
- Well... you know...
I know you can't
make it because of work.
I understand, Dhruv.
Wow! Will you let me talk?
I'm in Delhi for a conference
and I'll be in Chandigarh
tomorrow.
I'll be there by noon,
understand?
Text me the address
and I'll see you soon.
Okay, smartie pants... good
night!
That was Dhruv.
He is coming tomorrow in time
for the performance. I'm
shocked.
But in a good way.
Yeah, of course, I mean... I
thought
he would make it to the wedding.
I'm just surprised.
That's great, right? Now he can
watch your world class
performance!
Oh no, I'm suddenly very
nervous.
I won't be able to sleep
tonight.
Come on, Jai, let's practice.
- Relax!
You will be able to sleep
and perform too. Just chill.
Trust me! Right?
- Trust him!
Why not?
- Trust him, I mean.
- Breathe... - Okay, okay!
'You will be able to sleep...
trust me!'
Idiot.
Now where's Gayatri...
It's me, Jai.
Jai, what are you...
What are you doing here?
I'm taking a walk, why?
But why are you all
covered up like a thief?
Because it's cold. Do you mind?
What are you doing here?
I was thirsty.
You had water? No go back to
sleep.
Go! Get lost!
- No..
I'm not thirsty anymore.
- Very good.
Very good, now go back to
sleep! Go!
But Jai?
Can't you talk
without screaming? Woman!
If you don't tell me what
you are doing over here...
I will scream like a mad
woman and bring down the house!
You better tell her!
Arjun... is that you?
Yes, it's me!
- Where is Gayatri?
Where are we going? What's this
for?
Naina, if you ask another
question,
you will be strapped to this.
You will be asleep and
we'll get some peace.
Get it?
but...
Sorry!
You're idiots! I
could hear you in here.
Why don't you take
morning tea to Alok too!
Sorry, Biji. Let's go?
No, I like being held
under house arrest. Let's go.
Gayatri, have you taken the
thermos?
Yes, Biji. Let's go?
Of course!
But where to go?
"I fell in love."
Use these yellow and white
flowers..
..to decorate the wall.
- Good morning, uncle.
Naina, where are you off to?
- I'm going to pick up Dhruv.
Good morning.
- Hi.
So, all set?
- Yup!
See you. Bye!
- Bye!
Where were you? Forget her.
We need to set the flowers.
Alok! Come on,
not the flowers for me!
Come on! The women are
finalising the jewellery and
sarees.
We are left with the flowers.
Come on. Quick.
Make it quick or Alok will kill
me!
Yes. We will do it. - Yes. We
have to decorate that wall too.
Yes, sir.
Madam, chair.
Thank you.
Hey partner...
What's wrong? The train is
delayed?
No, a total delay.
Dhruv won't make it.
Something came up at work.
Ouch!
So are you waiting for the
decorator to show up with the
tent?
Come on... get up. Lend me a
hand!
I'm totally confused...
orange or white?
Yellow and white!
Yellow and white, sorry.
Come on... let's walk and talk.
So, do you also do this?
Make plans with your
girlfriend and ditch her?
Actually, that's Radhika's
nature.
Really?
Wow good! I'm glad,
here's to women's power!
Don't you feel hurt?
Do you feel hurt?
Of course, I do.
For a little while,
then I cheer myself up.
I think about all the good
things.
No relationship is perfect.
I guess you are right.
Nothing is perfect,
you get used to it.
I often think about the
direction..
..our relationship
is taking and then...
brain freeze!
So, it's best not to think.
Yeah... but you know Jai...
I've always believed that..
..our habits were once
something we could choose.
We have to choose right.
Interesting!
But let's say, just imagine...
..the choice is right..
..but what if a slightly
better option comes along?
Then?
Crazy!
Let's go and tell Govind.
The loser is still asleep.
Still asleep?
- Yes and it's one o'clock!
Let's throw water...
- Yes, water!
First water. And now, beer.
Arjun... you're not nervous
about getting married, are you?
Not really, why?
Because...
Let me have that.
Well if you have any doubts,
you can check with Govind.
He's done this twice!
Yeah man!
Starting today you are my best
man.
Just stay with me.
- Yes. I will.
You guys are devils! You
aren't invited for my next
wedding.
No problem, dude.
We'll attend the one after that!
Same old joke. Three
times a day! Like a routine!
Are you mad?
Just finish that.
What are you guys smoking?
What is it?
Think of it as a gift of
nature!
- Nature, huh?
He's getting married, he needs
it!
You guys are quite dangerous,
you know.
You want me to tell Gayatri?
- No, no way.
You've changed... everything
is,
'you want me to tell Gayatri?'
It's not rocket science,
just watch...
One, two, three...
Gayatri, I can't wear this!
What's wrong?
So what's the problem? You look
hot!
Arjun! I can't wear this!
Come on, you look good.
You're mad! I look like Santa
Claus.
What is their problem?
All they have to do is dance.
What's wrong with Santa Claus?
- It's all red!
What are you talking about?
- It's looking very nice.
Very nice!
You remember the steps, right?
Yes, every step. I
can't wait to dance.
I told you we were
going to have a great time.
Just look at you... matching!
Wow, this is fun!
I think I need to pee!
Come on guys! It's show time!
"Sound and disco. San
Francisco."
"Neither liquor nor
alcohol nor barmaid."
"Nor a glass of drink."
"Your arrival is what
cheers up my heart."
"Your arrival."
"Neither flower nor
bud nor bulbul's."
"Chirping."
"Your arrival is what
cheers up my heart."
"Your arrival."
"Love makes the world go round."
"Sound and disco. San
Francisco."
"Heaven in dreams."
"When I saw it."
"Heaven in my dreams."
"Flowers also didn't cheer me
up."
"I started searching for you."
"Neither the spring of
heaven nor fairies'."
"Smile."
"Your arrival is what
cheers up my heart."
"Your arrival."
That's it.
Where is Pinku?
I think he is on the stage.
Let's go.
Jai. - We are coming. Let's go.
Let's go. - All the best.
"One day I also went
to the jewelry market."
"I remembered your eyes
amidst diamond necklaces."
"Neither pearl nor
diamonds nor jewelries."
"Nor any treasure."
"Your arrival is
what cheers up my heart."
"Your arrival."
"When you come to me, baby."
Dhruv.
Wow, you look lovely. I made it!
My foot you made it!
- Why?
You missed the performance.
No... I caught the last part.
You were so hot...
so hot and I know you.
Let me introduce you to the
others.
- Okay.
Guys this is Dhruv.
Gayatri...
- Hi.
Arjun, congratulations guys!
Thank you.
- You must be so...excited?
Yes!
- It's like..
Just a second.
Jai...
Hey...
- Hi...
Too good, man. You
were amazing up there.
All thanks to you.
Thanks to me?
Yes, if you were here, you
would've been Naina's partner.
Oh that way, but let me
tell you, I can't do this.
Thank God for you!
That's true.
- Welcome.
Hope you enjoy yourself.
- Thanks.
Let me take you to Biji.
Okay.
- Take care, guys.
Bye.
- See you.
It's time to...
Bar. The bar is there.
The bar is..
Naina.
Life can be so unpredictable.
Biji was so full of life and...
I can't believe she is no more.
Darling, I think..
..anything Arjun's
family decides will be okay.
But I think right now
you should be strong..
..at least for Arjun.
Gayatri, you should eat
something.
You should eat something.
I think you should.
I'll get something.
Hi Naina...
- Hi.
You okay?
- Yeah.
How is Gayatri?
I'll check on her.
Where is Dhruv?
- He is taking a shower.
Naina
..can I see you tomorrow
at six in the morning?
It's important.
Yeah... sure!
Bye.
You are late.
I know, sorry. I always
have a problem waking up.
The five minute snooze ends up
being more than ten minutes!
Sorry.
- I know that feeling.
So why did you call me out here?
Naina, I need to tell you
something.
What?
After Biji's death I
realised something...
life is too short.
Everything is here and now...
the chances, the moments.
And a delay won't change the
facts.
Yes, but...
- Now I hope he understands
this.
What's up? Why did you call me
here?
Arjun... don't postpone the
wedding.
Have you lost it completely?
At this moment?
Naina...I mean..
Listen to me, Arjun.
Do you think Biji would like
it if you postponed the wedding?
Of course not, never!
Biji always told us
that life is very short.
And that we should
celebrate every day...
..every relationship, the
love we share, our friends.
And this is your wedding!
She was so excited and happy..
..that you and Gayatri
were getting married.
Here... now...
I know it's tough, brother
but...
God knows I know.
Biji is with us.
She is here and she will always
be!
Make sure she is happy.
You know this is the
generosity and love of our
elders...
..even as they leave us
they expect us to be happy.
Do you remember in school I
always failed in English
spelling...
Biji would teach me...
after learning it herself.
But she always got it wrong.
I got Gayatri to meet
her before anyone else.
Without her how can I...
Exactly the
way she would want you to.
Happy and smiling.
Go and talk to Gayatri.
"Why do we meet when we
have to lose each other?"
"When heart has to wither,
why does it blossom?"
"Why do we meet when we
have to lose each other?"
"When heart has to wither,
why does it blossom?"
I'm so glad you did that.
Anything for Biji, Naina.
Her happiness is in this.
Why did you ask me to be here?
You know what it is to lose a
loved one and still carry on.
And I felt that if you are with
me,
I wouldn't be all alone...
Well actually...
- I know.
But I promise
whenever you need me...
..no matter what... if you need
me...
I'll be there...
silent but strong.
Sure?
Sure!
"Lord is the savior."
Bye guys...
Bye.
- See you.
See you.
- Bye. See you.
Bye, Naina!
- See you. - Bye.
Shall we go?
Glad you made it. For a moment
I thought you're not coming.
Dhruv...
Take care, buddy.
- You too.
Congratulations.
- Thank you.
I'll get our bags.
- Yeah.
- Bye Jai. - Bye Naina.
If you ever visit Bombay...
Sure.
Dude, what's wrong with you?
Come on... cheers!
Cheers? For what?
Because we are free again!
Tell me, how was lunch?
And your mom?
Lunch.
It's too close to the kitchen,
do you have anything else?
This is too small, do
you have anything else?
I think this is fine.
Thank you.
What would you like to have,
aunty-ji? Some soup?
I'll have anything you call
for.
Your taste is the best.
Okay, no soup then.
One steam wantons without sauce
and a vegetarian noodles.
I don't like onions, carrots
and
mushrooms, so only add capsicum.
Yes ma'am.
What's up with you? Why so
silent?
China Garden is your
favourite restaurant.
Yes, mom, it is my favourite
but
Radhika is talking right now.
Idiot! Have you thought
about your wedding yet?
Come on, mom!
- Excuse me! - Yes?
Can I have one pepsi
with lots of ice. - Sure, sir.
Not aerated drinks again!
Excuse me, can you make
that an ice tea, please? Thank
you.
- And excuse me...
- Yes ma'am?
Please see to it that the food
is
very fresh and piping hot.
Sure ma'am.
And really hot! If it's not
hot, I won't accept it.
Excuse me, can you ask the
chef to use less ajinomoto?
Lunch! It ruined everything.
Any more questions, Mr. Govind?
No... so which restaurant was
this?
Govind... let's go
back to Chandigarh.
I can't get the wedding
out of my mind.
What are we doing here...
I mean what are we doing?
Bro, that wedding is over.
But more weddings will
happen I am sure.
But are you sure you can't get
the wedding out of your mind...
or is it 'someone' on your mind?
Do you think so?
I think so!
You know who?
You think I am stupid?
I know who! You want to know?
No!
So Jai is the guy from Delhi.
Stop it, Ritu!
I should stop it?
Okay.
I think you have a crush...
a little crush on him.
Dhruv still exists, you know.
He hasn't vanished.
Of course, that will be too
much to
ask. - Rubbish. You naughty girl.
Stop imagining things, Ritu.
The wedding is over.
I am back to my old routine and
he is back to his fun routine.
What were you saying, Jai?
Just a second...coaster..
..carry on.
Radhika, this isn't working.
What's wrong now? You want
to quit your job again!
No, this is not working.
You are frustrating me again.
What is 'this'?
This means us.
I am sorry. I know it's
coming like a surprise.
Why are we even together,
Radhika?
Because we want to get married,
Jai.
You want to get married or
do you want to marry me?
I don't understand... what
sort of question is that?
It may sound complicated but
it really is very simple.
At Arjun's wedding..
..I realised that though we are
together we really are far
apart.
It's because our priorities
are different.
Tell me..
..when was the last time..
..we really did something
together from our heart.
I just want to be honest..
.. that's it.
What are you getting at, Jai?
You mean the two years that...
I have invested into this
relationship are a waste?
Keeping track of your
21 family members'..
..21 birthdates and wishing
them is a waste?
Tolerating your annoying
habits is a waste?
Jai, to be honest, you are
ruining
my well laid out plan!
In the next two years I wanted
to have my first child...
now how's that going to happen?
Radhika, relax... calm down.
Probably the plan itself is
wrong.
I mean somewhere along the way
the plans scored over love.
But who knows... right? Perhaps
there's someone else for us...
Who will love us...
for the real reasons.
The right reason.
Someone else? You met someone
else?
I did!
But neither am I with her nor
is she madly in love with me.
There's no such thing like that.
She has nothing to do with
our situation.
I swear!
Have you told your mom?
She is sure to kill me!
I was hoping you could
break the news to her.
Coaster!
I guess you are right.
I mean, I am the strong type
but...
I thought something like
this would shatter me.
But I'm not.
Isn't that strange?
We could remain friends... I
mean,
if it's alright with you.
I need some time, Jai.
I'll call you.
Okay.
Jai..
.. if ever wish to pursue
the girl you've met...
please do it after you've
changed your habits.
It will create a good
impression.
- Hello. - Hi, busy?
Just working for the exhibition.
Any plans for tonight?
Just me and Arundhati Roy...
at the most some coffee.
That sounds exciting.
Don't rub it in!
I'll have you know, though I
may
not agree with her viewpoint but...
she is way more interesting
than ..
..your financial spreadsheets
and numbers...
with whom you spend every night.
Fine, let's change our plans.
Dinner.
Wow, sounds good.
- Tonight at 9pm. Don't be
late.
- Okay bye.
Weren't you afraid of her?
That was quite a risk.
I sure was but I figured that
it
makes sense to accept the truth.
As for risk, crossing the road
is also a risk. Isn't it?
Well that was it!
So Mr. Govind, now you and
I are in the same category.
Single... and officially
ready to mingle.
No, brother.
I don't belong to that
category anymore.
You know Sheila?
Sheila? God damn it Govind!
We are back in Delhi...
back to reality.
You took her number?
You basket, when?
What are you doing?
Come on bro, it's simple
technology!
FB... friend request.
I think I'll ask her
out for coffee today.
I think you should take
your sad story elsewhere.
I'm committed, man!
Committed my ass!
Being committed to the
idea of commitment..
.. doesn't mean you are
committed.
Have you lost it completely?
- Get lost.
Sheila? Facebook?
Loser.
- Give me a break!
Oh shit! Naina!
Hey Jai, how are you? Please
accept my friend request.
I want to tag you in
the wedding pictures.
Bye! Smileys!
Don't be silly! We were
all there at the wedding.
She wants to share the
pictures,
that's it.
Even I was there at the
wedding...
but nobody's sharing
anything with me.
Well Sheila is sharing...
her old age.
That was a good one. Let's
see the pictures.
Hey check out pinku... and
Gayatri!
Look at Arjun!
What now?
Now... back to work!
You like Naina, right?
Govind! Naina is with Dhruv
and she lives in Bombay.
Where do we live?
Jai.
Jai, we need to renew these
advertisement contracts.
Didn't you close the
endorsements
deal last time?
- Yes sir.
- Good!
So get ready, this time
you're going to Bombay.
- Here's the file. - Okay, sir.
Let's book your ticket.
- Hi... - Hello.
- Come... - Thank you.
So, I've ordered some wine.
The one you like?
Well done.
So, a dinner plan...
out of the blue?
Well, it has been a while..
..and there's something else.
What?
I'm leaving for Singapore
tomorrow for ten days.
- Great! - What?
That means you will
miss my exhibition.
Oh God! How could I forget!
I am so sorry... I feel so
stupid!
I have a very good reason for
it.
Go on!
The management thinks if I like
the set-up over there...
I could be the Vice President
for Emerging Markets.
Isn't that great?
That's great, Dhruv. I
am so happy for you.
You always wanted this.
- Thanks.
Don't worry about the
exhibition, really!
Will you marry me?
Your menu.
- Sir? - Thanks!
- Give us a few minutes? - Sure
sir.
Listen... I know that
everything
is happening very quickly.
But that's exactly how life
throws up opportunities.
I'll be back in ten days and
then you can decide...
the type of wedding, the
location,
the setting.
Toast?
Come on...
the future is about to unfold
with unexpected surprises.
Trust me.
Good morning, sir.
Have a pleasant flight.
Well, well... what could
have made my super..
..independent daughter
think of her mother?
Dhruv proposed to me.
He did? What did you reply?
Nothing.
What do you mean nothing?
He left no room for me to reply.
He was so sure I would
say yes that...
he didn't realise whether
I had said yes or no.
What's the matter, dear?
Aren't you happy?
I don't know, mom.
You know Dhruv and I have
been good friends.
I'm an emotional fool while
he is too practical.
I believed this would be a
good combination for us.
And that he would bring a sense
of balance to my life.
But now you know...
How did you know, mom...
that dad was the one?
Or uncle Ashu after him?
A sign, Naina.
A little sign and you will know
it.
You will feel him...
you'll feel that thrill that
just fills up your heart.
Mom, hold on a second. Hello?
If you ever visit Bombay...
- Jai! - Hi Naina.
Listen, I am going to call you
back!
Yeah, sure.
Bye!
Mom...
Idiot!
Call as soon as you land...
on the advice of a
two-time divorcee!
Jai... you are... fantastic!
Naina, just do what you've
always done in life.
Follow you heart, not your mind.
Trust yourself.
I know you will take
the right decision.
Love you, sweetheart.
I love you too, mom. Bye!
Jai... what are you doing in
Bombay?
Well... I thought I'd visit you.
Just kidding!
Work brought me here so I
thought
you could show me around Bombay.
I'm so bored here at
this guest house.
Your timing couldn't
have been better!
Really? My dad always
said my timing sucked.
How is that?
Well... my arrival into this
world
put an end to his honeymoon period!
Nothing has changed neither
you nor your sad jokes!
Please... before they
get any sadder..
- Coffee? - Yeah!
Thank you.
- Welcome, ma'am.
So, now your exhibition is
set...
anything else that's exciting?
Nothing actually. You know..
Gayatri's wedding was so high
on energy... You were there. -
Yes.
that now everything seems
lifeless.
I really get it.
I still sing those songs
in the shower and...
my mom thinks it's
a sign. Ridiculous!
Maybe it is! Is Radhika ready?
Not anymore.
We... we broke up.
But, why?
I've figured out a slightly
more perfect option, Naina.
Being single!
And to be honest, Radhika
and my future had..
..a question mark dangling over
it.
But my mom hasn't given up hope.
- You know how they are. - I
know.
I guess all mothers are
like that.
How is Govind?
Govind... he got himself into
an interesting situation.
Really? You mean, Sheila?
So what? A slap?
Not exactly...
Hello sir.
- Salesman?
- No, sir.
- Bank account?
Sir, I am Govind, Sheila's
friend.
I'm not a salesman.
- You are Sheila's friend?
- Yes, sir.
- Well... in that case, come
in.
- Thank you, sir.
- Would you like some tea?
- Yes.
Vinod, a cup of tea, please.
What?
Nothing, sir.
Sit down.
Can I clean my gun?
Oh... yes, please.
How did you and Sheila meet?
We met at Arjun and
Gayatri's wedding.
Since then we've been friends.
Rubbish!
- Sorry?
Rubbish... dirt in the barrel.
Don't guns frighten you, sir?
Are you holding the gun?
No, sir.
- Then what's to fear?
No, sir. I mean there are often
articles in newspapers...
'Man shoots himself with gun.'
Fear creeps in when the
barrel is pointed at you.
In the army...
Vinod! Inform Sheila that a
certain
Govind is here to see her.
What are you doing here?
Nothing, sir.
Why are you creeping up
on me? - No, sir.
Are you alright?
Yes.
Are you sure?
- Yes, sir.
Then what are you doing here?
Sir... view.
View?
- The garden.
What about the garden?
- Butterfly.
- Butterfly? You like
butterfly?
- Yes, sir.
Big one. - Yes. - Small one.
- Yes. - Red ones.
- All types sir.
- All types of butterflies.
You like butterflies?
I love...
- Butterflies... wow!
Hi...
Sheila, let's go, we're running
late. - Yes, come on.
Just a minute...
Is the coffee on a train or a
bus
that it will leave without you?
- No, sir.
- You will miss it?
Dad!
- Just a minute.
Sheila does everything
at her own time
We literally counted hours
before she was born.
She spent two years in
the second grade. - Okay, dad.
She will get married when
she thinks its time...
..it also takes a while
to understand people.
You get it? - Yes. - Do you
gamble?
- Sometimes sir.
Do you drink?
- Sometimes.
With guys?
Sometimes. - With guys?
- Oh no, no, sir!
I was married twice before.
To whom?
- To women.
Are you sure?
- Sir, you are welcome to check.
- Yes, sir.
Yes, sir. I love everything
about nature, sir.
I just want to have coffee
with Sheila, sir.
Okay, dad, that's enough!
Stop giving him a hard time?
Okay. That's it.
I am giving him a hard time?
- Yes!
He has been married twice
and he loves butterflies! - No.
No.
I am not giving him hard time.
Do you understand? Yeah. Okay.
Let's go!
Nine o'clock back home.
I'll make it, sir.
- I mean Sheila. Bye.
Okay, that's it, dad.
Bye, see you later. Come on.
Hey... see you later.
Okay, right, sir.
Come on!
- What's wrong?
- Nothing.
Your dad is quite
an interesting man. Nice.
I was just looked at my watch,
he
said we should be back by nine.
He said a lot of other things.
He said I do everything late.
- Right.
We'll be back late,
he'll understand.
- No, no... - Come on!.
- No. Really.
Oh, my God.
- Oh God! Butterflies!
It's too much pressure.
So when did they get back?
On the dot at nine.
This time Sheila finally gave
in.
It's amazing love makes
people do amazing things.
Yup.
11 o'clock tomorrow?
11? Oh, yeah. A tour of Bombay?
- Exactly!
Exciting. Alright, I'll see you.
Text me when you get home.
Jai, this is Bombay. Don't
worry.
Corrected again!
- Pink butterfly!
- Garden butterfly!
"We are awake as well as
asleep.
We are a bit lost."
"Lost in love. Love, love,
what is love?"
"We are awake as well as
asleep.
We are a bit lost."
"Lost in love. Love, love,
what is love?"
"The air is vibrant.
Conversations are fragrant."
"The weather is so warm."
"Why do we fall in love?"
"If you know, tell me. I don't
know."
"Why do we fall in love?"
"If you know, tell me.
I don't know."
"I don't know."
"Is this love?"
"Can you feel it?
Tell me. Love. Love."
Have you wondered why your
previous
two marriages ended in a divorce?
Okay.
Suchitra and
I were classmates.
Back then I was in a band...
I was big John Travolta fan.
- Really?
you know 'Saturday Night Fever.'
Oh, how did if he's your love.
Dad said the same thing when
he...
learnt that Suchitra
was a Christian.
There was a lot of drama and
we ran away from home.
Jai sneaked out with his
dad's car and drove us.
We got married in the church
as well as the temple.
I was 23 and madly in love.
Anyway...
Then?
then we turned 24
and started thinking like
adults.
We didn't work out. And she
left me.
After that I was quite low
and working for my dad.
My dad manufactured ball
bearings.
You know...those small round
things
that are used in bicycles.
I guess throughout school
and college...
I was ridiculed about balls.
I mean, my dad was the
ball bearing guy.
My second marriage was like
a life insurance plan. - What?
Nandini, daughter of wealthy
guy.
Sweet girl but very boring.
We were so incompatible that we
hated spending time with each
other.
We would invite friends over..
..so we could avoid
spending time with each other.
That bad?
I decided that enough is enough.
Good for you..
Exactly!
I left home again and started
living in a rented place.
Now I'm earning 84,000
rupees a month.
Post tax.
- I see.
I mean, I'm responsible for all
the mistakes and wrong
decisions.
It's amazing!
What have you decided now?
Well... since this train isn't
going anywhere, let's go...
walking.
Okay. Coffee.
- Coffee. - Come on.
- So let's take it slow. - Sure
"Emotions are infused in
breaths."
"Dreams are weaving in eyes."
"The dusk seems new."
"The ambiance is in
the heart's favor."
"The air is vibrant.
Conversations are fragrant."
"The weather is so warm."
"Why do we fall in love?"
"If you know, tell me. I don't
know."
"Why do we fall in love?"
"If you know, tell me. I don't
know."
"I don't know."
Naina, is absolutely right.
You are not like other girls.
Be a man! Stand up for yourself.
I mean be stern in life...
what's that word, Naina?
Confront. - Confront! Confront
all of them who have..
..broken your heart into
a million pieces.
Ritu, go on, be brave!
Sorry... don't you eat anything
apart from ice cream?
Come on, go for it!
- Okay.
Hey.
You?
- We!
Yes, I..
listen Bheem.
Bheem?
I just want to say, what
if I eat meat and eggs?
What if I have a couple
of bottles of vodka?
A couple of bottles?
Only sometimes, dude. Sometimes.
At the end of the day
I am a good person.
Bheem, what's going on here?
And I know the Hanuman Chalisa
too!
- Very good. Very good.
Father, it happened three years
ago, we were in college.
Yes, right but it's over today.
Finally I am dumping you,
never to get back again.
Bheem, shut the door!
We'll help you.
Very good, Ritu!
Thank God. I am actually good.
Now to the next one.
What are you doing here?
Honey bunny, is it the ice
cream?
Who are they?
Sorry... just carry on.
Yes, carry on.
He is not really...
I know! And I thought there
was something lacking in me.
It's alright. - Well...
technically you were lacking...
Okay, no over confidence.
One more to go.
Let's get the hell out
of here right now.
I guess God heard my prayer.
He's not at home, let's go.
Ritu!
- Yeah, I am getting it.
Ritu? Where have you been?
I called you so many times.
You neither take my calls nor
reply to the text messages.
That's true.
Sorry. Ritu, why didn't you
tell us?
You are doubting him
unnecessarily.
Look at his innocent face.
He could never cheat you.
- Cheat?
That's true, Ritu.
His eyes reveal his honesty.
He won't betray you.
Betray? What are you talking
about?
I had seen your text.
- Text?
Priya's. I'll see you soon.
Hugs and kisses!
Kunal.
See that... I was right!
You are Priyanka, right? - Yes.
Cheat and betray!
You don't get it, Priyanka is
my..
Priyanka is my?
I don't want to hear another
word!
Guys like you always take
girls like us for a ride!
Was it wrong that I love you?
Are you done? I love you too!
Can I say something?
Priyanka is my cousin.
That's right. He's told
me so much about you.
It's not good to doubt like
that.
Kunal, I'll leave now.
We'll also leave...
No, Naina, you and I
will leave. Sorry.
Sorry.
I am so happy for them, Jai.
So let's celebrate!
Just a second.
Timing.
Hello... yes, Riddhi.
What?
But... how...
I can't believe this.
What happened?
No.
I lost the venue for my
exhibition.
Some confusion about
the dates and now...
I can't even reschedule
my exhibition.
So change the venue!
Jai, this is Bombay and these
venues aren't easy to come by.
Mumbai.
Listen, I've got an idea.
Wait for my call.
I'll be right back, okay?
Jai, one second... hello?
Mr. Fix-it?
Yes?
What do you mean,
wait for your call?
Relax, I'm here, aren't I?
Jai..
..what's this?
Trust me, Naina.
All we need is a little more.
"My heart is singing a song."
"When you are with me,
my heart is tempting me."
"Look, you should be
in your senses."
"Tell your heart to keep quiet."
"The air is vibrant.
Conversations are fragrant."
"The weather is so warm."
"Why do we fall in love?"
"If you know, tell me.
I don't know."
"Why do we fall in love?"
"If you know, tell me.
I don't know."
You are right! All we
need is a little more.
"I don't know."
"What is love?"
Thank you, Mr. Fix-it.
You are welcome.
By the way who calls
pani-puri golgappas?
Sorry, it was a mistake.
It's a Delhi thing.
Right. - Shall we eat? I'm
starving..
it's three in the morning.
Even I'm hungry. - Sorry.
- I've put in the hard work too.
Right... I forgot!
We'd like two servings of
gol...
sorry, pani-puris.
Pani-puri!
Let's have pani-puri?
Three servings of pani-puri!
Hey... there's a queue.
Relax dude!
Jai, don't mess with them,
we'll go somewhere else.
She is right. Next time let
her mess around with us.
Forget it.
What did you say?
Just go away, okay!
Jai... stop it!
Jai!!
I'll give you a piece of my
mind.
Jai, stop it. Stop it.
I give you a chance.
- Jai. Jai.
Is this good? Is
this also a Delhi thing?
Naina, they were talking shit.
Right, it was shit. Jai,
you could've ignored them.
Sometimes I just don't
understand what gets into you
guys.
A small thing and
you lose all control.
A small thing? It's
not a small thing, Naina.
And people who treat
this as a small thing...
should be slapped right and
left!
Because they are responsible
for encouraging such behaviour.
You think you'll
change everyone, Jai?
Yes, Naina, I will.
Merely complaining
about things doesn't help.
Then you should slap me too.
Oh God!
What happened?
Jai, look... how cute...
probably alone.
What now?
Let's wait, probably
someone will come.
I don't think anyone is coming.
Are you thinking the same
thing that I'm thinking?
I'm afraid I'm thinking..
..the same thing
that you're thinking.
What do you say?
Let's go.
Oh my God! What do we call him?
Starving Starvo!
How about Lucky?
That's a nice name. Lucky.
Lucky.
Okay, Naina, I should get going.
Hold on, I'll be right back.
He fell asleep... sit!
Naina, it's okay.
Not a word. Come on.
Better?
I'm sure it would be if
it were on the right side.
Then why did you make that
sound?
- Because it's cold. - Really?
Drama queen!
I feel better. I should leave.
I guess I'll call you.
I guess you will.
Jai, lunch?
I would love to but I have
an important lunch meeting.
Really? I forgot you
even have to work.
Something like that.
Is it interesting?
Well, it is nice to
see you again, Jai.
And it's really nice
to extend this contract.
Thank you, sir.
How are things?
Sir, D Decor is doing fantastic.
We are launch more
products next year,
so we're really excited.
Should be excited,
it's all about quality.
D Decor's quality and designs
are the best. So, thank you.
Thank you.
How did you get hurt?
Some guys said something
about a girl last night.
You fought for a girl?
Is she your friend?
Yes.
A special friend?
I think so.
Does she know that you
think she is special?
No, sir.
Why? You haven't told her?
It's complicated, sir.
It's always complicated.
Jai, relationships are
only as complicated...
as you want them to be.
Remember this, in real
life and in films...
there's always a happy ending.
So, tell her what's in your
heart.
Where is she?
Actually, she is right behind
you.
She's like a little monkey.
Hello...
You better tell her or
you'll repent it all your life.
Take care buddy... see you.
Ma'am... pleasure.
Thank you... so much!
It's okay.
Thank you God for fulfilling my
wish.
Ritu will die of envy!
Naina! I didn't know
you were this filmy.
I mean it's cute but --
Listen, of course I am filmy.
By the way, 99 percent girls
who
meet SRK react in a similar way.
Right.
- He's just so charming.
Don't wash the hand, by the way.
Of course, I'm not
going to wash the hand.
Listen, haven't you watched
DDLJ?
I have but it has been a while.
So what?
Nobody makes a love
story like Shahrukh Khan.
We're going to watch it right
now.
No, Naina... - I can't
watch DDLJ, I promise! Oh God!
What unexpected rain!
Seriously! I think my watch
stopped.
What is this? You made a mess
again?
What is this?
- Not really.
Really? Look at this!
Here take this towel.
Here.
Dry yourself before
you pour out your anger!
Look at this... it says Bura
[Bad] Kebabs, not Bara [Big].
You want jumping chicken?
No!
Take your pick...
there's Chinese, Indian...
Nothing exciting.
Now what?
Do you know how to make
the perfect Maggi noodles?
Heat water, add the noodles,
let it boil for two minutes.
That's obvious my friend.
You also add cheese..
..chilli and my special
ingredient.
Is that so?
Tell me Sheila... you are
beautiful,
intelligent, funny...
and you know how to make
the perfect Maggi noodles.
I don't get it... you
can get any guy you like.
So how is it that you
still aren't... married...
The marriage question!
I was waiting for it.
This I don't get...
I mean, as soon as a girl is
born..
..you start thinking
of getting her married
It doesn't matter whether it's
through an matchmaking website
or...
the nephew of a neighbour or
through a distant relative.
Get her married off so..
..the parents feel
they've fulfilled their task.
What's with everybody
wanting me to get married?
There's a lot more to life than
that.
You were married twice,
what did you get?
True!
Thank God I didn't
give in to the pressure.
My logic was simple.
When I'd meet someone who's
outlook was off center like
mine..
..I would, you know and
you know what, I was right.
Well, I'm very happy to meet
you.
Wait. The secret ingredient!
Fried noodles?
- That's right!
In 'Maggi'?
- Yes. Try it.
Oh my God!
This is so good, I
think I want to marry it!
Hi Jai...
- Hello Naina.
Oh shit!
- What?
Sorry, I'll call you back.
Okay.
Hi Jai...
- It's Gayatri, darling.
Who is this Jai you were
expecting?
Gayatri? When did you get back?
Don't tell me you're set to
make me an aunt in nine months!
Shut up! I'll become an
aunt after you get married.
So is it Arjun's friend Jai?
Oh my God, Arjun was right!
About what exactly?
Just that there was some
connection between you and Jai.
It's not like that, Gayatri.
But you can make it like that,
Naina.
Dhruv proposed to me, Gayatri.
You know Jai and me...
..maybe in another lifetime.
Anyway, you know... just a
second.
It's your life, honey. Think
about it.
You want me to talk to Arjun?
Gayatri, it's Dhruv.
- Hi. - Hi.
- I'll call you back. - Okay,
bye.
What are you doing here?
- May I come in? - Of course,
come in.
Seven days are more than enough
to fall in love with Singapore.
Got done with my work and came
back.
When I landed I remembered
that...
I had forgotten my key back at
home.
So I had to come. I
would have called you. But..
What the hell? Why is this dog
here?
It's not a dog, Dhruv, it's a
puppy.
His name is Lucky.
A puppy is also a dog.
Where did you get it?
On the street, she was alone.
And you brought it home.
Naina, I am sure he
has 200 infections.
She!!
- Alright, she!
You are over reacting, Dhruv.
I'm not over reacting,
you know my allergies.
I have to take a shower.
Fine, you take a shower
and I will go to the studio.
I'm taking Lucky along.
I'll see you in the
evening and we'll talk.
Yes.
- Hi Naina... - Hi Jai.
Can I leave Lucky with
you for a few hours?
- Sure. - Thank you.
Everything alright?
Yes, I'll call in the evening.
Okay?
- Okay. - Thanks. Bye. - Bye.
Lucky, today I want you
to prove lucky for me.
Come on. Let's go.
Lucky, be my lucky mascot today.
So you will ring the bell.
Jai?
Dhruv?
Lucky... with you?
Well, Naina...
Naina gets everyone
involved in her social service.
Anyway, come on in.
So, can I get you something to
drink?
Coffee, beer, Bacardi?
No, thanks, Dhruv. Thanks a lot.
Hey babe, guess who is here!
Jai is here with Lucky.
Hi Jai.
- Hi Naina.
Actually, sorry, I should've
called.
That's not a problem.
Give me a second, I'll be back.
She's a little frisky, but
don't worry, I've fed her.
Thank you.
- She should be fine.
I guess, I should leave.
You just got here.
Yes, but I came to Bombay on
business and now it's over.
I should prepare to return.
You know what, spend
the evening with us.
Naina, I forgot to
tell you earlier that
I've invited some of my friends
over.
Now what? - Now we have to
organise dinner and drinks.
Why don't you invite
some of your friends?
Jai, you must stay, it will be
fun.
Thanks, Dhruv, but I should
leave.
No problem.
- Naina, he's your friend, tell
him.
Please stay, Jai.
Come on, guys. Let's play.
Each team has two players.
One player has explain the word
written on the top of the card.
So that's simple.
No, not simple.
The five closest
words used to explain...
that word are at the
bottom of the card.
And you have to get your
partner guess that very word...
without using those five words.
Ready?
Wait. I'll explain.
Say the word on top is Ritu.
The five words below is will
be...
- irritating, child, ice cream..
..silly and gorgeous.
So smart, Dhruv.
Let's get started. Now come on!
Naina, I think you
should partner with Jai.
But Dhruv --
But he doesn't know anyone.
He only knows Lucky and he
can't play.
And Ritu and I will referee,
okay?
Okay.
Okay, come on quick. Hi... I'm
Jai.
Okay guys, your time to starts
now.
Okay, Riya...
when we were in school...
your teacher ask you to
do this but you couldn't.
Maths?
Something else, come on...
Science!
Add them altogether, more...
Studies.
Okay, on to the next card.
You have this for your
breakfast.
Cereal.
No, something else!
Eggs. - No, not eggs,
something else, come on.
Okay, Scotch.
Whiskey!
- Move out of alcohol. Scotch.
I don't know.
- Time is running out guys!
Come on, Riya!
- Next!
Taxi?
Luggage?
Bags... where we first met.
Bus stop... bus!
Right! Okay this is very simple.
I said yellow and you said
orange.
Decorations... wedding...
flowers!
Right! Okay, go down.
Boxes?
- Jai, emergency!
Hospital.
- I'm here, aren't I?
Art gallery!
- Right! Okay.
Was...
Father.
Times up! That's a strange
clue but amazingly played.
Wow.
Well played guys, the
others still can't believe it.
Naina, dessert?
Yes, I'll come.
- Jai, join me for a smoke?
Yes. Come on.
You know, investment
banking is very stressful and...
to take the right decision at
the
right time can be very difficult.
Just like life.
And that's how I got this
habit of social smoking.
I get it, Dhruv. Sometimes
even I do it, bad habit, bro.
Yeah, what do you do?
I'm in marketing.
- Family?
Just mom.
You aren't married, yet? I
mean..
Well, even you aren't married.
Yeah, I guess didn't get
the time. What's your excuse?
I guess, I didn't get the right
girl.
Dhruv... they're
leaving after dessert.
Is this right?
What?
- Dessert plan!
Yeah.
- We'll leave too and we'll
drop you.
Good idea.
- Yeah.
Let's go.
Alright, Jai. It was a
pleasure meeting you again.
Stay in touch.
Bye Dhruv, all the best.
"There is loneliness."
"I don't know why."
"Why this punishment?"
"Who knows?"
"Paths are lonely."
"Arms are lonely."
"Eyes are lonely."
"Why do we meet when we
have to lose each other?"
"When heart has to wither,
why does it blossom?"
"Why do we meet when we
have to lose each other?"
"When heart has to wither.."
So that was a fun party.
Thank God, you had the spare
keys.
Thank God! Alright, Dhruv, see
you.
Naina, hold on.
What have you decided?
About what?
Destination or local? Big or
small?
The type of wedding, my love?
You always wanted to have a
beach wedding, didn't you?
Yes. I knew it, you know me so
well.
Before I forget...
Naina, surprise! We're going
to Singapore for the weekend.
Dhruv, but...
Don't worry, it isn't the final
move.
You just have to come
and finalise the house.
Don't you think this
is happening to fast?
Why so scared? We'll be fine.
I'll see you.
Bye.
- Bye.
"Why do we meet when we
have to lose each other?"
"When heart has to wither,
why does it blossom?"
Loser! About time you called!
Yeah... how are you?
I'm doing great. Absolutely fit!
I guess Sheila is the reason.
Coffee, Sheila and I...
it's amazing, dude!
Caffecino, frappecino, latte,
black coffee.
Tell me, are you in love
with coffee or Sheila?
I mean, both!
I am so happy for the
both of you, brother.
So how've you been?
I'm alright. Packing
things to come back.
Coming back? How is Naina?
Naina... is fine. She is with
Dhruv.
Anyway, I'm taking the night
flight tomorrow. So, see you
soon.
Jai, did you tell Naina
how you felt about her?
Govind, I've got to take this
other call. I'll call you back.
See you in Delhi soon.
"Look. Look."
"Things have changed
completely."
"You were graceful."
"I was not."
"Heart was blossoming."
"Those eyes filled with love,
and sweet talks."
"I don't know where it is lost."
"Why did my dear one go away?"
"Why did we separate?"
"Why do we meet when we
have to lose each other?"
"When heart has to wither,
why does it blossom?"
"Why do we meet when we
have to lose each other?"
"When heart has to wither,
why does it blossom?"
"Paths are lonely."
"Arms are lonely."
"Eyes are lonely."
"I don't know why
there is loneliness."
"Why this punishment?"
"Who knows?"
This one is better, it has A/C.
Arjun! Govind!
So champ, game, set, match?
What are you doing here?
You're in a bloody problem
and you can't even tell us?
What problem are you talking
about?
Everything is fine.
Bloody liar!
Naina and Gayatri are like
sisters.
And Gayatri shares everything
with me.
You really thought we wouldn't
know..
..what's going on
between you and Naina?
There might be
something between us but...
..there's something
between Dhruv and Naina too!
Let's not complicate things.
In the same way that you
and Radhika had something.
You had realised this
a long time ago that...
you and Radhika aren't
meant for each other.
That is why you
weren't confused about Naina.
But Naina realised this only
after she spent time with you.
She needs time.
But what else can I do?
What do you mean, what else can
I do?
Tell Naina the truth!
If you don't tell Naina the
truth..
..your life will be
one big compromise.
And every girl you date
will always be second best.
He's right, Jai.
You remember what Biji would
say...
Have the courage to
say what's in your heart.
And be willing to understand
what's in another person's
heart.
So, do this for Biji.
Just go for it, buddy!
You think she'll say yes?
Jai, Naina and Dhruv are
going to Singapore today.
So you really don't have time
to
wonder and ask stupid questions.
We should get going.
Let's go.
- We have to go!
- Come on!
Okay, I think we should. - We
better make a run for it, let's
go!
Ritu, I hope you could be...
I am hopeless.
I've checked that
the flight is on time.
Shall we go? I'll call the lift.
Naina, you're sure
you want to do this?
Yeah... I can't do this to
Dhruv.
"Why do we meet when we
have to lose each other?"
"When heart has to wither,
why does it blossom?"
"Why do we meet when we
have to lose each other?"
"When heart has to wither,
why does it blossom?"
"The paths are lonely."
Jai.
- Come on, they've left...hurry
up!
Slow down, dude.
It's Jai who has to talk to
Naina,
why are we running? - Listen.
"There is loneliness."
"I don't know why."
"Why this punishment?"
"Who knows?"
Dhruv!
Jai?
Do you mind if I speak with
Naina?
Sure.
If ever in the future
and no offence to Dhruv..
..you have the perfect option..
..and you also realise it...
..can we go for it without any
fear?
Do you think we can hope..
..that no matter how confusing
and irritating relationships
our story could turn
out a little different.
Jai...- This is the
right time to take a stand...
This is the right chance.
All I need is your answer.
That's it.
Jai is crazy.
He thinks even guys should
be decked up with henna.
It's because of him that
we ran out of henna and...
it's also because of him..
..that Gayatri's henna
ceremony was so much fun.
I danced a lot today after ages.
There's still more...
I'm back after the wedding..
- I'm back after the wedding..
..and everything seems so
different.
Life seems incomplete, as
if I left something behind.
I even turned my bags upside
down.
I guess the change isn't about
things and places, it's about
me.
Gayatri was right, and
perhaps so was Ritu.
The change is Jai.
How I wish I had met Jai years
ago!
I'd have all the
courage and the liberty..
..to express my feelings to him.
But Dhruv...
..he is a part of my life..
..and I'll have to face him.
What will I tell him?
You silly girl!
The truth, first to
yourself and then to me.
Naina, you and I were always
friends.
It was much later that we
decided to be with each other.
But it doesn't mean
the decision was right.
I wanted to tell you, Dhruv...
but... it all happened...
A little too quickly, right?
I get it... I get it.
Jai, I saw this diary the
day I met you at Naina's place.
When I spoke with Ritu..
..she told me what I
probably didn't want to hear.
And then that evening
you spent with us, Jai.
Sorry, Naina, but I
had to see it myself.
I've got used to looking out
for you.
Jai, do you remember I'd said...
to take the right decision at
the
right time can be very difficult.
Just like life.
Well, this decision
isn't an easy one.
But it's very
important for all three of us.
On that note, I have
a flight to catch.
Naina, I didn't book a ticket
for you, so don't worry about
it.
I love you so much, Dhruv.
I love you as much, Naina.
Now, you guys take care of
each other.
Yeah.
You are a great guy, man.
Take care of each other.
See you.
Naina... I...
Couldn't you have said this
earlier?
Naina, I...
- Naina, I... what?
Tell me it's a Delhi thing!
You didn't hear your bell?
Naina, I love you very,
very, very much!
I swear!
I have never heard a louder
bell!
I swear!
Hey baby... yes, it's done. Bye.
"Your wishes will be
fulfilled."
- I love you too!
I love you more.
You are right, brother.
- "Know that dreams come true."
"I am thinking this is
where I want to be."
No.
"Beloved, I am yours."
It's my diary.
"Understand what the gestures
say."
"Listen."
"Everybody is calling
to us from the heart."
"I am thinking this is
where I want to be."
Life is complicated, people.
Try to keep it simple.
Settle down with a
like-minded partner...
and be happy... simple!
Jai make it quick... first
time I'm meeting your mom.
Oooops not so simple
Coming.
"Beloved, your and my
conversations make me go crazy."
"With you I think I'll be
alright."
"Oh, yeah. Sometimes one
wrong can make a right."
"Beloved, at times the
season becomes an excuse."
"Never going to let
you out of my sight."
"Oh, baby. You make my morning,
days and night."
"Your kohl eyes look beautiful."
"An innocent boy got enticed."
"When you turned and looked
behind."
"I fell in love with you."
"Look, the paths are
calling out to us."
"We are walking without
thinking."
"I am thinking this is
where I want to be."
"Beloved, I am yours."
"Beloved, your and my
conversations."
"Make me go crazy."
"With you I think I'll be
alright."
"Oh, yeah. Sometimes one
wrong can make a right."
"Beloved, at times the
season becomes an excuse."
"Never going to let
you out of my sight."
"Oh, baby. You make my morning,
days and night."
"Beloved, your and my
conversations make me go crazy."
"With you I think I'll be
alright."
"Oh, yeah. Sometimes one
wrong can make a right."
"Beloved, at times the
season becomes an excuse."
"Never going to let
you out of my sight."
"Oh, baby. You make my morning,
days and night."
"Your kohl eyes look beautiful."
"An innocent boy got enticed."
"When you turned and looked
behind."
"I fell in love with you."
"Your kohl eyes look beautiful."
"An innocent boy got enticed."
"When you turned and looked
behind."
"I fell in love with you."
Sorry. Sorry. Sorry.
- Cut. - Oh, no..
My God. Sorry.
Cut. - You say that one
more time, I'll hit you.