Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
THE HERO ATTITUDE
One, two, three, four, six
Let my heart sing a tune
And let my heartbeat croon
I want to smoke
Till my eyes get hazy
Come on, guys. Focus in.
It takes so long to focus.
Check the sound.
A-B-C, 1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3.
Darling, I don't know what to say
For I'm going crazy
Have you booked
my return flight ticket?
You'll get it.
Don't just say it.
Get it done.
And business class.
I only fly business class.
May God save who loves you
Your charm is deadly
And so is your love
You're emotional
Along with all the famous
personalities of the town...
...the district collector,
opposition leader...
...and everyone is here to congratulate
Chaudhary Suraj Singh...
...because today is
his daughter's wedding.
You're fair and cute
The groom will fall
Head over heels in love with you
Greetings, Mr. Minister.
Please come.
An ant was climbing up the hill.
The ant climbed up the hill.
When is he going
to get on the hill?
It will. It will.
An ant was climbing up
the hill for a grain.
Bachelors find their destiny
in the lane of love.
Son, this is Hekri village.
The Jat Land.
Here, love happens
after marriage.
We ask our wife's name
after having two kids.
Get lost.
Uncle, start with
our traditional rituals.
And that would be Pappi Jat.
DLF's famous goon.
That's Mr. Chaudhary's
younger brother.
The bride's first uncle.
But I read in the papers
he's supposed to be behind bars.
Technically, he's still in jail.
Who's he?
We've called him from Mumbai
to shoot the wedding video.
He filmed three movies
with Chunky Pandey.
Suspenders!
Wonderful!
Shoot a nice video.
Please book my plane ticket.
Economy will do.
And that's the famous
encounter specialist...
...Bhupender Singh Chaudhary
AKA Bhuppi Blackberry.
The bride's second uncle.
He has committed
42 murders to date.
And If I hadn't been suspended...
...I would've completed
my half century.
Get me suspended.
Get me a train ticket.
Bhuppi.
He belongs to the brick mafia.
Rajjo Fauji.
-Rajjo.
-Pappi!
So they all serve in the army?
No, they have their own army.
They supply bouncers to all
the discos of Delhi and Haryana.
And if any owner doesn't agree...
...Pappi and Bhuppi
raid that place.
Disco closed.
I'll take a bus.
Just tell me the number, I'll go.
-Tenne.
-Yes?
Sir.
Tenne?
-Sir.
-What about the booze?
As usual.
Grandpa, you're the eldest in the family.
You start.
Sukhi, he's my son-in-law.
How can I drink before him?
-So? Why aren't you drinking?
-No one respects me.
-What's wrong, brother-in-law?
-What happened?
What's this?
-I don't drink this.
-Then what do you want?
Get me Black Dog.
A beauty spot
On your fair cheeks
Listen, dear.
Better change your shirt.
The guests are about to arrive.
I am wearing a shirt. Get lost.
If he was not
our sister's husband...
...I would've killed him.
Drink up, brother-in-law.
Have this before the Black Dog.
-You'll love it. Have it.
-Come on.
Fine. At least, say cheers first.
Say cheers.
Cheers.
Mr. Chaudhary is coming.
Hide it quickly.
It was a mistake, son.
It won't happen again.
Mr. Chaudhary.
-Mr. Chaudhary. Focus on him.
-Hello.
-Greetings.
-Bless you.
-Is everything okay?
-Yes, everything is okay.
Why is everyone
calling him "Bapu"?
They are all orphans.
Mr. Chaudhary
pays for their education...
...and provides for their family.
Isn't he a generous man?
Actually, Mr. Chaudhary
killed their fathers.
What is this family?
Mukesh.
Wasn't there a bicycle
parked outside the main gate?
You know, Renu...
...the first time your mom
stepped in this house...
...she looked as beautiful as you.
Where's Dimpy?
Dimpy has donned Renu's jewelry
and has gone snap-happy.
Dimpy is thoroughly
enjoying Renu's wedding.
Go and call her.
Renu.
Brother, you're too much.
You can't stand her leaving,
can you?
You love her too much.
People from 36 villages
draw inspiration from you.
Why are you scared
of sending her away?
Renu, my dear.
Seek your dad's blessings.
What happened?
Don't be scared.
I have chosen you a fine suitor
after careful thought.
They are a reputed family.
You'll be showered with love...
...and soon you'll even forget
your father.
The wedding procession is here.
Time for the rituals.
Go on.
Get ready.
Close it!
Get lost!
Show her face!
Didn't you hear me?
Let's throw him in the fire.
How dare a teacher's son
elope with our daughter!
I didn't know Rakesh
would do such a thing.
If I had a clue...
...I would've killed him.
Get up.
Who is he?
Rakesh's friend.
Three years ago,
they studied together in Delhi.
-Come on!
-Whenever someone elopes...
...their friends definitely know.
-Who are you?
-What's going on?
-Hello! Who are you?
-Are you Jitesh?
Yes.
Bang, bang
Hi, I am Karan.
You must have heard my name.
I am an actor.
Bang, bang
Two serials, a few films.
Whoa, I quite like this music.
Nice club, huh?
What the--
Tell me, where is Rakesh?
-We don't know anything. Please.
-Tell the truth.
I beg you. Please hear me out.
Sir, please don't hit me.
Tell me, where is Rakesh?
-Speak up! We'll beat you.
-Please!
Tell us.
Tell me, where is Rakesh?
Speak up.
We don't know anything. Bablu....
Bablu knows.
Hold on.
Sir, please ask Bablu.
They said his name
so many times. Who is he?
That boy seems clever.
He's very cunning.
We sent our boys after him.
But he is never at home.
-Pick him up.
-Yes, brother.
Sukhi!
Get the cars.
Take a few more people along.
What did you say?
I said take a few more along.
Take a few more people along.
Is Bablu Superman?
No, he's an entire army.
Are you Bablu?
You didn't have to corner me
to ask that.
-Where can we find Rakesh?
-Which Rakesh?
Rakesh Gupta? Rakesh Tiwari?
Rakesh Roshan?
Which Rakesh?
The one who studied with you.
He eloped with our niece.
What are you saying?
Rakesh!
Rakesh eloped!
That calls for a celebration.
I must tell everyone about it.
Listen up.
This is Blackberry.
It doesn't miss.
It connects directly.
Don't push.
Mister, why use your hands
when we can talk?
Why? What will you do?
Will you hit us?
Hit us? Hit--!
I didn't think about it...
...but now I must.
So you want to be a hero?
Can't help it.
Others don't have it.
And I can't lose it.
Just tell us, lover boy.
Or else we'll waste you.
Fine.
Okay. I'll tell you.
Choose one.
Hold on. No one interferes.
I'll choose.
-I'll choose.
-Please.
Tenne, hurry up.
This one.
Where are you hiding those two?
Who hit me from behind?
Tell us, where's our daughter?
First, tell me
who hit me from behind.
Tell us.
Where's our daughter?
-Tell us where she is.
-Quiet!
Speak one by one. Or forget it.
Listen.
Your daughter ran away
from home, didn't she?
She didn't run away
to become a sprinter.
I'm sure she ran away
with the boy she loved.
She must've eloped.
She wouldn't have eloped...
...if you would've allowed her
to choose her groom.
He was showing
the same attitude back there.
I hit you in the head
from behind.
But here, I will knock your head off.
Enough.
Come on.
Give me Rakesh's address.
You want Rakesh's address.
Okay.
Let's do this.
Whenever he calls,
I'll ask him and let you know.
Give me your cell number.
What's wrong?
You don't have a phone.
Okay. I'll send a letter to you.
I'll leave now. Goodbye.
Wait!
Get one thing straight.
Until I find my daughter...
...you will stay here.
Get in.
Close the door.
Bablu.
You too?
With friends like you,
who needs enemies?
Who gave them my name?
He did.
Come on.
Bablu.
What happened?
Thank God you're here. Save us.
Don't be scared.
I am here now.
I won't let anything
happen to you, okay?
They ruined my face.
If you only get in touch
through Facebook...
...that's what's going to
happen to you.
-Darn it.
-You think this is funny?
-Darn you.
-Bablu.
Rascal!
We're in such a tough situation
and you're thinking about a reunion.
-Darn you.
-Let go!
Excuse me.
Can I join in too?
-Who are you?
-I am Kiki.
I live in London.
I came to India
for the first time.
I just asked these Jats for a ride...
...but they beat me up.
They brought me here.
It's all because of
his red trousers.
A shaman told the Jats
to find a man...
...wearing red trousers in the north...
...and that he might know
Rakesh's address.
Forget it.
-Kiki.
-Yeah?
-Do you know where Rakesh is?
-I don't know any Rakesh.
-How would he know?
-Yeah!
-We thought you did.
-I don't know.
-What?
-Darn it!
We are in big trouble.
I said so!
Back in college, I warned you
that he's a big flirt.
Fine, let's just
sit around here.
Listen. Listen.
You have to find a way out.
Please get us out of here.
-Yeah, please.
-Then choose one.
-Enough of you.
-Bablu, I've had enough.
May I choose?
No....
This one.
Good.
-Tomorrow, let's party at DU.
-He is at it again.
Like old times.
The same attitude again.
You know it, don't you?
Others don't have it.
-And you can't lose it.
-We know. We know.
But you don't know...
...that your hero
has found his heroine.
She was a moon-like beauty
But she was annoyed
She was a broken dream
And she was all yours
Somebody fulfilled
My shattered hopes
We met but you soon went away
Life seems dull
Without you
Who is she?
-What's her name?
-Where does she live?
That's all I don't know.
Everything else is all set.
-Excuse me. Excuse me.
-Darn it!
We were planning
to run away from here.
So, what is the position?
Simple.
There is a railway station
just outside this village.
We'll sneak out of here
tomorrow morning.
Next we get on a train.
We disappear and I'll tell you
the rest of the plan on the train.
-Listen.
-Yes?
Any plans on coming back here?
Are you crazy?
Why would we come back?
Some unfinished business.
Bablu, stop.
Who is it?
-You baldy!
-Darn it!
-Take this.
-Save me!
Move quickly!
Who hit me?
I won't spare you.
Who are you?
A drop of satiety's enough
To set my heart on fire
I missed you every moment
Somebody fulfilled
My shattered hopes
We met but you soon went away
Without you, life seems dull
Life seems dull
Without you
Hurry! The train is here.
-Where is Bablu?
-I don't know.
-He was right behind me.
-Bablu!
-Where is Bablu?
The train is leaving!
Someone stop it!
-Come on, Bablu!
-The train is leaving!
-Bablu!
The train has left!
Bablu, the train is leaving.
-What is he doing?
-Oh, no!
Bablu! Bablu, come here!
-Bablu, hurry!
-The train....
-The train is leaving!
-Bablu!
-Bablu, hurry!
-Hurry up! We'll miss the train.
-Please hurry!
Come on! Hurry up!
Oh, no! Gosh!
Get in the line.
Bhuppi, these are the fools
that escaped.
Fatso.
Scoundrel.
You....
Don't you dare touch anyone!
So you're the hero.
I'll burn you in the furnace.
No one will know
where you disappeared.
Rajjo, enough!
You're a big-time ruffian,
aren't you?
You were supposed to
watch over them, weren't you?
Am I right?
How did they escape?
These boys will die
sooner or later.
But I might end up killing you.
Darn it.
Don't ever think
of running away again.
Don't worry.
We won't leave
till you find the girl.
He has an attitude.
Let's see.
Enough of your big attitude.
Why did you stop?
I didn't stop. She stopped me.
-Who?
-That girl.
She lives in this village.
Bablu, this is the Jat Land.
It's forbidden to even think about
their girls.
I can find you one
if you come to London.
Now that I've met her...
...I don't need to meet
anyone else.
Have you lost your mind?
Maybe.
I don't know.
It feels like
everything has stopped.
You mean constipation?
-Will you shut up?
-Okay, okay. I'll shut up.
But what is the position now?
First, we must find out
who the girl is.
No.
This news shouldn't be out
in the newspapers.
Bless you, dear.
May you be successful
in your efforts today.
The teacher has relatives, right?
Keep an eye on them. Wait.
There was a shootout!
A few died on the spot.
It was fun.
Where is Daddy's
dearest girl going?
College.
To submit
my home science project.
Your sister submitted many
such home science projects.
Aren't you ashamed?
Your sister ran away
and you're going to college.
What nonsense!
Renu's the one who ran away.
Shut up!
Wild one. Go inside.
And no more college.
-Home science.
-No college....
Renu ran away and they stop me
from going to college.
Dimpy.
Listen to me.
Stop going to college.
Learn cooking.
Brother Rajjo,
don't you have a home?
-You always hang around here.
-Listen....
Don't call me brother.
Soon we'll be related
in a different way.
How's that?
Are you making me your mother?
I will make you
mother of my kids.
Dad, they stopped me
from going to college.
Everyone suspects...
...that I will run away like Renu.
No, my dear.
I trust you.
Renu wouldn't have eloped.
That boy misled her.
He seduced her.
How can my daughter elope?
Do you remember?
As little girls...
...both of you used to play
with my mustache.
I'd trim my mustache down...
...and you'd turn it up.
You couldn't stand to see
your father's mustache down.
I wish...
...my daughter had not eloped.
Dad, I'll never do
what Renu did.
Do you trust me?
So please let me
go to college.
What?
-Let's talk later.
-Dad, please....
Okay, Dad.
Go.
Yes, you were saying something.
Our custom says those
who indulge in love marriage...
...will be killed
by their own family.
My daughter didn't run away!
She was misled.
And if she has eloped willingly...
...I'll burn her alive.
You don't help me.
My uncles and aunts...
...had their fun
when it was their time.
But when it's my time,
they declared an emergency.
-Why?
Don't you have fun secretly?
What do I do?
I just lie to go to college.
I don't lie
to go around with boys.
Exactly. Don't you want to?
I don't have time
for such nonsense.
I have two years for myself.
To enjoy my freedom.
I have to finish my education
and learn dancing.
I want to become Miss Haryana...
...and then marry
whoever my dad chooses...
...and have a kid every year.
If I stop going to college...
...my two-year plan will be ruined.
I hope Renu gets caught...
...and her husband leaves her
on the night of their honeymoon.
I hope she comes back crying.
She is a witch.
She ran away
and left me in a coop.
I can't go to college.
You can go to college
only after Renu is caught.
Those boys know where Renu is
and they will never tell us.
Of course, they will.
I'll deal with them.
So, what is the position?
Good.
There are just 300 houses
in the village.
Finding the girl
won't be difficult.
There's a crematorium as well.
Your cremation won't be difficult.
Excuse me.
Hello, listen.
-English in Jat Land?
-Excuse me.
A girl?
Although I never entertain boys...
...now I have no option.
Just tell me where my sister is.
I'm not talking
to your thin waist.
-Show me your face.
-You....
Please tell me.
I won't tell anyone. Honestly!
Okay, listen.
Yes? Tell me.
Your sister....
Okay.
And her boyfriend.
The place
they are hiding is....
-We don't know.
-Gosh.
-You think you're a hero?
-I don't say that, but they do.
I can't stop everyone
from talking.
My entire family is in trouble
because of you.
Not because of me,
blame your father.
Don't you dare insult my father.
There isn't
a better man than him.
I see.
Why did your sister leave him?
Even if I tell you...
...you know what will happen
to them when they are caught.
So?
They ruined the family name,
so they'll be punished.
If they are wrong,
then who's right?
Me and my dad.
There's one more.
-Who?
-Me.
Then we should help each other.
I mean, both of us
are in trouble because of Renu.
Right?
-Then do one thing.
-Hold on. Please.
-Let me speak to her.
-Let him speak.
-Let's help each other. Tell me.
-Bablu.
Okay, I'll find your sister.
Okay.
-And you find that girl.
-Girl? Which girl?
He's in love with a girl
from your village.
Love?
Not yet.
But it could be true.
Who knows?
How dare you!
You want other families to be
ruined like ours.
Their families will even stop girls
from attending college.
-She is a radio.
-You're done for!
-You're a goner. I'll tell my dad.
-Fine.
-Go away.
-We'll deal with you.
-Stop!
-Hey, she is going.
It's not true.
You'll get us killed.
Paste this photo
on your chest
He's been here for just two days,
and already in love.
And look at his audacity.
He's asking for my help.
I felt like kicking him.
What are you doing?
Why did you fall on me?
-You kicked me.
-What's this?
-"My love, Renu."
-Love letter?
"My lips found yours...."
"Kiss."
"Love."
"Two bodies, one soul!"
Oh, my!
"Yours, Rakesh!"
Why did she hide it here?
Gather this quickly.
Someone might walk in.
Switch off the fan.
They're scattering everywhere.
Darn it.
Oh, no! We're done for!
This is serious.
Uncle Bhuppi found the letter.
Hide them!
They even kissed each other.
"Touch me! Touch me! Touch me!"
"Kiss me!"
Now isn't the time to enjoy them.
Hide them quickly.
Quickly.
What are you doing?
Where's Dimpy?
She must be in her room.
Why? What happened?
Here. Throw them away.
No. Burn them. Burn them.
-Who, me?
-No, me. Go quickly.
-Dimpy.
-Oh, no.
What's this?
-What?
-Your sister's love letter.
I see.
So that's how they look.
I never saw one.
Wait.
What's in that?
Nothing.
-Tenne.
-Sir.
-Check what's in the basket.
-Okay, sir.
What's in the basket?
-Nothing.
-Nothing?
It's nothing, just rubbish.
If I find out someone else
was involved...
...I'll shoot them.
This is amazing.
Love letters in the age
of mobile phones.
-How romantic!
-Show us.
Did you see that?
Rakesh was really desperate.
-Time to show off!
-Forget it.
Kiki, we can get out of here.
See these letters?
Watch how I act.
Call Suraj Singh Chaudhary.
Quiet!
Call your father.
These letters clearly indicate...
...that you played a role
in your sister's love story.
Now we'll teach you a lesson.
We'll tell you....
You will do
whatever we say.
-Listen to me. Please--
-We don't want to see all that.
God!
Look....
Don't try to blackmail me.
I haven't thought about it yet...
...but I'll blackmail you now.
But I had no clue
about Renu's affair.
But it's clearly written
in these letters...
...that you watched
English movies with them.
Sometimes.
You were given your sister's
pocket money to keep quiet.
Sometimes.
But I didn't know
she would run away.
I see.
Honestly, I didn't know.
So you're saying...
...that falling in love is right...
...but love marriage is a sin.
I get it now.
Whatever tarnishes family honor
is a sin. Idiot!
So why did you help Renu
run away?
That's not in the letters.
But what if I write it?
What nonsense!
God! You're such a rascal!
Liar, blackmailer!
But it's true...
...that you got a secret tattoo
on your body.
You also took modeling classes...
...to become Miss Haryana.
You also took salsa classes.
You were saying something?
Girl, village....
Can't we make a deal?
-What's the offer?
-Wait. Write it down.
I want a mirror.
I haven't taken a bath.
My face is ruined.
I have an audition tomorrow.
And I want a laptop
with Internet connection.
And--
-Three pairs of shorts.
-Shorts?
Ask for food.
Who cares about shorts?
Get some food
for this hungry dog.
Do we have Dominos over here?
And-- Do we--
Do we get to eat something?
And please give me my passport.
Please--
-Please get us free quickly.
-It stinks in here.
-Wait, one second.
-Listen, girl.
-Yes?
Think of a scheme...
...so that I get to see the face
of every girl in this village.
What's this nonsense?
I mean, I have no experience
in such cases.
-Now you will.
-He'll get us killed.
If Dad finds out,
he'll kill me.
Forget your dad
and think about me.
Think about the one I love.
By the way...
...what does she look like?
Her little brown eyes
Her kohl-lined eyes
When she smiles
I smile with her
I want to savor her
And I want to save her
From the evil eyes of this world
Oh, God
I plead to you
Show me a glimpse of her
Oh, God
I plead to you
I'll give up my life
For one glimpse of her
My friends
I don't know what's wrong with me
I am in and out of my senses
In a flash
I roam around
Lost and senseless
Please make me
Make sense of myself
My life has been
Meaningless so far
I've found a reason to live
I don't fall in love easily
Nothing can make my heart
Race so easily
Your eyes twinkle like stars
And you're like the moon
Who rises only at night
I want to burn and feel cold
At the same time
Under your burning gaze
Oh, God
I plead to you
Show me a glimpse of her
Oh, God
I plead to you
I'll give up my life
For one glimpse of her
Idiot, you make fun of my acting.
Why don't you try?
Okay, I won't. Stop hamming it up.
-What are you doing?
-Please.
Guys....
Choose one.
-I won't.
-Come on, please do it.
May I?
Okay. This one.
But what is the position?
-I am going.
-Where?
Chaudhary's house.
-Why didn't I think of it before?
-Listen.
Hold on.
What if we had chosen
the other one?
Then I would've talked
to Chaudhary directly.
You're crazy.
Why do you want to get us
in trouble all the time?
Let me tell you since
you're so desperate to hear.
I...
...love....
I love what?
I'm not in the mood.
Without Dimpy's love
Rajjo is sad
Shut up!
Dimpy was only in 5th grade
when I decided to marry her.
If her sister hadn't eloped...
...we would've been
enjoying our honeymoon.
I would be kissing her.
Mr. Chaudhary
has given his word.
What will I do with his promise?
Oh, God!
-Are we having a power outage?
-You're drunk, brother-in-law.
-Tenne.
-Sir, let me check.
-Are you done?
-Yes, sir.
The TV's switched off.
It was a nice song.
Without Dimpy's love
Rajjo is sad
Mr. Chaudhary
Doesn't listen to my pleas
-Where's the bottle?
-It's next to the glass.
Where's the bottle?
Empty.
The glass is empty.
Forget it.
Here. Have some cheese fritters.
Give me the fries.
Brother-in-law,
you're trying to fool me.
What are you saying?
There were some fritters left.
Right.
-Who said that?
-I did. What are you gonna do?
You slapped me.
Don't spit on me, man. Look
the other way when you talk.
-Nobody respects you.
-Go home.
-Brother-in-law, I'll teach you a lesson.
-Forget it.
Dear me
Baby
Hey.
Listen up, girl.
You didn't find that girl,
did you?
You're good for nothing.
I swear...
...I'll tell your father...
...that you had a role
in Renu's love story.
Now get up.
She couldn't even
find a girl.
-What are you doing here? Are you crazy?
-Who is it?
We had a power outage
at the wrong time.
Hey, Ms. Slim Waist.
Who was that?
You fool, that was Shalu.
Oh, yes.
Wait here.
Let me apologize to her.
What are you doing?
It's so dark in here.
You'll get us both killed.
Where are you?
You're drunk.
Maybe.
-Maybe? Where did you get it?
-It's fine. Come downstairs.
I'm coming.
Stay here.
-Don't move.
-Okay.
I'll be right back. Don't move.
I can't even see his face.
There's a power outage.
Did someone call the helpline?
We're the only ones having
a power outage in the entire village.
Sukhi, go check the meter.
Where did he go?
The water is chilly
What the...?
And the day is sunny
Shameless.
Come to the beach
And take my picture
Naked fellow, stop singing.
-I see.
-Gosh.
Sorry.
Did you come here
to take a bath?
I've been locked up in
that coop for so many days.
What if I find that
girl tomorrow?
He and his darn girl.
She won't like me.
Yeah, right.
What if she wants to take me
into her arms?
But you haven't found her yet,
you good-for-nothing.
Darn you.
It hurts.
Get away from here.
You'll get us killed.
-Here.
-What are you doing?
Here's something
that belongs to her.
-Find her in 24 hours.
-Fine, leave.
Or else I'll tell your father.
I know. Now, go
or we'll be in trouble.
I am going.
I don't know about her beauty,
but her figure is good.
Stupid fool.
Listen.
Put a lantern in Dimpy's room.
Sukhi. He was here.
-Who?
-That Bablu.
-Bablu?
-Yes.
He hit me again.
How? Like this?
The boys are locked up
in the shed.
You have been drinking too much.
Please, Lord,
help that crazy boy find the girl...
...and spare me.
Please. Please.
Please do it for me.
Take those guys out.
Throw them in the car.
Hurry.
Where are you taking us?
We're taking you to witness
your friend's death.
He had a knack
for eloping with girls.
How did you find out where he is?
The rascal called his mother.
He's hiding in Mohali.
Where will he run now?
Come on, move.
-Where are they?
-C Wing, 12th floor.
-Tenne.
-Yes, sir.
-Keep an eye on the boys.
-Sir.
Bro, I need to pee.
-What happened?
-Where did he go?
Forget it.
Let's take the stairs.
What are you doing?
-Where are you going?
-Who is he?
-Hey!
-Get down!
Bablu, what are you doing here?
I couldn't take the front door.
-Where's Rakesh?
-What's going on?
-Bablu?
-Bablu? What are you doing here?
We had a plan.
Why did you switch off
your phone at the last moment?
I didn't switch it off.
The guys from her family
broke it.
My family?
Sir, this side.
After you fled,
all of us were abducted.
Why did you call your mom?
Her family found out.
Reception committee's outside.
Open the door.
Open the door
or we'll break it open.
Renu, come on.
-Renu, come on.
-Renu, open the door.
You should go.
I will handle them.
-Bablu.
-Bablu, what are you doing?
You will fall down.
Bablu.
-Renu, careful.
-I will fall down.
Renu!
-Careful!
-Yes?
-Bablu!
-Go away!
-Who are you?
Pull her up.
Bablu!
Sir, this way.
Rajjo, search the balcony.
Where are they?
-I think they went to Goa.
-Quiet!
Come on, Renu, move.
Yes, sir?
Come on!
Stop! Stop!
Come on.
-Come on.
-Give me your hand.
Don't worry.
No need to be scared.
Just don't give up.
You two aren't wrong.
And yes....
Keep this.
Don't worry.
I'm here. I'll handle everything.
-Okay?
-Thanks, Bablu.
Listen....
Tell me something.
Are you two happy?
Yes.
Okay. No need to be scared.
I'll handle everything.
Okay? Don't give up!
Listen. Take care!
Take care.
He ran away.
-Sir, he ran away.
-I know.
-Why are you screaming?
-You know Bablu ran away?
Found an earring
Find those love letters.
Everyone is puzzled
What are you doing?
Are you crazy?
By God, what a love story!
Have you seen him?
How does he look?
Is he handsome?
I am not interested.
And anyway, he's the same guy
who has made my dad's life hell.
Come on. Move it!
Lock them up.
-Shalu.
-Yes.
What are you doing here?
Nothing. Just cleaning up.
The place is so dirty.
No need. Get lost.
-Get out!
-Sure.
-Get in.
-Go on.
Bolt the door!
-Bablu, you cheat!
-Forget it.
You knew where Rakesh and Renu were
all this time!
You knew when they'd elope
and about their hideout.
You knew everything.
Why didn't you tell us?
Why should I?
You ratted on your friends
when they slapped you twice.
Another blow...
...and you would've told them
about Rakesh and Renu.
But, Bablu, try to understand.
That girl has a family.
They must be worried.
I don't care about them.
Rakesh is our friend, that's it.
I want to see him happy.
I'm not a hero like you are.
-We're your friends too.
-I know.
And when the time comes...
...I'll help you guys
like I helped Rakesh.
Bablu, that's not what we meant.
Try to understand.
Idiots, people would swear
by our friendship.
If you can help us all
escape from here...
...why are you risking
our lives for that girl?
Do you want to die for her?
I haven't thought about it yet.
You have gone crazy
over that girl.
Someone please explain to him.
Are you so crazy for that girl
that you don't care about us?
He has gone crazy.
You'll get killed
and you'll drag us down with you.
That girl....
-She heard everything.
-Really?
-Who was she?
-Oh, no.
-Where is she?
-Stop her.
You're amazing.
You got all the letters.
Actually, that boy is amazing.
He's been helping
Renu and Rakesh.
He's been helping them
all along.
He knew when they'd elope
and where they'd go...
...and he also knew
their address.
He knew.
Who is he?
-I don't know.
-Who is he?
I don't know, Uncle.
Didn't you hear me?
Who is he?
I don't know, Uncle.
Get those boys out!
Come on!
-Come on! Tell us.
-Uncle!
-Who is he?
-I don't know.
Speak up!
-Who among them is the guy?
-I really don't know.
-It hurts.
-What?
So what if it hurts?
You only care about your pain.
Look! Look at your father!
He raised both of you
with such love and care...
...only to be humiliated like this.
I really don't know, Uncle.
Tell us!
One of you knows
where Renu and Rakesh are!
Tell us where they are!
Who among you knows about them?
Speak up or I'll shoot
each one of you!
-No!
-Speak up. Who is it?
-Is it him?
-Speak up!
-Get lost.
-Take him away!
-Look at him!
-Sir!
-Speak up!
-Sir, I don't know--
I haven't done anything.
Please.
-Speak up!
-Sir, forgive me. Let go of me!
-I don't know, sir.
-Get lost.
Please trust me.
I don't know anything, sir.
Is he the one?
Speak up, Dimpy.
Look at him!
Is it him?
It's not me, sir.
Is it him? Speak up!
We've been wandering around
all these days.
We've been going crazy. Speak up!
Is it him?
I don't know, Uncle.
I really don't know.
You know everything. Tell us!
Speak up!
Come on!
Is he the one?
Is he the guy?
Speak up, Dimpy!
Where have you hidden those two?
Speak up.
I swear, I'll skin you alive.
Where have you hidden those two?
Speak up!
Hey.
Why did you stop?
I was having fun.
He's so stubborn!
I'm still the same Suraj Singh
who murdered 18 people at night.
I'm helpless
because of my daughter.
If she'd been home,
I'd have killed her by now.
Have you thought about
why she isn't at home?
You're a good friend,
aren't you?
How much more beating
can you take for your friend?
How long can you beat me?
Kill him.
Not him.
So you want to be friends!
Let's see....
-Beat them up!
-Bablu, tell them, buddy.
Bablu knows.
Bablu, tell them!
-Bablu, tell them!
-Get up!
Bablu, they will kill us.
Bablu, tell them, buddy.
Sorry, sir.
Bablu, please, tell them, buddy!
Bablu, tell them!
Bablu!
Speak up!
They are in Delhi.
Delhi. Delhi, sir.
Life seems dull
Without you, without you
Come on. Move it!
Move it!
Put them in the car.
-Tenne.
-Yes, sir.
Idiot, you had to fall in love
with Chaudhary's daughter?
Please don't look.
Let him.
This love story's
going to end in two days anyway.
Come on. Hurry!
Yes.
We are leaving now.
Start the car.
Listen.
Do you love someone?
Tell me if you love someone.
Someone else will get beaten up
because of you.
You are talking nonsense
in front of Mr. Chaudhary.
There's nothing wrong.
We're all going to Delhi.
What if she elopes
behind our back?
History will repeat itself.
Be brave if you love someone.
Speak up.
-Time to teach you a lesson.
-Rajjo.
He is trying to instigate me.
Put him in the car.
Come on!
This hero attitude only looks good
on-screen.
In real life,
the villain always wins.
Understood?
Stop the car.
Let's take Dimpy along.
-Take Dimpy along?
-We'll take Dimpy along.
Dimpy!
A hero wins, even in real life.
Now the love story begins.
Just whistle with me
Everybody go
Baby, come be my lady
Why do you make me crazy, beautiful?
I love you every day
I'll hold your hand and take you away
Baby, come be my lady
Why do you make me crazy, beautiful?
I love you every day
I'll hold your hand and take you away
I worry about the world
I won't let you hold my hands
I'm afraid you'll make
Some excuse and go away
Don't talk about leaving
I want to marry you
Come to me, bring your lips together
And whistle with me
Just whistle with me
Why are you so worried, baby?
I am your life, baby
It's your chance
So hold me tight
Or else you'll lose it today
Come with me
I'll teach you everything about love
Get a hundred out of a hundred
And bring your lips together
And whistle
-Just whistle, just whistle
-Yo!
-Everybody in the party, just whistle
-Just whistle
-Yo!
-Just whistle with me
Dance with me
Keep my heart with you
My love
Girl, watch out
The boys are out to flirt with you
I won't give them a chance
I want to be yours
I won't find a crazy lover
Like you anywhere
If you want to do something
And move ahead in life
Come to me, bring your lips together
And whistle with me
Just whistle with me
God is great
Oh, my God.
We're in Delhi.
But what's the position?
Draft your wills, boys.
I didn't understand one thing.
You revealed their secret.
So now they will be caught.
They'd be caught
if they were in Delhi.
I lied to them.
You're such a scoundrel.
Friends are scoundrels.
And if they aren't,
they are not your friends.
They boarded the bus to Shimla.
These are the details received...
...from the other police stations
of Delhi.
Don't you want to confess?
Come on, tell me.
Inspector, this won't help.
Stop it.
-Hello, Mr. Chaudhary.
-Any information?
We've rounded up local
goons, gangsters...
...pimps, drug peddlers...
...from every nook
and corner of Delhi.
But we haven't gotten a clue yet.
-But we're trying--
-Trying?
Get lost!
I'm sorry.
Sorry.
Please, just find my daughter
as soon as you can.
Otherwise I won't
be sorry next time.
Please.
I am really scared.
Bablu, can't we run away?
-Here.
-Very good.
We won't run anymore.
We'll make the Jats run
from one end to another.
-How much are you going to eat?
-This is the first one.
The first one's
just like the last one.
Try the green chutney.
Forget the green chutney...
...or else they'll get married.
Hey.
Get to the point.
If I know Rakesh...
...he'll go to a temple
to get married first.
What did you say?
Let's go to the temple.
Community wedding!
I want to get married too.
Do you have a mind of your own?
You always want
something or the other.
God.
Please bring Renu back.
I'll curse the day if I find out...
...that Renu eloped willingly.
I beg of you.
Renu.
Listen....
What are you doing?
Are you crazy?
I haven't thought about it yet.
But I guess I'll go crazy now.
Do you know why
I brought you here?
Because no one dares
to tell lies here.
Honestly...
...I like you a lot.
And if you try...
...I guarantee you that
you'll start liking me too.
Are you showing me attitude,
even here?
I can't help it.
Everyone doesn't have it.
And I can't lose it.
Let go of my hand.
Okay.
-What's going on?
-Don't look at us.
Look at Lord Hanuman.
Wait, I'll tell Mr. Chaudhary.
-No.
-Tenne, come here.
-Why are you beating him?
-He's having a fit.
Then make him smell
leather boots.
-Do you have one?
-I do. I do.
-Then do it.
-No.
Search everyone properly.
Look at her face.
Please find someone else.
-I won't find anyone like you.
-Of course you will.
There are so many girls
in this world.
Make an effort.
That's what I am doing.
But I can't find anyone.
I am not handsome.
You are.
-Really?
-Yes. You're very handsome.
Really?
Look, you are tall.
-What are you saying?
-Your features are nice.
Anything else?
You have a good nose too.
What else do you want?
I don't have good lips.
They are fine.
No one's going to kiss me,
what's the point?
She will. Of course she will.
Will she?
Then what are you waiting for?
Darn this phone.
See! He held her hand.
Didn't I tell you
he held her hand?
What are you doing,
Mr. Chaudhary?
You left her all alone.
This place is teeming
with weirdos, you know.
Please hold on to her.
We couldn't find anyone here.
We looked everywhere.
If I know Rakesh...
...he might've gone to
the court to get married.
Let's check there.
Love commando,
you're acting too smart.
Stay within your limits.
I own brick furnaces.
Thanks for telling me.
You won't need a funeral pyre.
Brother, please sit here.
Sukhi and I'll go
and check inside.
Wait here. We'll go in
and make arrangements.
Please sit.
-Be comfortable, sister.
-We're comfortable, brother.
Why are you crying?
We'll be together forever
in no time.
The officer wants to know
where her parents are.
Tell him her father is busy
looking for us.
Don't cry.
Baby, it's no problem at all.
Excuse me.
Why is she crying?
She's missing her father.
Her father is a scumbag.
Sorry.
He makes millions,
drives a Mercedes.
But he is so narrow-minded.
Don't cry, my dear.
And who are you?
I drive her father's car.
I am her driver.
In fact, I was....
Her father used to
pay me peanuts.
He beat me up.
He said, "Why do you love her?"
I eloped with his daughter.
Now let him search. Right?
-Won't your father be worried?
-He will, for a few days.
He'll look for us
and go to the police station.
We don't care.
We'll already be off to Manali
for our honeymoon.
Don't worry.
He'll come back to me begging.
Later on, he'll welcome me home.
Where do you get the courage?
From friends. Best friends.
Love you, buddy.
Haven't you heard that saying?
'"Ghalib, no one can control love."
You must have,
it's a famous one.
By the way, what do you think?
Do you think the girl sitting next to you
will never fall in love?
Tell me, sister. Will you live
all your life with this man?
Is he your father?
Will you live with him?
Listen, her relatives
are looking for her.
Darn these relatives.
That's their nature.
They enjoy it
while the search goes on.
They snack till they drop.
Total fun.
Am I right, mister?
-Pull your stomach in.
-Rascal!
Do you think a court marriage...
...is the answer to your responsibilities?
Don't you have a conscience?
You eloped with the girl.
Didn't you think
about her parents?
And you? Do you like
hurting your parents?
You should be ashamed
of yourselves.
-And you--
-Brother...
...they are not in there.
Their application
isn't even in the register.
Shame on you.
Why are you crying?
Don't worry. That man's worried.
I love you.
Everything will be fine.
Without you, life is dull
Life is dull
Excuse me, mister.
Have you seen them?
No, sir. I haven't seen them.
Go away or you'll die.
Listen to me.
I told you. We have no future.
Thank God you told me.
Easy challenges don't excite me.
That's why I chose you
as my wife.
Here.
Marriage form.
I already signed it.
We're almost married.
Sign it and we'll be
all the way married.
What?
Mr. Chaudhary,
Renu is in that van!
Stop! You Idiot!
-Stop the van!
-Stop it.
Come out!
-Get everyone out.
-Out!
Get down! Hurry!
-You! Get down now!
-Keep moving. Keep moving.
Come on, get down.
Come out now!
-Renu!
-The last one, come out now!
Come on!
-Renu!
-Didn't you hear me?
-Get down!
-Renu!
Renu.
Get out of the way.
Why are you guys
forcing everyone to get out?
You just want to
trouble everyone.
Madam, forgive me.
I made a mistake.
It was a mistake.
Everyone makes one.
Let's go.
Dimpy. Dimpy.
There was a girl sitting here.
Did you see her?
-No, sir.
-Dimpy.
Mister, my daughter was sitting
right here. Did you see her?
She was wearing a blue dress.
-Dimpy!
-Look there!
Mr. Chaudhary,
it's your mistake.
Why did you bring her along?
You lost both your daughters now.
No! Let go of me! Save me!
Go away! What are you doing?
No! No! No!
Help! Save me!
Let go of my hand!
Save me! Help!
Leave me! Help!
God is great
Let me go! Help!
Let me go!
Save me! No!
Let go of my hand!
Let go of me! No.
Go away!
It's a small word.
Nahi  in Hindi.
"No" in English.
And no means no.
Bablu!
Without you, life is dull
Life is dull
Dimpy!
Search there!
Dad!
How dare you touch her!
How dare you!
Are you a kid?
Don't you know that
you should stay together?
What if something
had happened to you today?
-Stay within your limits.
-Rajjo!
Dress your wounds.
Come on.
Listen....
It was an eventful day.
I didn't even thank you.
What for?
For saving me.
No one can save you, Dimpy.
Your life's already over.
I never got along
with my father.
He would ask me to do something,
and I always said no.
Have you ever said no
to your father?
No, right?
Have you ever lived
the way you wanted?
No.
Your family treats women
like animals.
Have you ever revolted?
You have to fight.
That's how you get equality.
You just get one life.
Do you get it?
-We only live once.
-Bablu, I want to live too.
-But--
-No ifs and buts.
Be brave.
Admit to your father
that you love me.
But you love your dreams,
don't you?
Yes.
So choose one.
Choose?
Go ahead.
Let's stay up all night
Let's not go home
You're with me
What's there to worry about?
Let's not go home
Let's stay up all night
Let's go wherever we want to
We might not meet
Each other again
Let's live our lives tonight
This night
Let's stay up all night
Let's not go home
I wonder why this night
Wants me to change everything
The night wants me
To touch the sky
And live in the moment
Tonight
So let's get up
And walk and falter
Let's get up and fly
I'll lend you my wings
Let's live our lives tonight
This night
-Let's stay up all night
-Up all night
-Let's not go home
-Don't go home
Let's stay up all night
Let's not go home
Sir, this is the guest house.
Clean this mess
and leave Room 2.
Open Room 7.
Tell us where they have gone.
I never ask a man if he has eloped
with someone's daughter...
...or someone's wife.
I charge them by the hour.
That's all.
-Who are you guys?
-Hey!
Just tell us
where we can find them.
They ran out of money.
The girl pawned her
gold necklace.
After that,
she had nothing to offer.
But I asked her
to pay the rent first...
...or get out of here.
Who is going to pay me now?
Rascal!
Don't touch him.
How do you know it was them?
Did they look like them?
That's them.
It was them.
Now pay up.
Come on.
Do you want to die?
Come on!
-What's wrong with you?
-Come on!
What's wrong with you?
Sir. Sir, calm down.
-Come on!
-You should go home, Mr. Chaudhary.
-Everyone is looking for you.
-What home?
Yes.
The lodge where my daughter stayed.
You saw the lodge, didn't you?
This is where
he kept my daughter.
Is this why they eloped?
Is this what you call youth?
Don't we understand
their feelings?
Even I was young 25 years ago.
I was so arrogant.
I never listened to anyone.
No one. I never listened
to my parents or my wife.
But then I became a father...
...when Renu was born.
She was so small
when I first held her.
I quit all my vices.
I slogged away.
I became rich,
and people respected me.
I even learned English for her.
And then someone
took her away from me.
Love....
Is this what you call love?
They are broke.
That guy is not capable
of supporting them.
He got help from his friends
and eloped with her...
...and he thinks he is a hero.
Is this how you become a hero?
He sold her gold necklace
when he ran out of money.
And if they don't get along...
...will he divorce her?
But...
...I can't abandon my daughter.
I am a father.
I raised her,
took care of her for 20 years.
I've fulfilled every responsibility
of a father.
I wanted to get her married.
I wanted her to be happy.
But where's my daughter?
Where is she?
I have lost her.
My reputation is tarnished.
I've lost everything.
I want my daughter back.
Where's my daughter?
The day I find her...
...I'll kill her.
I'll kill her
right then and there.
Listen....
Do you think
they will be caught?
I don't know.
You know...
...earlier even I wanted them
to be caught.
But everyone has a right
to make their own decisions.
I should too.
Because we only
live once, right?
Do we have to run away
like them?
I can't tell my dad...
...but I'll tell you.
I love you.
I love you, Bablu.
Renu!
Renu, stop!
-Start the car.
-Renu!
Renu!
Stop the bus!
-Dad?
-Renu!
Stop the bus!
Dad.
Renu!
Renu, stop!
-Renu!
Renu, come on!
-Come on!
Beat him!
Let him go.
Leave him!
No, Dad, don't beat him!
-No!
-Move it!
Come on!
-Move.
-Try hitting me now.
Let go of them.
Dad, please spare him.
Move back!
Don't touch them!
Sir, please forgive them.
Mr. Chaudhary,
please forgive them.
-Move away.
-Dad, please!
Dad, let him go.
-Sir, please hear me out.
-Don't you dare!
Don't you dare touch him!
I'll file a complaint
with the police.
He's my husband.
Had I told you,
would you let me marry him?
Why don't I have the right
to make a decision for myself?
Why?
Dimpy....
Tell me, what was my mistake?
Is it a crime
to fall in love?
Why don't you let us
live in peace?
You've been chasing us like dogs.
Like dogs! Why?
-Renu!
-No!
She's right.
I am a dog.
We're all dogs.
You ran away from home.
I was worried about you
the whole time.
I was worried whether
you were all right.
I've been roaming from one city
to another looking for you.
I fought with so many people.
I barked at them
and I snapped at them.
I am a dog.
Thank you for reminding me
of who I am.
I thought I was your father.
But I am just a dog
who is worried for his daughter.
I am a dog.
Dog.
Forgive me, my dear.
I was wrong.
I am a dog. Forgive me.
Enough, Renu.
Now apologize to him...
...and say that he kidnapped you.
Say it!
Your life will be spared.
Or else you know our law.
Say it.
Brother, please turn around.
Sit down. Sit down.
Didn't you hear us?
Lower your heads.
Look at your shoes. Look down!
Look down!
Dad...
...I am pregnant.
You are dead to me.
Now I have just one daughter.
Yes, we are about to return.
Dimpy, get in the car.
Bablu....
Sorry for the way
we treated you.
You are not my enemy.
I just love my daughter
too much.
Please don't say that.
If you get the time...
...do attend Dimpy's wedding.
Kiki, here's your passport.
Now you can go on
an adventure tour.
-See you, buddy.
-Kiki.
Goodbye.
Let's forget our differences.
I spared your life
because of Chaudhary's presence.
Otherwise I would've
burned you in a furnace.
Bablu, it's all right.
It's all right.
O, God
Why are you angry with me?
I wonder what mistake I made
My life went astray
When I got separated from you
I'll destroy myself
Kohl burns in my eyes
I can't wear my stubborn bangles
My bangles will jangle
Only in your presence, my beloved
I don't want to get decked out
Without my beloved
I wonder what mistake I made
My life went astray
When I got separated from you
I'll destroy myself
Just tell us one thing.
Can you live without her?
Let's go, then.
Let's abduct her.
Come on.
Clitter-clatter
The train chugs along
-Hold on, stop the train.
-Red signal.
Where's Dimpy?
How many times are
you going to ask, Grandpa?
Let's go play.
Come on. Come on.
I always thought...
...that I'd be safe in my home.
But today....
Today I am feeling scared.
Dad took me to Delhi...
...because he didn't trust me.
But I was determined...
...to never do
what Renu had done.
But when I left Bablu,
I realized why Renu eloped.
In this family, a girl child
is killed right after birth.
Dad didn't kill us then...
...but he is killing us now.
What should I do, Shalu?
Pappi, the guys from Delhi
are back!
-Brother, look who's here.
-Wow!
We treated you badly,
but you guys are here.
Good, very good.
So far, you've only
witnessed our fury.
It's time you see our love.
That's what we're here for.
Come on, please come inside.
You look so happy.
Yes.
He is here now.
I am not scared anymore.
Bhuppi, where's that boy?
Stop him.
-The wedding procession?
-No.
Bablu....
Bablu? Why him?
Forget it. I'll check myself.
-Where are you going?
-Nowhere.
Where are your friends?
They must be around
here somewhere.
Are you looking for someone?
Actually, I--
You're free, aren't you?
Come on. Let's talk.
Bablu, how about a cold drink?
He'll drink it later on.
Offer it to someone else.
Come on.
Have a seat.
Sit down.
-I--
-What pleasant weather.
Everyone's really happy.
He is a very nice guy.
He comes from a reputed family.
-If you--
-What about your family?
-Parents?
-They are fine.
I didn't expect you
to drop in like this.
But you did the right thing.
Because everyone's busy
with the wedding preparations...
...and I am all alone.
Now that you're here,
I could use some company.
Stay with me till the send-off.
Till the send-off. Please.
Will you stay with me?
My hand.
Sorry.
Listen....
-Is everything ready?
-Yes.
I've given the message
to Shalu the maid.
She'll deliver it to Dimpy.
There you are.
I've been looking
all over the place.
The guests are about to arrive.
Go and get changed.
And leave him alone?
The poor guy is alone.
He's here to attend the wedding,
not to chat with you. Come on.
Go, I'll just have
a chat with him.
You see...
-...the groom--
-He isn't going anywhere...
-...till the wedding is over. Come on.
-No, no.
The guests are about to arrive.
Come on.
-I'll be right back.
-Come on.
Not this one. Yes.
Brother, your turban.
-Do you know where he is?
-I don't know.
-Bablu.
-Where's Dimpy?
-We're looking for her.
-I have no idea.
Forget it.
Look over there.
I will. Relax. Just relax.
Bablu.
Has anyone seen Dimpy?
Remember you always said...
...that you stopped
because you saw me.
You inspired me to live my life.
I started flying.
I started living.
How do I tell Dad...
...that I want to live my own life?
He knows everything.
Oh, my God!
So, what is the position now?
Their position
is worse than ours.
-Dear, did we get laddus?
-Hurry! Let's go.
Hey....
What happened, Dad?
Why are you staring
at me like that?
Nothing.
You took such good care of me.
Yes.
You've always been there for me.
Today you're sending me
to a place...
...where you won't be with me.
But your decision must be right.
I can see my entire life, Dad.
But I will manage somehow.
Don't worry, Dad.
What happened, brother?
She has to leave someday.
Enough.
Get up.
Get her ready.
You know what's going on
in my house.
My daughter's getting married.
And you are also aware...
...that a boy eloped
with my elder daughter.
And now, you....
Why are you here?
Be honest.
You came here to elope with
my younger daughter, didn't you?
Eloping isn't difficult,
Mr. Chaudhary.
Nor am I scared.
When Renu ran away...
...I was amused
that you were troubled.
But when I saw you...
...I gradually realized
what a father feels...
...when his daughter runs away.
Today when I noticed
your plight...
...I was really scared.
I never thought
like this before.
I was happy.
I was always happy.
But today....
Today, I am sad.
There is no one.
I have no one
to share my pain.
No one can understand either.
But you can understand.
The other day Dimpy
went missing for 20 minutes...
...and I was worried to death.
Later I realized
Renu was missing for 20 days.
Do you know what's going on
in this house?
The girl I love
is getting married.
And she is also your daughter.
You want no trouble
at the wedding...
...and I want to stop
this wedding at all cost.
You want to save your honor...
...and I want to save my love.
We're sailing in the same boat.
No one loves Dimpy like you do.
But if there's anyone
who comes second...
...that would be me.
I came here to take her away.
But I'm not going to elope
with your daughter.
Bablu, what are you doing?
When it was time to act,
you got scared.
One needs courage to do
what I am doing.
Chaudhary knows Dimpy loves you.
Still he's getting her
married to Rajjo.
This is wrong.
Fathers are not always wrong.
Love commando.
Where are you going?
As soon as I got the news
that you were here...
...I came here to welcome
you personally.
You came here to attend
Rajjo's wedding, didn't you?
So you've got to have something.
Choose one.
What would you like
to have, this or this?
Please let us go.
This time, you won't
leave this place alive.
You've come unprepared.
You've got only
three boys with you.
Kill him!
Let him go!
Don't beat him!
Bablu!
Please spare him!
Please let him go.
Bablu!
-Bablu!
-Where's all the attitude you had?
That's it?
Where's all the attitude you had?
I'll put an end to you here.
And back there, it'll be
Dimpy's opening ceremony.
You....
-Bablu, kill him.
-Beat him.
-Bablu, beat him up.
-Don't spare him.
Beat him.
Bablu, kill him.
Finish him off.
Finish him off!
Stop!
Mr. Chaudhary--
What's so special about you?
Why does Dimpy love you?
I can't understand.
The wedding procession
is at the gate...
...but I'm standing here.
Why?
Because you love
your daughter a lot.
I don't want to
take away your right...
...to decide whom she marries.
If her future husband...
...troubles her in any way...
...I won't spare you.
If her future husband
troubles her in any way...
...I won't spare you.
Go on.
Take her away.
Brother, what about
our family honor?
I just want to see respect
in Dimpy's eyes.
You mean love marriages
are okay in the Jat Land?
If the boy is worthy,
then we don't have a problem.
Brother,
I am having an affair too.
-Me too, sir.
-Sukhi, you....
Bless you, son.
Please forgive Rakesh
and Renu too.
Yes.
So you got a hero attitude.
I can't help it.
Others don't have it
and I can't lose it.
This is the kiss song
Anything will do
Black or white
Anywhere will do
Left or right
Let's not fight
For the season of love is here
Set your lips
And wet both the cheeks
Give a kiss to get one in return
For this season of love
Don't be so sad, sad
It's time to be happy
If you're feeling bad, bad
Come and take a free kiss
Don't be so sad, sad
It's time to be happy
If you're feeling bad, bad
Come and take a free kiss
This is the kiss song
Don't be so sad, sad
It's time to be happy
If you're feeling bad, bad
Come and take a free kiss
Don't be so sad, sad
It's time to be happy
If you're feeling bad, bad
Come and take a free kiss
I've washed my face
And cleaned my cheeks
Give me a kiss
And bring pink to my cheeks
Dry or wet kiss
Give me a kiss and make my life
The coast is clear, so play
You know what I mean
What is the scene?
What are you waiting for?
Making me wait
Why don't you kiss me now?
Are you upset with me
Or do you got an attitude?
Why do you giggle
And have all the fun?
This is the kiss song
Don't be so sad, sad
It's time to be happy
If you're feeling bad, bad
This is the kiss song
Don't be so sad, sad
It's time to be happy
If you're feeling bad, bad
Come and take a free kiss
Don't be so sad, sad
It's time to be happy
If you're feeling bad, bad
Come and take a free kiss
This is the kiss song
Don't be so sad, sad
It's time to be happy
If you're feeling bad, bad
This is the kiss song
Don't be so sad, sad
It's time to be happy
If you
Don't be so sad, sad
It's time to be happy
-If you're feeling bad, bad
-This is the kiss song