SALAM.
Hello.
Hello. - Hello.
I told you not to kill him.
He's still alive.
Look.
Chocolate.
Grade four semtex.
That one alone is enough to blow up this factory.
And he's carrying six of them.
If I don't speak up you will kill me.
And what if I do?
You want a medal.
Son of a witch.
Some money and safe passage to the border.
I can tell you a lot, sir.
There's an electrician working outside..
.. he is also a RAW agent.
Where are you taking me? - Come on.
Sir, why have they brought me here? - What is your name?
Najeeb Khan. From Liaquat Bazaar, Quetta. What's wrong, sir?
I've been working here for the past three months as a welder.
What is wrong, sir?
What is wrong? - Major Rajan Sinha.
1 Bihar Regiment.
Take off his shirt, and look for yourself.
Two bullet wounds on the left shoulder.
Come here.
He's the guy who shot Usman Gul in POK last year.
Come on.
Take him away.
Another RAW agent is active in this area.
Will you untie my hands, please?
Shall I strangle you?
Your name please?
One of your guards..
He gave me all the dope about this place.
My guard?
Who?
Real name is Mahendra Sandhu.
Cover name.. Abdul.. Abbas..
I don't remember.
Which one?
$50,000 and safe passage to the border. - Done.
The fifth guy.
What is your name? - Ismail Yusuf Bashar.
Your full name.
Ismail Yusuf Bashar.
Take off his pants.
You'll find two Bullet wounds on the bum. Got it in Kargil.
What are you doing?
Who Mahendra Sandhu? I am Ismail Yusuf Bashar. He's lying.
He's lying, Colonel.
Leave me.
Lower your weapons. Down.
Put your magazines in this, now.
Now move.
Move.
Lock it.
Open it.
Only Rashid knew the code.
Take a guess.
Lucky guess.
If I survive I'll give you a slow death.
Every dog has his day.
Where is my partner?
What if Huzefa had killed me?
They'd have given you a medal.
.. and your wife a petrol pump.
Any last wish.
Yes, I want to kick your behind.
Send a unit to factory no.10. Immediately.
Start the car.
"There's word on the streets."
"There's a guy in the city."
"Forget the barricades."
"He has sneaked in."
"Things that are impossible to do."
"He's here to make them possible."
"He can turn night into day."
"So what's his name?"
"What is it?"
"He's here to turn the tables on you."
Stop the car.
Let me get down.
"He's here to take on countless enemies alone."
"He always does his duty."
"As a responsibility."
"He can turn night into day."
"So what's his name?"
"What is it?"
Peshawar.
I hope you enjoyed the flight.
Thank you.
My name is Farah Feqqesh.
What's your name?
"Call him Govind."
"Call him Gopal. Call him anything. Call him Hari."
"Call him Gopal. As long as he's there, nothing to worry."
"Call him Govind."
"Call him Gopal. Call him anything. Call him Hari."
"Call him Gopal. As long as he's there, nothing to worry."
"Call him Govind."
"Call him Gopal. Call him anything. Call him Hari."
"Call him Gopal. As long as he's there, nothing to worry."
"Call him Govind."
"Call him Gopal. Call him anything. Call him Hari."
"Call him Gopal. As long as he's there, nothing to worry."
"Call him Govind."
"Call him Gopal. Call him anything. Call him Hari."
"Call him Gopal. As long as he's there, nothing to worry."
Not... Not..
Arms dealer found dead in a graveyard outside Moscow.
Early this morning.
The murder of Russian arms dealer Andre Sukhorov..
.. has again thrown up this dangerous question.
Did Sukhorov possess a suitcase nuclear bomb?
And if so, where is it?
Both the United States and Soviet Union..
.. have acknowledged producing nuclear weapons..
.. small enough to be carried in specially designed backpacks..
.. during the cold-war.
These bombs, identified in Russia as KV series..
.. have the explosive power between..
.. Three and Ten kiloton of TNT.
The bombs at Hiroshima and Nagasaki..
.. were 20-30 kiloton each.
But the value of the suitcase bomb lies..
.. in its ability to be easily smuggled across borders..
.. transported by means widely available.
And placed as close to the target as possible.
A single suitcase bomb can devastate..
.. three kilometers of a modern city.
It will kill everything within a ten kilometer radius..
.. and the radiation will subsequently kill more.
Gentlemen Sukhorov is dead
I've heard the bomb is up for sale
This is what every terror group in the world is looking for.
This could start World War 3.
If this gets into the wrong hands, millions will be killed.
I was thinking billions.
Comrades!
It's my friend Dmitri's birthday.
So we all have a drink, okay.
Make drink.
You wanted to meet in a public place.
Abu Nazir has turned a public place, private.
I am impressed.
I've chosen the right man.
I need $50 million cash in three days, in Morocco.
So much in so little time.
Do you know my commission?
Do you know what I need it for?
India?
I need the money in three days in Morocco.
Do you have a contact who can be trusted?
I know the right man for the job.
I will give you $50 million cash, tomorrow.
All he has to do is buy 242.
242?
Abu, before talking about 242..
.. can you tell me how many calories there are in one potato chip?
20.
And how many chips did you eat just now?
I am sorry, I am a health freak.
And this can be.. dangerous for your health.
Comrades.
Come. We take drink.
Bring champagne.
This is Colonel.
My partner and friend. - Hi.
Five man army. - Yes.
When I was a child..
.. I watched a movie called 'The Five Man Army'.
Your boss Abu, reminds me of Bud Spencer.
Japanese. You'll slap me if I tell you the meaning.
What do you mean?
Hello, Vinod. - What's wrong, sir?
Recognize him?
Abu Sayyed Nazer.
Area of operations, St. Petersburg.
Main business, drugs, prostitution.
Also money laundering.
Single point contact between the Russian mafia..
.. and terror groups like Lashkar.
Rajan is handling this, right?
Rajan posed as his bodyguard for the past three months.
He had managed to get very close to him.
Had?
Last night Rajan sent this message.
Code Red.
Falcon 77 to Hasan Nawaz sir.
Sir, I've been exposed.
Abu has joined hands with some Colonel.
I don't know who he is.
They were discussing
about a large amount of money
They were planning a big strike against India.
During the discussion..
.. the number 242 kept coming up.
242 means something. I don't know what but..
This has all the data about Abu.
Your contact in St. Petersburg is Tatiana Renko.
Go find out why Rajan was killed.
What is 242?
Air India announces the arrival of..
..flight no. AI 6536 to St. Petersburg
Hi, my name is Jugal Kishore.
Welcome to St. Petersburg.
Where can I find Abu Nazer?
David Goliath 92754655A.
Here, Freddie. - Yes, sir.
Whether he's asleep. - Okay.
Or in a meeting. Or the toilet. - Okay.
Wait for him. - Okay.
Hand this over to him personally. - Okay.
Who? - Mr. Kazan.
Once more. - Mr. Kazan.
"I'll do the talking tonight."
"Let's talk about love."
"Let's freak out."
"Whatever has happened.. "
".. is the past."
"What you've right now."
"This is your moment."
"Steal the night and have a good time."
"Why are you sitting alone?"
"Feel the vibe and get into the groove."
"Live every moment."
"Blow away your sorrows."
Show.
Drink for all.
Victor, sit. You're not dead.
How about a game with me?
If you win, she's yours.
Come here, baby.
You haven't seen my cards yet.
I have three aces. Are you blind?
"I'll do the talking tonight."
"Talk something"
"Make fun"
"Whatever you lost."
"Is the punishment for your pranks."
"If you have lost it unintentionally."
"Then come, have a good time."
"Do it with your lips."
"Why are you sitting alone?"
This gun has real bullets.
"Live every moment."
Rajan Sinha, whose corpse was found on the tracks outside Moscow..
.. was a friend of mine.
Be sure, your corpse will never be found.
No last wishes for you, my friend.
What is 242?
Nikolai!
Call the others!
Call them now! - Stay their Nikolai!
Here is an easier question?
Recognize this song?
Stop! Stop! Stop!
One ear drum and one stanza to go..
What is 242?
The Colonel asked me to send $50 million to Kazan.
The courier is leaving for Morocco tonight
Freddie Khambatta.
Flight EK 309.
What is 242?
242 is the size of Abu's bazooka.
Wanna see?
Would you like to come home for coffee?
Sorry my dear. Got a flight to catch.
There are ten emergency exits on this aircraft.
They are all clearly marked.
In an emergency the floor path lights will illuminate..
.. and guide you to the nearest exit.
Would you like some water?
Sorry. - I am so sorry.
I am so sorry. I am so sorry.
Mr.. Freddie Khambatta. - Yes, sir.
So sorry.
I loved your perfume.
I.. I.. I am on duty, sir.
I am not allowed to wear perfume.
100% natural.
Love it. - Thank you, sir.
Thank you so much, sir.
Are you okay? - Yes, I am perfect.
Thank you.
Taxi. Taxi. Taxi.
Hindi. Indian. Indian. Indian.
Shoot the rascal.
Move aside.
Zilleh.
Zilleh, my darling.
My dear!
Zilleh.
Mr. Freddie Khambatta?
Hello sir.
Abu sent this, for you.
Drink, Mr. Freddie?
Sure.
How is my friend Abu?
He's on cloud nine.
Your first visit to Morocco? - Yes.
Welcome to Morocco.
What are you doing, Mr. Kazan?
Abu said deliver the note to Kazan..
.. and collect $10,000.
What the hell are you injecting me with?
Abu was murdered last night - What?
Who are you? - I am Freddie Khambatta, sir.
Increase the dose!
What the hell?
Relax. Don't be afraid.
Tell me your name?
Freddie.
Who killed Abu?
Don't hit him so hard.
Ask him?
What is your name? - Freddie.
What's your mother's name?
Shirin. - Where does your mother live?
She lives in Baroda.
What does your mother do in Baroda?
What does she do?
She is a school teacher.
Fourth grade.
Arya Vidya Mandir.
What does your mother call you?
Look here Look at me.
What does she call you when she's angry?
What does your mother call you when angry?
Tell me!
What does she call you?
Vinod. - Vinod?
Is your name Vinod?
Vinod.. Khanna.
Amar.
Rishi Kapoor, Akbar.
Amitabh Bachchan, Anthony.
I saw the film with my mummy in Apollo Talkies.
My name is Anthony Gonsalves.
I am all alone in this world.
What is he blabbering? Increase the dose.
Just relax. Stop.
Sit.
Who killed Abu?
Who are you? - Who killed Abu?
Tell me! - Who are you?
Who killed Abu?
tell me. - Who are you? - Relax.
Who are you?
I..
I am a RAW agent.
I killed Abu.
"Ra Ra Rasputin, lover of the Russian queen."
"It was a shame how he carried on."
"Ra Ra Rasputin,..
Did you get the money?
Forget the money.
Do you know what you said?
What did I say? - You killed Abu.
You are a RAW agent.
Did I say that?
How much Pentothal did you give me, madam?
50 ml. - Thanks.
Yes I killed Abu..
.. because he had a RAW agent working under his nose.
His bodyguard.
Mahim Murtaza.
Real name Rajan Sinha.
Who do you work for?
You know we're not supposed to take names, right?
Abu slipped up.
And I was sent here to check if..
.. David Kazan too is slipping up.
But look what you did to me?
Bravo, Mr. Kazan.
Can I get a towel, please?
I got the money but..
.. there's something fishy about this Freddie
Shall I kill him?
Why don't you stay the night?
What is on your mind, Mr. Kazan?
Who is that doctor?
Ruby Mendes.
My personal doctor.
Ruby Mendes. Nice name.
Did you give her that name? - Meaning?
Bathroom. - What?
Bathroom?
Thank you.
I am so sorry, madam.
Excuse me.
You should have told me someone's inside.
Who is it? - I don't know.
Some lady.
She's sitting on the commode, reading a magazine.
There is no one here.
What?
She was right here..
Where did she disappear?
She was reading that magazine.
She was wearing a blue kaftan. Big necklace around the neck..
.. and a strange tattoo here.
She was right here.
It was her.
My mother.
She passed away 22 years ago.
What?
What the hell did you inject me with?
You need rest, Mr. Freddie.
Rest.
Show him to his room.
Goodnight, Mr. Kazan. - Goodnight.
Hello, Dr. Ruby.
If you're feeling dizzy then take these pills..
And eat something.
I had two bottles of water.
Yet everything looks 3D.
Drink? - No, thanks.
Kazan told me that you saw his mother.
I think I saw a ghost.
Do you believe in ghosts?
What nonsense.
39 dead.
Don't they haunt you?
The ghosts of those who died in the London blast.
I am impressed.
You escaped from a British jail.
.. have been evading Interpol.
I am impressed..
Miss Iram Parveen Bilal.
Iram Parveen Bilal is dead.
My name is Ruby.
Goodnight, Freddie.
Does he know about the spycam?
He knows about me.
Yes.
A tourist group has just landed from London.
There's an Ml6 agent amongst them.
Maybe he knows about 242.
I am going out for a walk.
If you want to keep an eye on me..
.. then send Dr. Ruby along..
Here.
I don't think you exploded that bomb..
Why do you say that?
You have killer eyes..
But they're not the eyes of a killer.
Tell that to my London court judge.
You know everything about me.
Tell me something about yourself.
I cannot lie.
And you'll catch me if I tell the truth.
I am in the same business as you.
But why are we talking shop
.. in a romantic place like Tangier?
If you weren't so serious..
.. I would've invited you to dinner this evening.
And cooked for you too.
I am a good cook.
What's on the menu?
Wow. That means yes.
Well, that's a Kodak moment.
May I take a picture, madam?
Excuse me?
Excuse me? - Yes?
Do you speak English? - Yes.. yes.
Can you take a photo of me and my wife, please?
Okay. - How is Freddie? - very happy
Richard Maibaum, British Agent.
He's the Ml6 agent in-charge of the Middle East sector.
Something's happening.
Where can I find him? - Hotel Rif Spa.
Room no. 430. I am sending you a photo.
Understood. Understood.
Photo?
Not good here.
Fountain. - Okay. - Madam, fountain please.
Ready.
Smile.
Thank you. - Enjoy your honeymoon.
Shall we?
Have lunch.
I know a nice place.
Hotel Rif Spa.
"Your deep blue eyes."
".. with secrets hidden within"
"Praise the Lord for creating one such as you"
How many girls have you said this to?
Including you? 242.
You've brought $ 50 million to buy 242.
Do you know what 242 is?
What did Kazan tell you?
Excuse me, madam.
The menu.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
I am not feeling well.
I have to go back.
Of course, no problem.
I hope you will come with me to the auction this evening.
There are some other bidders but don't worry. I'll get 242
Sir Jagdeshwar
Thank you, Ladies and Gentlemen..
.. for your most generous contributions.
I am going to match the sums that have been raised here today..
.. and this money will help in building schools and hospitals..
.. in this lovely, this great country. - Good evening, Sir.
Your face reassures me that all is well.
242. The Rubaiyat of Omar Khayyam.
Poems on love and destiny written in the 11th century.
Very nice.
Good luck.
Why did you get him here?
He got me here. - ..through this lovely country through the..
..Humprey Bogart film Casablanca..
I should be keeping a watch on you instead.
This is the beginning. - Found this in Richard's room.
You must have dropped it in a hurry.
No, I didn't. When did you flick this?
And who is Richard?
Relax, we're on the same side.
Next item is a YU Rain mask.
An emblem of the YU tribe.
Please.
Hello.
I am Jagdish.
Great honour to meet you Sir.
Freddie Khambatta. Dr. Ruby Mendes.
From India? - India.
Pakistan.
Sworn enemies..
Can become great friends too.
Are you here for anything special?
She's interested in the Rubaiyat.
And I am interested in her.
I see.
Two hundred dollars.
Yes this choosen.. two hundred thousand dollars.
Excuse me.
Five thousand dollars.
Thank you very much. so have two fifty thousand dollars.
Hello, prince.
What are you doing here?
Where is Daya Master?
I thought the Tigers were finished.
What are you doing here?
Tell me. - Item no. 242.
Since when did you start reading poetry, Prince?
What is 242?
The next item is lot no. 242.
A collection of love poems from Persian poet Omar Khayyam.
The opening bid for this will be $75,000.
$75,000 from the gentleman at the back.
Thank you very much.
$90,000. $125,000.
$400,000. $450,000.
Come on, prince. Come on.
$500,000, going once.
It's a bomb. - Going twice.
KV series, Russian.
Nuclear bomb?
Sold. Lot no. 242, the Rubaiyat of Omar Khayyam..
.. sold to Mr. David Kazan for half a million dollars.
Excuse me.
It most buy of the sold interit conection..
Where were you, Mr. Khambatta?
Ruby and the Rubaiyat are both gone.
Thank you.
For activation, in those days
.. the command validation of a Russian satellite was required
But we have made changes.
You need to enter a password that's all..
.. that is required for activation.
This Rubaiyat of Omar Khayyam is the detonator.
Don't lose it.
So, my congratulations, Mr. Kazan. - Thank you.
And thank you, Dr. Rana, for your contributions. - Thank you.
What time is flight, Dr. Rana?
Cheers. - Cheers.
Dr. Rana, this is the best champagne in the world.
And you are drinking water.
His job was done.
Can you take care of him?
Freddie Khambatta.
I am Colonel.
Why are you standing here?
Join the party.
Party's over, Colonel.
The party's just begun.
If you see my mother again..
.. then tell her I said Hi.
Whoever he is, get rid of him.
Hello, my dear.
The pipeline goes through this lane..
.. and we have an observation post every 10 kilometers.
Sir, there's a call for you.
Hello.
Hello, Mr. Nawaz.
Hello, Mr. lftekhaar.
I can hear raging fire and roaring rain.
You are in Chaman.
Impressive, Mr. Nawaz.
Even at this age, you still have keen ears.
I can even hear what's happening in Morocco.
I just heard that David Kazan has bought a nuclear bomb.
What? Where did you get this news from?
Mr. Nawaz, you will have to share your source with me.
Because if there's any truth in this..
.. then we'll need to cooperate.
Tell me, General.
Are you involved?
I have no idea.
I didn't know at all.
If I had any clue about this..
.. then I would have called you myself.
Look, Mr. lftekhaar, whatever the problems between us..
.. this cannot be the solution.
Thank you very much.
Give me 12 hours. I will call you back.
Goodbye.
Cancel the inspection.
We will return to Islamabad right now.
Cancel my trip to China.
And call an emergency meeting..
.. of all the section chiefs tomorrow.
Specially section Q, okay.
Fine.
Take lftekhaar sir's convoy to the Turkhum border..
.. and blow it up with a launcher.
I'll keep you posted, sir.
Breaking news.
ISI chief lftekhaar Ahmed killed in a bomb blast.
Is this Zaheer's home?
This is Zaheer's home, but he is on the terrace.
Thank You! - You're welcome
Who are you? - I am Freddie.
Freddie Khambatta. - What?
Yes. I am Freddie.
If you are Freddie then who is he?
So you were telling the truth that day.
You are a RAW agent!
Who is the Colonel?
Where is the bomb? - That's what I came here to find out.
I thought you knew about him.
She's trying to confuse us.
Where is the bomb?
I am on your side.
I work for the British Intelligence.
And you killed that British agent?
I didn't kill Richard.
He was my handler.
I went there to inform him about you.
To show him your face.
You killed 40 people in London.
You were smiling as you got out of the car.
You were smiling.
I was smiling, because I was happy.
It was a beautiful day.
Boss, why are you listening to this nonsense?
I am responsible for the death of those 40 people.
Because my own friends..
.. had planted the bomb in my car.
I was waiting for them.
If I wasn't feeling hungry..
.. and hadn't stepped out..
.. then the blast would have killed me..
When one of the group was caught in Pakistan..
.. then ISI chief lftekhaar Ahmed came to see me.
He was convinced that I am innocent.
He convinced Richard.
They said that they will help me..
.. but I will have to work for them.
They sprung me out of jail..
.. and sent me to Morocco, to Kazan.
Kazan buys drugs from terrorists, and supplies arms.
So you are an ISI agent?
I just report to lftekhaar Sir.
He knows the truth about me.
Last month I intercepted Abu Nazir's phone call from Moscow..
.. that Freddie Khambatta is arriving with $50 million.
I informed Richard, that's why he came here personally.
Can you prove this?
Talk to lftekhaar sir.
He knows me.
lftekhaar Ahmed is dead.
He's dead?
And Richard too.
Now there's no one left to prove your story. And you..
Zahir.
He's one of them.
Now he knows about you.
Shoot him.
No.
I cannot kill anyone.
Not even him.
I don't know where the bomb is.
But the Rubaiyat is the trigger.
The bomb is useless without Rubaiyat.
And right now Rubaiyat is in Kazan's safe.
If you believe me then let me go.
I know the combination of that safe.
Otherwise go yourself.
But for God's sake get that Rubaiyat out of there.
Let's go.
Come on.
20 minutes.
Good luck, Iram.
She was lying.
You believed her?
She was telling the truth.
I have the Rubaiyat and the location of the bomb as well.
Meet me at Golden Farah restaurant, in 20 minutes.
Get lost.
"My friends deserted me."
"My love deserted me."
"Life's so.."
Indian?
Oh, good. Number one.
Goodbye to Morocco.
Indian? - Yes.
I am Suresh Krishna.
That's funny.. - My name is also Suresh Krishna.
By the way, I work for the United Nations.
Deputy Health Commissioner for Africa.
Is this a joke?
I am the Deputy Health Commissioner for Africa.
We need to ask you some questions, Mr. Shastri.
How are you feeling?
I am hungry.
We found Mr. Kazan's address in your pocket.
He's dead. His house has been burgled.
How do you know him? - I mean him in an auction.
Don't disturb the patient please.
I need to examine the patient Officers.
I will see you in some time.
Good morning. - Good morning, Doctor.
Three bullets and you're still alive.
You must be really lucky.
Do you believe in luck?
If I believed in luck I'd be dead a long time ago, Doctor.
I see.
Do you believe in luck, doctor?
Where is she?
Where is she? - Riga.
Riga.
Do you know where they are?
Look at that man closely.
Anton Brega.
Considers himself a Casanova.
He is an alcoholic.. and a womanizer
He has one more bad habit.
He's honest.
He's the Airport Security chief.
There's a pass card in his wallet which I want.
We'll be done by 2 o'clock tomorrow afternoon.
Until then you will have to keep him out of the airport.
So.. you have to spend the night with him.
Get lost! I am not your property!
Bloody reptile!
I just want to die.
No, actually, I just want to get drunk.
Sorry. - No, that's okay. That's fine.
Give me another one.
What do you want? Just get lost.
Okay. Sir, please.
Thank you.
Anton Brega. - Josie.
I told you to get lost.
We just got out of the third casino.
He has won around three-four lakhs.
He says I am lucky for him.
Now he wants to take me home.
Two more hours.
Our job will be done.
Take him to Hotel Riga. 405.
There's a room booked in the name of Josie.
Yeah, 405. - Darling, I've got some special champagne for you.
That's for you. Look at it.
Goodbye.
Hello, sir.
Welcome to Riga. Mr. Nawaz called from Delhi.
This packet is for you.
Any news about those two?
"My darling, I said."
"My darling, you heard it."
"Our hearts communicated with each other."
"My darling, I said."
"My darling, you heard it."
Hello.
Excuse me.
Yes.
That Brega is after me.
He's about to jump on me.
Relax.
Open the mini bar.
There's a chocolate box inside.
Feed him some of those chocolates.
He'll pass out for a few hours.
What about the package? - You want to see it?
Knock him out and leave right away.
Okay, fine.
I was waiting for you at Golden Farah.
Thank God you are alive.
Enough of your charade. - Listen to me.
Colonel had asked me to - Where is the Colonel?
I was just talking to him.
The bomb is here.. in the city.
The man in the room with me is..
You saved my life.
Time for a little chat, Colonel.
You okay? - Get me out of here.
Get here, now.
Get down.
Ready?
Catch them.
He's heading straight.
He's taking a turn.
He's near town square.
Straight and left.
20 kilometers from here.
He has stopped near Maxima Mall.
Don't you want to know why I lied to you in Morocco
Maybe you didn't like my shoes?
'The Colonel had killed Kazan.'
'He was about to kill me.. '
'And suddenly I saw.. '
'In another minute..'
'..Freddie Khambatta would've told him everything'
'The man you think is Freddie Khambatta is actually a RAW agent.'
'I thought that if I told the Colonel about you..
..I might gain his trust.' - 'Where is he? '
'Maybe he would involve me in whatever his plan was..
I did it to find out about the bomb.
'Sir, I am.. '
'Just a minute. Just a minute.'
'Sir, I am Freddie Khambatta.'
'I am a flight purser.'
'Abu gave me a $10 note. What was his name? '
'I don't know his name. He beat me.'
'He took the dollar I was supposed to give you.'
Colonel had taken my phone away.
I snatched someone's phone from the airport toilet
.. and tried calling you.
How will you face three armed men with one bullet?
Don't be afraid.
May God give your husband a long life.
It's stopped.
Come here.
Where did you get this? - What is that?
Where did you get this? - I don't know. What is that?
Where did you get this? - I don't know.
This tracker. - I am telling you, I don't know.
Dr. Suresh Krishna.
Dr. Suresh Krishna?
We are waiting for you
Sorry, sir. This is portable X-ray machine no. 311.
Maybe the colonel lied to you.
Brega's pass was used not to bring bomb into the city
.. but to take it out of the city.
13 flights have taken off..
..since Brega's death..
.. they can be checked only on landing.
The local police want to question you.
Cops in Moscow and Morocco police want to question me as well.
You are in a queue.
Keys please.
I'll be in touch, sir.
Who are you? - Mr. Khana.
Where are they?
They say you need too eat to gain something.
Whenever you get the opportunity, recharge.
Sit down, eat something.
What's on your mind?
Wondering what happens next?
Don't worry, we'll help you.
You cannot help me.
New identity, passport, character certificate.
Money.
What do you want?
What do I want?
I want my life back.
I want my father, who died when I was in jail.
I want the clinic, with a board outside saying..
.. Doctor Iram Parveen Bilal.
I want a home.
A husband who's crazy about me.
I want kids.
I want a normal life.
I want a world..
..where the Rubaiyat is just a book with beautiful poetry.
Not a nuclear bomb detonator.
There's a circuit inside that activates the bomb.
I have some more information.
Take that as well.
I overheard the Colonel on the phone last night.
He was fixing a meeting with Taimoor Pasha on the 28th.
At Hotel Gazebo.
Hotel Gazebo is in Karachi.
I don't know anything else.
And I don't want to either.
Can I go now?
Where will you go?
Anywhere.
I wanted to be a painter.
I thought I will be famous.
A house in the mountains.
Exhibitions in Paris.
Five marriages.
Couple of kids from each marriage..
But the cable snapped. - What?
One of the cables of the ropeway snapped.
We were in Mussoorie, on a school trip.
The entire cabin was dangling on one cable.
A sheer 2000 feet deep drop below.
The other cable could snap any moment..
Plunging us to our death. And then I climbed up.
I clung to a rope for eight minutes.
And managed to secure the cable.
I was 15 years old.
I got a medal from President Venkatraman.
Those eight minutes changed my life.
I always wanted to return..
.. to that place between life and death.
I am still hanging from that cable.
The day I let go..
In Delhi, when the dogs from one lane start barking..
.. do you know what the other dogs do?
Good evening, sir.
Sir, we've to leave for the airport in an hour.
You're leaving for London.
They are waiting for you at the Embassy.
I've got all the documents with me.
Passports. Documents and some money, sir.
Excuse me.
Can I clear the table?
Five minutes, Iram.
I've a flight to catch. Kill them.
Sir, I will wait in the lobby. - Okay.
Rajesh.
Sir.
Where is it?
I had no option.
How many people outside?
"My life was engulfed in darkness until you came with a ray of hope"
"Giving a meaning to my otherwise futile life"
"I was like a lost ship"
"and I wonder how you brought me to the shore"
"we have a connection"
"Show me a way out"
"Who know how do we get out"
"what else is there to say"
"I want to live"
"I choose your embrace over heaven"
"You entered my life like a beautiful dawn."
"Giving me a reason to live."
"was generous enough"
"Did me a favor on the way out"
"to bless me with your sight which was like a guiding star"
"like a hint from destiny"
"you pacified my estranged feelings"
"breaking the silence with a debate"
"I was like a lost ship"
"and I wonder how you brought me to the shore"
"we have a connection"
"I fail to understand how"
"but we do"
"Show me a way out"
"what else is there to say"
"I choose your embrace over heaven"
"You entered my life like a beautiful dawn."
"Giving me a reason to live."
Welcome to Somalia. - Thank you.
You got anything for me? - Take the plane.
We welcome you to Karachi, Pakistan.
Welcome to Pakistan, sir.
Any special reason to come here?
Her grandfather died in the blast.
If you hurry up..
.. then we can take part in the final rites.
Thank you.
Anytime, brother.
Next please.
Hello.
Relax. We are outside the airport.
You were fantastic.
I have returned after 15 years.
My home was on the next left.
Sorry to disturb your memories.
It's a one hour journey.
You can cry all you want.
Move, move.
Move the car.
Third on the most wanted list.
Taimoor Pasha.
How will we get in?
I was wondering how we will get out?
You? Did you recognize me?
Farah. Farah Faqqesh.
I know your name isn't Kapil Dev.
Iram Bilal.
Can you get us inside?
Of course.
They're with me.
Come.
Move on.
The program's on the 10th floor.
Can you hide her somewhere?
By God. This beautiful face isn't for hiding.
Together we will steal everyone's heart.
Hello.
"He looked at me."
"And it's made me crazy."
"Now that he has touched me.. "
"I feel anew."
"I have many lovers."
"But if you can win me over."
"Take my heart for free."
"The poor souls are so distressed."
"But if you can win me over."
"Take my heart for free."
"Your eyes are so bewitching."
"They put me in an illusion."
"You're eyes are so bewitching."
"There are others craving for my love."
"I am a bit nice, but they are cheats."
"My heart's invaluable, it's not for everyone."
"But I need to give it away for your sake."
"The entire market's sold today."
"But if you can win me over."
"Take my heart for free."
"I have many lovers."
"But if you can win me over."
"Take my heart for free."
Hello.
I need you to deliver package to Delhi.
What is it this time? - The usual.
Don't you get bored?
I am bored.
A small gift for you.
"I thought of buying your heart as well."
"Name the price, show the receipt."
"Then I can make you anything you want."
"You'll have eyes only for me." - A small gift, for you.
"You're the only one I lost my heart to."
"But if you can win me over."
"Take my heart for free."
"I have many lovers."
"But if you can win me over."
"Take my heart for free."
Tell Gajja that he'll receive a box of sweets.
The delivery should me made to Blue Bird in Delhi.
Understood. Goodbye.
"I can't live a moment with you."
What kind of security is this?
Who is this girl?
Interpol, Indian government, who is behind her?
We will find out. - Find out.
Who are you?
Who do you work for?
I work for Pakistan.
What is this?
The longer you take..
.. the more fun it will be for me
Don't worry about me.
I am in my own country.
You leave. Good bye.
There's another spy here.
Find him.
This is him.
Listen.. excuse me..
I am sorry.
We've found the spy.
Listen to me.
Your partner's been caught.
You are a traitor.
That's why Gen. lftekhaar never trusted you.
I am sure you are responsible for his death.
How do you know General lftekhaar?
Leave me. I haven't done anything.
What.. what is happening here?
I haven't done anything.
I swear.
I was only eating betel leaf.
Chewing betel leaf is allowed.
Is he your partner?
I don't know him.
I don't know her personally.
I saw her performing at the dance
She was singing.
I swear.. I swear I haven't done anything.
I came with the wedding procession from Rawalpindi.
And my father..
Father own a reputed hotel.
Your days of spying are over.. my friend.
Every dog has his day.
What is Blue Bird?
How dare you ask me questions?
Have you captured me?
There's going to be a big blast in Delhi tomorrow.
Unfortunately you won't be there to see it.
Won't you fulfill my last wish, Colonel?
You want a chopper to get out of here?
I want a chilled beer.
I am sure you can arrange for it.
Get him a beer.
But don't give him the bottle.
Bring it in a paper cup.
He's very cunning.
Anything else.
Juice for you?
Thank you.
Will you marry me?
Where to now?
Delhi.
We're in Karachi?
We need to reach Jahangir point in ten minutes.
Welcome.
The pilot says we'll leave at dawn.
You'll be in Delhi in two hours.
All the arrangements have been done.
You will have to fly really low..
.. for the Geiger counter to detect any radiation.
But what is wrong? Tell me.
Sorry, sir. I cannot tell you anything.
Mr. Nawaz is going to brief you.
You cannot make baseless allegations against Pakistan.
Do you have evidence?
Colonel Huzefa mentioned 'Blue Bird'.
What is 'Blue Bird'? - Colonel Huzefa died in Karachi yesterday.
So how can you say that he's involved?
I saw him giving orders myself.
Tehmur Pasha was present there as well.
They spoke about the bomb
You're betraying your country, and accusing others.
The meeting is over. - No, it's not over.
If this bomb explodes in Delhi, there'll be nuclear war.
We will launch a counter attack. In 20 minutes,
Lahore, Karachi, Islamabad will be annihilated.
More than 60 lakh people will die on both sides.
If you say Pakistan isn't involved..
.. then this is the time to prove it.
What is Blue Bird?
Name? Place? What is it?
Believe me, I don't know.
Mr. Khan, I can be court-martialed for bringing you here.
But millions can be saved as well.
Control room. 10 geo-stationary satellites.
And two roaming.
There are more than 4000 cameras installed in Delhi.
We can see everything.
And maybe you can see your wife in one of these cameras..
.. who just returned home after dropping your kids to school.
There are other mothers, children, families who have no idea..
.. that everything will be over in four hours.
I believe it, Mr. Khan. That you don't know.
But there must be someone in Pakistan..
..in ISI or in your embassy..
..who knows! Please, find out.
"These days he never stops anyone."
"No matter what you do, it never interferes."
"There's loot and plunder all around, and destruction."
"God is up above, and we're on earth."
Would you like to have tea?
"These days He pays less attention to us."
One world government.
Look I've never understood this term.
We are a small circle of friends.
Including top bankers, oil magnets, media personalities..
.. political figures, even an ex-president of the United States.
Yes. And this group has control over almost the entire world economy.
Maybe what you are saying is right.
But these immense resources.
If they are used properly, then anything is possible.
Governments have their own agenda.
Their own programs.
But at the end of the day..
.. it is the individual that matters.
Blue Bird is the Lashkar's safe house..
.. and Professor Yusuf Malik's house.
Ashiana Bungalow. Khilji road. Behind Qutub complex.
We cannot raid that place, sir.
What if they press the trigger? - We don't have an option.
There's one way.
Professor Malik. - Yes.
I am Iram.
Iram Parveen Bilal.
I want to meet the Colonel.
Who?
You've got the wrong address.
Please.
Iram.
Last year, London bombings.
Is the Colonel here or not?
Come in.
The Colonel didn't mention anything about you.
Where is he?
He's gone to the bus stop.
Will be back soon.
How far? - He'll be back.
Will you have tea?
Yes, thank you.
What is that?
Locate HOHO bus 6DL 3323.
Next stop is Red Fort.
Stay at Red Fort, one hour. - Built in 1638.
Come, ma'am, take care of your belongings.
I am heading towards the bus.
Are you ok?
Why are you standing? Sit down.
I am fine, thank you.
I will get biscuits.
She's working for the cops, Professor.
Kill her.
And don't disconnect the phone.
Let it be, I'll do it.
"I just spoke to the Colonel, you traitor"
Move in. Move in.
Are you okay?
He just called the Colonel. - Ok.
Triangulate this number. 9810160605.
Triangulating 9810160605.
Sir, this number has been switched off.
Near Pari Chowk, Noida. I am sending a chopper.
Jimmy, get out of the bus.
And find your own way to the target.
No, don't touch the timer until I say so.
"Since Bisleri got popular."
"Everyone forgot about wells and handpumps."
"Even though farmers produced food-grains."
"They had to commit suicide."
Where to, sir? - Janpath.
That will be Rs. 200.
Let's go.
What's in the bag? - Nothing.
Can I see?
The call's been triangulated in Noida.
Cell tower 26 D. come on, move.
How far is Noida? - Five minutes.
Move. Move. Move.
Move.
Hello, sir.
Yes, I've left the bus.
Take us to Kinari Bazaar.
Kinari Bazaar.
I'm heading straight. Please get down.
We've sat down now. Let's go.
It's a smart dress.
But it makes me look fat.
- I love sarees. - I look very smart.
I think this guy is taking us for a ride.
Where are you going?
Turn around. Take a U-turn.
Can't you hear?
Are you deaf?
Get down at the signal. - Why should we get down?
Get down at the signal. - I'll make the inspector teach you a lesson.
Look, sir. He's really.. - Get down.
What's wrong? Why are you screaming?
What is wrong?
He has the bomb.
Don't give him a chance to press the trigger.
Shoot only if you get a headshot.
Only if you get a headshot.
Not receiving Cam 56 from Barakhambha.
Cam 3 zoom in. Stay.
He's taken the ITO flyover.
He's entered the one way from the opposite side.
Why aren't you listening?
Oh, God!
We are checking the area around the cell tower, sir.
The mobile phone is switched off.
Frankly he can be anywhere.
Sir Metla is here for a charity program.
That is why there is a lot of crowd, sir.
Yes, certainly.
Dr. Ruby. - Sir Metla.
What are you doing here?
You are here for a charity function.
I don't do charity. I do investments.
We're getting late.
Good, sir. Good.
Move it. Clear the traffic. Move them.
Sir, driver body.
Bomb! Bomb!
I lost him.
Iram, come in.
Iram, come in. Iram, come in.
Thank you for your hospitality.
Is there a scheduled time for the helicopter to leave?
We should go now. It's really getting late now.
There was a technical problem, sir.
It's been solved. But we should leave immediately.
Okay, let's go.
I will think about it.
The pilot is the Colonel.
Get in. Get in.
Stop.
My glasses.
I need my glasses.
Please, my glasses.
Rascal.
Colonel, I am in an ice-cream parlor at Connaught Place.
Nirula's.
Only nine minutes left.
I will call you again.
Happy birthday to you.
Everybody out.
Get out, come on.
Go.
Everybody out.
Go, go, go.
Darn it.
Sir. I have found the bomb.
It's demanding a password.
Run, run. Vacate the place.
Everybody out.
Hurry up.
Come on, come on, come on everybody.
The firing circuit has completely failed.
I will have to open it completely.
Open it. - That will take time.
At least 15-20 minutes.
Ground all choppers, sir. Only four minutes left.
Waiting for coordinates.
Get me the map for outer Delhi.
Fly north by north east, Radial 045.
Fly high for the first two minutes.
Then at 500 feet for the last minute.
Setting course, north by north east.
Radial 045.
The old copper mine is seven kilometers away..
..from Delhi-Jaipur Highway.
You'll see an old copper mine.
The mine is 2000 feet deep
Crash the bomb in the mine. - Roger that, sir.
It was a privilege serving with you, my boy.
Jai Hind, sir.
Requesting personal time.
Connect me to Iram, sir.
Iram. Iram.
I know that. Iram, it's Vinod.
Iram. - Is everything okay?
Under control.
Are you fine? - I am not going to make it, Vinod.
What happened?
That bastard shot me. - Where are you hit?
How bad is it? - Two bullets on the liver.
I've lost lot of blood.
Can you come here? Please.
What happened? Can you come here?
I am in the helicopter, with the bomb.
Trying to take it as far away from the city as possible.
Why.. Why can't we diffuse the bomb?
It's asking for the password, which I don't have.
Listen to me, Iram.
I had decided..
.. that I would try and give you the life you wanted.
I just want you to know that I had decided that.
If there is something on the other side..
Then we'll meet soon.
Just one minute left.
Say something terrific.
Stay with me.
Iram.
Press it. Press it.
Password.
Kazan set it in Morocco.
Kazan?
Do you know the password?
Do you know his mother's name?
He killed her himself. - What?
Who? - Zilleh.
Zilleh? - Zilleh. Zilleh.
Who's Zilleh?
Who Iram?
His pet camel
Zilleh.
Spell it.
Can you spell it?
Z I L L..
Iram. - E H.
We did it.
We made it, baby.
You wanted a world..
.. where this Rubaiyat is just a book of poems.
Maybe you are in such a world now.
We found this on the Colonel's body.
Possibly his insurance policy.
Check it.
We cannot touch this man.
He's beyond our reach.
And its impossible to prove anything in court.
If anything happens to him.
An accident or..
Cheers.
In the last 48 hours Pakistan's army has raided..
..training camps and many sleeper cells of Lashkar.
And more than 200 operatives have been killed..
..and around 600 have been arrested.
These raids have served..
..a harsh blow to many terrorist organizations like Lashkar.
Sayyad, don't ask who I am.
Just listen carefully.
I know who's behind the incident that took place in Delhi.
Freddie Khambatta. - Agent Vinod, sir.
I would like to show you something.
Am I making myself clear? - Yes.
Lashkar is the most active group these days.
Yes.
The Zeus group doesn't want any publicity.
No comebacks.
I will cover my footsteps.
But what's the guarantee that you will spare me..
.. after the job's done?
There'll be 25 million Euros in your bank.
You take care of that.
And let us take care of the world.
Cheers. - Cheers.
What is this?
Why are you showing this to me?
My granddaughter shows me such videos on Youtube.
Smart idea.
You would've exploded the bomb in Delhi.
And the world would've thought..
.. that a group like Lashkar is behind it.
So Colonel used people like Abu, Kazan, Jimmy and Huzefa.
Put the stamp of Jehad on the operation.
You wanted to trigger a war between both countries..
.. and make millions.
Fascinating theory, Agent Vinod.
But why did you get this here?
Take it to the press.
It'll be fun for a few days.
But now you must excuse me.
I need to.. attend a function.
The Zeus group.
Great businessmen like you.
Senators, ex-prime ministers.
I've heard that whenever you meet..
.. something strange occurs somewhere in the world.
Some President's death in a plane crash.
A civil war in a small country.
Nuclear blast in New Delhi.
Wow.
Wow, Agent Vinod.
You think you know everything.
But I want to add to your knowledge.
A bomb blasts in Delhi.
But the real explosion happens in the stock exchanges of New York..
.. London, Tokyo, Hong Kong, Beijing
You would short stocks and make your billions.
But what about the millions that die in both the countries?
What about them?
You know what would've happened to China..
.. if the stock market had crashed?
How NATO would've seized Pakistan's nuclear bombs?
And we could have solved the Iran pipeline situation
These are complex issues.
You are a police officer.
It's beyond your understanding.
You will have to die. Sir Metla.
Today.
You're here to kill me.
I won't kill you, sir.
You're a hero in my country.
And you'll die as a hero.
There'll be roads built in your name.
Stamps issued.
Books written about you..
Goodbye, sir.
Sir Metla will be back soon.
Won't you sit down, sir?
Coffee, please.
What's he doing? - Second cup of coffee, sir.
Sir Metla.
Sayeed Kousar has sent his regards.
Who? - Lashkar, sir.
Bismillah.
It appears that Sir Metla was killed by the same terror group..
.. that planned a nuclear attack in New Delhi.
It was Sir Metla's heroic intervention that..
.. thwarted the well laid plan.
Our correspondent Marge Atkins is at the site.
Tell us what is happening Marge..
I know you.
You are Freddie Khambatta.
I don't like that name.
So what is your name?
"The bungalow's locked."
"How do I get in?"
"Laila's window is open."
"There's a gutter below it."
"Someone's at the window."
"Laila's having an affair."
"She has a blast at the expense of my love."
"My darling, after I am smitten by you."
"Where are you going blowing away my love?"
"She showers her love on everyone."
"But scolds me when I ask for some."
"Kisses for everyone else."
"But just a pat on my cheek."
"Laila is like a chameleon."
"Like the beats on the drums."
"Leaves her lipstick mark on the cheeks with her smooch."
"My.. My.. my.."
"My.. after I am smitten by you."
"Where are you going.. my love?"
"My darling, after I am smitten by you."
"Where are you going blowing away my love?"
"P U N G I.. "
"I am Laila, I will blow your love away."
"P U N G I.. I am Laila, I will blow your love away."
"After making those false promises in English."
"Where are you going blowing away my love?"
"My darling, after I am smitten by you."