Life is a bouquet of oranges,
bright and fresh
if sprinkled with laughter...
Plump with sweetness
Each week passes
light-fooled and easy
Each day dawns like
a Sunday morning
Woven with threads of such joy
Sparkles a story
its scent carried by the breeze
its melody whistled by the wind
In the white midday sun,
a golden spot of sunset
No time for gloom,
we cherish every happiness
Pockets full of small gestures
and big moments
No shroud of worry
we swirl in robes of content
Woven with threads of this spirit
Sparkles a story
its scent carried by the breeze
its melody whistled by the wind
Thank you for your help, sir
Life flows on
Whispering a new-old song...
In a blink and a sigh, I'm gone
Celebrate each moment,
together; hereon
Woven with threads of
our togetherness
Sparkles a story
its scent carried by the breeze
Well fielded, Kayoze
They say Catches win Matches
And Kayo's catch has certainly
turned the game around
Move
Not out, sir
My foot was on the line, sir
Sir, when I took the catch...
my foot was on the boundary line
C'mon guys, chin up
Papa, you know how well
I played today?
I took 7 wickets
You're listening, Papa?
- Listening, Kayo
The ball was high but far
Iran real fast to the ball...
and I dived
Fantastic
- And catch
Papa, that was a red light
Oh no
Sorry son
- No Papa, I'm sorry
Do you see a traffic cop?
No Papa, no one
How could you, Rusy...
I'm sorry
Bhau Waghmare'...
What sort of name is that?
Good morning, sir
Yes?
Sir, I ran a red light.
May I pay the fine please?
You didn't pay the
traffic cop there?
There wasn't anyone there
So who stopped you?
No one stopped me
You say you ran a red light
No cop there
So you should have left.
No big deal
No one saw you
Someone saw me
Who saw you?
My son saw me
He will learn from what I do
I ran a red light,
I must pay the fine
Bylaw, I can't take your fine
Please leave
Here's another headache
Stop there.
Don't offload that car
C'mon, get the car down
Inspector Mhatre, I told you...
Don't tow any imported car
in this area
It could belong to a politician
This car caused a
2 km long traffic jam
They park wrongly, we suffer
Inspector Mhatre,
please listen to me
One scratch on this car
means a big enquiry
Do you know how
expensive this car is?
Rs. 10.2 million -
cost in Mumbai
BMW 7 series, latest model
Sir, please take this fine
This is... '?
- The King of Honesty
Meet the Champion of Truth
One moment, sir
Remember?
- Of course!
Rustom Behram Deboo.
Head Clerk, Transport Office
Nandkumar Mhatre.
Inspector, Traffic
And - my son
Kayoze Rustom Deboo
Shinde, this man is amazing
A boon for the traffic police
Imagine that
He cleared that Ballard Pier jam
single-handedly
Wow
Don't harass him
No, never
Here, let me gift you
these blank tickets
Next time, write yourself a ticket
Sir, take the fine please
Shinde
- Got it, sir
Proud to meet you, Mr. Deboo
Thank you, sir
But sir...
What was your name now...
Rustom Behram Deboo.
Head Clerk, Transport Office
Rusy
Yes Papa?
Where are those noodles-shoodles?
Ready Papa, almost ready
Grate some cheese over them
Yes Papa
Let's watch some cricket, Grandpa
They're not cricketers,
they're salesmen
They sell soaps and pomades
Ever heard of Don Bradman
selling fragrant hair gel?
Now buzz off, weasel
Always knocking that ball
Papa, Grandpa is so mean
Let it go Kayo, it's ok
If he hates Indian cricketers,
why does he live in India?
What's that, weasel?
Nothing, Papa
Kayo, you don't speak
to your elders like that
Go, say sorry
Kayo
Sorry
Papa, your noodles
Too hot
Sorry
Added cheese?
- Yes Papa
Ginger and garlic?
And Mr. Kayo,
here are your shoodles
Last night I had a dream
I was at Lord's, watching
the Cricket World Cup final
India vs. Pakistan
Last 2 overs, India needs
30 runs to win
At the non-striker end is
Sachin Tendulkar
At the striker's end is...
Guess who, Kayo?
Guess...
Kayo?
Give up?
At the striker's end is
Kayoze Rustom Deboo...
Captain of the Indian Cricket team
Shoab Akhtar bowls at
5600 km/ hour
And Kayo easily flicks him...
That... was a wide ball
Last ball now
6 runs to win
All fielders at boundary
Bowler runs
Kayo lifts his bat up
Crowd chants...
North, South, East, West...
Kayoze is the best
Kayo... Kayo...
Bowler bowls and
Kayo swings his bat
Of all the witless, idiotic...
Kayo
Made the TV into a punching bag
Were you batting or battering?
Kayo... Kayo...'
Need a kick on your butt
I'm sorry, Kayo
There's a match tomorrow.
What do I do?
Sue him in the High Court
Now you'll say -
Look at the brighter side of life
Actually yes, Kayo
What if it had broken
during the match?
Listen, we'll buy
a new bat tomorrow
Remember the bat we'd
put a red mark on?
We'll buy that
But that's for Rs. 2800
So what? I'll get it for you
The match is at 9 am
but the shop opens at 9:30
You play one down, right?
I'll get it before your turn
Are you sure?
Sure
One moment
What're you looking at, Kayo?
- Nothing
Shoes?
- No Papa
Goodnight my angel,
now close your eyes
Goodnight love,
hush those sleepy sighs
Let the moon lull you
into a gentle web of dreams
As the night croons along with me
Goodnight
Excuse me, sir.
Does this shop open at 9130?
That's what it says here
Don't know when it actually opens
Welcome, everyone, to the
Mumbai University Ground...
and the Young
Mumbai Indians Tournament
First ball of the innings
And that's clean bowled.
Great delivery
Next batsman is Kayoze...
their captain and
their best batsman
Sahil, go
Sir?
Go, I said
Captain, what's your batting order?
Sir, I'll go two down
Slow down, you'll trip
A few days back I was
here with my son
We'd put a red mark
on a bat, remember?
Which bat?
There're 2000 bats here.
Where will you look?
Howzzat?
Huge appeal. And the
umpire raises his finger
Go, Kayo
Ball's keeping low, watch it
PTVA score -
27 for 2 wickets
Sir, my bat broke yesterday
So borrow one
But Papa's getting me a new bat
I'll go three down
Nawaz
I told you to keep that bat aside
Which bat? How will I know?
Go look inside
Oh yes, there too
Keep this
- What is it?
Money
Now he'll attempt the impossible
An easy catch
PTVA score -
32 for 3 wickets
That was close
9... 10... 11 Found it?
No, still looking
It's not going to wait around
for so many days
What now?
Yes
Sir, if the next wicket falls
and Papa's still not here...
I'll go to bat
OK
Please hurry
First you tire me,
then you hurry me
I'm sorry
How much for this,
after the discount?
If you give me 100 rupee bills,
then 1500 rupees
If you give me coins like this,
then 1700 rupees
Right. I'll mark it.
Keep it aside
Next ball
He tried to step out and play...
and he's out
Brilliant stumping
Shut your mouth
- The over ends
Manmeet, bat
Sure?
Kayo... Kayo...
Finally on field is
Kayoze Rustom Deboo
Score is 70 for 6 wickets.
Just 7 overs left
They need 9 runs per over.
That's a tough one
But if there's Kayo,
there's hope for his team
Next ball
Ajinkya plays it superbly
to leg side
Could be 2 runs
Kayo takes 1 run.
He's running for the 2nd
He's running...
- Sir, 1 minute
Still running...
He's just running...
He's running off the field
Quick Papa, please
Sorry I'm late, son
- it's ok, Papa
Yes, this is it.
Bye Papa
Kayo
One moment
Wearing your guard?
- Papa, not here
All the best
- Bye Papa
Here goes...
He's off
Watch now
All set
All wired
C'mon Kayo, hit
All alert
In position
Revved to go...
In to battle
He's hit a 6...
Ana' now a 4
Something zooms up. . .
Look, it's our score!
He's hit a 6...
Ana' now a 4
Something zooms up. . .
Look, it's our score!
The crowds hunger for runs. . .
They gotta have more
More...
And more...
He hits
Watch out
Up and a way
A big hit
PTVA needs 2 runs off the last ball
Last ball.
Kayo played it to leg side
Slight misfield
He's taken 1 run
and runs for the 2nd
There's a throw from the boundary
Kayo needs to hurry
Howzzat?
Alright everyone,
your attention please
Excuse me
Thank you
I'd like to introduce you all
to John McClan...
cricket coach from MCG, London
John and his team are here
to select Under-14 players...
for a cricket camp
The selected players will go to...
Guess where?
To the Mecca of cricket, yes...
Lord's cricket ground, London
So... Over to you, John
Thank you
Now listen carefully
The MCG is conducting a
coaching camp and a tournament...
for Under-14 players
We will select 10 players
from every country
He's upset?
A little
Rusy, this is an extraordinary camp
But it costs Rs.150,000
See, Kayo's the best we have
I don't want him to feel
he's losing a great opportunity
So I'll convince him
he doesn't need this camp
He'll understand
Don't worry, I'll handle him.
I'll just be back
The 11th player is an
international level cricketer
And here's the best part...
This means you could be
facing Shane Warne
Or...
perhaps bowling to...
Sachin Tendulkar
This is important,
so please listen carefully
The final selection is in 2 weeks
If selected, you must pay
the fee the next day
Jeet, forms
Hey
Hello
Good job, Captain
Cheer up
I'll see you at Lord's
Saurabh, especially for you.
Don't forget..
Excuse me, sir
May I have a form, please?
Are you sure?
Yes sir. The form, please
Papa
But Papa, how will we
get the money?
EPF
What is EPF?
Employees Provident Fund.
The Government's piggy bank
Every month, we put a bit of
our salary into it
The Government also puts in
the same amount
And when we need a loan...
like we need one now, for Lord's...
we can take it from the piggy bank
But if we can't unlock
the piggy bank...
do we break it, Papa?
Thank you, Papa
Long live the Government of India
Rusy, I'll sign this...
but I doubt you'll get
your loan in 15 days
Sir, if you recommend...
That won't help
Good morning, Mr. Kadam
Hey Babbu didi
Rusy, how're you? All good?
All good, thank you
Do carry on with your work
Last year, I applied for a loan
for my daughter's wedding
The wedding went off well
Babbu didi was the wedding planner
I still owe her money
Never mind that
Now, when my daughter
had a baby, I got a letter
Glad to sanction you a loan
for your daughter's marriage'
What's this?
Rice pudding for you
Do have some, Rusy
Some tea?
No, I don't feel like it
Something bothering you?
I'm looking for a car
See this picture
Ferrari Italia, 562 horsepower.
Top speed 320 km/ hour
Costs Rs. 34.6 million in Mumbai
Very good car
He knows every detail
That's amazing
You know every detail
Now tell me,
where will I get this car?
No one here has this model
Really? Any similar models?
Sachin Tendulkar has one
Our Tendulkar?
This is great news
Will he rent it to us?
I'll give him any deal he wants
Per km/ per second...
whatever he wants
And I'll return it with a full tank
Babbu didi, life is treating
him great right now
He doesn't need to rent out his cars
Then this sister of yours
is as good as dead
Tell me, why does it have
to be a Ferrari?
Because of my stupidity
Do you know of Tatiya Mandke?
He's a big shot politician
from the Worli village
His son's getting married
- Sir, I'll get back
What's the matter?
Don't like my tragic tale?
Stay and listen. I'm not done
So, Tatiya's son is to be married.
To impress him, I said...
It's your son's wedding
We'll do it Rome style
I was on a roll. I said...
Instead of riding the
traditional solitary horse...
your son will ride 560 horses
at his wedding
Tatiya said - How?
I said - In the Ferrari
The signature red car of Italy,
the Ferrari
560 horsepower
The thug took me seriously
He wants 560 horsepower
at the wedding
And I'm trapped
Hello
Yes, this is Babbu Chanchal...
Proprietor,
Chanchal Wedding Planners
Hello ma'am
Your name's been selected
for a personal loan
Interested, ma'am?
Give your mom a loan,
I don't need one
I need a Ferrari. Have one?
Silly loan peddlers
Since I bought this phone,
I only get loan offers
I'm fed up. Mark my words...
Loan for you'
We'll hear this on the streets soon
Go ahead, laugh at my misery
Truly, this is a big
business deal for me
Please try and get me
a Ferrari. Save my life
Or that goon will shoot me
Opera
It's the music of Rome
At our Pakya's wedding,
everything will be Rome style
Everything. Why?
Because Rome is the Capital of Love
Rani, your prince won't ride
to you on a horse
He'll zip to you in
the Roman car, Ferrari
Every bridegroom has
1 horsepower under his butt
But Pakya will have
560 horsepower under his butt
Great idea, Babbu didi
I have another idea
Babbu didi, no more ideas
The Ferrari's final
Dad, I want the Ferrari
All yours, son
Hit it, guys
The Ferrari £9 coming here
Pakya 's big day is near
What's the number?
- What?
Yes Papa, it's...
Papa, it rang
So answer it
Hello Papa
Hello
Papa, can you hear me?
Dimwit, here I can hear
even without the phone
Go farther away
- Sorry, one moment
Hello... Papa, now?
Still getting your voice directly
Hide elsewhere
Can you hear me
on the phone now?
No, it's the same. Go farther
From here?
Go behind the door
- OK
But Papa, can you hear me
on the phone?
Or can you only hear me directly?
Papa?
Rusy
I have an idea
Go into the bathroom
OK, yes, that's it
Hold on Papa, one moment
What a cartoon character
Hello. This is
Rustom Behram Deboo...
Head Clerk, Transport Office.
Who's speaking please?
Your pop
You bought a phone
to just chit-chat?
No Papa, I heard that
cell phones owners...
get loan offers from banks
What loan?
Papa
I want to send Kayo
to London, Papa
Why?
Papa
MCG cricket camp at Lord's
To send Kayo to London,
you'll take out a loan?
Papa, Kayo's an excellent cricketer
With the right training,
he'll play for India some day
I know Rs. 150,000 is a lot...
Have you lost your mind?
To send Kayo to London,
you'll take out a 150,000 loan?
In no time it'll be 300,000,
then a million
How will you pay it back?
You'll sell this house?
You'll put us on the street?
Don't you dare stuff
his head with trash
Now hang up.
Can't you hear me directly?
Stupid idiot
Papa, Kayo...
Go on, get out
Get him to finish school
Then teach him water-proofing
Mumbai homes are always leaking
You want to take him
to Lord's on that scooter?
Goodnight Pa pa
What is so good
about the night?
Stuff your Goodnight
Can barely find his way
within Mumbai...
and wants to go to Lord's!
Papa, should I speak
to him or will you?
Kayo, you're still awake?
Where're you going?
What're you doing, Kayo?
He's always so rude to you
If Mama was here,
this wouldn't happen
Kayo, I can't fight with Grandpa
And Mama wouldn't have, either
She would've scolded him
- No son, she wouldn't have
Why not?
When I grow up, I'll show him
Let me go, Papa
I'm sorry, Papa
It's ok. Come here
Kayo, many years ago...
there were two friends...
just like you and Sahil
Their passion was also cricket
Like you both, they broke
windows all the time
Both had the same dream...
To play for India some day
At the age of 14,
they played interstate cricket
They made centuries together,
were an unbeatable partnership
Finally, both were called for
the Indian team selection
Rumor had it only one of them
would make it to the team
Oh no... Then?
Then jealousy crept in
On the day of selection,
both played superbly
Every ball was hit for a 4 or 6
It was the drinks break
And one friend
betrayed the friendship
Then?
It was a bouncer.
He couldn't see it clearly
The glass damaged his cornea
He was left with some vision,
but couldn't play cricket again
And the other friend?
He was selected to the Indian team
Became rich and famous,
traveled the world
He never came to meet his friend?
No, never
Who's he, Papa?
Do I know him?
Dharmadhikari
Dilip Dharmadhikari?
The world knows
D. N. Dharmadhikari
But his friend...
was forgotten long ago
Where is he now, Papa?
You're crying, Papa?
He's in our living room
Grandpa?
Kayo?
Was he the best?
He was the bestest
May this mind...
its thoughts and deeds
Every stride and step
Tread the path of Truth
Truth and Integrity . .
Make for a tough path
But remain fearless
and unwavering
Always, with head held high
Stand strong...
On the tough, honest path
Ana' remain fearless
and unwavering
Always, with head held high
...Lord's, London. So, I need a loan
Sorry, not possible
Good morning, ma'am
- Good morning
I'd like to meet
a loan officer, please
He's here
Good morning, sir
My name is Rustom Behram Deboo...
Head Clerk, Transport Office
You didn't call me,
so I've come over
I was going to call you?
I have a new phone, you see.
So?
So I thought you'd call me
with a loan offer
It's ok, sir
Sir, my son,
Kayoze Rustom Deboo...
is an outstanding cricketer
He plays one down and
never returns to the pavilion
He's been selected for
a cricket camp at Lord's
So, sir?
Sir, the camp's a bit expensive,
so I need a loan
Sir, one moment
Sir, see Kayo's certificates
Sir, this is for Man of the Match
This for Highest Scorer
Sir, for fielding too
Sir, see his medals and trophies
This is for Man of the Match
This is for batting... fielding...
One last thing
I want to show you, sir
His medals, sir
Sir, if you see him play...
I'm sure you'll approve the loan
Can I see your
salary slips, please?
Yes, I have them here
Transport Office?
Head Clerk, sir
How much money do you need?
RS. 'I 50,000, Sir
Sorry, you're not eligible
- I know that, sir
You can't get a loan
on this salary
I know that, sir
Sir, that's why...
I've got you his
certificates and trophies
Sir, look at Kayo's talent
OK, how much can I get
with my salary?
135,000?
125,0007
Sir, if a father's salary is low,
can his son never move up?
Please leave
Why would anyone with
a fat salary want a loan?
Only someone who has
less money will come to you
Security
Sir, see his caliber and decide
Come to the club once
and see him bat
Sir, he's wonderful
Sir?
Sir...
Give him this. Tell him to
remember this name
He'll be on TV some day
As he hits a sixer,
all of India will clap for him
And your boss will smack
his head in frustration
Have a good day
Smack his head?
He'll crack his skull
I tell you, Rusy...
he'll suffer so much,
he'll commit suicide
Don't stress. Don't let
this spoil your mood
We'll find another way
Mr. Kadam mentioned that
your father, Behram Deboo...
played interstate cricket
Yes, he was the youngest
interstate player
That's wonderful
Like grandfather, like grandson
Cricket runs in your blood
You didn't give it a shot?
Actually, I...
That's alright. Cricket's loss,
Transport Office's gain
You know, relationships
don't mean anything today
But one bond is still strong -
the bond of cricket
It got me thinking
Your papa can tell Sachin -
There's a family wedding
Give me your Ferrari for 2 days
How will Sachin refuse him?
Papa won't...
OK, imagine this
Sachin asks your papa...
Can I borrow Rusy's scooter
for 2 days?
Your papa will never refuse him
That's the bond of cricket
Yes, but Papa won't...
OK now let me explain
what's in it for you
Come closer
You speak to your papa...
and get me Sachin's Ferrari
for 2 days
In return, I'll give you
Rs. 150,000
A gift, for you
I'm a Government employee.
I can't accept gifts
Ma'am, I've to leave now,
if you don't mind
Sorry, I've to go,
Our Kayo will go to London, Rusy
Ma'am, what...
Don't worry about it
Go about your business
Listen to me calmly
You know the proverb...
Opportunity knocks your door once'?
Look, once this wedding's over...
you'll lose your chance of
sending Kayo to London
I'm at your door, ringing the bell
Ding dong
But you've locked yourself in
Unlock the door
- Look lady...
Got a problem, Grandpa?
There's a lady here
Go on, now. Do your thing
Open the door, let me in
Take the Opportunity
What do you say?
Well?
Ma'am, give me some time.
I'll talk to Papa
Papa
Sachin's making a century.
Come and see
OK, in a while
Now, Papa
I have some work.
I'II join you, son
Sixer
Bye Papa. See you
Hello?
Wrong number
Hey Mr. Popular
- Yes?
Your social circle's expanding.
Who was it?
Wrong number, Papa
You get dirty jokes or not?
Wrong number, I said
Always been a wrong number
Hello?
Babbu didi,
Sachin knows me very well
Don't you worry, I'll handle it
I will speak to Rusy
I'm his father,
he has to listen to me
And when this is done,
you must visit us
Yes, I'll speak to Rusy right away
See you soon
Rusy, you didn't tell me...
you're getting Rs. 150,000
for Sachin's Ferrari
No Papa, I told Babbu didi...
Listen, don't you want Kayo
to be a cricketer?
Pull up a chair. Sit down
Listen carefully
This is what you must do -
Go to Sachin's house and say...
I am the son of Behram Deboo'
You must understand...
the bond of cricket is stronger
than any other bond
Sachin doesn't drive
that car anyway
It's rotting in his garage
Papa, you're not fooling
with me, are you?
Would I fool with you
on something like this?
What's wrong with you?
My dear Rustom...
Good morning,
Mrs. Sachin Tendulkar
How do I address her?
Good morning, Mrs. Tendulkar
Very good. Continue
You know Tatiya Mandke,
the politician?
His son's getting married
For the wedding,
Tatiya wants his son to be in a...
Ferrari
What a fine idea
He's a very caring father
So I thought we could...
both... help him
You see, you have 3-4 cars
If you can lend one of them...
like the Ferrari...
say the Ferrari...
to Mr. Mandke for a few hours...
he'll pay me Rs. 150,000 for it...
and Kayo can go to Lord's
Any chance, Mrs. Tendulkar?
Very good. Smile
Hello?
Hello Rusy, any luck?
You spoke to Papa?
I have the Ferrari key
in my hand
What? Seriously?
You're a hero
Actually, someone at the house...
probably thought
I was the car cleaner
Gave me all the car keys
I haven't mentioned
the wedding yet
I'll speak about it and call you
Wait, don't
You got the car key
without asking for it
It's a sign from above
Just take the car and come here
What? No ma'am
That would be stealing.
I can't do that
Listen, do as I say
No one will get to know
It's a matter of a few hours
Once the wedding's over,
we'll return the car
I'm sorry ma'am,
I can't do this
Rusy, think of your
son's potential
He'll blossom at Lord's
Sachin played for India
at the age of 16
Your son will play at 12
Youngest player ever
Do your duty as a father
Sir, the latest bestsellers
No, thank you
Hey, nice wheels
No son, step back please
No, don't do that
Babbu didi, where should I
bring the Ferrari?
You did it, my tiger
This is great
Come into the Worli village
You'll see the
wedding festivities
Drive towards them
The Worli village?
OK
The turmeric ceremony
of our beloved Pakya
Stop this
Mr. Mandke
Our Ferrari is coming hers
Pakya, smile if you want
your photo taken
560 horsepower
Our Ferrari is coming hers
What's the matter?
Let the Ferrari turn around
and go back
See what's written about me
in the paper
Public coffers empty,
Tatiya has plenty'
Oh no
Page 5 today,
front page news tomorrow
And that's the end of me
As you know...
there are more politicians
in prison than in power
Now here's my idea
I will tell the Press...
I'm spending money...
but not on my son's wedding
I'm arranging a Mass Wedding
Listen, all of you
Tomorrow, right here...
201 couples will be
married off by me
200 are my social work
1 is my...
homework
My son Prakash
He will wear a number
and pose for photos
Pakya
What's this number scam?
Each couple in a mass
wedding has a number
I will have '201' on me,
and so will my wife
If not, wives can get
switched around
Is that so?
- Yes
So you'll wear a number
and get married?
Yes
Man, you're our Crown Prince
Don't do it
Then Tatiya will be in the
Union Cabinet
I won't wear a number
around my neck
You will wear a number
You will marry the way I want
My friends will laugh at me
They'll mock me -
'Didn't get a Ferrari...
but wore a number plate
at his wedding'
I won't...
Forget this wedding. Cancel it
Cancel it, I don't care
I won't get married your way
But we've started
the turmeric ceremony
How can we cancel now?
Babbu didi, do something
Yes, just a moment, excuse me
Son, listen to me
You want to sit in the Ferrari,
take photos with your pals?
I'll make it happen for you.
Trust me
One moment, excuse me
Can I suggest a win-win
compromise, sir?
There's a ceremony
at the bride's house today
Let's go there in style
The boys can have
their fill of the Ferrari
They'll celebrate,
get their photos taken
In return, tomorrow...
Pakya will wear No. 201
and get married
What do you say?
Well?
Well, son?
One moment
They're kids
Compromise
Take the Ferrari or your dad
will put you on a tricycle
Because you're my father...
I'm ready to compromise
Hit it
Shambhu
Lazy bones... Watching TV?
Where's Shambhu?
Shambhu hasn't come in
He hasn't?
- Nope
So who took the car keys
from me today?
Shambhu has the day off
What's the matter, Mohan?
The car's been stolen
How can that be?
I saw the car leave today
I opened the gate for it
You mean...
you let the thief go?
Don't try to trick me, Mohan
No one steals in broad daylight
The thief took the car
from under your nose
What were you doing?
Watching the match,
eating bananas
Big oaf
When a car enters the gate,
it's my responsibility
I ask...
Where do you want to go?
Whom do you want?
When a car leaves,
it's not my responsibility
I can't ask...
Where are you going?
Why are you going there?
I'll get beaten up
Spare me the details
Explain this to the
Residents' Committee
Not the Committee, please
Because of you, the car's gone
This is now a police matter
- No police, please
I'll lose my status in the village
You'll lose your status
in the village?
So confess that
you aided the theft
But you gave the thief the key
How did the car key
leave the house?
You were alone at home
Boss and his wife are
out of town
The cops will catch you first
Let me explain this to the
Residents' Committee
Wait, please. Don't...
Don't make a big deal
out of it, man
Listen...
Only you and I know
the car's been stolen
Does anyone else know?
- No
We can't go to the cops
or tell anyone about it
Got it?
If we stick together,
we're safe
If not, we're both sunk.
Got it?
Come, let's look for the car now
But Mohan, where do we look?
It's a red Ferrari-
hard to miss
It's here
The Ferrari's here
Babbu didi, I've a task for you
Turn the Ferrari into
a florist's delight
Sir?
Put so many flowers on it...
that one wouldn't know
if it's a Ferrari or...
a bullock cart
My Ferrari
Sir, not so close to the car
Sir, you'll scratch the car
Give me the Ferrari key
- Sir, where is Babbu didi?
Give me the car key
I'm sorry sir,
I can't give you the key
I will drive the car, sir
Sir
Sir, stay back
Sir, please step back
Babbu didi
What chaos
Ma'am
Please don't tell anyone
this is Sachin's car
OK
And only I will drive this car
And ma'am, I have to return
the car in a few hours
Don't worry. You handle it all
Here, put these flowers
on the car
Ferrari
The Ferrari key?
- Later
First clear the area
Your boss played
superbly yesterday
As I was saying,
Shamshu bhai...
I have a small problem.
I need your help
Anytime. I'm here to help
But you didn't keep your word
You'd promised me a photo
with your boss...
I'll get Boss here
You can pose with him
against any car
Seriously?
Sachin Tendulkar
will come here?
Of course. If I tell him that
Shamshu bhai, the garage owner...
is a big fan of his,
he won't refuse
Mohan, you've made my day.
Come on in
This is my friend, Mahavir Tambe
Pleased to meet you
He heads a huge
security guard force
We're here because...
his car's been stolen
A car stolen from the
Head of Security?
Bad days...
Easy, now
What car was it?
Alto
- Scorpio
Alto or Scorpio?
Business as usual, don't worry
Mohan
Both
Both?
You see...
we were driving along
in the Alto
It stalled
To tow it, we called
for a Scorpio
Actually, we were in the
Scorpio, the Alto came...
You're explaining?
No, you go ahead
So, the Alto stalled
We got the Scorpio to tow it
As we were towing it,
he wanted to go
Go?
- Nature's call
We went to the side of the road
The thief sat in the Scorpio
He left in the Scorpio,
dragging the Alto with it
Steal one, get one free
I want to know,
Shamshu bhai...
The Alto, Scorpio and
other stolen cars...
Where do they go?
Scorpios go to
Bihar, U.P. or Nepal
And the Alto?
- The Alto...
Forget the Alto, Shamshu bhai
Mr. Tambe can afford
many such cars
Yes, I can
May I speak now?
I'm just curious...
Can I ask you a question?
Ask away
When a big car is stolen...
say a BMW or a Ferrari...
what happens to it?
Tea
I don't tell anyone this
But I'll tell you
These big cars...
can't be sold openly
Right
So what we do is this...
We dismantle them
and sell them
Boss
Mohan, that's Boss
Dismantle them?
Yes
At Sion village or Worli village
There the car is taken apart
So this is the...
Tire
Goes to Opera House
What did you rip?
Rexin
Goes to Mahalakshmi
The seat
Goes to Mohammad Ali Road
And the steering wheel
comes to me
Right, the steering wheel
Now what's left?
The body
- Right, the body
The body can't be sold
So we take it...
and put it into a furnace
It melts into a...
ball
Have one
- No, thank you
Mr. Tambe?
What's that?
S class
Mercedes
My man stands proud
and commanding
Gave his word
and got me a Ferrari
As the ghetto gapes
and stares
I lap it all up, put on airs
Let me go now
Don't flirt and tease
Let go of me
Release me please
My man stands proud
and commanding
Gave his word
and got me a Ferrari
As the ghetto gapes
and stares
I lap it all up, put on airs
Let me go now
Don't flirt and tease
Let go of me
Release me please
All around they encircle
and .adore me
Slip away now
you won't get a whiff of me
Hundreds like you
dangle in queue
Why should I la y
my gaze on you
All around they encircle
and .adore me
Slip away now
you won't get a whiff of me
You're too naive for
Iove and Desire
Too soft and sweet,
all smoke and no fire
Your performance won't
lure me to you, sir
Take your routine
elsewhere, to another
Let me go now
Don't flirt and tease
Let go of me
Release me please
I Swish like fish,
my cheeks like pear/
Hips lush with youth,
I twist and twirl
Why chase ms,
you Te not my kind
Paws off and
watch your behind
I Swish like fish,
my cheeks like pearl
Hips lush with youth,
I twist and twirl
Meet me later,
I have to rush, dear
It's for my man
I dolled up and came here
He slid this ornament into me
A mirror, quick,
to see the glow he 'll see...
Let me go to him
Let me go please
Have to go now
Need to go now
Let me go now
Don't flirt and tease
Let go of me
Release me please
I'm going now
Let me go now
Let me go to her
Alright Rusy,
here's Rs. 150,000
Before the Press gets here,
take the car away
Thank you
Mohan
How much does a
Ferrari cost?
I'll tell you
If you sell that hole
you call home...
to three people,
over three years...
you still won't get a Ferrari tire
Don't fib
It has just two seats
No seats in the back
A scooter also has two seats
A Ferrari also has two seats
How much extra can
two wheels cost?
4... 5000?
Hello?
Good morning, ma'am
Yes ma'am. OK ma'am
Have a good day
What's the matter, Mohan?
That was Mrs. Tendulkar.
Boss is coming back
I'm off to my village
Wait
Tell the cops
I committed suicide
And my body is in
Shamshu's furnace
Wait, calm down
We have some time.
I have a plan. C'mon
Leave me out of it
Boss is back tomorrow night,
don't worry
Come with me
Mohan
Police
Run
Run!
C'mon, hurry
Mohan, wait for me.
My helmet
Put it on. Use your head
Mohan
Mohan, I can hear
the sound of the Ferrari
You're going mad. Run
Rustom Behram Deboo,
Transport Office
Sir, why's the police
here today?
The Ganesh festival
and Sachin's century...
That's when the police
works overtime
Just a precaution
- OK
Not starting?
It'll start, sir
Listen, try this
Run it down the slope
in neutral
Then slip it into 2nd gear.
It'll start
OK...
Get on the slope
In neutral?
- Yes
Keep it in neutral.
Now put it into 2nd gear
There, it started
Rustom, hold on
Help me with this
Got to nab this red car
Yes sir...
Hello?
Rusy, where are you?
It's morning
Where were you?
Papa, something terrible
has happened
What... You had an accident?
Papa, I stole Sachin's Ferrari
You crazy?
I was fooling with you
Where's the car?
The car's being towed away
Now do as I say.
Come straight home
Wear your helmet
Hide your face from the cops
Something really terrible
happened, Papa
What now?
Papa, I left Rs.150,000
in the car
Kayo can't go to Lord's, Papa
Kayo... Lord's...
Pawar, prepare that report.
I'm leaving
C'mon Jadhav
Jadhav, slow down
Stop, I said
Inspector Mhatre,
what have you brought in?
It's called a car.
Has four wheels...
Sir, this is no car.
It's a celestial chariot
The chariot of my God
It's Sachin Tendulkar's Ferrari
But your God parked
in a No Parking zone
Will my God come
to get his car, sir?
Whether it's your God
or his driver...
don't release the car
without taking the fine
Don't worry, sir.
I'll watch over this car
0 Lord, thank you
There's the Ferrari
Looking good, Pakya
But the Ferrari can't be seen
Where is the Ferrari?
Look for it
Go to the next one
It's covered with flowers
Is it a Ferrari
or a humble taxi?
Pakya, your dad's fooled you
His dad fooled him
How many done, Babbu didi?
180 couples done, 20 to go
20...
You. Come here
Married?
- Yes sir
What was the hurry?
Never mind
Get your wife
and get re-married
But sir...
- If she objects...
tell her you're
renewing your vows
She'll be thrilled.
Run, now
That makes 181 couples
Give me a minute
What's this?
- What's what?
What's this, Babbu didi?
Who told you to use
so many flowers?
Who does that to a Ferrari?
It's a wedding car -
it must have flowers
You're Mr. Mandke's
son, no less
If there were fewer flowers,
people would gossip
They'd call us stingy
They're gossiping now
Saying it's not a Ferrari
under the flowers...
it's an ordinary taxi
People will say anything
You know the truth.
You know it's a Ferrari
Walk the path of truth, son.
It's useful in the long run
You wronged me, Babbu didi
C'mon now...
You committed a fraud
Our deal is off
No compromise
At my wedding tomorrow,
I want the Ferrari
Without flowers on it
Go on, now
Told you to get an abortion
Look at what you produced
What kind of talk is that?
Mom...
What sort of guy did you marry?
If you had asked me,
I would've rejected him
Be quiet
You all go ahead
Pakya...
Don't say anything
Leave, I said
Going
Babbu didi, please handle this
The Press will not see
the Ferrari
That's final
That's my order
Then the Press will not see...
me wearing a number
That's my wish
You can't afford a wish,
you pipsqueak
Dad, no...
Don't mess with me, boy
Sir, couple no. 182
I'll see you at home
What happened?
Scram
I've always told you...
to stay away from cricket
It's made you into a thief now
The Great Gangster
of the Deboo family...
Rustom Behram Deboo
Papa, I have to
send Kayo to Lord's
Why are you so dense?
During recession in the
white man's land...
camps like this are invented
They look for gullible fools
like you, who fall for it
You want to go to prison?
In prison, hold a slate,
get your mug shots taken
Make your family famous
Cricket ruins you, I tell you
There're many dirty games
behind this sport
Answer this...
Who knows cricket best,
you or me?
Papa, I know...
- No, tell me...
who knows cricket best,
you or me?
Papa, I know some cricket too
I played well once
But you didn't let me play
Well, thank me for it
I saved you
Protected you
Papa, don't protect Kayo
Let him live his life
He's a gifted cricketer
He'll make you proud one day
That pint-sized rookie
a cricketer?
He knocks a ball in a sock
in the living room
That won't make him
a cricketer
Papa, you haven't
seen his game
He's captain of his team
In India, millions of kids
play cricket
From the city center,
if you hurl a pebble...
it'll land on a captain's head
Rusy
Remember this...
In a cricket team,
there are only eleven players
What of those who don't
make it to the team?
I'll tell you
They sit on a sofa,
stare at the
use a remote control,
and tuck into peanuts
You may as well put a
Kayo-sized sofa next to mine
Why are you destroying his life?
I'm not destroying his life
I'm helping him make it
You think he'll ever make it
to the top eleven?
No Papa
He's way ahead of the top eleven
No one is even close to him
Not even you
Know who you're talking to?
You're talking to
Behram Ardeshir Deboo
You know who you're talking to?
Papa, you were the bestest?
Bowl as many balls as you want
Just...
try and get him out
Kayo
Papa
Want to play a match?
A match?
Now?
With whom?
Papa?
He's asleep?
Yes Papa
Today's the selection?
You take Kayo for it
I'll get the money
Where will you get
the money from?
An old friend
He owes me one
I'll call you when
I get the money
You just get Kayo to the ground
You're looking good
Rusy
- Yes Papa?
Give Kayo this tip
Yes?
When...
a bowler bowls...
Go on, Papa.
When a bowler bowls...
No, let him play
the way he does
He'll knock them off their feet
Everyone ready?
- Yes sir
Let's go.
Batsman to my right
Bowlers to my left
I want to meet
Dilip Dharmadhikari
Well?
From my club, at least
one boy should go to Lord's
You want your son to go?
He really wants to go
Do something
You do something
about those TV rights
Consider it done
Then consider this done, too
Gattu Godbole,
his name. RC Club
Gattu Godbole. OK
Excuse me, sir.
Mr. Deboo's here to meet you
Who Deboo?
- Behram Deboo
6th floor
Deboo
After so many years
Please sit down
You've put on some weight
What will you have?
Tea? Coffee?
Beer?
One coffee, please
How many years
has it been, Deboo?
38 years
How time flies
So, to what do I
owe this honor?
38 years back...
I had a friend
We did everything together...
shared all secrets...
checked out pretty girls together
We made thousands of runs
together in record partnerships
Those were the days
Dilip
What you did to me...
After 38 years, you're here
to make me feel guilty?
No
- Is that so?
Not at all
That's not so
I'm ready to forget and forgive
If I do that...
then you're my only friend
Yes
You are my friend, yes?
- Of course
Well?
Dilip
I have a grandson
Deboo, you're a grandfather?
I don't look old enough, I know
He's a cricketer
Of course he is
You know that
cricket camp at Lord's?
He wants to go for that
Well, you see, I must tell you...
the selection is based on merit
And in this position,
I can't favor anyone
Hold it, Dilip
I'm not asking you
to do anything wrong
I'm just clarifying
I understand your position
He's so good,
he will be selected
The problem is the Rs. 150,000
to be paid after that
It's 150,000 yes
So I thought of some options
Can you ask the Board...
for a grant or scholarship?
No, it will not work out
If we do it for one,
we'll have to do it for others
And if the Press gets wind of it...
I know
In this position, actually,
my hands are tied
I understand
What now...
There's another option
As my friend...
can't you loan me Rs. 150,0007
Yeah?
One moment
I'll just be back
Kayoze - Net no. 2
Every gaze is fixed on you
Each heart harbors new hope
The crowds support you
So do what champions do
With a mighty bat,
make a hefty score
More...
He hits
Up and a way
In the air
A big hit
Thank you
Sir, he won't be back
Why?
I speak from experience
Sir
I'm a big fan
You took eight wickets...
on the dead pitch
of the Matunga Club
I still remember that clearly
Sir, an autograph please
Hello Papa? Any luck?
It'll work out, don't worry
How's our boy playing?
He's knocking them
off their feet
Papa, you went to meet
Dilip Dharmadhikari?
It didn't work out, did it, Papa?
It's ok Papa, we'll find a way
It'll work out, Papa.
Don't worry
Later... I'll call you later
Well played, Kayo
Nice
Sir, I have to leave
on some urgent work
Would you please
drop Kayo home?
Sure, no problem
Shot
Don't worry, I'll drop him
Get away from the car
Don't touch the car
Don't touch the hood
Everyone move back
Stop taking pictures
Who are you?
Rustom Behram Deboo,
Transport Office
So help me out here.
Move everyone away
Sir, I have an idea
There's Sachin
Where?
There
Sir, where are you off to?
To Sachin...
Sir, that was just to distract them
Before they're back,
put barricades here
I'll be back in ten minutes.
I have another idea
Thank you
Sir
Excuse me, sir
Sir, your scooter key
Thank you
- Mention not
Good news, old chap
No Ferrari has come
here for gas
In Mumbai, there are only
five gas stations...
that stock gas for the Ferrari
We've checked all five
This means...
the thief has gas for only 50 km
But 50 km in which direction?
The car may have gone
50 km this way...
while we go 50 km that way
That makes 100 km
Your brain measures
1 centimeter
Don't put a 100 km load on it
C'mon, start your Ferrari
My brain's not working
Give me the helmet
That scooter key looked like
the Ferrari key to me
Don't remind me of the key.
C'mon, hurry
And how much for this?
5000... 3000... 2000...
1500... 1500... 1500...
Rs. 1500...
What model, what size?
Tell me, Your Royal Highness?
Size... It's big
Is it a truck?
You need a large banner
Sorry
Excuse me
Sir
A banner
Banner?
Why a banner?
Lower it carefully
That's great
No one will touch it now
Clear off now
Sir, one moment
BCA?
Bombay Cricket Association?
Sir, I was once President
Of BCA?
No... Our BCA is...
Borivli Cricket Association
A cricket club for our constables
Sir, I'm famous for my
quarter centuries
Sir, you're here for
Sachin Tendulkar's car?
Who's the senior officer here?
Who brought Sachin's car here?
It wasn't me.
It was Inspector Mhatre
Get Inspector Mhatre
Get Mhatre here
Sir, Inspector Mhatre
plays football
He knows nothing of cricket
This is Sachin's car
He didn't know that
The car was in a
No Parking zone, so...
Yes, but how will I know if
the car's with cops or thieves?
It's like this, sir...
When we confiscate a car...
we make a chalk circle there
In it we write the name of
the police station the car is at
If you make a chalk mark...
and thousands walk over it...
won't it get erased?
Yes... But sir,
we have to follow orders
Who's the senior officer here?
Who's your senior?
I'm the senior-most, sir
But don't scold me sir, please
Did I scold you?
Did I get angry?
Did I raise my voice?
- No
Who dares to say
I scolded you?
I want to meet
your senior officer
Sir, take the car
Yes, take the car
I'll handle Inspector Mhatre
No fine, nothing
You must take the fine
- No sir
Sachin will scold me
Please sir,
I don't want anything
OK
But how do I take the car...
Sir, I'll get you a tow truck
It'll drop you where you want
Free of charge
- Totally free
Gautiya... Ashok...
Hello?
Hello Papa, this is Kayo
Yes son?
Papa, I got selected
I'm so proud of you, son
Kayo, listen - I got the money
Got the money?
Sir
One moment, sir
Papa, hold on
Sir, it's Papa.
He got the money
Rusy, congratulations
Today, both father and son
are victorious
Thank you, sir
Kayo sounds...
He's jumping with joy
Sir, I'll see you tomorrow
morning then
OK. Here, talk to him
Kayo listen
- Yes Papa?
I'll call you later
I'll call you.
I love you. Bye
Gautiya, let's go
- Gautiya, drive safe
Thank you, sir
What's wrong with Pakya?
Dad's here.
Give me the number plate
Whoever wants to take
a picture, take it now
Tomorrow's newspaper
should print this headline...
Politician's son commits suicide'
Pakya, what are you doing?
Get down
Yes, come down
At the wedding today,
I want the Ferrari
If the Ferrari is there...
I'll be there
If not, I'll go up there...
your vote bank
will go down there
Why are you doing this?
Get down. Come home
Mom, stop talking
You're talking too much
The People's Representative
is not talking at all
Lokre
Speak, o Savior of the Masses
You're so brave, aren't you?
OK, go ahead and jump
Jump or I'll shoot you, Pakya
Dad's going to shoot me, man
Don't be afraid, Pakya
1...
2...
Don't move, Pakya.
He won't shoot
3...
Melodramatic clown
Holding his father to ransom
What does he think he's doing?
Just get him the Ferrari
You think it's candy?
My dad wants to be famous
Now watch
In front of the Press,
I'll arrive in a Ferrari
Kayo
Papa
Hi son
See this - the money
The money?
I'm going to Lord's?
- Yes
My Papa's the bestest
I feel one boy from every club
should go to Lord's
It keeps everyone motivated
Ajay, has any club been left out?
Yes sir. JD club,
MBM club, RC club...
RC Club... I believe
it's a very good club
We should have a boy from there
Who's the President?
Mr. Godbole
Godbole...
Call up Godbole
Ask him to recommend a player
Sir
Sir, on the board is a shortlist
of our 16 best players
Yes, but some of these
will back out
That first name, for instance
Unfortunately, he doesn't
have the money
No sir, he has no such problem
His grandfather came to me...
for a fee waiver
He's automatically out
Teja
Hello?
It's Vilayat
Yes sir?
Rusy, you've got the money?
Yes sir
I've got the money.
I told you
But he's saying you
don't have the money
Wants to cancel
Kayo's selection
Who, sir?
Who's saying this?
Dharmadhikari
I see now. it's a
misunderstanding
I have the money, sir
Can you...
come to the club now?
Right away. It's important
Sir, I'll see you there then
Bring the money
- OK
Rusy
Now turn around
Go on
Hurry up
Wait here till I get back, ok?
All the boys been signed up?
Let's fly to London
And wish you all a great,
happy new year
Happy new year, sir
Good evening. Gentlemen,
sorry to come in like this
This is my son, Kayoze Deboo.
Actually, Vilayat...
Hello sir
Vilayat called me.
I'm here to tell you that...
I have Rs. 150,000
- One moment
What's this?
How did you get in?
The selection is over
I don't even know
if this boy plays well
He's better than you ever were
Bowl to him once
He'll smash you
Deboo. You're back?
Tell everyone here...
Didn't you say you
don't have the money?
Rusy
- Yes Papa?
Give me the car key,
I'll get the money
Papa, I have the money
Car key, Rusy,
don't argue
Papa, the money...
- The key, Rusy
I've brought the money
You also brought money?
Yes
- Amazing
Here, Dilip
Tell me if you want more
I have another 150,000 rupees
Take next year's fee,
if you want
Did you count it?
- Yes. It's 150,000
All good?
- Yes
Well?
My decision is final
The selection is over
You son-of-a...
- Wait Papa...
Papa, one moment
Papa, please
For 38 years, Papa has
battled you in his dreams
He's hit you
But he never realized
he was hurting himself...
while you were untouched
But today if you play dirty...
I'll forget you were
once Papa's friend
You'll get clobbered,
Mr. Dharmadhikari
Seriously clobbered
This boy was selected on merit
If he doesn't go to London...
all committee members will resign
You're going to London?
Take thermal underwear
so you don't freeze
Papa, can I go to the fountain?
Yes, go
Quickly tell me...
Where did you get
the money from?
I took it out of the Ferrari
The Ferrari?
I went to the police station,
covered the car, got in
I got in, but it was a
tense situation
The cops started towing
the car to Sachin's house
With me inside
I managed to slip out
with the money
Where did you get
the money from?
Give me a moment
- You must tell me
Tell me, Papa
Hold on. Give me a moment
Papa, tell me how
you got the money
I brought the car here
What car? The Ferrari?
Papa, this is Sachin's car
What is it doing here?
Gautiya dumped the car
and scooted
Give me the key, Rusy
We need to leave fast
Let's disappear
Yes, little one
You see...
the car came to your papa
for official work
I told your papa to get
the car home...
but your papa refused
So I called up Sachin
Sachin said - Please take it,
take the car
I'll top off the tank
and send it to you
I said there's a young
Sachin in my home
1... 2... 3...
What do we see...
Let's go drive all night.
Right, Rusy?
Come, sit
C'mon, enter your kingdom.
Very nice
Papa, we have to drop
the car off at Sachin's
Yes, I know.
We'll fly it there, you'll see
Hurry Rusy
Grandpa
Thank you
Does Sachin sit on this seat?
Since it's his car,
this is the seat he sits on
No seats behind, anyway
And this is the
steering wheel he holds?
When he drives, he has to
hold this steering wheel
You want to touch it?
Yes
- Go ahead
Such small fingers you have
1 2... and...
C'mon let's take a ride
Spin, roll or dip, you decide
It's a groovy trip all the way
In a oar that ain't a car...
but a whirlwind that
whisks you away
Fa fa fa fa...
Ra ra ra ri...
Fa fa fa fa... Ferrari
Sa sa sa sa...
Wa wa wa wa...
The swashbuckling
Ride in the Ferrari
Life bursts out,
bright and glamorous
From drab and dull
to unique and marvelous
We zip ahead without
a cars in the world now
It's a taste of
new adventure and cheer
Why waste the chance
we were given here
Let's dart away on
winged paths now
The heart holds sway
it must have its way
It's a magical night today
Fa fa fa fa...
Ra ra ra ri...
Fa fa fa fa... Ferrari
Sa sa sa sa...
Wa wa wa wa...
The swashbuckling
Ride in the Ferrari
It's a Ride in a Ferrari
A Ride in the Ferrari.. Yeah
Hello?
- Rusy, come home quick
What happened, Uncle Pesi?
There're some ruffians here.
They're asking for 'Rustom'
OK, I'm on my way
What happened, Papa?
Kayo, where's the money?
Here, in the bag
Pakya, the Ferrari
Kayo, stay inside
Rusy
Who are these people?
One moment
Who are these fellows?
Let me talk to them
Pakya, what's the problem here?
Tell me, do you people
have no other names?
I yelled 'Rustom' and
20 Rustoms came out
Then I asked them for the Ferrari
And they knew nothing of it
You didn't tell anyone
you have the Ferrari?
Pakya, what is the matter?
Please give me the Ferrari key
I can't. I have to return the car now
Look wise guy...
- Easy, Pakya
It's ok, man
I've cleared this with Babbu didi
You can check with her
Don't mess with me
Give me the Ferrari key
Pakya, that's not possible
Pakya, I'm sorry,
that's not possible'
Smart-ass
Pakya
Why don't you speak to Babbu didi...
Papa
Rusy, shall I call the cops?
- No, I'll take care of it
OK, enough of your antics
Let go of me.
Pakya, this is wrong
Pakya, you can't take this car
I'm taking it. Get lost
Papa
This is Sachin's car.
You can't take it
My papa got it from office
Get out
Hey mister, don't touch him
You can't take it.
It came to my papa's office
How can you take it?
It's my papa's...
Listen squirt, he stole it.
From Sachin
Hey Bandit King -
you didn't tell him?
Papa, you stole Sachin's car?
What the...
Kayo, I...
Where do you think
you're taking the car?
Stop, scoundrel
Kayo, wait here
Papa
Taxi
Mohan
It's almost midnight
Boss will be here soon
Tell me...
how much cash
do you have on you?
Look, a mobile temple
I have 500 bucks, Mohan
But it's still ten days
to my next salary
You'll get the next salary
only if you get the Ferrari
C'mon, offer it all to God
Only He can save us now.
C'mon, let's donate this
Peace and Wealth breeze in,
Suffering beats a retreat
The Ferrari
Ferrari
The Ferrari!
It's the Ferrari, yes
Mohan, this way
Hurry
Pakya
Get back inside
Found our Ferrari
Where?
- There, ahead
What happened?
I don't know
The Ferrari stopped
Maybe the carburetor is clogged
Go check it, quick
Open the hood
Which button do I press?
Press all the buttons
It's open
Pakya
What?
The engine fell out
There's no hole underneath
How did it fall out?
Back off
Mohan
The engine's gone
The engine's in
Shamshu's furnace
This car's engine is
in the back, you blockhead
Look in the back
Pakya, the engine's here
The engine is safe
in a glass box
You. How did you know
the engine was in the back?
This is our boss's car
We also own an Alto, a Scorpio...
Tell him, Mohan
- Right
This is our boss's car.
Move away
If it's your boss's car...
tell me why it has stalled
Well, you see...
But why should I tell you?
Yes, who're you to ask?
Move aside
Go, Head of Security
- Take out the gun
What's wrong with the car?
The car's run out of gas
Now what?
Let's take gas from that scooter
Take gas from the scooter,
put it into the car
It's like this...
You don't put regular gas
into a Ferrari
A special kind goes into it
And only we know
where to get it
Listen up
Pakya
- Quiet
Look, I need your help
This is your boss's Ferrari?
Get me to my wedding
in this Ferrari
Once I get there...
the car's yours.
You can take it back
If you don't help me,
then this engine...
No, don't
How will we get him there?
The Ferrari is out of gas
Well?
The trials of life...
I have an idea
are eased by the Lord
Mohan, how much
farther is the gas station?
Why don't you take
the bullock's place?
We may reach faster
Any fractures?
- No sir
Hello, Uncle Pesi?
Rusy here
Could you please check on
Kayo at my house?
He's not answering the phone
Thank you
He looks fine
Let's get a CT scan
- OK sir
Rusy, Kayo is nowhere
You come home quick
Those goons were hanging
around for a long time
Kayo
Rusy, where're you going?
- They're dangerous guys
The dawn of auspicious days
Welcome, my friends
from the Press
Today, I give 201 couples
a loan-free life
No. 176 - Please come here
Of these, 200 are my social work
And 1 is my homework
My son Pakya
The Ferrari
Prakash Mandke, No. 201
That brings me to the end...
TV crews
- Long live India
Here, look here
Here
- What's happening?
Hit it
I will show you...
I will give you Breaking News
Here a Pakya...
there a Pakya
Reporters, tell me
how many Pakyas?
So who's the real Pakya?
Follow me
You see this groom?
Now see my dad's social work
Look at this
Grandpa
His grandson is older than me
That concludes
what I had to say...
Oh no you don't
Who's this 201 ?
C'mon 201 , lift your veil
Show yourself
What is this?
- Melodrama
I've learnt from what
I've seen since childhood
Should I shoot?
Aren't these your words?
1...
Should I shoot... 2...
Should I shoot? Take this
What're you doing, son?
Watch it
It's Babbu didi
Dad's made
laughing stock of you too
Pakya, where's my son?
Look, his son's also missing
Babbu didi?
Pakya
Tell me where my son is,
or I'll shoot
Tell me
Mom, I don't know
where his son is
My son would never do that
He would never kidnap
someone's child
Rusy, wait
Where's his son?
I swear I don't know.
Ask them
Where's his son?
When we left, he was
running towards the sea
And he was crying
Mom, this guy stole the Ferrari
His son got to know
I think he's gone towards
the sea to commit suicide
Be quiet
Suicide? Your son's
committed suicide?
You've lost your son.
How do you feel?
Do you think he killed himself?
Where must he be?
- What happened, sir?
Where is your son?
What is your answer?
Everyone look here
If you live near the beach,
please come out of your home
Please rush to the beach
If you see a child running,
please stop him
He's my son, Kayo
He runs very fast
Don't let him go near the water
Not into the sea
My son's this high
4 feet, 9 inches
Dusky skin
This is him
He's always smiling
Kayoze Rustom Deboo.
His full name
Kayo, I didn't know what to do
Couldn't get a loan from work
The bank refused me a loan
I didn't mean to steal, Kayo
I made a mistake
Grandpa is right
We shouldn't dream at all
Please give me back my Kayo.
I can't live without him
If you want to Contact me,
call me on my phone...
Listen, you guys
search Girgaum beach
I'll check Dadar and Juhu beach
Keep in touch with me.
Call me every 5 minutes
I'm just leaving home...
I'll call you back
Kayo, where have you been?
Sir, Papa...
Sir, the police will take
Papa away. Please help me
Whoever finds my son
can have my apartment
It has one bedroom
and a large living room
Just find my son please
Rusy?
Please help me
Hello?
Rusy
Papa, Kayo's gone
Kayo's gone
Papa
Kayo
Where were you?
I'm sorry, son
I'm sorry, Kayo
I'm really sorry,
I shouldn't have done it
If I don't go to Lord's,
you think I won't play cricket?
I have the world's best coach
He'll train me
And you know, Sachin
didn't train at Lord's
He trained right here,
at Shivaji Park
And became the No. 1 cricketer
I'll be No. 1 too
100 centuries
Don't be upset, Papa
C'mon, be a good boy
Tomorrow, if I tell you
I want to go to the moon...
will you steal a spaceship
from NASA?
You understand, Papa?
I understand, Kayo
Now you'll say -
Look at the brighter side of life
Actually yes, Papa
If I'd gone to Lord's,
I would have gone alone
When I'm selected
for the Indian team...
I'll take you with me
I'll tell the Cricket Board clearly...
If you want Kayo in the team,
you have to take Papa along
I can't sleep without you
And who will wake me
for the match in the morning?
My Kayo's grown up
Grown up too soon
The flight has landed
Boss is back
Sorry, but can you
please hurry up?
Our boss's flight has landed
We have to take the Ferrari back
Babbu didi,
please return this money
Pakya, could you...
Thank you
The key, sir
Please forgive me
I must ask Sachin
for forgiveness too
Not today, sir.
We'll handle it from here
Meet him another day
You can take a photo
with him too
Yes. Sorry, got to rush now
Yes, I'll open it
Pandey, Boss not back yet?
Boss is back
When?
- Right now
Open it, quick
Please don't tell anyone
I gave out the Ferrari key
that I opened the gate
I would've lost my
status in the village
Saved
- Don't worry
Well done
Kayo
You know something?
You put a ball into a sock
and kept knocking it
That really irritated me
Now throw away that rotting sock
I'll come to the nets.
I will train you
You will play for India
You don't need to
go to London
Those players
should come here
We could teach
them a thing or two
Stop here
C'mon little one,
give me a hand
Who are these people?
Uncle Rusy, put Rs. 50 in this
There you go
It's done
We'd collected Rs.149,950
Now we have the complete
amount of 150,000
This is for you
But what is all this?
Rusy, our Kayo will
go to London now
Uncle Rusy...
this lady contributed
the largest bundle
Come on up
The gentleman from the bank
also put in a big amount
And everyone from the colony
brought in 50,000 rupees
Now where's the gentleman
from the shop?
I'm here
And these are the shoes
you had marked
Kayo
All of us saw you on TV
Thank you, but I can't take this
Why not?
We're not giving it
to you for nothing
We all want a ride
in the Ferrari
But the Ferrari is back
at Sachin's house
Sachin's Ferrari?
Want Sachin's Ferrari?
- No
We don't want Sachin's Ferrari
We want our Kayo's Ferrari
Look, he will play for
India some day, right?
Will he?
- Definitely
There, Papa has spoken
So when Kayo plays for India,
won't he buy a Ferrari?
Won't he?
- Definitely
Then it's settled
So this is the rental fee for
Kayo's Ferrari, in advance
Thank you, but I can't...
When you get the EPF loan,
return everyone's money
But I don't know...
if you'll get the
EPF loan before.”
you get Kayo's Ferrari
Hey King of Honesty,
don't think so much
The signal's turn green.
Zoom off to London
Hey Champion of Truth,
send him off
May this mind...
its thoughts and deeds
Every stride and step
Tread the path of Truth
Stand strong...
On the tough, honest path
Ana' remain fearless
and unwavering
Always, with head held high
Hurry up, Rusy
There he is... There's Kayo
C'mon Kayo
He's hit a 6...
Ana' now a 4
Something zooms up. . .
Look, it's our score!
Go Kayo
He's hit a 6...
Ana' now a 4
Something zooms up. . .
Look, it's our score!
The crowds hunger for runs. . .
They gotta have more
More...
A big hit