Mother.. I've heard that..
a beautiful world
exists beyond this village.
Big cities, grand markets and..
huge houses where
movies can be seen.
There's nothing of that sort.
Now get down.
Mother, you always break my dreams.
Dreams are meant to be broken.
Get down.
- No, I won't.
You won't?
What if I make you fall? Tell me.
You're my mother.
You'll make me fall?
If your mother makes you fall,
she will also help you to your feet.
If you fall in the city,
no one will help you to your feet.
Get down.. now!
No, I won't.
Get down.
Mother..
When He has blessed you with
one life, why think twice?
We barely get down to it...
and the bitch next
door is already on a roll!
Forget about her, darling.
Why don't you soothe
what's excited in here?
Get off!
Now go to sleep. We
aren't doing it anymore.
Bloody idiots!
They can't do anything
without making a sound.
Marbles, cricket...
the choicest abuses...
He even made me wear boy's clothes.
If my father had his way...
he would even make me tease girls!
Didn't your mother ever stop him?
She gave birth to a girl instead of a
boy, so she remained a mute spectator.
Amma, tell me something...
I have what boys desire.
So, who is better?
Me or a boy?
Stop talking nonsense.
It's all rubbish!
Now don't be so coy. You're no less.
I can tell a lot of men have
been hard at work over here.
Stop it!
What?
Last night was fun.
Tonight could be even better.
My wife has a night-shift...
so tonight...
I merely touched you and it leaked...
your pen!
If I come over, what
will become of you?
You bitch!
My wife is right about you.
She is right about you too!
You like to go riding but you can
barely stay on for a few seconds.
You are mine...
so why hide from you...
You can take a peek.
When you will truly be mine,
then you can see the entire picture!
You can go in...
You can also go in...
You are out...
you can go back.
Okay, you can go in.
You are out.
- Sir... - You can't come in.
- The selection is done. - Sir,
sir... I want to be an actor, sir.
And I wanted to be a director.
Sir, I don't want to
dance like other girls.
I want to act, sir.
And I wanted to make offbeat films.
Sir, I'll do
anything to become an actor.
And to become a director
I could not do anything.
Would you like to see
what's not in these pictures?
Do you want to hear
the story of my film?
Sir, you aren't even listening to me.
Sir, step out of your film.
And you step out of your dreams.
There are 25 like
you waiting outside...
and tomorrow there will be 50 more.
You're good for nothing.
Neither do you have the seductive charm
of a lover nor the grace of a wife.
You are very dull.
I've been living on
sugar for two days...
so how can I look spicy?
Hold on...
take this and have something to eat.
And think about what you
want to do with your life.
Not everyone can become an actor.
Let's go somewhere else.
Why?
We can be by ourselves
at some late night show.
It will be fun.
I'll pay you.
How much?
20 rupees.
Only 20 rupees for me?
Take it.
Bloody pervert!
You're at the end of your life
and you want a fresh climax?
Neither do you have the seductive charm
of a lover nor the grace of a wife.
You are very dull.
Not everyone can become an actor.
There are 25 like
you waiting outside...
and tomorrow there will be 50 more.
Just a minute...
I'm not dull.
Who are you? What do you want?
Don't you remember?
You gave me some money
before rejecting me.
Here's your money.
I'm sure I have something for
which that guy forked out 20 rupees.
Sudhir, where is that girl?
How do I shoot the song sequence?
Where do I get a girl who
won't mind ripping her own skin?
Your whip scares the girls away...
You want me to do it?
Think you can bear the pain?
I bore it for so long, I'm
sure I can bear it ahead too.
Pan the camera.
Some say the glass is half full...
some say it's half empty.
And some are like Silk.
They say at least there is a drink.
Enjoy it.
It's stupidity.
But often stupidity manages
to get things done that...
hard work and intelligence can't.
Sir...
Sir... sir...
You want to take the camera
through the girl? - Do you?
What sort of a shot is this?
You horny bastard, filthy mind...
- Sir... - Shut up!
You play the flute behind my
back and now you want to sing!
Give me that reel.
Please sit, sir...
I left the shot for one
day and see what happened.
Where is it? Stop it!
Sir, we'll cut it, please...
If you don't cut the reel,
I'll cut you somewhere...
and then you won't know
whether to wear trousers or skirts!
What's the occasion, Amma?
You're all dressed to kill.
Who is the poor guy?
Check out the newspaper,
your movie is out today.
Aren't we going for
‘first day, first show'?
Look...
Amma...
wait here, I'll just get ready.
Everybody should know that...
every film has only one hero...
Director!
Every film one hero...
Who?
Director!
Everybody is staring at you.
Who is that?
- The director.
Oh...
- Come on!
Take off your sunglasses.
Where is our seat?
Amma, we'll watch my
first film from up close.
You mean it's the first row?
Here it is.
No, here.
- Wow, it's Selva
Ganesh's film. - Yes!
His films are entertaining.
Off with your sunglasses.
- Amma... - Yes?
Mark my words, now all
my problems will go away.
The dance director said
he liked my performance.
Really?
Another thing, Amma...
My life has moved from
‘pack up' to ‘action'.
Now I won't let it slip away.
Hey! Shhh!
Stop talking.
What do you mean 'shhh'?
She is the heroine.
She is the heroine?
The heroine?
If she is the heroine,
can I get a refund?
Is this your song?
No.
This one?
Probably this is your song.
No...
Where is it?
Where is your song?
Miss Heroine...
heroine...
Can I at least have your autograph?
What has she done?
She's there in the whole film.
Reshma...
Madam... can I have your autograph?
People in Hollywood are
probably wondering..
..why I am wasting
my talent in India.
I wish you had left for Hollywood
before putting me into a loss.
I would have been better off.
Sir, you haven't
tasted real respect yet.
Nayla has written
such a fantastic review.
Look at the wonderful
things that have been printed.
Hey... You english show-off!
I would've been happy if at
least the tickets were sold.
Sir, you wait and watch...
because of this film, you
will have a trophy in your hand.
And a begging bowl in the other.
Nowhere in the film did
the 'hero reason' come alive.
Not 'hero reason'.
It's heroism.
If you know it, why
didn't you portray it?
Sir, the thing is...
one man thrashing a dozen bad guys and a
dozen hot girls falling for one man...
doesn't click with the audience.
Real films are those that
compel the audience to think.
The audience wants to
feel something else...
and you want them to feel their mind?
Sir...
Abraham sir deleted one song.
That song would have worked wonders.
Which song?
This one... take a look.
Let me watch it.
Dear friend...
you should go to Hollywood.
We will miss you but you should go.
You robbed the film of its life!
Life?
You mean... that fatso...
I will add this song as
a special feature and...
release the film
again in smaller towns.
That will definitely
recover some money.
Abraham, what are you doing?
what are you doing?
Abraham... what are you doing?
What did you do that for?
You've set the positive on fire.
I still have the negative.
Mark my words, this girl
will set the screen on fire!
Hey, What are you doing?
I'm taking a picture.
You can't do that, get out!
Ticket, ticket...
Blackie!
Blackie... listen...
I want a ticket.
Not you again!
The amount you have spent
on watching this film...
would have got you the girl.
- Are you serious? - Of course!
Selva Ganesh has
proved once again that...
he will go to any
length to make money.
This is not a film,
it's a volley of abuses.
This is the respect that I like.
The more these critics pan my film,
the more my film will earn for me.
Well done, Vimal. Good job.
Thank you, sir.
I want this girl.
If merely her glimpse can
arouse the crowd to this extent...
imagine what will happen if
she danced to an entire song!
Get her.
But sir, I don't know who
she is or where she came from.
Well then, find out.
I'm sure someone knows.
If she is present in the song, surely
she hasn't appeared out of thin air.
Find her!
Yes, sir.
This girl will be my
biggest discovery.
Who is it?
What is it?
G...G...G...
G... G... what? Who are you?
What do you want?
Money!
What's this?
That's one less than hundred.
Why?
I bought this for one rupee.
Are you high? Should I
bring you back to reality?
Forgot everything?
Film... I saw your film.
Ever since then I've
been saving up for you.
You are lying!
I haven't acted in any film.
Go away from here...
get lost!
The middle word in life is... "if".
The big "if'!
If only that bastard Selva Ganesh
had spent five more minutes..
..in the bathroom...
if only he had driven 5 kmph slower...
everybody's life would
have remained the same.
But no.
He was eager to screw me and how!
Even sitting on a
couch didn't feel safe.
The sun arose that morning
to shine bright on Reshma...
and to burn me to ashes.
Baby, should I call for more?
Enough, Amma.
Baby, all the people who've had
breakfast with me in the past...
today enjoy dinner at 5-star hotels.
Join hands with me and the world
will praise you with hands joined.
Have some more... keep eating.
And you will be the best.
I can see it, you have that...
desire.
Silk!
Today onwards your name is Silk.
And your name is Mr. Worm.
What?
Silk is created by worms.
Baby, whether I'm
Selva Ganesh or Mr. Worm...
but all I am is an
opportunity for you.
And this opportunity
won't come by again...
it will only go to someone else.
Okay, sir...
music...
One, two, three, four...
Silk, no heat...
no heat!
We want to titillate the public...
not put them to sleep.
And sir, extraordinary shot.
Sir, extraordinary...
but one more, sir, please.
Cut it!
Silk, what are you doing?
Imagine Surya sir is
a log of sandalwood.
And you are a serpent...
wrap yourself around him.
And Surya sir, very good shot.
But she's a newcomer, sir.
One more shot, sir, please.
George...
Surya gives only one take. That's it.
Here I am...
Sir, please, sir...
A day with Surya is worth
a hundred thousand rupees!
Understand?
A good looking fruit
isn't always sweet!
Set up my solo shot.
Hey you...
come here.
What's your name?
Reshma...
Silk.
Two names to go by and you
can't do one silly step.
See this...
plastic cover?
Whether it's there or not...
it makes no
difference to the cigarette.
Similarly...
whether you are in this film or not...
it makes no difference to anyone.
You know something...
if there's no cover and it rains...
the cigarette won't even light up.
Pack up!
Heroine says that it's going to rain.
I've been hit by a
shoe because of you.
But I won't let it happen again.
You made Surya sir very angry.
You go!
And don't ever come back.
What are you doing in here?
I'm here to get tuned, and
then we can make some music.
You switched your
melody pretty quickly.
It's your personality, sir.
I've been admiring you
since I was a little girl.
I was scared to be next to you.
Now that's believable.
If God puts in an appearance...
the devotee is bound to be scared.
Sir, please give me another chance.
Why should 1?
I'll be devoted to you.
I'll do anything you want me to.
Don't you read the magazines?
The magazines say that...
I've tuned 500 girls.
But have you ever
tuned one girl 500 times?
- Is it true about the 500... - No...
501!
Sir, Surya won't act with her.
Sir, there they come.
I guess Surya sir is all charged up.
Suryakant may die but he
won't let go of a new girl.
Cut...
What?
She's doing it all wrong again,
she missed a beat.
To hell with the beat,
look at that heat...
she'll set everyone on fire.
Extraordinary, sir, very good, sir.
Mind-blowing, sir,
very good shot, sir.
Madam...
ticket please.
That's your seat, sit there.
How does it matter?
This place is empty.
I don't want problems later.
Go and sit according to your ticket.
Mother...
congratulate me.
Your son has stood first in college.
Bless you, my dear.
You've fulfilled all my wishes.
If only your dad were alive today...
Cut it!
Very good shot, Surya sir.
Excellent shot.
Just like a young boy.
That was... that was very good.
You are very convincing as my mother.
Naylaji!
What a pleasure, what brings you here?
Last month's
magazine hasn't sold well?
Probably because you
didn't grace the cover!
So what's brewing... under cover?
This is new!
Lalitha was the heroine in your
last film and both of you were hot.
And now she is playing your mother?
You see...
youth is meant to be tasted...
not wasted!
A heroine's life...
is like an elected government.
The party lasts for five years...
after that it's there for support.
Sometimes left... sometimes right...
and sometimes even centre!
I've heard that new girl, Silk, is a
passionate supporter of your party.
Everybody is talking about her.
Of course, I gave her a break.
She is very talented.
When God has blessed
her so abundantly...
there's no harm in
taking a piece of the pie.
Right?
You know me...
I believe the more I can be of
help to others, the better it is.
But she is a quite down market.
You write up on her was perfect.
Well, I have to, Surya sir.
To portray men as saints...
women have to be depicted as demons.
Sir, madam is here.
Yes.
See you later.
What about my interview?
We'll do it later.
This is important.
Quick, some filter coffee for madam.
Is Silk here?
The cinema hall was filled with men...
every one of them only to see me.
And as soon as the
song was over, they left.
It was amazing.
Don't be so excited.
Take a look at what
Nayla has to say about you.
Who is Nayla?
The most important film
critic and gossip queen.
When she writes,
everybody pays attention.
She says Selva took the
help of dirt to sell his film.
Dirt...
that's you.
Look at my picture, it's so gorgeous.
Now, I will stop at nothing.
Help me with more work...
But why should I help you?
Because I love you and...
we still have 499 times
remaining to get tuned.
Come in...
So, Akbar and Anarkali
are on talking terms?
Sir, good sense of humour, sir.
Abraham, this is Silk.
Hello.
Surya sir, I want to talk
to you about my next film.
And this film will showcase you.
You won't need a cheap and
disgusting act to promote this film.
Abraham, everybody
knows you make good films.
Thank you, sir.
I owe it all to idli, rasam and rum.
But your films aren't...
commercially successful.
They captivate the
audience at film festivals but...
they fail to bring in even
a dog at local theatres.
Is that right?
Right, sir.
Spice it up, Abraham, spice it up.
Add some sex.
Have Silk dance to a number
or two, whatever you like.
Let me tell you...
successful films are those that...
have the right spice.
Right, Selva?
You are genius, sir.
It's a curse, Selva. It's a curse.
Sir, I'm a director, not a pimp.
I want to make a film, not sell sex.
Perhaps you can work with
that cheap girl but I can't!
Right.
Fine, Selva you direct it.
Okay, sir.
Then bye.
I wasn't dejected that
they chose Silk over me...
I was dejected that
they decided so quickly.
Why do you have a problem with me?
I have a problem with your parents.
They shouldn't have
given birth to you.
My parents didn't give birth to me.
Silk was brought into this world...
by the people who admire me.
Your admirers occupy the
first four rows in a cinema hall.
The 40 rows at the back are mine.
I will prove that films don't
need gimmicks like you to sell.
Films need three things to sell...
entertainment,
entertainment, entertainment!
And I am entertainment.
A woman is like a rainbow.
As many faces as the colors.
Some consider her a lottery.
If you win, you've hit the jackpot!
Some think of her as love.
If you fall in love with her...
you will gasp for every breath!
But she ravaged me like poison.
That now even water
burns me up from inside!
Your sweet torment
surreptitious torment
Here and around
I am angry
you are the reason
Cajole me my love
I will tease you
you are a bombastic girl
Aha Aha Aha
Ooh la la, Ooh la Ia,
Ooh lala, Ooh lala
You are my fantasy
Don't touch me, Don't touch me,
Don't touch me, Don't touch me
I am a young lady now
Ooh la la, Ooh la Ia,
Ooh lala, Ooh lala
You are my fantasy
Don't touch me, Don't touch me,
Don't touch me, Don't touch me
I am a young lady now
When touched by you
my heart whistled
Give me a sweet kiss on my cheeks
When touched by you
my heart whistled
Give me a sweet kiss on my cheeks
Your youth, is fluid
which has drenched my heart
Aha you brought the rain
what could my poor youth do?
Ooh la la, Ooh la Ia,
Ooh lala, Ooh lala
You are my fantasy
No no no no no
Don't touch me, Don't touch me,
Don't touch me, Don't touch me
I am a young lady now
By dropping your saree repeatedly
you make me restless
After storming a fire in me
what can the poor saree do
Poor thing
Oh poor thing
I will tease you
you are a bombastic girl
Oh no
Ooh la la, Ooh la Ia,
Ooh lala, Ooh lala
You are my fantasy
Ah ah
Don't touch me, Don't touch me,
Don't touch me, Don't touch me
I am a young lady now
Hey hey hey hey
Ooh la la, Ooh la Ia,
Ooh lala, Ooh lala
You are my fantasy
Oh oh
Don't touch me, Don't touch me,
Don't touch me, Don't touch me
I am a young lady now
You want to interview me?
At my place?
This evening... great!
- Amma... - What is it?
it was a call from Manorama magazine.
They want to interview me.
They want to show the
world how stars live.
No film star lives like you do.
Refuse them.
Amma, these opportunities
don't come by again and again...
they will only pass
on to someone else.
What will you show?
The tiny room you live in?
I brought this deer from Africa.
Superb, sir.
This gun is an antique from Bulgaria.
Sir, deep breath, stomach in.
Click my picture...
Go away... get lost!
Oops... you're early.
Ma'am...
I can come back later.
Now that you are here,
let's begin the interview.
You mean like this?
But have you worn something?
Do you bathe with your clothes on?
No.
Exactly!
Having a bath with your
clothes on is cheating...
and Silk doesn't cheat.
What you see is what you get!
What are you doing?
You are only taking my pictures
What about my house?
When the goddess is
present in her full glory...
who cares about the temple?
Thanks to Silk I was out of work.
All day and night
she danced in my mind.
But she didn't care a
damn about these things.
She was running in a race...
where you must look straight ahead.
Sir...
Silk is very good at
creating headlines.
But this isn't right, sir.
A girl, that too an actress...
moreover on the front page!
Bad news, sir.
She's flying high.
Let her.
No matter how high the popcorn goes...
it always falls back in the pan.
Excellent, sir, excellent!
That's brilliant!
What are you looking for?
Someone from Manorama
had interviewed me too...
but those idiots
didn't print anything!
When will you grow up?
You brought all this
to your new house too!
What if Surya sees it?
He will be pleased
that before I met him...
I would make do with his pictures.
Surya and you are worlds apart.
I'm worried.
A thousand girls like
you are crazy for him.
And a thousand guys
like him are crazy for me.
What's to worry?
We have the world at our feet.
He has another life...
he is married.
If I had met him earlier,
perhaps he would have married me...
and I would've been his wife's place.
"If", ‘perhaps', 'l would've been'...
when these words crop up in love,
it's better to step back.
Amma, I know I don't
have any right on Surya.
But what can I do?
There are no brakes in love.
Let's talk about something else, Amma.
You know something, sit...
do you hear that?
What?
- Listen carefully.
I don't hear anything.
Precisely! That's the
best part of living here.
You don't hear the
neighbours and no unwanted sounds.
Silk, make it more seductive.
This scene should
make the public go wild.
Make it hot.
Leave me!
Mr. Worm, take your shot.
That was fantastic.
What a shot!
Very good, very good...
So Silk...
were you thinking about Surya sir?
Why think about someone, with
whom I can be whenever I want to!
Ratnamma, I have
dialogues in this film.
I'm very nervous.
Why?
People will laugh at me.
Why did the Worm
have to have a premiere?
I won't attend the premiere.
Why not?
Ratnamma, I'm a dancer.
I don't even have the
‘ting' of acting in me.
You listen to me
nothing will happen...
I know her... listen to me.
Let me at least talk to her.
- Silk madam... - You can't go in.
Ratnamma... I'll call you later.
Just let me talk to her!
Silk madam... Silk madam!
Madam...
how are you, madam?
You!
Silk madam... how are you?
I'm good.
God is playing games with me.
I thought...
a thousand rupees
might be enough but...
you... you seem to be... very rich.
Even a million won't be enough.
You know something...
you've been lucky for me.
Every time you appear...
something good definitely happens.
Now you're leaving me high and dry.
I'm giving the security
guard a thousand for the kiss.
Thanks a lot, madam.
You are very nice.
Some people make
films touch the heart.
Some people make films touch the mind.
The body part they wanted to touch...
well, this film was a hit there!
Thank you...
- Very nice. - You liked it?
What a film, what a film!
You liked it?
Like?
I haven't seen such a
disgusting film in my life.
There's something nice
and superb about this film.
Silk?
Now you will realise that to make a
good film you need a good director...
not a dancer!
But don't you worry.
You think this film will do well?
Not a chance.
But I am still
willing to work with you..
because you gave me my first break.
Here...
have this and...
even the abuses will sound sweet.
Mr. Worm!
That bastard ripped everything apart!
Forget about him.
I am sure even his
alcohol is as bad as him.
But...
what if his words come true?
We haven't made this film for him.
Our fate will be decided on Friday.
Industry has sunk to new lows...
thanks to Selva Ganesh and...
more importantly Silk.
By Nayla.
Down with Silk!
Hello Silk...
It's been so long.
Is this the first time you're here?
You act very well even in reality!
Sir, a little closer, please.
Yes, that's fine.
Let's go inside.
The action always takes place inside.
All night you stick to me like glue...
otherwise you don't
even want to hold me.
Hello...
Control yourself, Silk.
The people here know me.
If my wife hears about this,
it won't be good.
See you later at the farmhouse.
So, now what?
Enjoy the race.
Lay a bet on a good horse.
I've bet on you.
Don't let me down.
Evening... farmhouse.
That's Silk.
What is she doing here?
Are people like her allowed in here?
Let alone her films, I
don't even look at the posters!
You!
You are... here at the race course...
Why not?
Can't I come to the race course?
I'm a star too.
You think only these
well dressed people
with their English
accents can come here?
You are Silk, aren't you?
Yes, so what?
I am your fan.
I didn't think
anybody here would know me.
Apart from a dozen
horses and a few asses...
there's no one here
who doesn't know you.
Thank you.
I want to lay a wager
that number 9 will win.
How do I do it?
Silk madam, don't bet on that horse.
This horse has never won.
Nobody has ever bet on him.
Did anyone imagine that
India would defeat West Indies
in the cricket world cup final?
But India won!
If nobody bets on him,
why will he win?
He's a horse, not an ass.
Here's the money.
It will.
Ramakant sir...
finally someone bet on your horse.
This horse never won a race for me...
but I hope he wins this race for Silk.
Come on come on, Mountain Storm.
At night you prefer to be like
the hands of a clock at 12 o'clock.
But during the day,
your clock says 6 o'clock.
I have to control, Silk.
Yesterday if we were seen together...
you would've lost nothing...
but I would've lost everything.
So, which horse did you bet on?
The horse that won.
I'm the horse that wins.
- Surya! - Radhika!
Go hide in there...
Surya!
Yes? Just coming...
Go in will you...
Go in...
Press my head no one does it like you.
Silk never took the easy path.
Then how could her life ever be easy?
She had broken a million hearts...
and now her heart was at stake.
People say only the heart
breaks but they're wrong.
Every single part of the
body goes into mourning.
The throat becomes dry...
and cheeks remain cold...
eyes welled up with tears...
and heart... empty.
I learnt about Silk's
misery much later...
otherwise I would've celebrated.
Excuse me!
Are you alright?
Why wouldn't I be?
Should I get a taxi for you?
Why? Don't you have a car?
You... will come along... with me?
Why not? Are you going to rape me?
What?
Why would you say that?
Excuse me...
just a minute, please.
Don't worry. Just do it.
What?
You aren't the first man to think...
‘while shifting the gear if
I could somehow touch her.'
What... no...
I wasn't thinking of that.
You work for Suryakant?
I'm his brother.
Suryakant... Ramakant...
brothers.
Did you see his wife go in?
Yes.
That's when you figured that...
since the permanent one
is in, I will sneak out.
One brother takes me to bed and...
the other is
erecting a bed in his mind!
Why are your
thoughts always so twisted?
Because virtue doesn't
stand a chance in this world.
What do you do?
I'm a writer. I write.
Which was your last film?
I haven't got the first one yet.
And you'll never get one.
Why not?
According to you, there's
only one hero in your family.
And that's Suryakant.
According to you, who is he?
Hero or...
a villain?
I've given up classifying people.
Moreover...
the hero and villain don't matter...
because I'm the vamp in every story.
I want to go home...
will you take me there?
Yes.
You see that window?
I escaped from it on
the eve of my wedding.
Won't you go in?
Mother...
This award goes to Silk.
And to give this award...
I would like to call Mr. Suryakant.
I want to present an award to the
person who chose Silk for this award.
She is despicable and...
the person who chose her even worse.
But mister... who the hell are you?
Abraham...
director.
Been a long time since I saw you.
I finally realised...
where to be seen and where not.
Success has gone to your head.
But many like you have come and gone.
I haven't come here to go away.
Look, I'm up here and
the others are down there.
You think the people
down there adore you?
They are laughing at you.
They know very well that
you don't belong with us.
You are the fantasy from last night..
..that nobody talks about
the next morning.
You are our dirty secret!
At least say thanks...
I really don't know
where to begin from.
If I begin right at the start,
my mother will be hurt.
If I talk about the present,
you might feel offended.
Because today I won't stop.
Everybody's right eye is twitching
and heart on the left is throbbing...
anticipating what I'm about to say.
You must be
wondering why you ever put...
a nobody like me on a pedestal.
Some people are famous
because of what they do.
I'm infamous for what I do.
Vulgar...
disgusting...
sexy...
dirty...
the words that are
applied to describe me.
Just so someone's
film could take off...
I was used as a boarding pass.
Yet people say I'm vulgar.
You made me dance...
but nobody noticed my
effort or my sincerity.
You were busy noticing something else.
Yet you label me disgusting...
sexy...
My films are not meant to be
watched with the family but...
people watch them alone and
end up with a bigger family.
If I open a few buttons...
then everyone will break into a sweat.
Don't you worry...
I'm leaving...
because except for me,
everyone else here is honourable.
But I must say, your
honour is unbelievable.
You make films about sex,
you sell them...
you watch them, you show them...
you even present them with awards...
but you're scared to acknowledge them.
Neither will you change, nor will I.
Wrap yourself with your
so-called-honour and...
I will carry on shedding my clothes.
I will continue making
these Dirty Pictures.
And I will bring these
Dirty Pictures before you.
Who are you?
Nayla.
Oh!
So it is you who writes
all the bad stuff about me.
It will be bad if I
stop writing about you.
What do you mean?
I mean...
what you're doing
today is a rebellion.
Years later people
will call it freedom.
I don't get you.
Stay as you are...
like a storm...
don't think too much.
Because if you do, you'll fade away.
I am Silk.
I'm not some film that will
change after the interval.
That's Surya's wife and
she's coming towards us.
Finally I've met you.
I've heard a lot about you.
I'm sure you have...
but there's a lot more to me.
I like you better in
person than on the screen.
I heard a lot about you
too and you're less either.
He looks just like his father.
He even behaves like him.
You have no idea...
what it is like to
be a superstar's wife.
Even so there isn't a lot
of difference between us.
No...
there is a lot of difference.
No, Radhikaiji...
the difference is as big as a mole.
I have a mole near my heart and...
you have one...
on what you sit.
What? How do you know?
Your face gave it away.
That you have a mole...
right where I said it is.
Hey writer boy!
Are you going to stand by
your brother and not talk to me?
You're pretending as
if you don't know me.
What do you want?
Tell me.
What I want...
can only be enjoyed at night.
Night?
Why not now?
What will people think?
What will Surya think?
Right here, right now?
This is between you and me.
Actually...
things didn't work out with Surya.
Now it's all up to you.
I'll see you at night... alone!
What are you doing?
You are doing it all wrong.
Do it right.
Don't hold it, let me do it.
You're doing it all wrong.
I know how to slide it in.
Is this your first time?
Never mind me.
Slide it in properly.
We haven't even moved
yet and you're all wet!
Whatever you do, do it nice and easy.
Now ease into first gear...
slowly.
Easy, yes... slowly...
Look straight ahead.
slowly...
Yes, that's the way.
Look straight ahead.
What are you doing?
Now add a little pressure on
this pedal, it's the accelerator.
Okay...
Thanks.
Now that you've bought a car...
you should've hired a driver as well.
I bought the car from
the winnings at the derby.
I can't decide whether...
I should hire a driver or a jockey.
Do you know that was my horse?
Well then...
you are lucky for me.
No, you are lucky.
I saw you whispering to
the horse before the race.
What did you say?
It seemed depressed.
I said nobody has
ever looked at my feet.
Hold your head high and
leave everyone behind.
And it did.
Your words are so loaded
with horsepower that...
they rein in the wild spirit in men..
..While they revive
the sagging spirit of horses.
Tell me...
who holds your reins?
Meaning?
If I spell it out, you'll blush.
Do you have a girlfriend?
No.
Why not?
In the beginning,
a girlfriend is delicious as cream...
but then she slowly
engulfs you like cholesterol...
and finally strikes
like a heart attack!
Fine, I'll see for myself...
how long an ascetical celibate like you
can resist the charms of a single woman.
Ooh la la, Ooh la Ia,
Ooh lala, Ooh lala
You are my fantasy
Ah ah
Don't touch me, Don't touch me,
Don't touch me, Don't touch me
I am a young lady now
Hey hey hey hey
Ooh la la, Ooh la Ia,
Ooh lala, Ooh lala
You are my fantasy
Oh oh
Don't touch me, Don't touch me,
Don't touch me, Don't touch me
I am a young lady now
Trying to meet you is like
jumping across an electric fence.
Sit.
You can get a 440 volt shock anytime!
Did you think I'm AAA battery?
I'm a transformer.
Transformer!
Are you planning on
giving me something lethal?
Are you out of breath already?
You better save some.
What is this?
Neither is it your birthday nor mine.
So what's this cake for?
Blow away your old life.
And wish your new
one a happy birthday.
What do you think you're doing?
Are you okay?
Many who have gained fame
hide behind their black deeds.
At least you are covered in white.
You are crazy.
Happy Birthday.
- What are you doing! - To you too!
Hello!
Hey guys, stop press now!
Anything new about Silk?
I have something that
will create a sensation.
Tell us, Nayla. What did Silk do now?
I haven't thought about it.
About what?
What do I label Silk?
Manipulative or helpless?
Vamp or just a victim?
How are the pictures?
I'll cut them out.
What about the
rubbish written about us?
I don't know what has been written.
In fact, I don't care and never did!
I cut out the pictures,
but only if they are good.
A newspaper may go stale in a day...
but the news in it remains
fresh for years to come.
And these journalists never
write anything good about you.
Now they've labelled you Draupadi.
Ma'am...
Nayla madam is busy at the party.
She said she can't meet anyone
and I shouldn't let anyone in.
Didn't you tell her it's Silk?
Yes, ma'am, I know you. I told her.
What's this party about?
Ma'am, the party is to celebrate
Nayla madam's best journalist award.
A lot of high profile people
and celebrities are present.
Thank you.
Kumar...
call the police.
I guess they heard I'm on the way.
Yes, sir.
But they are looking in
the opposite direction.
Honk... honk!
Otherwise they won't give way.
I can't stay here like these idiots.
Let's go back.
I'll check what's going on.
Are you alright?
What are you doing?
Stealing the thunder
from Nayla's party.
You are unbelievable, Silk.
Why ruin just one party,
when I can ruin two!
Driver, start the car... come on!
There are many stars in
this industry, Silk...
but there's only one hero
- you.
That was unbelievable.
You publicly wrecked
her private party.
Now Nayla will never celebrate
anything, not even her birthday!
Once Silk decides on something,
she goes through with it.
Surya, for instance.
His mouth was open
like an uncovered manhole.
I hope you didn't mind...
me kissing you.
My heart said so and I did.
Even though the
heart is on the left...
its decisions are always right.
Wow, the writer rises...
You should sleep.
Tomorrow I have
narrate the story to Vijayan.
And you have a shoot too.
We just left two
people burning with anger...
and you want to put it out?
If I stay back, a fire
will start over here.
Then let it.
Ooh lala, Ooh lala
You are my...
You don't call out to
others when you're on the edge.
The bullet exits the gun...
The villain's spirit exits his body...
The end of the film.
And the audience exits the theater.
What kind of ending is this?
I didn't even have a fight sequence.
Swords are pulled
out of their sheath...
Clothes ripped apart...
Bodies ripped apart... Blood all over.
That leads to the end of the film.
You should have a sword fight,
yes a sword fight.
Sir, the lead hero is a cop.
How could he have a sword?
That's a valid point.
Perhaps an ancestral sword...
a family heirloom.
But, Sir... the lead
hero is an orphan.
Boring!
Lead heroes of the 60s
and 70s were orphans.
We are in the 80s now.
Let him have a family.
And a sister...
give her dignity...
And then take it away!
His sister's trampled dignity...
should reflect on his sword.
Now that will heighten the climax!
What do you say, Vijayan?
Sir, what an imagination!
Genius... Sir, you're a genius!
It's a curse, Vijayan. It's a curse!
What do you think, Rama?
I have one word...
Superhit!
Sir, sensational, this
will be sensational!
Silk couldn't differentiate
between a man and a horse.
A horse at its peak will win derbies.
But a man at his peak
moves like time itself.
Then he can neither stop.
Do you remember...
when we first met...
you couldn't utter a word.
And now you make excuses!
There was a time when I'd merely
think of you and you would show up.
And now...
you think twice before meeting me.
Cut it!
What are you laughing for?
You think this is a joke?
You are the one making a joke, madam.
We shot this scene yesterday.
I need a cigarette!
Silk...
what's going on?
Once upon a time,
you'd act out a scene and..
..I didn't feel like calling
out ‘cut'.
But it seems like you
don't feel like acting anymore.
How can I?
There's nothing new to do.
Everyday it's the same old scene,
same old dialogue, same old story.
You can only act in
one particular film...
and I'll make it.
I know why you're so arrogant today.
You've signed on
that new girl, Shakeela.
But Venkat sir...
there can never be another Silk.
And we don't want another Silk!
Everyday it's something new.
A new spat with Surya...
or a new scene with his brother.
Or your love for the bottle.
In that case, ‘pack up'!
Make this film with that...
that girl... Shakeela!
Silk, wait,
don't make a mistake. you'll regret.
People who walk out on their work...
spend the rest of their
lives begging for work.
But they get nothing.
I am Silk.
Silk.
Don't forget I'm a star.
When stars fade away, they
become one with the darkness.
And when the bare darkness strikes...
the first thing it takes
away is the star's shine.
Hello...
Ramakant, please.
Madam, he is busy at a pooja.
[Religious offering]
Pooja?
For what?
Madam, it's a pooja for his new film.
Tell Ramakant it's Silk!
Sorry madam, I can't disturb him.
Hello...
Hello, give the phone to Ramakant!
Madam...
Tell Ramakant it's Silk!
It's Silk madam on the line.
She wants to talk to you.
Tell her I'll call her later.
Okay.
I'm sorry, madam.
I can't disturb him.
Suryakant sir...
Sir, I'm very happy.
One brother will write,
the other will act.
Today is a great day.
And Silk will dance.
Excuse me.
Vijayan!
Yes, sir?
Silk...
will not act in this film.
The audience has seen
every inch of her talent.
Sir, as you wish.
But sir...
the public demands excitement.
We will change the trend.
Everything that Silk did...
we'll get the heroine to do.
That's fine...
sir but what about
the heroine's image?
The public goes for the goods on
display, the store doesn't matter.
when honour is disrobed...
it's the 'honourable'
ones that enjoy it the most.
You're right, absolutely right, sir.
Ramakant, what do you have to say?
Sir...
Silk madam on the line.
Silk...
what a coincidence.
We were just talking about you.
I'm here with Vijayan and Surya.
They don't want you
for their next film.
And I think their decision is right.
You won't do this film.
Absolutely not!
On the first day of the shoot...
I would like to
introduce you to my parents.
Hello, Silk ma'am.
I am Mutthu.
I am a small time film maker.
I would to work with you.
This is my card.
Drop it at my place.
Okay, thank you very much.
Excuse me.
Well, the set is beautiful.
Congratulations.
It's all thanks to you.
And don't make a mess today.
My parents will be here soon.
Your mother is fine but...
how old is your father?
Silk, please!
Relax will you!
I'm a hit with the men in your family.
You know... I don't like such jokes.
Ramakant sir...
One second.
Silk madam...
I'm a big fan of yours.
Thank you.
I am Shakeela.
So you're Shakeela!
You've heard about me?
Yes, but it was probably a lie.
Why do you say that?
Do you have a mirror at home?
Break it...
because it's lying that
you can be another Silk.
You are wrong!
I'm sure I have something...
I have the talent.
Is that so?
Come on then!
There is that night of the honeymoon
I am that night
The joy of that night
I am that joy
That knocks the lover senseless
I am that intoxication
The mantra to love and
relationships that you have read
I am that book
I am that book.
I play like the banjo
I blossom in dreams
Gentlemen, make me infamous
I intoxicate you like whiskey
I grapple like a hiccup
Get intoxicated, my gentleman
We forget
ourselves
give me a drink like that
Make the room dark
open your eyes
Whatever is in your heart
whisper it in my
ears through some crowds
Don't worry about the danger
Surpass all the limits
Come forth
don't struggle with me
leave everything to me
Bad
half...sullen...departed
broken, is your dream
without me
It is only me
I am that intoxication
Blend us together
Let her go!
She isn't worthy of you.
Women like Silk
don't belong at home...
a bed is where they belong.
What have you done, Silk?
I had told you... don't think.
You gave up too soon.
Say what you want to!
Couldn't you control
yourself for just one night?
What difference would that make?
Would your parents
think I'm a decent girl?
What is their impression now?
They think you are
lewd and disgusting.
Well, you're in love
with someone like her.
That's my character on screen.
I'm not like that in real life.
You mean you'll stay
like this all your life?
Lewd and disgusting?
The thing that made me Silk...
how can I let it go?
Surya was right...
women like Silk
don't belong at home...
Of course, a bed is
where they belong isn't it!
Silk's noose is ready for both of you.
You call me lewd and disgusting...
see how I ruin you!
What you're
proposing is a very big risk.
Think about it.
When God has blessed
you with one life...
why think twice?
No, think again.
You could lose all
that you have earned.
I never thought I'd
get what I have earned.
You need to do a lot of
films to earn that much.
But only one is enough to lose it all.
It's your blood and sweat...
that's why I'm telling you.
I've seen you rise up...
I can't bear to see you fall.
Silk trusts her Mr. Worm.
I love your idea of a triple role!
One mother and two daughters.
That's what I thought.
When people see one Silk,
their tongues hit the floor.
When they see three Silks together...
their trousers will hit the floor!
Remember Abraham?
What about him? Is he dead?
He is alive.
He is also making a triple role film.
And he is playing the lead.
Ramakant is writing the script.
Mr. Worm...
do you know why Silk is so expensive?
Because it is meant to shine.
Let him make his film.
We will watch it and
so will the public.
The era of hate was over.
Now it was time to
destroy Silk, once and for all.
She stole my idea to
compete against me!
I will put an end to her!
Hello, Mr. Worm...
Good good!
Mr. Worm, will the
trousers come down or not?
Everything will come down.
Your cheque.
Thanks.
You stepped on the beach
and the tide subsided.
When the tide rises...
you will be the first to drown.
I even swam through the
giant waves in a storm...
and that's the reason I've survived.
But you...
you're back to where you started from.
Well, even you've come to me.
You can't live without me.
My biggest fan.
I'm here to celebrate your defeat.
Why?
Don't have anyone to
celebrate your success with?
I had told you...
you can't defeat me.
But the fight was a pleasure.
Silk is born to give pleasure.
To her well-wishers and her opponents.
And you are extra special.
That's what the newspapers say.
But there's something you
still haven't revealed...
the fact that you like me.
Flop actress.
She had the last
word like the lead hero.
I like her?
If she were the last woman on earth...
I'd castrate myself!
Murli...
a large coffee, please.
And for the two women?
Beer or tequila?
Success does bestow a
certain energy, Murli.
Two girls?
It's not what you think.
One brought you home last night.
And the other is waiting
outside with her camera.
Ask the one with the camera to wait...
and send the one
from last night packing!
I'm leaving!
Last night was great, wasn't it?
No way!
And you should be with Silk, not me!
All night you kept talking
about that disgusting woman!
Oh, I'm sorry baby.
Tell me something...
when I was talking about her...
was it with hatred or affection?
What?
The problem is I... I hate her...
but she thinks I love her.
I want to know what my
feelings have to say.
You are mad...
absolutely mad!
Bye... I will call you.
Yeah, sure!
You don't even know my name!
Yet you spent the night with me and...
are calling Silk disgusting!
How did I end up in this
Shakespearean tragedy, Silk?
Earlier I fought with you
and now I'm fighting for you!
Your girlfriend left
hurling abuses at you.
She was nothing.
Last week a girl almost broke my head!
Back then you were nothing...
now you are.
Next week again I'll be nothing.
I'm not some film
that changes every week.
You just reminded me of someone.
I imagined I was the only
antique piece around here.
Hey, by the way, congrats.
You've defeated Silk.
I can't believe you guys!
I get no credit for my success.
You're congratulating
me because Silk failed.
Abraham...
whose corner are you in?
Our corner or Silk's corner?
I hate her.
And if you want to
continue talking about her...
then this interview is over!
I didn't know that...
Silk is such a sensitive topic.
Tell me something...
what brought about this
drastic change in your films?
You see... one day I was watching
my own film and I fell asleep.
That's when I realised something.
Films need three things to sell...
entertainment,
entertainment, entertainment!
Silk... anything important?
I have come here to get high.
You know acting always gets me high.
Silk, you know very well that...
neither I nor anybody
else will give you any work.
But if you want some money...
Do you have five rupees?
Five rupees?
When I first tried to get
into films, someone told me...
that nobody would give me any work.
He gave me five
rupees and sent me away.
Sir, give me five rupees.
Probably those days will come back.
I was the dog that...
had gone mad after biting Silk.
I never let a friend
get close to me...
but Silk was, all
thanks to our enmity.
Why did I go to her?
For company?
For lack of a friend,
an enemy would do.
Don't stare at me.
It's as if the oven is
awaiting a marinated chicken!
At least try to give
yourself some respect in your words.
Anyway, what are you doing here?
For lack of a friend,
an enemy will do.
I've destroyed you...
I was here to see how
many stitches Silk needs.
Have a coffee... I'll pay for it.
Two Silk coffees, please.
The coffee that goes by
my name is quite famous.
Try it.
It's the best cure for a hangover.
You will burn in hell!
And you...
you will enjoy it as a
bonfire and warm your hands.
My heart and mind
were caught in a duel.
I guess I was too high
that I began to like Silk.
The mind warned...
‘Don't be an idiot, control yourself.'
For every man there is a woman.
If you can stay away from her,
life will be great.
Otherwise it's over.
I viewed from different angles...
in different poses...
even stood on my head...
but same results.
I can never like you.
You better get yourself checked...
or you won't like your wife
the day after your wedding.
Do you have any alcohol?
Do I look like an idiot?
That I offer you a
drink and let you abuse me?
I want a drink because
I don't want to abuse.
I think you're the type of girl...
who looks better after a drink.
This is the worst!
You mean it struck a
chord in your heart.
The colour of the bathtub is awful...
there should've been more bubbles...
I didn't like it.
Then give it back.
I'm keeping it.
What about this?
Even children wear
more clothes than you.
If you manage to live
up to a ripe old age...
you will look
exactly like your mother.
That's not my mother...
it's me!
Nayla wanted to interview my mother.
You know Nayla...
she can be very persistent.
It was not easy to say 'no' to her...
but it was easy to
become my own mother.
So... I dusted my hair with powder,
wore a dull saree...
and gave the interview.
Have you done anything straight?
Why didn't you take
Nayla to your mother?
My mother had slammed the door on me.
Why would they talk about me...
when they are
embarrassed they gave birth to me.
If you weren't born at all,
how would the world ever know...
that women can also be like you!
Is that an abuse
disguised as praise...
or praise concealed in an abuse?
I can't praise you...
and lately I can't even abuse you.
Be careful, Abraham.
I guess... you're starting to like me.
I told you, you're the type of girl...
who looks better after a drink.
Have you ever been in love?
Love that leads you to bed...
yes.
Love that takes away your breath...
no.
How many people have touched you?
Many have touched me...
but nobody has ever touched my heart.
This is what happens when...
a boy and a girl meet,
they get close...
they kiss... end of story.
I've gained infamy because of that.
But if this story ends
here like this, it will be...
Be what?
It'll be a sin.
Love is a song of the Gods
Love is a festival of
lights for the heart
Love is a fragrance
Love is a burst of morning hues
Love is a lilting waterfall
Love is a prayer
Love exists in every breath
Love lays in the eyes
Separate my heart from my soul
destroy me in love
make my existence
complete with love
To you
I surrender all my love.
My love is an absolute submission.
To you
I surrender all my love.
My love is an absolute submission.
Love is a song of the Gods
Love is a festival of
lights for the heart
Love is a fragrance
Love is a burst of morning hues
I think of you in the morning
I think of you at dawn
My destiny
holds only your name
In your fire I burn
playing with the coal
In my dreams, I walk ahead
to tell you...
To you
I surrender all my love
My love is an absolute submission
To you
I surrender all my love
My love is an absolute submission.
Walking together
our hands leave each others' grasp
Don't meet me in such paths
Talking
the night fades away
Meet me in those nights
Who am 1?
Who is God?
Where you are
I find everything
Our lips meet
my lips blossom
Why should I move away?
To you
I surrender all my love.
My love is an absolute submission.
To you
I surrender all my love.
My love is an absolute submission.
I'm sober, and yet
you're still beautiful.
Nothing else could be
worse than this, Silk.
Even your enemy
doesn't hate you anymore.
Hello?
Silk.
Who is it?
Who is there?
Who is it you want?
Ask, ‘what do you want?'
My money. All of it!
I told you I will give it back...
I'm not going anywhere.
You have my house as collateral.
Listen, madam!
As soon as I sign my next film,
I will return everything.
I saw your last film
and the empty theatres.
You think anybody
will offer you a film?
You have until next week...
or you can forget the house.
I had no idea that Silk
was so badly shattered.
She herself didn't
know what was she up to.
Oh great, you are here.
Come...
I've been waiting for you.
Come in...
Everything is ready for you.
Everything.
What do you mean ready?
What's the story?
Script... dialogues?
Story... sexy.
Dialogue... sexy.
Expression... sexy.
Madam, from your head to your toe,
you should only exude sex.
- What are you thinking about?
-l don't... I don't get it...
what's going on?
Don't worry.
I don't think I can do it.
Listen to me, please.
Don't be scared of them.
They are all junior artists.
But you are different.
They are rehearsing.
Come with me.
Have a seat.
I'll explain it to you.
We will do exactly as you say.
Don't worry at all.
Just a minute.
Listen madam...
right now I have a film...
and money.
It's yours, keep it.
Madam, right now you
don't have either of them.
What are you worried about?
Do it.
Trust me, just do it.
I suggest you have a drink.
Relax... then think about it.
No problem at all.
Drink!
Madam...
you make one film with me and I
will plant a garden of money for you.
And then, both money
and films will chase you!
Here take this...
don't think, just take it. Come on!
Good.
Madam, we're ready for your shot.
Come!
Good. Good Silk.
Make it sexy.
Police police...
You are Silk, right?
Hey, madam.
Why don't you freshen up...
If you need anything,
he will help you.
This way, madam.
Please.
Come on, Silk... pick up.
I have such a big
surprise for you... answer!
I haven't been able to talk to Silk.
I guess she's not at home.
Okay.
There's something I
need to do right now...
so, tomorrow I'll take you there.
Alright.
Okay.
‘Congrats! What a film!
Brilliant acting!"
Everybody had words of praise.
The buttons of my shirt gave way...
my chest was so puffed up with pride!
Then what was I missing?
I was at the party...
but my thoughts were elsewhere...
Silk...
Silk... Silk... Silk...
Her name kept ringing in my mind.
But she...
she wasn't even answering her phone!
Hello?
- There's something strange about you.
When I ignored you, I
bumped into you everywhere.
Now when I want to see you...
you decide to vanish.
Abraham, do yourself a favour.
Find yourself someone nice.
Listen...
I have a big surprise for you.
You want to sign me for your film?
Even better.
I'm waiting.
Right now...
I'm stuck at a boring
party with boring people.
Who is there?
The usual suspects.
Suryakant, Ramakant,
Venkat, Vijayan, Selva Ganesh...
Tell them I've said ‘bye'.
Where are you going?
To bed.
I'm very sleepy.
See you in the morning.
Promise. I'll see you.
Abraham sir...
it's your party.
We were looking for you.
You just vanished.
Where were you?
I was talking to Silk.
The bus isn't moving, then
why are you running after it?
She's worthless.
You can talk to her anytime.
Enjoy the party.
What did she have to say?
She said bye to all of you.
Is she going somewhere?
It's the right thing to do, Ramakant.
She should go away.
There's nothing left for her anymore.
Silk!
When life becomes miserable,
that's when you begin to understand it.
And a million questions arise to
which you will never get the answers.
Why didn't mother hug me as
soon as she opened the door?
Why didn't I realise that...
worshipping a star and loving a
star are two different things.
The person whom you taught
to stand up for himself...
why didn't he stand up for you?
Everybody wanted to feel me,
why didn't anybody hold my hand?
You can hear the
pages turn in a library.
You can even hear
honking in a 'silence' zone.
But when ears that are accustomed to
applause fail to hear the abuses...
life begins to
resemble an empty theatre.
I don't know whether
Silk was right or wrong?
The matters in a person's
life runs for really long.
But the judgments are passed up there.
Up there.
Silk must be creating an
uproar up there as well.
Ooh la la, Ooh la Ia,
Ooh lala, Ooh lala
You are my fantasy
Don't touch me, Don't touch me,
Don't touch me, Don't touch me
I am a young lady now
Ooh la la, Ooh la Ia,
Ooh lala, Ooh lala
You are my fantasy
Don't touch me, Don't touch me,
Don't touch me, Don't touch me
I am a young lady now
When touched by you
my heart whistled
Give me a sweet kiss on my cheeks
When touched by you
my heart whistled
Give me a sweet kiss on my cheeks
Your youth, is fluid
which has drenched my heart
Aha you brought the rain
what could my poor youth do?
Ooh la la, Ooh la Ia,
Ooh lala, Ooh lala
You are my fantasy
No no no no no
Don't touch me, Don't touch me,
Don't touch me, Don't touch me
I am a young lady now
By dropping your saree
repeatedly
you make me restless
By dropping your saree
repeatedly
you make me restless
After storming a fire in me
what can the poor saree do
Poor thing
Oh poor thing
I will tease you
you are a bombastic girl
Oh no.