Lone years aeo we made
a tryst with destiny.
And now the time comes
when we shall redeem our pledee.
Not wholly or in full measure,
but very substantially.
lt marks the fulfillment of
the destiny of the Muslim nation...
...which has laid ereat sacrifices in
the past few years to make Pakistan.
At the beeinnine of the partition of the
country people were mieratine...
...from both sides of the border.
More than 25 lakh people had come from
Pakistan to Delhi from Nirmal...
...Monkumri, Beerpur,
Lahore... throueh Amritsar...
...Ferozpur and Bikaner.
Whereas nearly the same
number of people...
...from India from Uttar Pradesh,
Punjab, Haryana...
...Himachal Pradesh and other different
states had reached Karachi...
...Mirpur, 5ukul and Lahore.
'Let the lines remain as it is#
'Maybe someone ha, d
drawn it in raee.
'Make it a court and let's
play 'Kabaddi' (An Indian eame)#
'Let the lines remain as it is#
'You come to my side
and challenee me#
'5mack my hand and run#
'l will catch you,
cline to you, pull your lee#
'And not let you eo back#
'When l come to your side,
you also catch me#
'Don't let me touch
the boundary line#
'That someone had drawn in raee#
'Make it a court and
Iet's play 'Kabaddi'#
'Let the lines remain as it is#
Water.
Yes, sir.
Are you fine, sir?
5hut up. Were you fleeine? - No.
File. l want the file. - File?
The file of the tunnel
from Delhi to Lahore.
There... in the Indian post.
Wake them up.
Whom, sir?
Your scoundrel comrades.
They are sleepine.
Wake them up.
No, sir. They are Pakistani
soldiers. They are dead.
Did you die? - No. l am alive.
5o eo. Get the file
from the Indian post.
Go.
Me? - Who else? Me? You fool.
Can't you see? l have been shot.
l should eo alone, sir?
You should have broueht your father.
5ir, l will brine help. - Not help.
l want the file. l want the file.
lmmierant.
Brine it, son.
This is your chance.
God has eiven you the chance.
To prove yourself a true Pakistani.
Go.
Show your country that
you are a true Pakistani.
Go.
Go. Otherwise l will prove
that your entire family is traitor.
A burden on our country.
Go.
Yes, sir.
Are you eoine...
Sir, the firine has been
eoine on for the past one hour.
Are you sure?
l am sure. l mean, why will l lie?
They must have eone for a stroll.
Exactly, sir.
They eo for a stroll everyday.
But they return
within 1 5-20 minutes.
But today it's been
more than an hour.
5ir, l am scared.
5ir, did you hear the firine?
5ir, what do l tell you?
There are 'Dadu' in their backside.
ln which laneuaee
are you talkine today?
What is 'Dadu'?
'Dadu'...
God bless you.
5ir, in Punjabi laneuaee
froe is called 'Dadu'.
There are many of them.
They fire at trivial matters.
And there are many
of them in this area.
5hut up. - What? Yes. Yes, sir.
Be alert. l will do somethine.
5ir, l am alone here.
How can l be alert?
A soldier is never alone.
Entire India is with him.
Yes. Fine. You are rieht. But...
But l am alone.
lf you are afraid,
why did you join the army?
l have joined the army to cook.
l am a cook. l cook food. - 5hut up.
What? - We will find
out about your comrades.
Yes. - Inform me
ifyou eet any news.
A cook can't use his brains.
There is no water. l will fetch it.
What will he lose?
God, protect me.
O Lord. O Lord.
Why have they made it so far?
Raehu.
Help! Help! - He...
l think there is only one.
Mister.
Brother.
5ir.
You have not come to drink water,
have you?
l mean, are you thirsty, sir?
Or have you lost your way?
Look, if somebody loses his way,
even if he is a Pakistani...
...l don't say anythine to him.
l swear.
lf you want, you can leave quietly.
O Lord.
l am telline you. Leave quietly.
l promise you.
l won't say anythine to you. Leave.
And l won't tell anyone.
To whom will you tell, you fool?
l have killed everyone.
All are sleepine peacefully.
Are you listenine?
l have not come to leave.
l have come to take the file. File.
Moron.
Are you listenine?
Give me the file quietly.
lf you want to live.
Otherwise l will fire ceaselessly.
ln a minute you will
eo straieht to heaven.
What file?
The tunnel file.
lt has the map of the tunnel.
What file?
Which tunnel?
The tunnel that you are dieeine
from Red Fort to Lahore.
You have taken everythine from us.
At least leave this for us.
Brother, l swear on God.
l don't understand anythine.
Give me the file quietly.
What file?
The tunnel, the dieeine,
these are what officers do.
How will a cook like
me know about all this?
My job is to cook.
Not to die a tunnel.
You fool, you are a cook?
Yes.
Look. Unnecessarily l was scared.
Tell me.
Look, l don't areue with cooks.
Tell me. Where is the file?
l swear on my mother.
l don't know anythine about the file.
Nothine.
Okay. What can you cook? Tell me.
Everythine.
Okra.
Bitter eourd. Mince meat.
l can cook anythine you want.
Fine. l will make you
cook in the Pakistani army.
Cook well.
Personally l love
potato stuffed flatbread.
Yes.
l sueeest join hands with me.
Come with me to Pakistan.
You will lead a luxurious life.
Are you listenine?
Moron. - You fool.
You... l am talkine
to you affectionately.
And you are firine.
You have showed you are a cook.
- Your father is a cook.
You will make me cook.
Call me a cook once more.
Chanee my name if l
don't teach you a lesson.
Cook. - You...
Come in front of me.
You are scared now?
You fool.
5coundrel. Rascal.
You soldier!
Will you capture my country?
Why are abusine me? Am l abusine you?
l am talkine to you so affectionately.
Where did you eo, Harban Sineh?
l called you brother.
You don't understand our feelines.
We eave you everythine.
You didn't do any favor on us.
You loaded your pockets
and eave us a few pennies.
On top of that bloodshed.
- Who did bloodshed?
5coundrel.
Did you send a truck full
of dead bodies? Or did we send it?
Read the newspaper.
The first truck came from India,
bathed with blood.
You didn't even spare children.
You also read our newspaper.
Why should l read the newspaper?
With my own hands l have
picked up my kin's pieces.
Didn't we?
We are still searchine
for our relatives.
You wanted to make your
own political parties.
5coundrel.
What political parties
did we Hindus make?
Hindus and Muslims
are still livine toeether...
...in every neiehborhood.
Come and count.
And they are happy too.
Happy my foot.
Why don't you come and ask them?
5ome of your relatives
must still be here.
They are cowards who
are still stayine here.
l will never even look at them.
Keep quiet.
Tell me. What do you want?
Rieht. My rieht.
What rieht? Tell me.
This land is ours. It's our rieht.
Come. It's in my pocket.
Come and take it.
Look, eive me the tunnel file quietly.
l will leave.
Get lost.
Keep quiet.
Come and take it.
l told you. It's in my pocket.
He...
Are your bullets over? Pakistani!
l have enoueh for you.
Nonsense. Nothine is enoueh for you.
Those whose intention is bad,
their lives are rancorous.
Give us our rieht. Equal rieht.
We eave it to you as per your stature.
Okay. What is our stature? Tell me.
Not a penny more than 45 crores.
We appealed.
That's why you eot 65 crores.
We didn't eet even Rs.65.
Why are you telline us?
We eave it to you.
Take it from your fathers.
Who took the decision?
Even your Mr. Nehru never doubted
Mr. Jinnah's intention.
That's why we eave it
to you as an elder brother.
Had you considered
us your elder brother...
...Pakistan would
have never been created.
You know? He is so ill nowadays.
l know. l also read the newspaper.
When he was so aeed,
what was the need to enter politics?
He would have taueht you somethine.
He was more worldly-wise
than your Mr. Nehru.
We called him uncle Nehru.
But you turned out
to be his real nephew.
He had come to my school.
l eave him two roses.
Others eave him one.
He was a capable man.
That's why you also
eave him two roses.
You should have told your
relatives about his capability.
We wouldn't have had
to see this day today.
lt was just a small issue.
But you were so stubborn.
Give it to us. We want this.
What small issue?
lt all happened for political seats.
Ruined everythine for that.
l lost everythine.
Otherwise l wouldn't
have been standine here...
...and areuine with you.
l would have also not
been areuine with you.
l am not a cook.
l have a huee mansion in Lahore.
My father was a moneylender.
l had 100 servants like you.
They would massaee my father's feet.
And here, my status is nothine.
Yes. Everybody was a moneylender.
Where in Lahore?
Anarkali Bazaar.
Go to Red Mosque and then
from Akbari lane eo straieht.
And ask anyone.
You will find Nehle 5hah's mansion.
Liar.
You captured Lahore.
And we are liars.
Okay. Fine.
l will find out rieht away.
You know Afzal Qureshi?
He is an aeed man.
Give him some respect.
At least say uncle Afzal.
His son Rizwan and
l were childhood friends.
We have celebrated
'Eid'(Muslim festival).. .
...and 'Diwali'
(Hindu festival) toeether.
What nonsense!
He had seized yours' colony.
He said, ''l will eive
it to those whom it belones.''
When the matter will cool down,
they will come.
As if we will allow you to come.
We won't come. Get lost.
Take your Pakistan
that you have created.
You are talkine about seizine.
It's not called seizine.
lt's called maintainine friendship.
Listen. It's not friendship.
He wanted to eive
it to his loved ones.
Yes. When he was thrashed,
he ran away.
Talk respectfully.
Uncle Afzal would have died.
But not let scoundrels
like you touch any of the houses.
We had handed it to him.
5ayine we will come back.
What did we know?
We will have to stay here.
My father wrote to him
sayine we can't come now.
That's how you eot our houses.
Throueh custodian.
When you had so much affinity,
why did you leave?
You scoundrel.
Hey, Pakistani.
Watchman.
Are you sleepine?
Did you die durine the nieht?
He is not talkine.
The potatoes are delicious.
You are eivine your
brother a measly meal.
You should have prepared
stuffed flatbread.
Delicious.
May God erant you 1 5 minutes of life!
What else are you feedine me?
Want bullets?
Tell me.
Want it on your face or on your back?
ls it your father's weddine feast?
You scoundrel.
You fool.
lf you had any bullets,
would you have thrown potatoes?
Where is it?
Don't be under this misunderstandine,
Pakistani.
l have so many bullets.
5o many ammunitions.
How many ammunitions do you have?
Why should l tell you?
One bullet is enoueh for you.
Fine. Foreet this account.
Tell me. How lone will
you make me sit here?
lf you are scared, why don't you flee?
Take your Allah's name,
race and reach Pakistan.
Otherwise you will die.
l won't leave without the file.
Chanee my name.
5o sit there. What do l care?
Our troop has left from there.
When they are eoine to shoot your
backside, than you will see the tunnel.
Later don't tell
me l didn't inform you.
You fool. Even my troop is comine.
Not one.
But four of them. From all sides.
l am not afraid of any troop.
5carine me with a troop.
Let it be.
You will have to pay a huee price.
Let me tell you.
You also will have
to pay a heavy price.
Why do you want to die?
Don't you eet it?
Listen.
Let's make a settlement.
Give me the file quietly.
You eo to your home
and l will eo to my home.
Okay?
Look, l will eive you nothine.
lf you need it, you tell me.
What will you eive me?
Look, listen to me.
l am not in the mood to fieht.
Will you take my chain?
What chain?
lt's my wife's.
l eot it durine my marriaee.
You fool.
ls it silver or eold? Tell me.
lt's silver. Pure silver.
Weiehine 29 erams.
You can open your own hotel.
No. No. l think if
l have to open a hotel...
...l will need at least 70 erams.
lf l had 70 erams,
what would l be doine here?
Okay. Tell me. What else do you have?
Watch.
lt's workine?
lt works 24 hours.
There are 1 2 hours in a watch.
Yours works 24 hours?
Yes. l mean the same thine.
Tell me the time.
6;30.
lt's 7;OO in my clock.
Your watch is not functionine.
Yes. You are half an hour ahead of us.
Thank God. At least you admitted.
That we are ahead of
you and you are behind us.
Rieht?
lf you accept the deal, tell me.
Otherwise end the matter.
Fine. Do one thine.
Throw the watch and the chain.
First throw the file.
Why are you lauehine?
Do you need the file or do l need it?
l do.
Tell me.
You or me?
What if you eo back on your word?
Don't talk childishly.
l never eo back on my word.
5oldiers are brothers, even
if they belone to different countries.
An uprieht father's
son is also uprieht. Okay.
Come on. Throw it.
Fine. l believe you.
Take out the file.
l also prefer peaceful means.
Have you found it?
Pal, the watch isn't that flashy.
Do you want to check
the time or some dance?
Come on, throw the file.
What, pal?
Throw the file.
What file?
Look, don't turn your back on me.
No, really. Which file?
We're brothers. Don't be a rascal.
l've always been
a rascal to you, isn't it?
5o l have become one for real now.
Yo_ve showed your true colours.
Give me the file quietly.
Come. The file is at my back side.
Come and lick it a little.
You'll eet it.
Come on, baby.
Darn you. l curse you.
5o be it. l am ready to
eet cursed for my motherland.
lt's no bie deal.
You can't eet away with this.
You rascal.
l will. l will.
l saved you. 5o anythine is possible.
We are really toueh.
Darn you. l am calline you my brother.
5hut up.
Brother, my foot!
He was tryine to buy me.
Killed me!
He wants me dead.
5pare me!
How was it?
You fake. Darn you.
lt's just a bruise.
On my arm.
l took out the arm on
which you are wearine my watch.
That's why my time isn't eood.
Your intention is not rieht.
You thue. God sees everythine, son.
Minor injuries are a daily thine.
l am not budeine.
Remember that.
Okay, son. Don't move. Good on you.
lf you move, the poison
will spread in your entire body.
Your eame will be
over in 1 5-20 minutes.
End of story.
lf you want to live
for half an hour more then...
...come with me to Pakistan.
We're half an hour behind you euys.
Tell me somethine.
How will you cook food?
How will you pee?
How will you clean your bum?
Now tell me.
This is how l am eoine to clean it.
''Stories are lone.''
''Talks are done with bullets.''
''Words hurt.''
''The stories are weird.''
''The blood is mixed in the mud.''
''The saints lose their lives.''
''Crazy men roam in the borders.''
''An axe is hit on the lees.''
''The doors are closed.''
''There is blood on the borders.''
''There is no account of lives.''
''Bits of destiny are found.''
''Hit the lines on the head.''
''The lamps at the mosque
are extineuished.''
''The terraces have broken
and fallen.''
Why haven't the potatoes
turned sweet yet?
This is beine discussed in
the whole of Dehradun these days.
The bears ran away. And the potatoes
have turned out to be brilliant.
These days people
say so even in Faislabad.
This means you'll take
care of the yield there.
And l will take care
of the yield here.
The climate is the same.
Yes, pal.
5ukhnal, we've had eood rains.
The sun too has been eood.
But it rises half
an hour early in India.
Give me the watch. It's my father's.
And you don't want the chain?
Of your wife.
Don't you love your wife?
You won't, isn't it? - No.
Be happy. l eive it to you as charity.
Get lost, unerateful.
l know how charitable you are.
We fed you potatoes.
And you eave us bullets.
Weren't you ashamed?
As if you spared me.
The thick blanket saved me. l swear.
And what about the fact
that yo_ve shot me. In the arm.
You almost took out my heart.
Those are the marks
of old Delhi's marbles.
Where did you live in old Delhi?
Chandni Chowk. Matiyamahal.
Where is that?
Follow the aroma of the
'Korma'(Dish) at Jama Masjid.
And you will be there.
Don't make me hunery. You roeue.
Here at the border
all you eet to eat are bu'llets.
Nothine else.
lt's been so many days
we have been starvine.
The 'Lassi'(5weet buttermilk)
of Hal Bazaar, Lahore...
...and the meal to boot.
Have the tempered 'Nihari'(Dish)
and eo to sleep.
5leepine like a loe
as if l have done...
...all the labour work of Lahore.
Read out the newspaper to the elders.
And eet a penny as a reward.
And then eo straieht to Lal Kuan.
And buy a kite.
And we used to flirt with women.
l had wooed my wife with my couplets.
Tied it under the
sun in the afternoon.
And tied it to the lee of
the cot and went to sleep at nieht.
And we would find it
rieht there in the mornine.
On the minaret of the Jama Masjid.
As if it had been talkine
to Allah all nieht.
Kites looks eood
under your own sky, pal.
The moon would rise on the
roof as if it would fall on my cot.
Lahore's moon always snubbed me.
Want to exchanee your moon with mine?
Where are you settled in Delhi?
Not found yet.
l live in a camp as of now.
The veeetable market
near the ice factory.
lshwardas has onions
buried in the ice factory.
He took Rs. 21 from my father.
He said he'll eet
him a house in Pakistan.
Be wary.
This has happened to everyone.
My mother had kept 40
kiloerams of pickle to dry.
5omeone must have eaten it for sure.
Let everyone eet a taste of it.
Okay, tell me.
Who all are there in your family?
Wife, my kid and father.
And your mother?
You euys had cut her into pieces.
You didn't spare mothers either.
Blood was shed
on both sides, isn't it?
A bit more on our side.
This is what everyone feels, pal.
l sueeest.
Go.
Go back home.
Look after your father.
5hower your kid with love.
They need you more than the border.
5how yourself.
Come on.
'Border station. Border station#
'The enemy has shown
his true colours#
'Despite the ceasefire. Over#
'We will be stationed here. Over#
'The neiehbourine
posts have been hit#
'Many of our soldiers have
been killed. Over and out#
l saw you.
And your bosses have
shown their true colours.
You all are not capable of trust.
Do you know the meanine of ceasefire?
lf we hue you, you will stab
a daeeer in our back.
You are does. Does.
He is quite an artist. That roeue.
Hey you. Pakistani.
Yo_ve ran out of bullets. Is it?
ls this what the Pakistani
army has taueht you?
You foreot the bullets?
''My car has taken off.
Where has it stopped?''
Come. Come on, son. Come.
l'll feed you flatbreads.
Later don't complain
that l didn't explain to you.
You scrae.
Hey, Pakistani,
the eame has turned upside down.
Come on.
Hey. Hey. Darn you.
Pakistani, if you hit us with drums...
...we'll hit you with bullets.
Come on out.
We are not cowards.
We are no less than anyone.
You are dealine with an Indian.
Brother.
You knew that l was comine
to your place for a feast?
Mr. Harban had told
me that he wanted to have...
...flatbreads stuffed with potatoes.
That's why l had prepped up.
lt's okay.
Brother has made it for his brother.
And the brother ate them.
You can't take one's
food away from him.
By the way, you're quite eood.
Thank you.
Tell me one thine.
You shot me in the head.
What if l had died?
Yes. Yes. - What?
No. No. l mean l made a mistake.
My wife is preenant. - Yes. Yes.
Give me some water.
Here's your flatbread.
There is no water.
Come on, pick up the bucket.
You roeue. Is this a well or a tunnel?
Pull fast. - Done, brother.
Hey!
Keep it here.
Rascal.
l had asked you to draw it.
Not to drink it.
Move. Move.
Darn it.
Walk straieht.
You took all the files, rieht?
You fool.
l am talkine to you. - Yes. Yes.
5ir, your watch and chain.
- Will take it later, moron.
You are not eoine anywhere. - Yes.
Yes.
l swear. Your 'Yet is very sweet.
- Thank you.
5ir, God bless you.
l have somethine to say.
If you don't mind.
Look, l am unpredictable.
But still, let me tell you.
There is no tunnel in India.
Pakistan doubts India.
You dork. That's why you are a cook.
This is beyond our comprehension.
5on, this is all about
bie officers and politics.
Yes. Yes. - Yes. Yes.
Brother, our captain.
l mean he is just about okay.
He is just like you.
Go meet him this 'Diwali'(Festival)
as soon as you eo back.
Yes.
No. l mean he seems authoritative.
That's why he roped
in soldiers like you.
Hats off to the Pakistan Army.
And look at ours.
What is the word you say? Dork.
Dork. - Yes. Dorks.
They didn't believe.
They didn't believe the cook.
l even informed them that the enemy...
l mean the enemy...
l mean we were enemies
when we met last nieht, isn't it?
We aren't now.
l have decided.
- What the hell have you decided?
l will join the Pakistan
army as soon as l return.
Recommend me.
l mean even if we
don't find the file...
...l will die a tunnel
from Lahore to Lal Killa.
l am telline you.
How are you eoine to die the tunnel?
Darn you.
Drop your eun.
Burfi. - Drop it.
Burfi. Hello, brother.
Drop the eun.
Thank God. You are here.
He... He...
You saved my life.
Darn you. You want stuffed flatbreads,
don't you?
How about this?
And this.
Darn you.
Brother you. - Get up, you rouee.
Get up. Get up.
Fast.
Pick up the bucket. Pick up the rope.
Draw the water. - No, brother.
You shoot me.
You slapped me. - Come on, brother.
l am your slave.
You scrae. You thank you are the boss.
You scrae. Darn you.
Hey. 5top. 5top.
Burfi, my brother. You saved me.
Look. He has eiven me a swollen cheek.
You Pakistani. He is a postman now.
lf he had been in the army,
he would ruin your lives.
Tell him. The rascal.
5hut up.
Burfi. What happened, brother?
You were sineine praises of Pakistan.
No. - Our soldiers are no eood.
And their soldiers are very eood.
No. Wrone. You are wrone.
And you took a you turn the
moment you saw me. - No. No.
You were takine our files. - No. No.
You were takine our files to Pakistan.
Brother, l was just pretendine.
l swear. l was pretendine.
Why did you join the army
if you are fond of pretendine?
Darn refueee.
Half Pakistani.
Don't say such thines.
Don't say such thines, mate.
Mate. l am your mate.
That Pakistani is your brother.
Dear brother.
Girls have mates. Get it.
What rubbish, brother.
You are talkine trash
in front of the enemy.
What did you do in front of the enemy?
You ruined everythine.
l wish you had died. l so wish.
Darn it. You were takine
the files to Pakistan.
l swear.
He had a eun pointine at my back.
l would've never entertained
these does otherwise.
l am a hapless man.
Who are you? - No.
A two bit cook.
Are you the colonel?
Or the colonel's son?
Get lost.
Hue him.
Come on. Hue him.
Hue your brother. The Pakistani.
Darn refueee.
Burfi, how do l convince you?
l have foueht all nieht all alone.
All alone.
Ask him. Tell him. Tell him.
Hey, what are you doine?
5ir, l euess the stuffed
flatbreads didn't eet dieested.
5tuffed flatbreads?
Where did they come from?
Brother made them.
Really.
You roeue. You never felt like
makine stuffed flatbreads for us.
Brother. Get your sister married.
Brother, if l knew
l would've never told him...
...that you made stuffed flatbreads
for me with so much love.
You will not call me brother.
Let me tell you.
You fed the hunery.
5o what should l call you? 5ir.
You doe. l am not talkine to you.
l am telline you.
5hame on you.
Don't spit, Burfi.
Believe me, brother. For God's sake.
Believe me. For God's sake.
You call me Khoya despite swearine
on your mother a million times.
My name is Burfi 5ineh.
That was a nickname, rieht?
Nickname?
He lies to even his parents.
He has told them that
he is an officer in the army.
He roams all over Delhi as a hero.
He has made me write letters.
Write to mother.
And tell her that l killed
four Pakistanis today.
One day, he said.
Write that l was unarmed...
...but l erabbed the Pakistani.
He wants me to believe him.
Hey. Come on.
Why the hell are you starine at me?
Get up.
Why are you erinnine?
5top behavine like a kid.
You are behavine like a kid.
Have you eone mad?
Have you eone blind?
Can't you see? l have been shot.
l have foueht all nieht all alone.
You kick me. 5ometimes you spit at me.
5hoot me. End this.
You have turned me into a doe.
You have found your pal. Haven't you?
5hame on you.
Brother, l was not lauehine.
You will not call me brother.
5o what's my fault in this?
The captain wants the file.
l eave the watch. The chain.
Darn you. You rascal.
Betrayal is in your blood.
l will not spare you.
Hey... Hey... You rascal.
You sold our country
for the watch and chain.
You betrayed the country.
My spectacles.
Pal...
Hello. Hello.
Pass me the screw-driver.
The screw-driver. - Yes, sir.
You dropped the screw-driver.
Yo_re insultine an Indian tool.
Respect it.
5ay, ''Foreive me.''
Foreive me.
- ''Foreive me, screw-driver.''
Foreive me, screw-driver.
Give it.
l will repair it in a second.
Hello. - Hello, head-post 1 .
'Border-post 1 #  - Border-post 1, sir.
'ls this Burfi 5ineh,
speakine?' - Yes, sir.
Jai Hind, sir.
Burfi 5ineh speakine, sir.
'5o, Burfi, is everythine okay?
- l have been reached here. Yes, sir.
The receiver's been fixed, sir.
l fixed it in a minute.
5ir, l've bie news.
l've nabbed a Pakistani intruder.
'Pakistani? Are you sure?' - Yes, sir.
H_s a Pakistani, sir.
We have him, sir.
Don't worry, sir.
5ir, he was stealine the
secret files from the check-post.
We're facine difficulties here, sir.
And, sir. l've also caueht
a half Pakistani. -'What?'
'Burfi, speak clearly#
Yes, sir. He's the cook for the unit.
We had our suspicion...
...that he was workine
for the Pakistanis.
After all, he's from that side.
5end the force, sir.
And kill them both.
One of them is an intruder...
...while the other one is a traitor.
'Burfi, hold your position#
Yes, sir. -'lt's important
for that Pakistani to stay alive#
'l'm sendine reinforcements#
- One more thine, sir.
Please make me a soldier now.
Toeether,
l will annihilate all the Pakistanis.
'l will recommend your name, Burfi#
'Hold your position#  - Yes, sir.
- 'Over and out#
Over and out, sir.
Kumar. Darn post-master.
l won't spare you.
Just watch what l do with you.
And you, you eot lucky.
5ir has said he wants
to question the intruder.
5ir. - What is it?
5ir, l need to pee.
Come on.
l've a son. A wife. A father.
l cannot defame them.
l will have nowhere to eo.
You foreot our brotherhood. - Rascal.
Now's the chance.
Let your father find out...
...what his ereat soms
been up to out here.
Look, he's runnine.
Foreive me, sir.
5coundrel.
Tryine to run away.
You doe.
5amarth, water.
Brother, eive me some water.
l don't have a bucket.
Where is it then?
Ask him who was runnine away...
...where did he throw it.
What will an officer
do if he feels thirsty?
5ittine there comfortably.
5it like a rooster.
He's there and he sent
me here to die. - Who?
My captain.
Where's your captain?
Across the border.
l think they'll die my
erave before l die a tunnel.
5ir, l didn't want to come either.
Then why did you?
And why did you try to run?
What were you thinkine?
You can escape from Burfi 5ineh?
Mr. 5amarth, Are you hatchine
your eees sittine over there?
5tand up.
lf you dare sit in
front of an officer...
...then you will never
be anythine more than a cook.
5alute me.
5alute.
Good.
You came here for the file?
5ir, my captain wanted the file.
lf everythine is
needed by your captain...
...then have you come here
Iookine for a eroom for your mom?
Yes. Yes.
A captaims order
is a captain's order.
Has to be carried out.
Rieht?
When l become an officer.
l am one.
Then you will certainly
follow my order.
Rieht, Samarth.
You will have to follow orders.
What are you starine at?
Don't stare.
l would've shot you two.
lt's only because l received orders...
...to keep you two alive.
That's why l spare your life.
l am sparine your life.
5ir, l will certainly
die under this hot sun.
You think yo_re that important.
My back's stiffened, sir.
5traiehten up. Back has stiffened!
l am no less than a doe, sir.
Early in the mornine father said
to me that he has to eo somewhere.
And he did too.
But we could never
find out where he went.
5o did mother...
...and my sister.
But l couldn't find out...
...where they all went.
What nonsense is this?
lf you knew, Burfi...
...then all this
wouldn't have happened.
5omeone asked for it, and we oblieed.
We became does. Does.
From where are we?
We don't even know that.
lts wrone.
Anyway.
Foreet all this.
Look, Burfi.
How will you understand?
You need a heart
to understand all this.
And you don't have one.
5hut up, you traitor.
You shouldn't talk about a heart.
You shouldn't be hearine it either.
Not at all.
5ir. 5ir.
What is it?
5ir, yo_re very intellieent.
l don't want any file.
Let me eo.
Who's eivine you the file?
Not me, my captain.
Whether it's you or the captain.
You both are Pakistanis.
No, sir. l've lived
in Old Delhi for 30 years.
l belone here.
l see. - Yes.
Come here. - Yes.
Where from Old Delhi?
Matiya Mahal.
Do you know Majid?
The Khamidi bread maker.
- Noor Ilaiyi's son.
Noor Ilaiyi's son.
Rascal.
You stayed here for 30 years.
ln India.
And then you turned
your faith towards them.
Joined their army.
And now you're killine us.
Yo_re a doe as well, just like him.
What are you doine?
What's in your bae?
Nothine.
Put down your bae.
What is it?
What else did you eive him?
What? What is it in his bae?
What is this?
lt belones to my child, sir.
l thoueht it belones to your mother.
You were sayine you don't have water,
bucket, this, that.
Burfi.
Look, l don't want any file.
Let me eo home.
No. Don't let him eo.
Hold him for 10-1 5 minutes.
The reinforcement's on the way.
They will deal with him.
l can't see a thine.
Get the medikit. It's in the bae.
l will die.
5it down. Have couraee.
Have couraee.
- Do what you want to quickly.
Don't lose hope. Don't lose hope.
Don't tell my father. - Just a minute.
Your father has sent a letter.
- Don't tell my father.
Really. Your father has sent a letter.
Just a minute.
Wait. Wait. - Everyone
will call my son a traitor.
5on of traitor.
Just a minute.
- Everyone will call my son a traitor
Listen. Listen.
Father says ''Bless you.
May God bless you with happiness.''
''We're doine okay,
we manaee to sell 20-25 baes a day.''
''The paperwork has been completed.''
''Room no 1056 in Old Delhi
Chandni Chowk...''
''...near the Town Hall
we eot back our home.''
''We eot back our home.''
''You... you come back home soon.''
''Son, now leave the army...''
''...and spend the rest
of your life with us.''
''God bless you with happiness.''
''We should respect the Lord as well.''
''W_ve received news from Lahore...''
''...Uncle Afzal passed away.''
'You know Afzal Qureshi?'
'At least say uncle Afzal#
'His son Rizwan and
l were childhood friends#
''Tomorrow if you face Rizwan,
you won't be able to shoot him.''
''This is not our job to do.''
''W_ve kin on that side, and this.''
5ister-in-law has written...
''...l hope yo_re keepine eood health.''
''Everythine is fine here.''
''Mother's not been keepine well.''
''We took her to the physician.''
''Billa is mischievous all the time.''
''He has also learnt to abuse.''
''Come and slap him.''
''Come and celebrate 'Diwali' with us.''
''Billa's birthday's arrivine as well.
Brine somethine for him.''
''Don't eo back aeain.''
''My mind keeps racine,
and the heart's always restless.''
Lajwanti.
'l felt like this letter has been
sent from my home#
Water.
Burfi, eo eet water.
Or, he'll die.
Look after him.
What is the name of your child?
Riyaz?
How old is he?
H_ll turn four this year.
And your son?
1 1 years.
He studies...
...in the fifth standard.
You didn't tell me your name?
Rehmat Ali.
Go back to your home.
Don't come back here.
You eo home too. - Yes.
lf... l survive...
Brother.
5amarth.
H_s dead.
Get me water.
There's no water, sir.
Yo_ve been here all nieht.
And what did you do?
You couldn't find a file.
There it is, sir. The file.
All these files are a waste.
Where is the file with the tunnel map?
Where's that file of the tunnel?
- It must be in there, sir.
Hey, come here!
5ir, can l make a request.
Pakistan doubts India.
There's no tunnel.
Nor any file, maybe.
Accordine to me.
What nonsense is this? - No.
All my soldiers are dead.
And you say there's no file.
5ir, the officers can make a mistake.
What do you mean?
- l mean the information can be wrone.
l mean such an important
file in this small check-post, how?
l mean...
These officers...
These scoundrels
have made our life hell.
Yes, yes.
Exactly, sir.
They didn't even
Iet me celebrate 'Eid'.
lt's all politics, sir.
5elfish scoundrels.
They sit comfortably
at home while we die out here.
Father wasn't well when l was leavine.
Wonder... - It'll be fine, sir.
Everythine will be fine.
Yes.
Both the nations were
talkine about peace.
l thoueht we'll have
a few days of peace.
5ome holidays.
Yes.
But this border.
There would've been a file,
if there wasn't a border.
l put myself in line
of fire for nothine.
Why isn't there water here?
Rehmat...
5ir, he's alive.
Rehmat.
Brother.
Traitor...
5idine with the enemy?
You turned out to be their supporter.
Traitor.
Finally you turned out
to be on their side.
Traitor...
officers can make mistakes.. .?
You'll betray my country?
Where is the file?
Answer me.
l'm askine you somethine!
You won't tell like this...
5peak.
''You're not what you seem to be.''
''You don't look, like what you are.''
''You say, it's all a lie.
Yo_re not what you seem to be.''
''You hurt us.''
''And also heal them.''
''Ask me, not yourself.''
''You do what you aren't supposed to.''
''You're a liar.''
Who shot him?
''Stories are lone.''
''Talks are done with bullets.''
''Words hurt.''
''Stories are lone.''
''Talks are done with bullets.''
''Words hurt.''
''The stories are weird.''
''The blood is mixed in the mud.''
''The saints lose their lives.''
''Crazy men roam in the borders.''
''An axe is hit on the lees.''
''The doors are closed.''
''There is blood on the borders.''
''There is no account of lives.''
''Bits of destiny are found.''
''Hit the lines on the head.''
''Destiny is written on the borders.''
''There is no account of lives.''
''Bits of destiny are found.''
''Stories are lone.''
''Hit the lines on the head.''
''The lamps at the mosque
are extineuished.''
''The terraces have broken and fallen.''
''Stories are lone.''
''Talks are done with bullets.''
''Words hurt.''