Dostoevsky was held captive
in a rat-infested fortress,
subjected to a mock execution,
shipped off to a brutal
prison camp in Siberia
with a sadistic maniac
in charge,
who lashed men for sleeping
on their wrong side in bed.
There's a correct side?
Apparently,
Jesus slept on his left.
Is it helping?
Not being Dostoevsky?
Yes.
Cool.
Are you going to bed now?
- It's only...
- It doesn't make
much difference,
to be honest.
Okay.
- See you later.
- Mm.
As government sources
dismiss press reports
of Robert Sutherland
being burnt out,
the Prime Minister
abandoned a press conference
at number 10,
Downing Street.
They say he's been suffering
from dizziness,
after a minor illness.
We believe that
the Cerberus code,
is part of a massive,
critical, infrastructure hit,
of which the water supply
in Kent was just a starter.
It might come all at once,
or in waves.
But we do know it's massive.
So, we don't know
if Cerberus is the Chinese,
or the Russians.
Well, like our own tax
on the Iranians,
it could easily
be a joint enterprise.
There are no identifiable
command callbacks
that we can find in the code.
Now, normally,
a virus would need
to refer back to a controller,
who might tell it to start,
stop, destroy yourself.
But here, there's nothing.
There may be no way
of stopping it now.
- Fraser.
- Sir. We've ranked targets
of the general critical
infrastructure attack
into a "Top 5,"
but it's not exhaustive.
One, a few,
or all of these.
We can't sit around
and do nothing.
They could bring down planes,
black out the entire country,
cripple the water supply.
They've already
had a good go at that.
How do we end this
in a face-saving way?
Increase our retaliations.
See, that is not going to work...
Division 45 was created
precisely for that reason, wasn't it?
We've boasted
about our offensive capacities.
The Americans
have made it very clear
that they are
not going to help us.
So, we do it
without them.
Well, I have to admit,
when I was Home Secretary,
I'd always have a bit
of a snooze
when people banged on about
the danger of cyber-attacks.
Sorry,
is it a time for joking?
Um, in all fairness...
I do not need a translation
service, thank you.
I've already sacked one traitor.
- Anyone else considering acts of disloyalty...
- Piffle!
Anna Marshall wasn't disloyal.
That's a categoric error,
Robert,
which is frankly,
rather disappointing,
from a man who never tires
of reminding us
that he studied
philosophy at Balliol.
And don't give me
the Scottish stare either,
you're from Stirling,
not Drumchapel!
I think it's a matter of record,
I never saw eye-to-eye
with Anna Marshall.
She's the kind of
ghastly liberal snob
who thinks her cleaning lady
is a loyal friend,
rather than
a reluctant wage slave.
Misplaced loyalty, yes.
Unbearably sanctimonious,
Christ, yes!
But she was never disloyal!
I'm afraid,
Prime Minister,
I'd have to agree with the
Foreign Secretary on that one.
The loyalty bit, anyway,
not the cleaning ladies.
For what it's worth.
Well, let me enlighten you
on that, Fraser.
It's worth nothing!
It looks as if all that's left
is to banish Kent to France.
Get a grip, man!
He's losing it.
- You went in too hard.
- Bugger that!
He's the bloody
Prime Minister!
If he can't cut it, he should
make way for somebody who can.
Well,
as Home Secretary,
I shall continue
to chair the meeting.
Protocol suggests
you are correct.
Right, our top priority...
Come to tell me
you agree with them all?
No.
Good.
I need time to find
a replacement for Fraser.
You're not going to fire Fraser.
High Chaparral?
You remember it?
Linda Cristal
played Victoria Cannon.
You're my new Chief of Staff.
No, thanks.
Maybe I should
re-appoint Peter Mott,
just to play pointless games
of one-upmanship with Archie.
Tale told by an idiot,
all right.
You're angry because Archie
kicked your ass for a change,
and I understand
how that must hurt.
But I'm not here for
chit-chats, or quotations,
my job is strictly
national security.
Would you like me to
update you on our strategy?
Oh, we have a strategy, okay.
You have instructed me
to be proactive.
Yeah, sorry, yeah.
Yeah.
Just not used to people carrying
out my instructions anymore.
Heracles killed Cerberus.
Now, we can run around
trying to protect everything
from power stations
to air traffic control centers.
But in the end, it's like
chasing 100 cats at once.
If you do want to up the ante,
don't bother with
any more symbolic targets.
You have to play very dirty.
With what?
With Heracles.
You know...
characters from Greek mythology
are all very well and good
when it comes to scary
operational names, but...
It's a bit more than that.
It's malware designed to confuse and disable
missile defense systems around the world.
Cyber war works like
any other war.
It escalates very fast.
If the attack vectors
aren't controlled properly,
or if it extends beyond
the prime target,
this war could escalate in
ways we can no longer contain.
Senior cabinet sources have muttered about
instability within the Sutherland cabinet
after the rumored sacking of his
closest advisor, Anna Marshall.
This has still not been
confirmed by Downing Street.
Meanwhile, here in Kent, the
election remains on a knife edge
as Francine Bridge
accuses her Tory opponent
of trying to stoke
a fake culture war,
and Rodger Hawkins continues to flirt
with the Firestorm conspiracy website.
Back to you in the studio.
It's all gotten very ugly.
Look.
Hawkins put this in?
I don't know
if he printed them,
but his people
are distributing them.
Right, well, I'll speak
to his people, then,
'cause I can't believe they'll
sanction this kind of stuff.
I can! It's more siren now
than dog-whistle.
What's happening
with Anna Marshall?
She resigned.
I heard she'd been fired.
- She resigned.
- Right.
The police have been in
touch with me about security.
Right.
How many is it this time?
Rape, or death, or both.
God!
217.
Four credible.
One very credible.
A group calling themselves
J 23,
formed out of the remnants
of national spirit, have sworn
to prevent Kent
from having a black MP.
Of course,
they didn't actually say black.
I can't stay at home
while I'm in London.
No, sure, sure,
we'll get you a flat.
I'm going to stay with Anna.
It's two hours' drive
from the constituency.
Yeah, but what about the press?
I mean, I think we've got bigger
things to worry about, don't you?
Your destination
is 1.5 miles away.
At the next junction,
turn right.
Turn right.
You all right?
It's a one-way street, love.
You can't be turning the wrong
way down a one-way street.
Yeah, I know.
Well, why did you, then?
My SatNav.
It told me...
Hang on,
I know you!
Now hold on,
could I get a selfie?
Oh no, no!
- Hiya.
- You all right, madam?
No, I've had an accident.
Highways England has
issued an urgent traffic alert,
warning drivers
that accidents are occurring,
due to faulty motorway
ENS SatNav data.
Motorists are urged not to begin
any journey by road, until further notice.
- So it's started.
- It's bloody mayhem out there.
What's happening?
They've attacked
the traffic control system,
including SatNav apps.
People are getting
a ton of misinformation.
There are accidents
across the major cities.
Also, the motorways
are gridlocked.
They've put up fake speed
warning signs of 30 miles per hour.
That's about normal
for the M25, isn't it?
- Funny if you're getting cut out of your car.
- What?
- Who are you?
- I'm Audrey Hem...
No, I don't actually care
who you are.
She works with me,
leave her alone.
Carry on then.
Traffic lights, control centers,
SatNavs, the works.
- We need to prioritize the motorways.
- Agreed.
But who knows
what they'll target next?
In some places, the
tailbacks are already so bad,
that we are going to have to
organize emergency relief deliveries.
Also, this.
Firestorm symbols
are everywhere.
- Where's the PM?
- I don't know. He was informed, so...
- We need to act!
- I know!
So...
are you going to
get the ball rolling?
I am.
I thought he was
going to shoot me, Anna.
I'm surprised.
He just took a photo.
Till that moment, all
the threats had just felt,
a bit unreal.
Apparently, all the
navigation apps are buggered.
They're driving into rivers,
and the wrong way down
motorway slip roads.
I almost did that once,
actually.
One of those mad
loopy junctions
with an Aldi and with
a Frankie and Benny's.
Is that one of ours?
- I've never seen that.
- Has he?
I don't think so.
Even Robert...
- Obviously, it has to be you.
- Obviously!
This is in
the national interest.
We can't have
an absentee Prime Minister.
100 percent agreed, Joseph.
Tell me something
I already know.
He's using you
as a stalking horse,
and then he'll step over
your twitching corpse.
The long and
the short of it, Motty.
I wish you'd stop
calling me Motty.
Joseph Obasi is
not an enigma at all.
He's simply a man
who has one thing,
and one thing only,
on his mind.
- Nothing wrong with that.
- Nothing wrong with it at all.
I'm all in favor of ambition.
- He's allowed to be ambitious.
- Very liberal of you, Archie.
And he's right, we can't have
an absentee Prime Minister.
Okay, you go and find a
peasant girl with a low bodice,
and an inviting neck.
I've got some thinking to do.
My President is rather busy with
events in the South China Sea.
And if we deploy Heracles,
how do you think that'll
affect his job done there?
Don't do it.
We have no choice.
We would find a move
like that very concerning.
Not as concerning
as we found it
when a substantial part of
the North Sea landed on Kent.
Oh, I'm sorry, I forgot.
You don't like it when I
mention that little gaffe, do you?
I'll speak to the President,
again.
Make sure he understands
exactly what's at stake?
People won't be happy.
Happiness is overrated.
Quick word.
Are you prepared for this?
Yeah.
'Cause, uh, we may have
to go right to the brink.
And cold wars can very
easily become hot ones.
Is it three hours or five?
- Is what?
- The time difference with Santiago.
Five.
And the clocks go forward.
- He's going downhill.
- Obasi's on maneuvers.
- What, he's the one leaking on Robert?
- I know!
Robert thinks it's me.
His head's not with us.
We can't survive this
if he's not on top of his game.
He can't even sort out
this shitshow in Kent.
Obasi can sort out Kent,
he's had enough of Hawkins.
I'm off to Pixie Hollow.
Good morning, Anna!
May I come in?
You don't like me, Anna.
That's not exactly true.
I know what you're
going to say, and I get it.
I'm not everybody's cappuccino.
I was going to say, "That's
not exactly true, I detest you."
Good.
But that loathing,
which I assure you,
is entirely mutual,
shouldn't be based
on incorrect assumptions.
One of which is,
that my self-deprecating humor
betrays a lack of seriousness.
The other assumption is that
I don't care about my country.
- Not true.
- Get on with it, you vile old crook.
Robert's in a bad place.
Since your departure,
the cyber threat to our
nation has intensified.
You have to come back.
I can't.
If you don't,
Abassey will move,
and I'll be forced
to move with him.
You don't want to move?
Who knows Robert best?
- In politics, I mean.
- Me.
You.
And after you?
Okay.
Go and talk to him.
- He won't see me.
- He'll see you.
Do you think it was easy
for me to come here?
What's that old Nazi doing here?
Just planning a bit of genocide.
Rude millennials,
first on ze list, I'm afraid.
Carry on clicking, comrade.
Change.org will come.
It's a critical situation, Anna.
Earlier,
I spoke to Francine Bridge
about a controversial leaflet
circulating
in her constituency.
I have never suggested
that Kent should pay
reparations for slavery.
It's an absurd invention,
which is being used by
a renegade Tory candidate
who is clearly allowing himself
to be used by the same forces
who were behind Firestorm.
And who
do you think that is?
I have no idea!
- Good to see you, Joseph!
- Yes.
Let me show you the, um...
You're doing
door-to-door canvassing
in the middle of town
and surrounding areas?
That's right,
the less traditional areas.
Traditional? Right.
And what campaign material
are you using?
Err, the leaflets
have a new batch.
No, that's not one of ours.
- Whose is this?
- Err, independent guess...
- Have your team handed any out?
- Not to the best of my knowledge.
Rodger, its a moot point whether
you're a Russian or just a useful idiot.
- Yet, I've supported you when others have not.
- I know, I know!
But you seem to be under a
misconception, which is sadly common,
that I will dismiss any allegations
of racism as political correctness.
Or that I think that there's no such
thing as structural discrimination.
For the record,
neither are true.
Okay look,
the very fact that you're here...
The very fact that I'm here,
proves that one of the holders,
of the three great offices
of state has come to visit.
So, show some damn respect!
Respect works both ways, Joseph.
On reflection, I think it would
be better if I returned to London,
and informed the Prime Minister
of what I've found here.
Yeah, send him.
Send him!
Send Archie! Send
Malcolm X, if you want.
He's unavailable. Due to
being dead, you total chump!
Because I'm going to win
this election,
with or without the support
of the leadership,
who no longer represent
true conservatism,
and takes the knee to
George Soros and the like.
And the like?
Of course.
Full house, Rodger.
I've seen enough.
If we suspend him now...
We don't have a candidate.
If I were a betting man...
- Which you are.
- Which I am.
I would expect Firestorm
to support him now.
It's a perfect outcome.
One they possibly planned.
If we suspend him,
- doesn't that increase his chances of winning?
- Yes.
And then we'd have to figure
out who's victory would be...
Who would be
the bigger ass-ache.
And I'd suggest it's not
an embittered and vengeful crank
crawling back to Westminster.
Worked for you.
In fairness, Archie does not serve
the interests of a foreign power.
Who asked you?
And while I went
to work for him
because the only
other option
was political oblivion,
he is 100 percent committed
to keeping you in post.
Unless you make
it impossible.
I was unaware there was
even a debate on the issue.
Might I make a suggestion,
Prime Minister?
Why are you calling me
Prime Minister
instead of Robert,
all of a sudden?
You're the one
who calls me Robert.
What are you up to?
My suggestion would be to find
somebody who can act as a clandestine link
- between us and the opposition to lance this boil.
- No.
Someone who's close to
Francine Bridge and the opposition.
- No!
- Well, that's a terrible shame, Prime Minister,
because I assumed you hadn't
got your head completely stuck
in the soup tureen of paranoia
from which you've been
guzzling, of late.
This is the last fucking time,
Archie...
I've already asked her
along for a meeting.
Archie!
I thought we agreed.
- Rookie error.
- What, you don't want it?
I wanted to give Robert
one last roll of the dice.
Hopefully, it's worked.
You think he still
has it in him?
We'll have to see,
won't we?
But when Robert's
firing on most cylinders,
I would put my money on him
before anybody else.
Which is what I did.
I did not advise Rachel
to go away.
I made the wrong call
on Hawkins.
You made a call. Your reasons
for doing so were unders...
- I made the wrong call.
- Yeah, okay, you did.
We've never fallen out.
Yes, you were very angry once,
when I was voted onto
the ball committee, and,
you came bottom because
nobody really knew who you were.
I loved you.
I just never ever
dared to say it.
It doesn't matter now.
Would you like me
to talk to Francine
about a meeting with the
Leader of the Opposition?
- Yes.
- And you should address the nation
on the threat
we're under.
Time for honesty
with the people.
You're good at that.
Okay.
You need to stop
watching and start acting.
Make them stop or you
will share in the disaster.
Okay.
Interfering with missile
defense systems
in the middle of a geo-political
crisis isn't the solution.
No one thinks we'll go
through with it, do they?
No.
They think your PM is,
and I quote:
“A dying bee
crawling towards oblivion”.
A dying bee?
Maybe.
But make sure they know that's
when you're most likely to get stung.
If they don't push the
kill-switch by 3 pm tomorrow,
we will activate Heracles
with consequences
that will knock everybody
off their balance.
Our American friends
have found out
the next big cyber-attack
will be the economy.
The banking system, all financial
transactions, credit cards...
- So, how do we...
- We don't.
The malware is already
buried in the system,
sending back
reassuring data,
while preparing its chaos
once they detonate.
And the same will be true across
our entire infrastructure system.
Including nuclear power
stations.
The Prime Minister
is going to address the nation.
Then what do we do?
Then we check our hand,
and adopt our best poker face.
I am speaking
to you today,
because of the very grave situation
in which the country finds itself.
Late last night,
the latest in a wave of serious
cyber-attacks was launched on our country.
This one involves the
disruption of our financial systems
and was designed to bring
our economy to its knees.
I'm afraid to say that no one will
be able to use any kind of cards
for purchases or
withdrawing cash.
And our intelligence
shows that this situation
is only likely to worsen
in the coming days.
Now, this could involve
an attack on
our critical infrastructure,
the like of which
we have never seen before,
which could result in
further loss of life,
catastrophic impacts
on the vulnerable,
and indeed, the
destruction of our economy.
And it is my firm belief
that what began
as “Operation Ruin Britannia”
is now a joint operation
between two hostile nations.
Are you listening?
Does he sound like he's
crawling into the long grass to die?
Unless we have clear evidence that the
kill-switch has been activated in Cerberus
by 3 pm today,
we will go to
a new level of conflict
with dire consequences
for everyone.
Including you.
Clearly, though,
the cyber and
information attacks
are part of
an overall assault,
which includes a campaign
of misinformation
extending to my own family
alongside interference
in our political processes
that has led to a crisis of faith, in
those whom you should most trust.
As a result, one of our
most distinguished judges
was brutally murdered.
And there are still, according
to the security services,
credible assassination threats
against senior politicians.
Now, as of today,
I have suspended
the party membership
of our candidate in the
forthcoming Medwick byelection,
because of his involvement
in the Firestorm platform,
which I believe is being supported
by Russian specialist cyber-units
and for distributing
racist propaganda.
Now, it is too late for us
to nominate an alternative,
so, I call upon you to
vote for any candidate
so long as they are wedded to the
principles of democracy and the rule of law.
Lastly, I have this to say
to those who seek to bring
our country to its knees,
whether that be in Moscow, Beijing
or the capital of any hostile nation.
We may not be the power
we once were.
And perhaps, that is why
we have been chosen
for this demonstration
of brute power.
But we have a history
of continuing the struggle
when the odds
are against us.
And I will stop at nothing
to end this unprecedented,
and completely unprovoked
attack against our country.
Cyber-warfare
is still warfare.
Just because it takes place out
of sight and without explosions,
does not mean that it does not
cause extraordinary suffering.
And we will defend ourselves
by any means necessary,
just as we would if we were being
threatened by nuclear weapons.
We will undertake a struggle
of Herculean proportions
to defend ourselves
as a sovereign nation state.
Thank you.
If I could just have everyone's
attention for a moment?
In this rather
unprecedented time,
I'd like to welcome
the Leader of the Opposition.
Very grateful, Robert. That was
an excellent speech, by the way.
Thank you.
- Nice to have you back, Francine.
- All right, no need for that.
So, how does this stop?
What do they want?
We don't know.
It looks like
we've reached a point
where the war
is almost running itself.
So, what do we do?
We have an offensive
cyber capacity.
It involves interference
with missile defense systems.
It was developed by
Division 45 of the Cyber Unit
with other countries,
including Israel.
But we have modified
its attack vectors.
Modified?
We've made it more of a
shotgun than a precise weapon.
Why?
Because if we unleash it,
it will have two consequences.
First, it could give off
false missile alerts.
Yeah, well, that's
quite dangerous, isn't it?
- That is quite dangerous.
- What's the second consequence?
If we release it
somewhat wildly,
then it could fall into
the hands of smaller fish.
It could start off that
inadvertent hot war
we've been warned
so much about.
I think the days of
suggesting nuclear subs
with no weapons
are over.
And I think when the country
is under threat as it is,
it is the duty of any
reasonable opposition
to support the government
in its task.
Thank you, Chris.
Anna will coordinate
with your office
over that other
small matter in Kent.
Unfortunately,
this new J23 group
have issued further threats
with regards to violent
interventions in the election.
We're increasing
security,
and I'll be briefing
both of you
once our main problem
is out of the way.
Watch out.
I may not give her back.
We'll see.
Obviously,
we wouldn't actually do it.
Release Heracles.
I've been asked before,
in the event of a nuclear
attack, would I push the button?
And your answer
is clearly “yes”, because...
That's how deterrents work.
Would you?
Would I push a button
that incinerated millions
of men, women and children?
I'm afraid sighing
doesn't really cut it.
- Hegel...
- No.
- I don't think philosophy...
- There's always a place for philosophy.
And I think there's
a genuine dialectic
- when it comes to...
- Would you push the button?
If you saw a nuclear missile
headed towards London.
You know
what I'd do.
I'm heading over
to Labor Party HQ.
And then, down to Kent
with Francine.
But you'll come back?
What do you think?
- Hi.
- Hi!
They've detected the
Cerberus virus in a nuclear plant.
It's been lying dormant
and harvesting data.
When's the deadline?
30 minutes.
Our currency's taken
a massive hit.
Stock exchange suspended.
No time-stamping possible on any
transactions makes it impossible.
We're heading
for total financial collapse.
You are aware of the risks?
This has the potential
to start World War III.
It will destabilize anti-missile
defenses around the globe.
How about the Americans?
Have we heard anything?
A sign of any sort?
Nothing.
So, the idea is to make it
less of an election,
more a referendum
on democracy.
Yep.
Agree with that.
- Tolerance.
- Wishy-washy.
Well, we can toughen it up,
but we need to make sure
you sound reasonable
next to Rodger.
That shouldn't be too difficult.
What's wishy-washy
about tolerance?
I'm just saying
better words, that's all.
Don't give yourself
a hot flush!
How many bloody times...
They're not a joke.
I know! I'm sorry.
Don't do it!
We need
a signal, Kelly.
We need a sign.
This is not the
time to light a fuse.
We are piling pressure
on both players.
They have to send an
immediate message that it's over,
or we go active.
Yeah?
Thank you.
That was the Governor
of the Bank of England.
The pound is
in total free-fall,
and all their systems are
compromised by Cerberus.
They can't do a thing.
We're heading for the buffers.
Stand by, Eleanor.
Stand by.
Well, go on then,
if you want to get past.
Did he just hit your car?
Activate Heracles.
Do it now!
Out! Get out, get out!
- What's going on?
- No, I know him! He's safe.
He's one of Eleanor's, go, go!
- Get out, get out!
- Miss, clear the vehicle. Go!
Go!
Wait!
There's a change in the pattern.
Timestamping's
back to normal!
Transactions are clearing again.
They've blinked.
There's a kill-switch.
With both the US
and the Chinese fleets
pulling back from the brink
in the South China Sea,
there are hopes that the cyber
threat to the UK has also diminished.
The Prime Minister, Robert
Sutherland, had this to say earlier.
Assassinations, electoral
interference, false alerts.
And lastly,
an all-out cyber-attack.
The aim?
To create such chaos,
that it would
destroy our democracy,
and show the world
what damage can be inflicted
without the need
for missiles.
I am pleased
to tell you tonight,
that the threat appears
to have receded,
thanks to the efforts
of our own cyber defenses.
We should be
in no doubt, however,
that there is no room
for complacency.
For next time, the
consequences could be far worse.
Tonight, I must also
express my outrage
at another terror attack on
a parliamentary candidate,
Francine Bridge,
who has fortunately survived
without major injury.
The life of my colleague
and friend, Anna Marshall,
however, hangs
in the balance.
Anna represents the best
traditions of our country.
Tolerance, decency,
and a desire to serve
the national interests.
I hope you will hold
her in your prayers,
as I do.