Audrey!
- Audrey! Hold on!
- Help. I can't see.
Audrey!
- Help me. Help!
- Audrey! Audrey, hold on, I'm coming!
- Audrey!
- Help!
Come on. Hold on.
It's okay.
Come on. Come on.
It's gonna be fine.
Do we have
an update from Fraser?
Yes.
He's alright and is overseeing
the Strategic Command Center.
One of his team is missing,
presumed dead.
As is the local MP,
Clive Turner,
who was assisting
with the evacuation.
Yes, I heard about Clive.
Must call his wife.
- So, current casualties stand at?
- -Um...
Over 300.
And it will go up.
Many still missing in flood areas
or in buildings that have collapsed.
Things are absolutely chaotic.
The hack on our communication
systems have made things impossible.
Operations to deal with inland flooding
are messed up by the loss of ECON,
and triage is also made far more difficult,
especially for the burns victims.
They've resorted to
mobiles in most cases,
but that's putting
a huge strain on the system.
Additional lives are certainly
being lost because of it.
Okay, so the correlation
between the cyber-attack...
- Is it correlation?
- The time of the attack
coinciding with our arrest
of the Kostenko suspects
suggests a concerted
hostile nation
rather than some
script-kiddies in a basement.
So, you think the choice of the
emergency services was deliberate?
They found a zero-day weakness in
ECON which is a relatively new system.
Establishing authorship
is complicated
because there are a lot of
new obfuscators in the coding.
I know you lot like
everything bilingual, but...
She means they exploited
an unknown weakness
in the new emergency
network communication system,
and there's also a lot of deliberate rubbish
written into the code to act as chaff,
- so we can't tell who did it.
- Thank you, Home Secretary.
That is an admirable summary.
We are working flat out for a
patch for the Ruin Britannia hack.
Well, let's hope
that's the end of it.
If the cyber-attack is linked to our
detention of the Kostenko suspects,
and it's costing lives...
So we could just release them
and get it over with?
No.
Okay.
Summon the Russian
Ambassador immediately.
- We don't know for certain...
- That journalist, Hari Misra.
He claimed on the Breakfast Show this
morning that two arrests had been made.
Get him to divulge his source,
or he will be given a painful lesson
in the true meaning of cancel culture
in the basement under
Thames House.
Get our communications fixed and bring
me proof that the Russians are behind this,
so we can decide on a proportionate
response. In short, Eleanor,
do your job.
Anna.
- He's not in a particularly good mood.
- Sorry?
Oh, don't worry, I'll be kicking
someone down the ladder a lot harder.
There's also the Singer Report into
the J23 shootings making him jumpy.
- We're supposed to get an advance view of it tomorrow.
- I hear it won't destroy him.
- I hear that too, but until we see it...
- Anna...
that's not what I want to
talk to you about.
It's about Edin Tosumbegovic.
Edin was waiting
for his killers.
He knew it might not be quick,
what they had in mind...
so he put a bullet
through his own head.
I will go to my house...
and I will sit under the fig
trees among the butterflies,
and I will wait
for you to come.
I love you.
I have always loved you.
- Do you think I was a bit harsh in there?
- I've spoken to her.
You okay?
I'm fine.
Singer Report will be with us
tomorrow. It's confirmed now.
- Are you sure you're oka...
- Jesus Christ! Yes, I'm fine!
Just back the fuck off!
Home Secretary.
- How are you?
- All right.
I thought I was going to
drown in that car.
- Look, Fraser, you don't have to be here.
- I'm staying here.
One of my team
was out on the naval boat.
I heard that, I'm truly sorry.
She didn't want to
go out, you know?
- There was no point in her going.
- There will have been a point,
or you wouldn't have sent her.
I really must try
and contact Audrey's family.
Okay, are they fixing the comms?
We're fighting this battle with
our hands tied behind our back.
If they don't fix this hack, we're
going to lose hundreds of lives.
They're doing what they can,
but there's no fix in sight.
Are we sinking?
The explosion damaged the raft.
We're taking on water and
losing air, we haven't got long.
How are we still alive?
Sheer good luck.
The blast pushed us away
and towards the wind farm.
- What are we going to do?
- The wind is pushing us towards the turbines,
so you need to get some rest before
we head back out into the sea again.
- What?
- About the third turbine along is a maintenance vessel.
The raft has taken on too
much water, we'll need to swim.
I can't.
If you don't, you'll die here.
No helicopters can fly in these conditions,
and they won't be able to see us anyway.
I'll help you get there.
I'm not going back
in the fucking sea, okay?
I would rather die here.
Fair enough.
I'll head out
in about 20 minutes then.
I'll come back for your body
if I can find any help.
Were you born to a woman or did
they just carve you out of granite?
The swim will be fine
as long as you stay close.
Don't rub your eyes.
And don't make any sarky
comments either, I'm trying to help you.
Focus on staying alive.
Oh, I never
sweat the small stuff.
Sorry.
So, it appears in the
midst of a terrible disaster,
a serious cyber-attack
has been launched
on the United Kingdom's
emergency services.
I turn to you, Archie Glover-Morgan, I would
imagine that as a former Home Secretary,
- who is behind this?
- That's for the security services to ascertain.
If they're up to it.
There's a report out today, a
journalist claiming this is linked to the.
Kostenko assassination. It also says
that two arrests have already been made.
I can't speculate on that, but the
idea that whoever is behind this
could paralyze our most
critical communications
does suggest that somebody
has got things very wrong here.
I imagine a senior figure will have
to pay a price for this appalling lapse.
We're going to
hear from your successor.
Let's go to Kent and join
Mr Obasi. Good morning.
- Things look very bad there.
- Good morning, Karen. Yes,
and I would like to pay tribute to
the incredible effort and heroism
- of the emergency services.
- Of course.
You are, it appears,
attempting a rescue mission...
I think you should see this.
...in what seems like an almost
complete communications blackout.
- Is that anyone's fault?
- Believe me, we will be carrying out an urgent review.
This is the Ruin Britannia code that is
crippling the communications network.
The call-back code is definitely
pointing towards a Russian source,
but that could just be
a framing device.
- What's it going to do next?
- We're not sure.
It doesn't appear to have a kill
switch built in. This sequence here
- is what's worrying us.
- Why?
We think it could be lining up to attack
another part of the communications system.
The mobile networks
are all they have left in Kent.
We can't lose them too.
I'm sorry.
You don't have to apologize.
Do you know now?
Yes.
Have you made your mind up
about the prisoners?
I've been carrying out
consultations.
- With whom?
- The Archangel and the Prole.
Wait. Moral philosophy?
Sometimes, you can go
with an intuitive hunch
on maximizing utility.
Let a pair of criminals
go to save lives...
Sometimes, you have to apply
a higher form of reasoning.
Well,
the Russians have issued strong
denials to the press-rumors
that their agents had anything
to do with the cyber-attack.
I can't let them go, Anna.
And for what it's worth, I think
that's the right decision.
It would show fatal weakness.
You always were an Archangel.
Even back in college when we
were just a pair of Tory geeks.
Shut up, geek.
I was a high-fashion queen.
- I had all the invites.
- Yeah.
- Your eleven o'clock.
You ready?
No.
We need to go now. Come on.
I'll help you.
We're as close
as we're gonna get.
Come on.
Right this way.
I want you back
in the shadow-cabinet.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Just one small
problem with that.
Well, actually, there are quite
a lot of large problems with that.
But not being an MP is probably
the biggest one, right?
Oh, there'll be
a bi-election soon enough.
Particularly if what I'm hearing
from Kent about...
- Too soon, maybe?
- Maybe.
Well, let's just talk in general terms
until the funeral has taken place.
- What if the local party refu...
- The NEC can impose a candidate, or...
- have a limited short-list.
- They haven't all gone away, you know.
I don't want 'em all
to go away.
I'm not the most
popular person in this party.
- You do remember the way I was treated?
- Yeah, they can piss right off.
Some of what went on
was an absolute disgrace.
Although, in fairness, some on the
right of the party didn't help much either.
- I'm not on the right. That's the whole bloody...
- Yeah, I get it.
The thing is...
I don't really care much about
labels anymore. What I care about
is having smart,
competent people
who can deal with Joseph Obasi
across the dispatch box.
- Wait...
- No, it's not because of that.
It's because Obasi is bloody sharp, and
will make mincemeat of anybody who isn't.
You're smart and you're
competent. I like that.
Okay.
Get them to sort my
membership card out first though
because knowing this lot, it won't
arrive before the next General Election.
I'll personally put it
in the post, you wait.
- Sorry.
- Okay.
Yeah.
You okay?
It's no use, it's dead.
I tried to call out, but all we got was
some weird error message about Britannia.
Is there anyone else on board?
Couple of lads were outside,
and got blown away.
Have you done
any damage assessment?
Port side took the full force
of the explosion.
And we're taking on water. With this
swell, unless they get someone here soon,
we are going down.
The emergency services search and rescue
operations in Kent have been heavily...
The Ruin Britannia virus is now
attacking the mobile networks.
The flooding is not relenting,
and people are still being
found in collapsed buildings.
We won't be able to cope with no
emergency communications or mobiles.
At the moment,
our prime suspect is Sednit.
The Russian
cyber-attack division?
Yes, although, we need
to be very careful.
There is a chance that
it's being made to look
like a Russian attack
to throw us off the scent.
We should have just let them
slip away in the first place.
Well, that's not helping our
current predicament, though, is it?
Have to admit, Robert, I am unsure what
the Archangel would say about this one.
- Russian Ambassador here?
- Yeah, he's waiting in the terracotta room.
Is it worth
hundreds of other lives?
Yes, I'm aware
of the calculus, thank you.
This is an absolute catastrophe.
Nobody can talk to anybody now.
We have people waiting for
transfers to burns units,
the entire triage system
is going to fall apart.
We're going to need
some little ships.
Couriers.
They're going to have to be able
to carry communications by hand
between the emergency services
and the hospitals.
It's the only option now that
the phone masts have gone.
Miserable bastards.
Sutherland should
let the Russians go.
It's tough.
I would never have arrested them
in the first place.
- Luckily, those aren't my choices.
- -Sir.
He's authorized. Show him in.
What's up?
Audrey Hemmings'
next-of-kin. Her brother.
I have to speak to him.
Go on.
- Ambassador Voronin.
- Prime Minister.
So, you are, of course, aware that
we have two of your citizens detained.
Only one of them is actually
a Russian citizen.
And are you aware of
speculation in the British press
linking them to the assassination
of Mikhailo Kostenko?
I am aware of yet another
attempt to blame my country
for every mishap
you bring on yourselves.
Shall we just cut to the chase?
If you are referring to your
current communications issues...
In the middle of a major rescue
operation which is costing extra lives.
You will be accusing us
of blowing up the ship next.
Of staging an earthquake.
I wonder what could've made
us so ridiculously paranoid.
Your game of "blame the Russians
for all your problems" will not work.
I would especially counsel against
it if you do not want to look very foolish.
So, all of this is totally
unrelated to the fact that.
Klara Lechkova
is implicated in the crime,
and is related to a senior
member of your security services?
I can assure you
that the person you have
detained is not Klara Lechkova.
She is currently at
her dacha outside Moscow
to the best of my knowledge.
Our intelligence
services tell me
that the woman you have
detained is actually Larissa Petrova.
A low-level criminal and
fraudster who is also involved
in the commission of teams of foreign
criminals to break into luxury houses.
Rodrigo Araya is simply a madman
who believes he is the
reincarnation of Che Guevara.
By all means, prosecute them
for shoplifting and lock them up.
I can assure you that my
government will be delighted.
- All our information... -They've tricked us.
- So that we look stupid.
How can you
say that, Anna?
- I don't feel stupid at all.
- But the fact that it might not be Lechkova,
- doesn't mean they weren't involved in the assassination.
- Exactly.
- If it was an attempt...
- Can I just be really clear about something.
A significant part of the Kent
coastline is no longer there.
We are going to have to resort to smoke-signals
soon to organize hospital transfers.
- I think we should...
- So wasting precious time
having the Russians
make us look like fucking idiots
- was really not part of my to-do list this morning.
- It wasn't top of any of our...
Go and find out who these
clowns are that we've detained,
and find out where
the real culprits are.
So...
putting aside whoever
killed Mikhailo Kostenko...
Exactly.
What if it's not connected
to this cyber-attack?
What if it's something
else completely?
There's loads of
weird shit going on.
The killing, then the boat,
- then this cyber-attack...
- Who says they're connected?
What do you think caused the earth
tremors that made the ship go up?
I don't know, what normally causes
them? Stuff moving underground.
Big North Sea drilling contract given
to the Chinese Jiayoõu Corporation.
The Yanks were pissed off
about that as well.
Watch and see if they try and
pin the blame on them for it.
Okay, I gotta tell you, I'm not
one for conspiracy theories.
I don't think mobile phone masts
can cause pandemics
or George Soros can
conjure up an earthquake.
Okay, but something's going on,
- because I've got MI5 all over me.
- Good.
Someone's leaking you explosive
stuff that affects national security.
That's their job.
You'd better be very careful.
What was she doing on the boat?
- Observing the naval operation.
- Why aren't you out there looking for her?
You've seen what it's like
out there. Visibility is terrible,
we almost lost a chopper today.
I told our mum she's missing,
but they'll probably find her.
Now I get here, and...
my mum won't be able to cope
with this. Audrey's the baby.
The one with the brains, me
and Fred always looked out for her.
I just feel there's something I should
be doing, some way of finding her.
I'm sorry.
If conditions improve, we'll send
rescue helicopters in the morning.
I'll tell my brother.
- There's no phone coverage.
- How come?
The virus has spread from the
emergency services to the mobile networks.
Bloody hell.
That must make it impossible.
Yeah, it's pretty hard.
I've got to try and assemble
a team of couriers who can
scuttle between all the
emergency sites with hard data.
I might be able to help
with that as it goes.
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
So, why haven't
they come for us?
Helicopters can't fly out with
all the debris in the air.
Things must be bad onshore.
Really bad.
- She's taking on a lot of water now.
- We can't stay here.
Where do you suggest we go?
We have to climb up
to the platform!
You go first.
- Just focus on getting to the top.
- Oh, great, yeah!
I'll be right behind you!
Okay?
Go!
Don't look down!
Do not look down.
Come on! Come on.
Come on.
- You okay?
- Yeah, yeah, good.
Put it on the screen.
The Ambassador was correct.
This is not Klara Lechkova.
This is an impersonator who
used her documentation,
and Araya is...
just a piece of work.
Okay.
So, Kostenko gets hit.
The Russians
frame themselves for it...
Which implies they knew
about it, at the very least.
But then, in punishment for arresting the
people they actually wanted us to arrest...
- So we would look stupid...
- They launch a cyber-attack.
Look into retaliatory cyber
operations for this disgrace.
Division 45 are already on it.
I will bring you
a target list later.
- Are we sure...
- I'm not letting this go.
It's one thing to whack oligarchs
on our shores, it's quite another
to rub our noses in it
during a disaster.
Okay, on that.
GCHQ are also picking up
some other noise.
What noise?
That the drilling operation
in the North Sea
might have contributed
to the explosion.
- Is there any hard evidence for that?
- No, not yet.
But it is a rumor that will grow
legs and be running pretty soon.
We've been under a lot of pressure not
to move forward with the Jiayóu Contract.
Well, you might want to
announce a pause on that.
Just to evaluate things.
This will really piss
a lot of people off.
- Audrey Hepburn?
- Yeah.
And my brothers are Fred
for Astaire and Cary for Grant.
- His real name was Archibald Leach.
- I know, yeah.
Oh, yeah. I like those old
black and white films as well.
- Where you from, love?
- Originally from Bermondsey,
but then we moved out
to Rochester.
Bet your old man's
proper 'Wall, right?
He died. But yeah, he was.
More Millwall in Rochester
than Bermondsey now.
Game's gone though, hasn't it?
Money men killed it.
No, get yourself down
to a lower league game,
they're still a good laugh.
Sometimes, me and my brother go to Fisher
FC. It's lovely at night if you look out...
Will you stop talking?
It wouldn't hurt to be
polite now and again.
Look, I'm trying to think and
you are distracting me.
I'm going to swim to shore.
You'll never make it. Not in
the dark and in these conditions.
We have no food or water,
but more importantly, shelter.
Exposure will set in with the wind chill
and the temperature could drop even further.
You'll probably die first...
because you're older
and out of shape.
Thimble of laughs, this one.
Yeah, he's a one-man
comedy channel.
- I'm gonna go for it.
- You're mad.
You can't leave us.
He's gonna die out there.
Mr. Glover-Morgan,
Prime Minister.
Return the whip
to my little band of brothers,
and you increase
your majority by eight.
You will see me talking to
you as a sign of weakness.
- Not at all.
- And it is.
But I want you to understand
something very important.
My parliamentary situation
is weak, but I am not.
That's not a mistake I've ever
made about you, Robert.
If you were weak, you wouldn't
be talking to me now.
- The Singer Report will exonerate you.
- We'll see.
In a way that's
convenient for both of us.
- You never resigned on principle.
- I certainly did.
It just depends which principle
you are talking about.
There's a mark, Archie.
Don't overstep it,
or things will get
very nasty very quickly.
Well, as we are being candid,
please take this in a similar spirit.
I care about my country, and when it's
in peril, I wish to be in the frontline
- defending it.
- I believe that, too.
I don't think you are the best man
to lead either the party or the country,
but I will work with you
to keep both in one piece.
- I'd like to give you one piece of advice.
- Go on.
Sack Eleanor James. She should never
have allowed us to get into this mess.
She's not the person
to get us out of it.
Always wanting me
to sack someone.
Oh, Anna.
No, imagining you telling her
you're returning the whip to us
will be karma enough.
I should, perhaps, tell you
I have asked Peter Mott
to be my adviser.
You absolute child, Archie.
I want to be back in the
COBRA room during this crisis.
As?
You could always make me
Foreign Secretary.
You're not joking, are you?
I have a certain manner, Robert, you
know that. It has served me well over time,
kept me amused,
but at the moment,
you simply don't have the
quality to fill the big offices of state.
You need somebody with fighting
spirit, who can handle a tough interview,
and has blood rather
than sawdust in their veins.
Stewart. Stewart! Stay awake.
You alright? Come on.
- I'm not going to make it.
- 'Course you are.
'Course you are, mate, come on.
Tell... Tell Jeanie...
- Tell...
- Who's Jeanie?
Is she your wife?
I'm so cold.
Come on, mate. Come on, Stewart.
Come on.
We're at your disposal. Just
send us where you want us to go.
Who are these people, Fraser?
Mods. That's
Audrey Hemmings' brother.
I think the press might be
interested in this one.
- Yeah.
- We're in the clear.
Leak it. Right now.
In one of the more unexpected
moments in this tragedy,
the communications gap is being
plugged with an army of volunteers.
In this case, it's not so much
little ships as little scooters.
A group organized by the brother
of one of the victims of the blast
have offered their services
in the struggle to keep data
moving between the different...
News from London.
Cyber Unit have got a patch
for the emergency network.
- Still no phones?
- No.
They're playing whack-a-mole
with it right now.
God knows where
it's heading next.
Thanks, Fraser.
I'm truly sorry about Audrey.
Thank you, Home Secretary.
At least, now with some communication, the
rescue teams are getting back in the air.
He was such a good man.
At Christmas,
he wore this hat that lit up...
just to entertain the kids.
Everybody loved him.
He would've done
a favor for anyone.
He...
He was kind.
He was a kind man. He...
He... He was...
He couldn't fix
my roller skate, though.
Stewart? It's here.
Stewart, it's here.
He's done it, he's made it.
Stewart...
We're safe, okay?
We're going home. We...
You're not gonna die. Hey!
Hey, we're here! We're here!
Hey! Over here!
Over here!
Okay, first,
welcome back, Fraser.
And thank you
for all your efforts.
We were delighted to hear that
Audrey Hemmings has been found alive.
Thank you, Prime Minister.
So, the, um, emergency services
are working normally again in Kent?
They are. It's a basic clean-up
operation now, although, there is still
a hell of a lot
still to clean up.
We estimate we've lost
a third of the town's buildings,
and the casualty rate
will continue to climb
especially because of
the triage delays.
So, the cyber-attack has abated.
The patch to ECON has worked,
and we are able to
access the system again.
Good to hear.
Retaliatory measures against
selected targets have been initiated.
I have spoken to both the DTI
and Director of Communications.
We are putting
the Jiayou contract on hold
until we have had a full
investigation into the explosion.
We need to dampen press speculation
and not link the two elements publicly.
- Yes.
- Right now, they are more interested in the Singer Report,
which unfortunately,
has been leaked.
That is unfortunate.
Who could possibly have
a reason for doing that?
This has not
been a tribute
to our preparation.
- Cyber-attacks are constantly...
- I'm not talking just about cyber-attacks.
- ...evolving...
- We have been made to look completely ridiculous.
Hopefully, these counter-measures
will put an end to this nonsense,
and we can go back to the
painful job of cleaning up.
I cannot promise to deliver
something outside my control.
I can only work
to that objective.
- Don't sack Eleanor.
- It's nothing personal.
Don't sack her. I know people
want a head, don't give it to them.
- We've stabilized the situation.
- For now.
Look, now that this
Singer Report is out of the way,
there's something I really
need to discuss with you.
- Why am I getting the feeling I'm really not going to like it?
- Because you're not.
- Hari Misra? What do you make of him?
- Ah, he's a cocky fuck.
And he always seems to be
one step ahead of the press.
We can't ever be seen to be
weak on national security again.
Yeah, that's what I said.
Useful to know, though, so,
y'know, keep him in earshot.
Another scoop coming your way.
Destroy the drive when you're done.
This arrived.
Still trying to see if Paul
Mason's available for next week.
Okay.
Jessica, shut the door please.
There's loads of
weird shit going on.
The killing, then the boat...
- then the cyber-attack.
- - Who says they're connected?
Now, what's their little game?
What do you think caused the earth
tremors that made the ship go up?