Hello, Rohan. Good morning!
Mrs. Mukherjee, good morning.
-How are you?
-I am fine.
So? Excited?
Can't you hear the excitement
in my voice?
Rohan, please be there at 10:45.
I will be there on time, don't worry.
Ok.
But, it would be better if
you could be there, Mrs. Mukherjee.
I mean, since you've set up everything.
So, if you could make it,
it would be very nice.
Why, Rohan? Are you
scared of a girl?
If I had to lie, then no.
But, honestly, a little bit.
I guess it's probably because
it's the first time.
Rohan, is someone going along with you?
Yes. The one and only, Zafar.
Oh ok... good!
All the best, then!
-Yes, Mrs. Mukherjee. Thank you!
-Ok, Rohan.
-I'll see you. Bye.
-Bye.
Hey Percy, what happened?
-Has the chain come off again?
-Yes.
Your old cycle will
never get a new twist!
Yes.
So what do we do?
Fix it, please.
Tell your dad to buy you
a new cycle now.
Rohan uncle, you know my father.
He hasn't changed his
father's vintage Lambretta yet.
-My cycle stands no chance.
-Your father is a typical Parsi.
-Hold the bike.
-Yes.
Good.
It's high time you learnt how to fix this.
-Yes.
-I've shown it to you so many times.
Let's test it.
All set.
Yes!
Thanks, Rohan.
-You are welcome.
-Wow. You are the best.
Tell me, how do you ride a bike?
With faith and confidence.
When you have these, you don't
need to see the road ahead. Remember that.
-Yes.
-Papa is here.
Good morning, Cyrus.
Son, how do you catch me everyday
without even seeing me?
Do you have a code locked
in your nose for everyone?
Mutton curry, Cyrus.
Your code.
-See you in the evening, Percy.
-Yes.
Mutton curry.
Is she here?
Tell me.
Brother...
You are quite fair.
But, she is even fairer.
Your kids will look like foreigners.
Here...
-Hello. Hi.
-Hi.
I am Rohan Bhatnagar.
Sorry, I am late.
It's all right.
This is Supriya... Supriya Sharma.
Hi.
And I am Geeta Sanyal.
Hello.
It's best if Rohan and
Supriya sit here,
you and I can sit there.
One particular snack
is very famous here.
Rohan, shall I ask for
an extra helping for you?
No...
I'll order some for you too,
my dear sister-in-law.
You come, please.
Ok.
I am so sorry.
Sometimes Zafar speaks nonsense.
I hope you don't mind.
It's all right.
By the way, every time
Mrs. Mukherjee mentions you
she's all praises.
Has she said anything about me?
Yes, so often that I could not
think of anyone else but you...
if I wanted to get married.
What do you mean?
I owe a lot to Mrs. Mukherjee.
I am here because she insisted.
Actually, I don't ever
want to get married.
Please turn down this proposal.
Any excuse will do.
Like?
Like... you didn't like me.
That means...
I have to lie in spite of not wanting to.
Rohan, I work.
I earn a living.
I don't depend on anyone.
But, in real life how can two negatives
make a positive?
Actually,
it's funny because...
I don't want to get married either.
Then... why?
The same... Mrs. Mukherjee's pressures.
Yes.
But...
in just this meeting,
I have learnt that...
you are not just confident
but also very independent.
And I think that's...
that's really amazing.
Thank you.
Can I say something, Su?
A man's self-confidence is his strength.
You and I... we are not weak.
Then why are you so afraid
of walking with me?
Because darkness cannot
light up darkness, Rohan.
Right.
But having someone
with you in the darkness...
can make it seem less daunting.
I am confused.
Do you want to get married or not?
I do.
But, not yet.
I want to give you some time.
Just to be sure.
Of you... of me.
Of us.
So, you know...
Let's... let's just see.
Would you like some tea?
Yes.
My friend has done it.
Look at their approving smiles...
it's a yes!
Congratulations on the wedding!
Welcome the Lord Ganesha!
Welcome this beautiful Lord!
Oh sweet Lord... welcome!
Lord Ganpati!
Welcome!
Oh sweet Lord...
Welcome the Lord Ganesha.
So, shall we meet tomorrow?
When? Where?
Why?
If you want to be sure,
it's important to meet every day.
Isn't it, Su?
Every Monday, Wednesday and Friday
I am at the dance studio.
You dance, too?
I play the piano and
students dance.
You literally make people
dance to your tunes.
I get it now.
Rohan...
bye!
Bye, Su.
-Shall we go?
-Handsome!
Hey, is it your birthday today?
New clothes and all?
Shall I send you
some cake and wafers?
Yes, send them.
Son of a...
I've heard that love is blind.
But, the blind falling in love,
now that's new to me.
That was nice.
I know it's simple but I couldn't.
-Yes, please?
-Is Supriya here?
Yes. There she is.
-Can you...?
-Sure. I'll take you.
You guys go. I'll come.
-Supriya?
-Yes?
Your friend is here.
Hi.
Rohan!
Surprised or shocked?
Pleasantly surprised.
Thank God.
Sit.
There's... There's a stool...
Good... thanks.
How are you?
I am good.
So, till what time is this dance class?
I think this is the last session.
Coffee afterwards?
Yes. Sure.
Ok.
Let's take a five-minute break.
Su?
-Yes?
-You don't dance?
I dance.
You dance well?
I think I dance quite well.
-Really?
-Yes.
And you?
Actually, I...
Su, what is the size of this dance floor?
40 by 40.
So, square.
Any levels?
One.
And...
why do you ask that?
Because I feel like...
we should try.
-What?
-Yes.
Are you asking me to dance with you?
Yes, I am.
Rohan, are you mad?
What will people think?
If we start thinking
what people will think...
then, what will they think of us?
Su, come.
-Rohan, you are...
-Come.
Er... where are you going?
Oh, sorry.
Where is the floor?
Here.
I thought you were joking.
Hey, Supriya.
Where are you going?
That's my friend, Rohan.
He wants to explore the dance floor.
Oh, cool.
Shall I play the track?
Yes. Yes, please. Thanks.
Where does the level start from?
Right here.
"When our"
"Steps align"
"Our journey begins"
"And wherever we walk together"
"The world will walk with us"
"My love"
"Give yourself into my arms"
"Like a cloud gives
Into the breeze"
"My love"
"Give yourself into my arms"
"Like a cloud gives
Into the breeze"
"When we walk together"
"To the same beat"
"For where we walk"
"There many will gather"
"The earth cries out in joy"
"My love"
"Let's gather all our dreams
In our eyes today"
"Let's make happiness our own"
"Let's gather all our dreams
In our eyes today"
"Let's make happiness our own"
"Listen, love"
"Let's have some more fun"
"Say 1-2-3-4"
"My love"
"Give yourself into my arms"
"Like a cloud gives
Into the breeze"
"When we walk together"
"To the same beat"
"For wherever we go"
"There many will gather"
"The earth cries out in joy"
"My love"
"Move to the rhythm, my love
I see you with my heart"
"My love"
"Move to the rhythm, my love
I see you with my heart"
"My love"
"Move to the rhythm, my love
I see you with my heart"
Rohan, enough.
How many shoes are you
going to make me try?
One more, Su.
One more.
Su, this is the one.
Why?
What is right about this one?
This one has the right tone.
When you wear this,
I will know how close you are.
Or how far!
Come, I think we should
buy this one.
Yes, please.
Rohan, it's a lot more crowded today.
Just a minute.
-What happened?
-It is very crowded.
Su, there is no need for this.
Ladies and gentlemen!
I am with you.
Come.
-Su, I feel hungry.
-Yes?
-Yes.
-Let's go to the food court.
It's on the first floor.
-Excuse me, where's the escalator?
-There.
Put your hands together
and please welcome
none other than... Mr. Vikram Khanna!
Thank you!
Rohan!
Excuse me, sir.
Su!
Guys, hold on one second please.
Stop pushing guys, please!
Rohan...
What are you doing?
One second, please.
What happened?
I need to go down.
Wait, you cannot go down.
Su!
-Give me some space!
-Su!
Rohan!
Excuse me.
Excuse me, is there a lady here?
She is blind too, just like me.
Why don't you go
to the help desk, please?
-Let's go.
-Where is the help desk?
-Move aside.
-Excuse me...
Excuse me...
Sorry... excuse me.
Excuse me, sir, can you help me?
I need to get to the help desk.
Sorry, buddy. I have no idea.
Excuse me.
Tell me.
Excuse me, I cannot find my friend.
Like me, he too cannot see.
Please help me.
Sorry, madam.
There is no one here.
Please call a security person.
Security...
Let me look... hang on.
-His name is Rohan. Hello...
-You wait here.
Here we have Vikram for you.
Come on, Vikram.
We are dying to hear you.
Tell us about your new film.
Every love story has
action and emotion.
But, this love story has such a twist
that no one here would've ever seen it.
Excuse me.
So, let's hear it for Kahaani Pyaar Ki.
Excuse me, is the stage this way?
Excuse me!
Excuse me.
Can you help me, please?
Excuse me!
Can you help me?
Just a minute, guys.
Security.
I have been looking for my friend
for a very long time.
She is lost.
Can you help me?
You have a mic.
If you announce her name on the mic...
It will help me.
Get him on stage.
-Thank you.
-Please come.
Such passion.
Is she a friend or your girlfriend?
Please, if you could take her name...
Make the announcement yourself.
Your love story comes first,
then mine.
Here.
Turn around.
Su...
Where are you, Su?
Can you hear me, Su?
I am sorry, Su.
I don't know how my hand let go.
I am on the stage
at the center of this mall.
-Excuse me. Excuse me.
-Yes?
Will you take me
to the stage, please?
Sure, please come.
Su.
Rohan.
Are you ok?
I am ok.
I am sorry, Su.
Let's go.
Come on.
Thank you!
All the best, buddy.
Have a good life.
Thank you!
Were you crying?
-Not at all.
-Really?
Rohan,
you can let go of my hand now.
I am not going anywhere.
Su.
Yes.
There was never light.
But, I felt true darkness
for the first time today.
I've always lived alone.
But today, I felt loneliness
for the first time.
What are you doing?
I am looking at you
by touching you.
I've seen you without touching you.
-What?
-Yes.
How so?
That day... at the restaurant.
And, to tell you the truth,
it was love at first sight.
Rohan, please tell me.
You are scaring me now.
Where are we going?
Home.
What?
Our new home.
We've reached.
Come, come.
-Hello.
-Yes, darling?
-Where are you?
-Where am I?
Floating high above the ground...
-but just below the skies.
-What do you mean?
I've come to show sister-in-law
the new house.
But what will she see?
That's what I want to see.
-Zafar, what are you doing?
-What happened?
Where's your attention?
Look down!
What happened?
What is this?
The elevator shaft.
Service lift.
Sixteen steps and then this hole.
-Remember.
-Yes.
It's a construction site.
Be careful.
If I had fallen from here who knows...
whether I would reach heaven or not.
Thank you, bro.
I suggest you wear this.
A harness.
It's perfect for you.
Rohan...
Su, this is our main door.
Welcome.
Come sister-in-law, come.
This is your living room.
-Which is the size of my entire house.
-Shh...
Rohan,
we won't put a lot of furniture in
our living room. Ok?
Ok. Yes.
Just basics.
And a swing in the balcony.
-Perfect.
-Isn't it?
And lots of candles.
-Candles?
-Yes. Scented ones.
I love scented candles.
Really?
Come here. I think you will love this.
-Come.
-What?
The sun...
wait... I think...
in the evening, the sun sets here.
And every time, a sweet breeze blows...
-There.
-Yes.
-Feel it.
It's beautiful.
Wow.
Su,
it feels as though in real life too,
two negatives are
going to make a positive.
Really?
Using my own words against me?
But actually, Rohan.
I have never even dreamt
of such things.
I was afraid.
No, Su.
Dream them.
Dream more.
Make them big, Su.
Don't hold yourself back.
Because now my goal
in life is just this;
to make myself capable enough,
to fulfill every dream of yours.
"All our dreams"
"Locked behind shut eyes"
"Where do we find the key?"
"It's in the chalice of the moon"
"And yet, if I make dreams come true"
"Will you tell me"
"Am I worthy of your love?"
"Or am I not?"
"This mischief, this fun"
"This is our way"
"How do I explain?"
"For it is life's secret!"
"This heart doesn't beat here"
"Just your voice echoes here now"
"This is the beginning
Of all our joys!"
"All our dreams"
"Locked behind shut eyes"
"Where do we find the key?"
"It's in the chalice of the moon"
"And yet, if I make dreams come true"
"Will you tell me"
"Am I worthy of your love?"
"Or am I not?"
"When my fingers draw a heart
In the soft sands"
"It will call your name
These bangles will quiver"
"Your charms are like
That of soaring butterflies"
"These colors of joy
Will not fade"
"All our dreams"
"Locked behind shut eyes"
"Where do we find the key?"
"It's in the chalice of the moon"
"And yet, if I make dreams come true"
"Will you tell me"
"Am I worthy of your love?"
"Or am I not?"
Parveen knows all your
rituals and customs.
She has even decorated
your bedroom.
Zafar... thanks!
Don't be silly.
-Listen...
-Yes?
I've got a special gift for you.
What?
Balloons...
Condom.
Not in front of everyone.
What are you doing?
No one is watching.
You are insane.
-Don't worry, everyone's busy eating.
-You're crazy!
Listen, anyway...
in India, whether it is
an election or a marriage,
everyone wants results
in the first year.
But, you don't rush.
There are a lot of children
in the colony already.
You take your time.
You are absolutely mad.
How long?
Hang on. I am coming.
Hurry up.
The siren has gone off?
The party will leave now?
Yes. Where to?
Amit has planned a party.
Son, Wasim,
your best friend,
Amit, is the legislator's
younger brother,
and we are butchers.
If we cut meat every day, we eat.
You have to come to the shop
tomorrow onwards.
-No excuses.
-I will come.
I am leaving now, father.
Where did brother go?
He has left with his childhood buddy.
Wasim, tell me something.
In the blind couple's
first night together,
will the lights be on or off?
Bro, I don't know about the lights.
But, the fan will be turned on for sure.
Why?
It's going to be very hot.
Amit, how do the blind...?
What?
I mean... without seeing...
Simple... by touch and feel.
Candles.
You remembered?
No.
Are there candles?
I don't know how they got here.
Really? Liar!
Su, you've completed me.
How can I leave
any of your desires unfulfilled?
I can't see but I can feel.
Everything is so beautiful.
What are you doing?
I feel ticklish.
I won't let that happen.
Hands up, Romeo!
Who is that?
Don't worry, baby.
Save me!
No! No!
You can't do that, Romeo!
It's a sin... a sin!
If you do that, I'll have
a heart attack, Romeo.
I... I...
I've got a heart attack, Romeo!
I've got a heart attack now.
Aunty, control your emotions.
Mumma...
Game... ha-ha... over!
-How was that?
-Fantastic.
Ok.
Amazing.
How does he dub
without seeing the video?
That too, while switching
between so many voices.
Are you sure he is blind?
He listens in English
and speaks in Hindi.
-You know...
-Brilliant!
-Hello.
-Su, Hi!
Guess who's in the studio today.
If you don't tell me,
how would I know?
Who is it?
Talk to him.
And guess who it is.
Hello, Supriya-ji.
How are you?
Who is this?
I am Amitabh Bachchan.
Rohan's friend.
How are you?
Amit-ji... is that you?
Namaste.
Ever since Rohan has met me,
he has been constantly
praising your beauty.
He hasn't said any such thing to me.
All men are the same.
They never say anything
to their wives.
Jaya-ji has the same complaint.
Yes, thank you. Thank you, Amit-ji.
Bless you.
May you have a
happy married life.
I take your leave
with these good wishes.
Rohan, did you hear that?
Amit-ji has blessed us so generously.
Does Aamir Khan come to your studio?
Not just Aamir, I'll get all the
Khans for dinner tonight.
Ok?
But, listen,
we are eating out tonight.
-Ok?
-Bye.
Bye. See you.
Do you know, Su?
I now know how it feels
to feel hot even
when it's air conditioned.
You gave me such
a huge love bite last night.
Huge?
I am a dubbing artist.
It's the first time a dubbing artist
was left speechless.
Ever since Anup pointed it out,
I've been walking around
with my shirt buttoned till the top.
Can you imagine?
But, who started it?
You.
Me?
Oh God. What lies!
Oh, lies?
You know, Dastoor auntie
met me in the morning
and took all the details.
No way!
And then she related
the history of her love bites
that she got 15 years ago.
Mrs. Dastoor?
Love bites?
-Can you imagine?
-Oh God.
By the way,
I've been wearing a scarf
around my neck since this morning.
Su, please give me your hand.
Your left hand.
The time is nine o'clock p.m.
I bought it with my first salary.
I will wear both.
One watch will tell me the time,
and the other, your love.
How much?
80 rupees, sir.
-80 rupees?
-Yes, sir.
Here's a 100.
Thank you, sir.
Are you fooling me
or testing me?
What happened, sir?
-It's 80 rupees, right?
-Yes, sir.
Why are you giving me
back just 10?
Give me 20.
Sorry, sir.
It happened because I was in a rush.
Here.
-What happened?
-It's fine now.
Let's go.
You know, Supriya-ji...
That auto rickshaw driver
was trying to fool me.
I knew it was you as Mr. Bachchan!
Mr. Dubbing Artist!
Using my words against me?
No, seriously.
You are quite smart,
I better watch out.
That, I am...
Who is it?
Amit?
It's you, right?
What is it, Rohan?
I am scared. Let's go.
There is no need to be afraid, Su.
I know him.
Don't play hide-n-seek, Amit?
If you want to say something,
come forward.
I have to hand it to you, Rohan.
How do you know who it is?
You have a dangerous nose.
Get out of the way.
Make up your mind.
Sometimes you tell me
to come forward.
to get out of the way.
Get out of the way!
Ok. I've moved out of the way. Go!
Listen buddy, I have to ask you
something very important.
Even after trying really hard,
I am unable to score with a maid.
You've managed a fine target
even in the dark.
Show some respect.
She is my wife.
Get it?
Rohan, let go of my collar.
Oh! What's this?
Look, Wasim.
Looks like our handsome man
enacted an entire porn film last night.
You don't say!
Did you give her a love bite too?
Where did you give it?
No, don't tell me.
I'll find it myself.
Rohan!
Don't think I am weak.
I am telling you this once.
Don't ever forget!
Don't think I am weak.
Shilu auntie, sister Mhatre,
Mrs. Shirke, come everyone.
What's wrong, Supriya?
Why are you yelling?
These boys are
misbehaving with us.
But there's no one here
besides the two of you.
They were right here.
Rohan?
Where did they go?
They've gone, Su.
They've gone.
Let's go home.
-Look, I don't care.
-Yes...
What did you tell me
while booking the flat?
Yes... I remember.
-That you will hand it over in December.
-Yes, I did.
Then how can you tell me
that I'll get it next year?
The papers are still being processed.
-What paper, Rajesh?
-Listen...
Rajesh...
I don't care.
Either give me possession of the flat
in a month or return my money.
That's it.
-I'll... talk to the boss.
-Yes.
Don't worry. I'll sort it out.
Yes, thank you.
What are you doing, Su?
What I should have done last night
when you slapped that man.
Then why didn't you?
Sorry. Sorry.
Supriya, good morning.
-Good morning, auntie.
-What's this?
Actually, auntie,
our fridge isn't working.
Can you keep the milk
in your fridge?
Sure.
Su!
Where are you?
I tried calling you
so many times today.
Do you know who came
to the studio today?
Aamir Khan!
I wanted you to talk to him
but you didn't answer the phone.
Unbelievable.
It was a fabulous chance.
You missed it.
At least answer me.
Su.
What happened?
Su?
Su, are you ok?
What happened, Su. Tell me.
What happened, Su. Tell me!
Tell me what happened.
Tell me.
Based on your wife's statement,
we've taken Amit and
Wasim into custody.
But, in such a case, a medical report
is necessary, Mr. Bhatnagar.
And it is important to
get it done right away.
Within 24 hours.
Because we can keep them in custody
only on the basis
of the medical report. Or...
Please prepare her.
Her family?
No... I am her only family.
I'll...
There is no case, sir.
She can't identify them.
And the smart asses didn't say
a word during the rape,
so she can't even identify their voices.
The entire case rests
on her sense of smell.
Will she go around sniffing
everyone in the courtroom?
And will the judge accept a
testimony based on smell?
That's why exactly I am sending her
for a medical test.
Hello.
Yes?
Ok.
The call has come?
At such a time,
it's usually what happens.
So what? Calls keep coming.
Don't worry about my calls.
-Do your duty.
-Yes, sir.
Take her to Masina hospital
for a medical test.
Yes, sir.
Listen, Inspector Chaube
has sent a car for you.
I apologize for the delay.
Let's go to the hospital.
And, Inspector Chaube
has called you to the police station.
Yes, sir.
Open up!
You said we were going to the hospital.
Where are we?
Open!
Is anyone there?
-Who is it?
-Hey!
Stop irritating me with
this constant knocking.
Look, we will keep you here
for 24 hours.
-After that, you can go.
-But, why?
Quiet.
If you bang the door again,
your wife will be--
Rohan!
Rohan?
Rohan.
Are you ok?
I am fine.
Rohan!
Supriya!
Rohan.
-We've reached the hospital, sir.
-Thank you.
Your report is ready.
The doctor is asking for you.
Mr. Bhatnagar,
don't expect a lot from this report.
The 24 hours from the
time of rape are critical,
from an evidence point of view.
You came here after 30 hours.
And that too, drenched.
All evidence seems to have been
washed away.
What?
Kidnapped you?
Locked you up and
threw you in the sea?
Yes.
Do you have a witness?
Witness?
Do you think I am crazy?
I've got you figured out.
You are extremely cunning.
Madam.
Have you really been raped?
-Or are you just...?
-What are you saying?
You don't seem to understand.
You'll be put away
for a long time.
For trying to frame the legislator.
Defamation and fraud.
You will be charged with both.
Where is Inspector Chaube?
I want to talk to him.
Sir is on duty.
And what will you speak to him about?
Talk to me first.
Look...
'No clinical evidence of rape.'
It is clearly mentioned.
You are frauds.
First, you lodged a complaint for rape
and then, you disappeared for 24 hours.
You thought you would
cook up a story in 24 hours.
Am I right?
What sort of person are you?
You want to make a quick buck
using a woman?
-Have some shame.
-You...
If it weren't for your uniform,
I would've broken your jaw.
This is rubbish.
I don't believe this report.
I will redo the medical test.
Come on, Su. Come.
I don't want to go anywhere, Rohan.
-But, Su.
-I don't want to go anywhere.
-Su...
-Why don't you understand
what these people are doing to us?
Please.
I have been raped.
And ever since then, that's what
they are doing to you.
Please, Rohan, take me home.
I am very tired, Rohan.
Please...
I feel disgusted here.
Please, Rohan.
-Please take me home.
-Ok, Su.
Let's go home.
Rohan.
Dinner is ready.
Eat.
I am not hungry, Su.
You eat.
Rohan, if you don't want to eat,
then come to bed.
I will sit here for a while, Su.
Su, please... go to sleep.
Rohan,
I understand...
Now I am not the same person I was.
If you don't want to stay with me,
I have no problem.
I have my NGO job.
I will go back there.
I know that things will never be
the same for us again.
I will assume that...
everything before yesterday
was a dream.
The food is on the table, Rohan.
Eat a little.
Your wife is so gifted
that she can stay without food
she can stay without water...
Sorry.
Rohan, I don't want to force you.
But, we have a deadline.
You have dubbed the voice earlier.
So, I don't have a choice.
Ready.
Great.
Let's go again.
Your wife is so gifted
that she can stay without food
she can stay without water
but she can't stay without talking.
Su...
The time is five o'clock p.m.
I am really sorry for yesterday.
I was silent because
I didn't know what to say.
Yesterday, for the first time,
I felt weak.
I was angry with myself.
So angry, that I forgot
to wipe your tears.
I am really sorry, Su.
But now, everything will be ok, Su.
We will go back to how
we were before.
You and...
Su... Su...
What have you done?
Speak to me, Su.
Tell me...
Say something, Su.
Su!
You can't do this, Su!
No... no!
No, Supriya, no!
You can't give up, Supriya.
No!
"I am with you, burning in this fire"
"All my dreams, burnt away"
"Those moments I spent with you"
"My beloved engulfed in flames"
"The ashes of our yearning rise"
"To ask me"
"Am I"
"Worthy of your love?"
"Or am I not?"
"Am I worthy of your love?"
Listen,
I'll go to the garage for a bit.
I've left some rice in the fridge. Eat it.
Let's go.
Your wife was pretty.
I am legislator Madhavrao Shellar.
Amit's older brother.
I don't know why I feel that...
you won't vote for me
these elections.
Youth is like a racehorse.
It sprints at the sound of a gunshot.
They have more spirit than
blood running through their veins.
I was once young like Amit.
I too, fell for Mhatre's wife...
from the colony.
But, I couldn't do anything about it.
I didn't have the support.
My father was a poor mill worker.
But, Amit does have support.
Mine.
Which means, what I couldn't do,
Amit can.
I own the cops.
I got Amit released.
Mr. Bhatnagar, I feel sorry, too.
You were newly-weds.
It was still the honeymoon
and she left the world.
But...
you were the first to be with her.
Amit got nothing special.
Don't talk to the media.
Don't talk to the people in the colony.
The more you talk,
the more it'll give rise
to defamation.
For Amit.
I have to send him to Delhi.
People in the colony
will forget in a few days.
You should forget, too.
Delete it from your memory.
All right.
Mr. Bhatnagar,
I didn't get one thing about your wife.
If she wanted to commit suicide,
why didn't she do it after
she was raped the first time?
Why wait till the second time?
Bye.
"Rohan,
I know that neither you
nor your love is weak.
We would've been fine in a few days
and would return to our normal lives.
But if what happened today,
continued to happen,
you would have broken.
And I wouldn't be able to bear it.
Today, when you went to work,
I was cooking in the kitchen."
Who is it?
Percy.
Sister, I found the ball.
Good, and don't worry about the glass.
I will clean it.
Sister, have you made flatbreads?
Yes. Stuffed with potato.
Will you eat some?
Tomorrow, flatbreads stuffed
with cauliflower?
All right. Done!
Thank you, sister.
-Ok. Bye.
-Bye.
Even we will eat flatbreads.
That day you...
you didn't hear my voice.
That's fine.
Hear it today.
And get used to hearing it.
Because from now on,
we will keep visiting.
I will come whenever I feel like.
Let's try something new today.
"I know how much pain you are in.
And I love you so much.
I couldn't let you go through
this agony repeatedly,
I have to go.
I regret that
I am leaving you alone.
I have one last wish, though.
I am leaving these two watches behind.
If it's possible, cremate one...
and bury the other.
Yours, Su."
Rohan,
these are the ashes.
These are not ashes.
It is my Su.
You will have to bid
sister-in-law goodbye.
Come, let's scatter them in water.
No, Zafar.
I have bid her goodbye with fire.
Water will have to wait.
Here.
What is it?
Have you come to mourn your wife
at the police station?
I want to meet Inspector Chaube.
Sir is on duty.
You have his mobile number.
Give it to me.
What do you think?
That everybody is sitting
idle for you?
Do you know what a large area
falls under him?
There are so many cases.
You don't even have a case.
You are a fraud.
Don't come back here.
I won't.
But, I won't leave without meeting
Inspector Chaube today.
Will you hold a demonstration here?
Can't you understand?
Sir is out on duty.
"Inspector Chaube... Inspector..."
Inspector Chaube,
I want to talk to you.
Hey!
Inspector Chaube.
Get out... out!
I told you to get out.
We've given you enough respect.
Now, get out.
-Nalawde.
-Sir.
Yes, sir.
Tell me.
Everything happened very fast, sir.
My Su's departure,
the closing of this case
and their release.
Mr. Bhatnagar,
we had to release them because
we didn't have evidence against them.
And your wife committed suicide.
We can't see him but he exists.
Behind every suicide the killer exists.
My Su was not weak.
And even she understood that
there is more darkness in your law
than in our world.
She would've lived
with this truth,
but after the second time,
she broke.
Second time?
What do you mean?
They came back, sir.
They raped my Su, again.
What?
He's talking nonsense, sir.
Don't worry, Inspector Nalawde.
I won't make the mistake
of filing a complaint again.
And anyway,
neither I, nor Su have
any hope for you now.
I only came to tell you that
if your system had helped me a little,
I wouldn't have to do anything.
Now, I will have to.
For my Su.
What do you mean, you will have to?
What will you do?
Will you take revenge?
A reply, sir.
I will respond to them.
And you won't need an FIR
or a medical check-up.
You may only need a post-mortem.
And you will go scot-free?
Yes, sir.
Like they did.
Perfect crime.
And what do you think?
That our eyes will remain shut?
No, sir.
Your eyes will be open,
but you won't be able to
see anything.
Your ears will be open but
you won't be able to hear anything.
You will want to say something
but you will not be able to speak.
And most importantly,
you will figure it all out,
but you won't be able to
explain it to anyone.
Are you playing a game with us?
Giving us four options,
A, B, C, D.
They started the game.
You enjoyed it.
I will end it.
-One more thing.
-Say it.
Say everything today.
There won't be
any lifeline in this game, sir.
I'll take your leave.
Amit...
-Yes?
-Where to?
There's no fixed plan yet.
I will call Wasim.
Do you know
why Nalawde is here?
We've already paid him four lakhs
to cover things up.
Plus, the news has reached
the party headquarters.
And, you don't care.
You mess around and
your brother has to pay for it.
Enough.
No more hanging out with Wasim.
Concentrate on the campaign.
There are only two months
for the elections to begin.
If I hear about one more stupid thing,
I will send you
to our sister in Pune.
Do you understand?
Yes, I understand.
I am going.
Will he listen to you?
What can I tell you, Nalawde?
We have the same blood
running in our veins.
He won't listen.
He won't understand.
He will go over to Wasim's and party.
"Some desire me"
"Some are intoxicated with me"
"I am wild youth"
"My lovers are all over"
"Some yearn for me"
"To some, I am a lover"
"Many a prayer are said
To make me theirs"
"The whole world"
"Revolves around a beautiful woman"
"Why does the world then say"
"It's wrong to fall in love?"
"The whole world"
"Revolves around a beautiful woman"
"Why does the world then say"
"It's wrong to fall in love?"
"The whole world"
"This girl is the one"
"She's dynamite"
"She causes fights daily in every alley"
"Give me a little time"
"Love isn't a crime"
"I find her better every passing day"
"Are you a girl or wine?"
"People want to know
When will you fall in love?"
"The world is queuing up and so am I"
"The whole world"
"Revolves around a beautiful woman"
"Who says"
"To fall in love today"
"Trust the kind that never ends"
"Who says"
"To fall in love today"
"Trust the kind that never ends"
"Some desire me"
"Some are intoxicated with me"
"I am wild youth"
"Lovers are all over"
"Some yearn for me"
"To some, I am a lover"
"Many a prayer are said
To make me theirs"
"The whole world"
"Revolves around a beautiful woman"
"Why does the world then say"
"It's wrong to fall in love?"
"The whole world"
"The whole world..."
Today was great fun.
"The whole world revolves
around a beautiful woman."
"Then, why does the world say,
it's wrong to fall in love?"
Look, Wasim.
So what if the dance bar has closed?
Our bar is open 24 hours.
Let's have a couple.
-Come.
-How much will you drink?
-How much?
-I will drink.
We will have to stop meeting anyway.
Why?
Father is very angry.
Yes.
Even brother is very angry with me.
He says, "You mess around
and your brother has to pay for it."
"No more meeting Wasim."
"Concentrate on the campaign."
Bloody...
if I concentrate on the campaign,
who will concentrate on alcohol?
-Isn't that right?
-Let's go.
We've had enough.
Go? Ok.
So, we'll leave now.
Come on, Wasim.
Be careful. You drink so much.
"The whole world revolves
around a beautiful woman."
Brothers and sisters, it's not pride,
but everyone knows what
our party has done for the locality.
Putting an end to injustice.
And progress for everyone.
This is our party's mantra
and this is its goal.
Victory to Maharashtra!
"Putting an end to injustice."
"And progress for everyone."
"This is our..."
"So what if the dance bar has closed?"
"Our bar is open 24 hours."
"Let's have a couple."
"What do you think?"
"That everybody is sitting around
idle for you?"
"Do you know what a large area
falls under him?"
"There are so many cases."
"You don't even have a case."
"You are a fraud."
"Don't come back."
Rohan.
Why are you listening to
the voices of people that I hate?
These voices have
silenced our love, Su.
But, very soon...
no one will ever hear
these voices again.
Hello.
Figure out a solution
for Wasim quickly, Nalawde.
He is always stuck like
a magnet to Amit.
Tell me, sir.
What is the order?
You guys detain people temporarily
during festivals.
-Yes... yes.
-What is it called?
Preventive arrest.
What an idea, sir.
I'll pick him up today.
Sir, I am... a little short.
Don't worry.
I am right here.
Meet me later.
-Ok.
-Yes. I'll come. Victory to Maharashtra!
Victory to Maharashtra!
Hello, sir.
What have I done?
You haven't done anything.
Neither will you.
-What?
-Rest inside for three days.
I will release you after that.
Take him.
Sir, please listen to me.
Come.
What disgusting behavior
is this, Amit?
What happened?
Who is it?
Hear me out.
My love, don't think so much.
No one will even know.
I am not calling you for free.
I will pay you.
Tell me, should I book a room?
Come, we will have some fun.
You are so dead.
You are dead!
So what if you are my son's friend?
You are dead now!
By tomorrow, this note
should reach every home.
-Sure.
-Each and every home.
Everyone should be
talking about brother.
Got it?
Come.
Shakeel uncle?
But, why did you slap me?
-What have I done?
-What have you done?
You are asking me what you have done?
-I will stick your phone into you.
-What?
For the rest of your life,
you will neither be able to walk nor sit.
-If you call again.
-But, call who?
Stay away from my daughter.
The old man has lost it.
-Hello.
-I made a mistake.
I thought I was talking to Payal.
Think about it.
Have I ever spoken to you
this way in so many years?
No.
Meet me once.
We will meet face to face and
clear this misunderstanding.
I don't want to meet.
Look, Lubna.
We are childhood friends.
Don't sever our friendship like that.
I want to meet you once
and apologize. That's it.
Meet me once.
Please, come.
All right.
Where do you want to meet?
Sorry for what?
Why did you lie to Shakeel uncle?
When did I call you?
You unnecessarily
got me slapped in public.
He was a college friend.
What if father found out?
Can't you take a slap for me?
I am sorry.
If you don't believe me,
I will apologize in person.
Shall we meet?
Mind your tongue, Shellar.
She is my daughter.
And don't forget that
we are butchers.
Hey... chicken thief!
There is no need to scream.
There is no need to scream!
Look, your son enjoys
his drinks with Amit's money.
Now, even your daughter has
started enticing him.
Shellar!
Be quiet.
Don't scream.
Go.
Go behind the mosque.
And see it with your own eyes.
You will understand.
You will know who called whom.
Go right now.
Lubna...
apologize now!
You seemed to be in
quite a mood on the phone.
What are you looking at?
Apologize.
Shut up! Enough.
-What?
-Are you mad?
You aren't going to change.
What are you saying?
On the phone you said that
you wanted to apologize.
And now, you are back
to your ways.
Why would I say sorry?
I think the entire butcher family
has lost it.
-No.
-Father?
It's not our family,
but yours that has gone mad.
And the biggest lunatic
is your brother.
-Hey!
-You get out of here.
I will deal with you later.
First let me cool him off.
Put the knife away.
Shakeel...
That day you slapped me,
I didn't say anything.
You play with my daughter...
Put the knife away, Shakeel.
Put the knife away.
Father!
How dare you file the complaint.
Is he dead?
Mr. Shellar, there's
Inspector Chaube above me.
What do you mean?
Your hand is first to reach
the wad of notes.
Am I wrong?
Then do the work.
Tear up the complaint.
I'll figure out what the problem between
Amit and the butcher's family is.
Send Wasim to me.
So, should I release him?
Who?
Mr. Shellar, on your order
I put Wasim in jail for three days.
Are you drunk?
When did I tell you
to put Wasim in jail?
Do I own your jail?
Do I?
No, sir.
Remember, Nalawde.
Even a dog is loyal to the one
that feeds him the bone.
Don't try to bite that hand.
Clear? Do you get it?
Yes, sir.
Leave.
Send Wasim here.
Go. Out!
Rohan, enough.
How many shoes are
you going to make me try?
This one has the right tone.
When you wear this,
I will know how close you are.
Or how far!
Hi.
You're awake?
I haven't slept.
What?
Then what were you doing?
I was waiting for you to wake up.
Good morning, Mrs. Bhatnagar.
Good morning.
Good morning, Mr. Bhatnagar.
"Since a few days"
"I've become accustomed to you"
"You've become my necessity"
"I smile through your lips"
"I flow in your rhythm"
"I cannot live without you"
"I promise"
"I soar in your breeze these days"
"These days"
"I only walk"
"With you these days"
"There is nothing remaining of me"
"Everything is yours"
"Since a few days"
"I've become accustomed to you"
"You have become my necessity"
I didn't get a chance to get
used to them, Rohan.
They won't get time either, Su.
Don't bother.
Sit.
What's going on, Wasim?
What's going on between
Amit and your father?
Brother, Amit misbehaved with Lubna.
Have you lost it?
Amit considers your sister his own sister.
Do you think he could do this?
And your father brought
a knife to kill Amit.
Chaube has filed a complaint.
Now, what I am saying is...
I have sent Amit to Pune.
Tell your father to
rescind the complaint.
Do you remember,
I got you out in the
blind girl's rape case?
Do you remember or not?
I will bear your father's
medical expenses.
You rescind the complaint.
Do you understand?
Yes.
Go.
-Hello.
-Wasim, this is Amit.
You are calling from Mumbai, right?
The number is from here.
And your brother says that
you've gone to Pune.
Are both brothers
making a fool of me?
Wasim, I never called Lubna.
At least meet me.
I want to meet you and
clear everything.
Where will you meet me?
Amit?
Come, Wasim.
Look. I've got you
the best whiskey today.
Scotch.
I have to make
peace with my bro,
so I thought the whiskey
should do the trick.
Isn't it?
You stabbed my father.
Misbehaved with Lubna.
Do you think
I'll have a drink with you?
Forget the bad behavior.
What respect did you show
the blind girl?
Hey.
Lubna is my sister. Get it?
And we both had fun
with the blind girl.
And that too, twice.
And what's with this
new concern for the blind girl?
Who is she to you?
Everything.
She was everything.
How did you manage
to sound like Amit?
It was you on the phone,
wasn't it?
I am blind
but I can hear.
And I can make you hear
what I want.
Enough.
The lights are on now,
and you are off!
"We can't see him but he exists."
"Behind every suicide the killer exists."
Sir, has the blind guy
started playing his game?
Are you crazy, Nalawde?
Look at the preparation.
And he cannot see.
He is incapable of this.
What is that on his shoulder?
Sir, a handkerchief.
A. S.
Amit Shellar.
Nalawde, animosity runs
just as deep as friendship.
Find out where Amit Shellar is.
Yes, sir.
This is not a suicide,
but a murder.
How are you, Chaube?
Amit was in Pune yesterday.
Do you have proof of
Amit being in Pune yesterday?
Are you questioning me
or doubting me?
Both.
Look, Chaube.
The number of years
you've been playing cop,
I've been playing politics.
Do you think I'll allow
something so stupid?
Amit is a rascal
but he's not stupid.
Do you think he'll commit murder...
and then leave his handkerchief
on his shoulder to get caught?
For now, circumstances and evidence
are both against your brother, Shellar.
And if my investigation
leads me to your brother,
I will not step back.
Did I ask you to step back?
Remember, I support my brother.
Madhavrao Shellar.
Go.
In the name of Allah
who is merciful and benevolent.
All of you, please pray
for the soul of the deceased.
Who is it?
Are you crying?
One day you too, will have to cry, sir.
The day you cut onions at home.
Come, Inspector Chaube.
Will you have vegetables
made in the Kolhapuri style?
What do you do?
I am self-employed, sir.
I know a bit about sound
and I make do with it.
Where were you last night?
At home, sir.
People stay awake
because of the noise,
and the silence doesn't
let me sleep.
Yet, I am trying, sir.
Is there a witness who can confirm
you were home last night?
What sort of question is that, sir?
Does anyone keep a witness
while they sleep?
But sir, why are you asking me
these questions?
Because Wasim was murdered last night.
And you think that I did it?
At first, I didn't think so.
But, seeing you at Wasim's burial today
got me thinking about it.
Then, I remembered your challenge.
Did you forget?
Sir, I said that in a fit of rage.
And why would I murder Wasim?
Because he raped your wife.
For which you found no evidence, sir.
Then, why did your wife commit suicide?
Sir, what are you here to investigate?
Wasim's murder or my wife's suicide?
An eye for an eye makes
the whole world blind, Mr. Bhatnagar.
A perfect world, sir.
If everyone is blind,
no one will need the police.
Sir, have you ever arrested a blind person
in a rape or murder case?
A perfect world, sir.
Where everyone is blind.
By leaving behind
Amit's handkerchief next to Wasim,
you've tried to mislead the police.
But, the road ahead won't be so easy.
-I know that now Amit--
-Will burn, sir.
The food, sir.
Please let go of my hand.
It will burn.
Thank you, sir.
It doesn't feel right to use
the third degree on a blind man.
But, if needed, I won't hold back.
The next time we meet,
it won't be in your kitchen,
but in our interrogation room.
Remember that.
If only you can find evidence
against me, sir.
-Did you call, sir?
-Yes.
Did you get Amit
and Wasim's call records?
We'll get them by tomorrow.
Did you get Shakeel's statement?
Yes, sir.
He is very angry with Amit.
He said that he would avenge
his son's death
before the mud in his
grave dries off.
Amit is going through a bad time, sir.
-All right.
-Thank you, sir.
-Hello.
-Hello, this is Nalawde.
Tell me, Nalawde.
-You are in Pune, aren't you?
-Yes, where else will I go?
They found your handkerchief
on Wasim's body.
Have all of you gone crazy?
I did not kill Wasim.
I know.
I even know who killed him.
It's your turn next.
Tell me his name.
He will be next.
Not on the phone.
Meet me.
You know where to meet, right?
How would I know if you haven't told me?
What warehouse did you
keep those blind people in?
The one at Madh. Why?
Exactly! There.
And listen,
I don't want anyone else there.
We have to meet in utmost secrecy.
All right.
Rohan, are you ok?
Blind guy, you?
But... Nalawde's voice?
How did you manage his voice?
Rohan, you are quite the artist.
What a plan?
Blind fellow, I am not Wasim.
I am not going to die so easy.
Avenging yourself?
Will you take revenge?
Now?
Do you have a plan B now?
You want to play the game
of revenge, right?
Let's play.
Here.
Pick it up.
Up!
You hit me once... I'll hit you once.
Hit me.
It's my turn.
Give it.
Give it to me.
I have to hand it to you.
You are blind, but gutsy.
Handsome! Are you dead?
Your wife was stronger than you.
I had to try very hard to
bring her under control.
Especially the second time.
Here.
I am giving you one last chance.
Pick it up.
Come on.
If you had continued to wear your shoes,
you may have survived.
Even a dead man can
smell your socks.
Now, you tell me...
do you have a plan B?
You were right.
-I am taking my revenge.
-Hey!
You didn't kill Supriya.
No.
I won't kill you either.
Do you know who will kill you?
No.
I'll tell you.
Tell me.
Brother, it's Amit.
He has tied me up
in the Madh godown, brother.
Please come and save me.
I'll tell you everything.
I am coming, Amit.
I am coming.
Please, brother.
I am an artist.
I agree.
I am good.
-Rohan...
-I am so good.
Rohan, let me go.
Rohan...
Rohan, what are you doing?
Rohan, don't do this.
I said I was sorry, Rohan.
Let me go.
Rohan, what are you doing?
Amit!
Don't you worry.
Don't worry, I am coming.
I am coming!
Sir...
Where is the body?
The body is completely burnt, sir.
He didn't burn himself,
he's been burnt.
Shakeel has burnt him.
Shakeel is still in the ICU
in the hospital.
Find out who did this.
Or the whole city will burn
just like my brother did.
Let's go.
Sir, I am sure the blind guy
is playing his game.
I suggest taking him in.
Are you crazy?
We don't have any evidence.
To top it off, he's blind.
All the social organizations
and the media will hound us.
Rohan, you did as promised.
Enough.
Get back to work.
Get back to your life, Rohan.
No, Su.
There is still work to be done.
This episode is not over.
Rohan, who were you talking to?
How did you get hurt?
It's nothing.
Listen,
are you bunking school again?
There is a football match between
our colony and Navjivan society.
I am going for practice.
Percy, you are a lost cause.
And what now?
Now, speak to the principal or
I will get a scolding.
And one day, if your father finds out.
Then what? You and I.
Don't worry. Nothing will happen.
Please. For the colony's sake.
All right.
But, this is the last time, Percy.
Yes.
Percy Dastoor.
Percy Dastoor's father.
Hello, Father Rodrigues.
Good morning, Father.
This is Cyrus. Percy's father.
I am so sorry, Father
but Percy has fallen sick again.
We tell him so much,
but he eats so much junk.
From today, we won't let him
eat junk food even by mistake.
Nor will we let him miss school.
Yes, Father.
Of course, Father.
Don't worry.
So, the secret is in your voice.
I kept wondering why Wasim went
to that closed theatre to meet Amit?
It was their drinking spot,
but Amit was in Pune.
Why would he come
to Mumbai from Pune...
when he was safer in Pune?
Who called him?
Why did he agree?
Whose voice did you mimic to call him?
You are very talented, Rohan Bhatnagar.
Remember...
you told me there would be
no lifeline in this game?
But, you have given me
a lifeline on your own.
24 hours.
And this case will be closed.
Thank you, sir.
For what?
For the 24 hours.
Nalawde,
get me Rohan Bhatnagar's
call records and keep them ready.
-It's urgent!
-Ok, sir.
Get Amit and Wasim's call records too
and keep them on my table.
I'll check them myself.
-How many men are at the police station?
-There are four, sir.
Get everyone to Guru Kripa
colony immediately.
Ok, sir.
-We have to keep a watch on someone.
-Yes, sir.
Yes... now.
I am giving you 24 hours.
But, we won't take our
eyes off you for even a second.
Inspector Chaube...
will you answer a question for me?
Truthfully.
If you were in my place,
what would you have done
to Wasim and Amit?
I am in no hurry for your reply, sir.
But, the day you answer me truthfully,
I won't lie to you.
Hey, WhatsApp club.
Yes, sir...
Be alert.
You slack, and there will be trouble.
Switch off the mobiles
and keep a watch.
-Yes, sir.
-Fools...
The time is 10:20 a.m.
-Sarmalkar,
-Yes...
I am messaging you
four landline numbers.
Give me their addresses.
It's very urgent.
The time is nine o'clock p.m.
-Sarmalkar.
-Yes, sir.
-I gave you four numbers.
-Yes.
You've messaged the address
for only one number.
-Where are the rest?
-Sir, all four have the same address.
-What?
-Yes, I did a thorough check.
-They all have the same address?
-Yes, sir.
That's why I sent one message.
All right.
Hey!
Where are you headed
this late in the night?
Sir, in Mumbai, this time is not late.
And, even if I want to go somewhere,
do I need permission?
Hey!
Don't get smart with me.
You are Bhatnagar's friend, aren't you?
Yes.
Is that a problem, too?
Which of them is Rohan?
Sir, this is my family.
But, I'll show you their faces.
Because you are mistaken.
Come to the side.
-Come.
-There.
Parveen.
Are you satisfied?
Can I go now?
Go.
What time does this open
in the morning?
7:00, sir.
-Hello, sir.
-Nalawde.
Is everything ok there?
Yes, sir. It's all ok.
Just be alert.
This case will be closed
by tomorrow morning.
Yes, sir.
Sir, Chaube is here.
I would've definitely
offered you a drink...
but you won't drink with me.
I will, today.
Why?
Are you feeling sorry for me today?
It's not that, Shellar.
You never understood...
but I've always helped you.
After the rape, when you called me...
I handed both of them over to Nalawde.
Knowing, that he would
hand them over to you.
In Wasim's case,
if I wanted to, I could've arrested
your brother from Pune.
But, I didn't.
Why?
Because I call for a show only when
I have all three aces in my hand.
Now, neither you; nor this city
has to burn.
Because we've found the person
who burned your brother.
Tell me the name.
Name the price?
Take as much as you want.
Tell me his name.
I will hand him over to you
tomorrow morning.
Not in the morning.
Right now!
If I tell you right now,
you won't believe it.
I will get him tomorrow
with a witness and evidence.
The thing is...
I will take a promotion
from the government,
and money from you.
Cheers.
I would've killed them both.
Amit and Wasim.
Remember, you asked me a question?
How did you kill him?
Wasim?
Amit?
No.
Shellar.
How did you get out of the colony?
-Zafar.
-Yes, Rohan?
Listen.
I need yours, Percy's and
Sakharam's help.
Sakharam, who?
The one who fumigates in the area.
Where are you headed
this late in the night?
-Speak.
-Brother, it's me.
Amit.
What?
Amit?
Brother, we...
we made a huge mistake, brother.
I received my punishment for it.
But, now it's your turn to be punished.
What rubbish.
It's not rubbish.
I am telling you the truth.
Who is this?
I am the same person who called
your brother to the godown.
If you have the balls,
tell me your name.
Rohan.
Rohan Bhatnagar.
Wait. Wait right there.
I'll come to your house and kill you.
There's no point in going there.
The police are everywhere.
Tell me where you are!
You will come, right?
You won't chicken out?
Take down the address.
Shellar!
Do you know,
why I called you here?
This is where Su and I
were going to make our home.
But you people did not let that happen.
Hey, Bhatnagar!
Enough is enough.
If you wanted to hide,
why did you call me here?
Come on out.
Sir!
Get him.
Anna!
It's your turn now.
Now what?
You already played your card.
I have a plan B for you.
Your brother asked me
the same question.
I didn't have a plan B, then.
I do now.
Come.
Drop it.
It's over Bhatnagar.
A press of the trigger...
and your story ends.
But, that's too easy.
You killed my Amit in such a way...
I could not even perform
his last rites.
So, I am going to make you suffer.
Get up!
My Su didn't have an easy death.
You will not have an easy death, either.
I won't die alone.
We will both fall.
But, only one will die.
Su committed suicide.
But, it was a murder.
This is a murder,
but it'll look like suicide.
So, Amit killed Wasim,
and Shellar, Amit.
And repenting on killing his brother,
Shellar committed suicide.
Very good.
That's very smart, Rohan Bhatnagar.
But, every criminal leaves some
trail behind after committing a crime.
You've left a whole witness.
Just one more hour.
Don't move.
Do you remember the fourth option, sir?
What do you mean?
It's ok, you'll figure it out...
but you won't be able
to explain it to anyone else.
Did this man make calls from here?
Mimicking different voices.
Sir?
If I could see,
I would've surely told you.
A perfect world, sir.
Where everyone is blind.
No.
I see peace on your face
after many days.
So what if I am not with you
in the world?
I'll always be with you, Rohan.
Walk on.