Hey!
Get my phone.
They have provided self-help books
to the students taking the exam.
Sir.
The students are worried about
how the test will be.
We are worried about
what the questions will be.
Sandhya...
Get me some chilled water.
We will try our level best...
Has she gone deaf?
She can't even get me a glass of water!
Lazy woman!
- What?
- Sir, parcel.
- Sign here.
- Give me a pen.
I don't have a pen.
- You don't have a pen?
- No.
What's wrong with everyone?
Victory to Arun Gawli!
Former Mafia don Arun Gulab Gawli is
fondly called "Daddy" these days.
He is now a changed man.
He takes his political campaign seriously,
by focusing on helping the poor...
... with medicines, electricity,
and water.
Now we have drinking water, not
the many problems with water like before.
Now we have a garden to play in.
It has new swings
and it's fun to play there.
- Tell me more, dear.
- He built a gym in the school.
We also have uniforms, notebooks,
and lunch at school now.
Do we have to give him
police protection now?
They've turned him into a hero.
People used to be terrified
to enter the Dagdi Chawl...
...but today he is looked up to
and compared to Robin Hood. Suddenly...
Geeta, I don't know who Robin Hood is.
He is a thief, but not a villain.
He takes from the rich
and gives it to the poor.
That's good.
The residents here are
very happy with him...
...and they are praying
that he wins in the next elections.
Open all his old cases.
Do you remember Vijaykar?
He's been after him since 1986.
We have even held back his retirement.
He must be remembering
the numbers of old cases too.
There's one thing in life
that's very rare...
...an opportunity.
Your entire life can pass by
in search of that one chance.
I felt as if my life had passed by too.
But there it was again...
...an opportunity.
How many people were there?
Two, sir.
Two.
Did you see the shooter?
No, sir.
Why?
Someone shot MLA Mhatre.
This is a big case.
- Tambe...
- Yes, sir.
I think it's him.
It's him.
Hello, ma'am!
I've got pedha for you.
You like pedha, don't you?
Have some sweets.
So, where's the leader of the nation?
What did he do now?
You want to know what he did.
What has he not done?
He started with extortion,
moved to gambling, robbery, smuggling...
...and then murder.
Your son will soon go in
for a long vacation!
He doesn't owe you anything.
So, why can't you leave him alone?
That's exactly what
I'm trying to figure out.
He's not even letting me retire in peace.
He thinks that he can become a Gandhi
merely by wearing a Gandhi cap.
He became what he had to.
I don't know whether it
was bad luck or bad influence.
But the worst thing
in his life was poverty.
There's no smoke without fire.
There's a strike.
No one will work today.
Stop working, everyone. Stop everything.
- I've got lunch for my father.
- Forget his lunch... Get lost.
No one will work.
He hasn't eaten since morning.
Hey boy! I'll have to knock
some sense into you.
Who are you calling 'boy'?
You cannot understand the plight
of a mill worker's son.
Go ask about the 200,000 workers
who lost their jobs.
Go and ask what happened
to their children.
- Babu, you're cheating again.
- Come on, play.
Put that coin back.
Will you play or not?
I won't play if you cheat.
- You play, Rama!
- Let it be.
Where are you going?
Sit.
Play with Rama.
Play.
Don't show me your teeth.
You should have seen the other guy's face.
Once again...
...you danced to their tunes.
You don't get it.
You must get them
to dance to your tunes.
Do you want ice cream?
Uma will get some for us.
Uma, come here.
Tell him about Parsiya's
famous ice cream parlor.
Why go there now?
Well, Parsiya opens
his gambling parlor at 9 a.m. ...
...and closes by 8 p.m.
When you enter, you'll see the manager.
I'll be sitting next to him.
- I'll sit there and...
- "Here she comes, my friends..."
Rama, please don't do this...
"Her veil is a curtain. She pretends..."
Hey! Shut up!
Why the hell are singing?
Can't you see who's behind the veil?
Haven't you seen a girl before?
Why do you stare at me
that way every day?
- She's angry!
- What?! Come!
Come here! Talk to me.
I wasn't the one singing.
I like you!
Why don't you show such courage...
...in front of those union leaders?
After seeing her, I miss Hilda.
I need to visit the barber, and then
I'll meet Hilda. I have to go.
Aren't you getting married
to another girl?
My mother wouldn't like Hilda...
...and I can't break my mother's heart.
- Shall I call her out again?
- Get lost!
Hey. Don't you like me?
People say you're involved
in dishonest work.
What are you trying to say?
What do you do?
I'm in the import and export business.
Really? Import and export!
Why don't you import something
so that she can export?
Stupid fellow!
Shut up!
Hilda, stop his mouth.
Hold this.
The balcony is empty
if want some privacy.
Come, I'II bring you home.
"They didn't really want
to get into fights."
"They just wanted to have a good time."
"Oh, really?"
"Why were they constantly visiting
Parsiya's gambling parlor?"
Who knows what to do?
Do you see the open door?
We have to go in there.
- Is this the one?
- Yes.
Arun, you handle two of them.
Babu, you handle the other two.
Vijay, you...
What if there are more than two to handle?
How do you know
how many men are inside?
Vijay, go and get a count.
Why me? They will see my face...
Blackie, the whole
of India looks like you.
- No one will notice you. Go.
- Come on, go.
Be careful.
Run!
Damn it!
What are you doing?
Damn!
Arun!
Let's go!
He stole from a thief.
He didn't just steal... He murdered.
Shall I remind you?
Arun had nothing to do with it.
It was all done by that smuggler
Babu Resham.
Arun, what place is this?
You asked me where I work,
so today I'm showing it to you.
Hey, Babu.
Here.
He's a stupid fellow!
This is the key to Babu's vault.
What happened?
Nothing.
What's all this, Arun?
These are imported items.
VHS...
It must be expensive.
No one's asking you for money.
Take it.
Take whatever you like.
Arun, let's go.
Hold on...
I said you don't have to pay me.
Didn't I say it's for free?
- What is it?
- There's a big problem.
I'II be back, Mom.
What happened?
Parsiya killed Uma.
"They never imagined that Parsiya
would kill Rama's brother Uma."
Let's go take revenge!
Have you lost your mind?
- Rama, let's go to the police.
- He was my brother.
Come on, Babu.
I told you he's a damn coward!
Come on!
- Come on, Babu!
- Hey, Rama. Rama.
- You're not coming?
- Let go.
- What do you mean, dog?
- Let go of me.
- Are you coming or not?
- No, I'm not.
What do you mean?
Are you going to go and salute the cops?
When you needed us,
we were there for you, Arun.
Don't ever show your face
around us, a**hole.
Rama!
What's wrong with you, man?
Let's go.
Hold it.
You motherf***er! Move back!
Kill him! Kill him!
Let's go... Let's go...
Hey... No!
Let go of me. Let go of me.
Who in God's name is it?
- What is it?
- Where is Arun?
- Where's Arun?
- What are you doing?
Get up! Get up!
- What have you done now?
- I didn't do anything!
Get up!
You didn't do anything?!
- Come to the police station!
- Leave him!
- Leave me!
- Come on, you filthy scum.
Let him go!
Get inside!
That's enough drama for one day.
Did you see how they
dragged him to the van?
He has lost all respect!
We belong to different communities
and so our lifestyles differ.
Zubeida, you won't say anything now.
Come with me to the village.
Do you recognize him?
Have you seen him before?
Have a look at him. Do you recognize him?
- Have you seen him?
- No.
Have you ever seen him?
Have you seen him?
Hey... I'm asking you.
Speak up.
Are you enjoying getting drenched?
Come on, get in.
Here. Have some Vadapav.
Take it.
Finally, he is one of us now.
Forget it.
I have Lord Shiva's blessings with me.
Not even one person recognized me.
Isn't it a miracle?
Idiot, that was no miracle!
You have the don's support.
Got it? It's the don.
Don't ever forget his favor.
Don rules Dongri these days.
At his command, everybody
refused to recognize you.
Babu's connected with him.
He said he will meet on Friday.
Okay. You'll meet my henchman
after Friday's prayers...
- ...near Musafirkhana's poultry farm.
- Greetings, Rafique.
How are you, Babu?
Have a seat. Have a seat!
So... What was I saying?
Friday, after prayers.
And it mustn't be postponed
until Saturday, get it?
- Good bye.
- Watch out!
Sorry...sorry!
It's an old and unique piece.
In our line of business,
always keep your eyes open.
- I didn't see it.
- Have a seat.
You sit there.
- Behave yourself.
- It wasn't me.
Alright. Did the angels give you a tip?
Yes, place the bet.
Okay. Alright.
Do you know who he is?
Bump him off!
- This guy?
- Yes.
Samad Khan.
He is a Pathan.
He is ruthless.
I told the don
all about your act of bravado.
He has all the details of
the Parsiya murder case too.
Bet 2 million on Midget's Century.
When?
We'll tell you.
If you're caught, you're on your own.
We won't come to rescue you this time.
Have you ever used an English weapon?
- We'll use it.
- That's good.
You may come here to get
10000 rupees after you finish the job.
But we haven't discussed
the money yet.
We'll discuss it
once the job's done.
You're the first man who's ever...
10,000 rupees is more than enough.
It will be done.
We are taking on the Pathans...
...for the sake of friendship.
We'll talk once the job's done.
Have you lost it?
It seems the don is in a good mood.
He gives his word.
Get Samad killed,,,
Then we can talk about it.
Samad, won't you say goodbye?
Bye.
- Leave him!
- Kill him!
I didn't see anything.
Yes, I had an affair with Babu.
He even asked me to leave town with him.
I refused to go.
You see, I come from a good background!
I want to know the details of the murder.
Come...
Give me the names.
Listen... Come on... Talk.
You wanted a new beginning, didn't you?
Take some money
and make a new beginning.
That would be good for you.
After they killed Samad...
...the don kept his word.
In fact he even offered friendship.
- Greetings.
- Yes!
- The don sent it for you.
- Okay.
Goodbye.
I love the don's style.
'Samad Khan's Brutal Murder'
Check this out, Rama.
Babu... Rama...
Arun.
B.R.A. Gang.
What about me?
What about you?
You went there to kill him,
but you got battered yourself.
Does anyone have any objection?
Hurry up!
Come on!
Do it properly.
Come on.
Give Maqsood his money back.
I don't want to work under anybody.
So what do you want to do?
Become a businessman like Tata or Birla?
If I work here in this line,
I need to be an equal.
Look, Babu...
The dockyard area belongs to us.
We must get a share in it.
Think about it
The docks will belong to you
and we will rule over Agripada.
You speak to Rama.
I'll make him understand.
Who will talk to the don?
Don.
What does he put in
this custard ice cream?
He has never told this to anybody
outside his family.
He refused me twice.
Don, would you like some more?
That's enough.
How much can I eat?
Forget it, Arun.
The don said he'll think about it.
Maqsood has bought both
Poonam International and Caesar's Palace.
And we...
...we are doing his big jobs
for loose change.
It hurts me to give him such a big share.
If you want to be around for long,
learn to be patient.
The higher you fly, the harder the fall.
And hurt your ass!
It's time you settle down. Get married.
You aren't earning a penny,
yet you're getting married.
I'm done. So long.
- Wait! Where are you going?
- See you.
Idiot!
Who was Hilda?
My friend.
Hilda was crazy about Arun.
But Arun loved Zubeida.
So Hilda settled for Rama instead.
"I am with the one who I love."
"I killed two birds with one stone."
"The sparrow in my neighborhood
started dancing to my tunes."
"She started dancing to my tunes."
"I have a new parrot here
and he is amazed by her."
Rama married the woman
his mother chose...
but celebrated his wedding night
with Hilda.
Why are you shouting?
Rama, let's go.
"She started dancing to my tunes."
Hey... What are you doing here?
- Rama...?
- No, no. Go down.
He's decorating the place for you.
Go back down... I'll call you.
They were like wild horses.
They had made a gang
but they weren't capable of managing it.
And one day Babu showed us
what a beast he was.
Babu, open the door.
Nothing will happen to you.
What can even happen?
Dammit!
Quiet!
Are you going to open the door
or must I call the police?
What is it?
Open the door now!
What's the matter?
Have you lost your mind?
Don't go inside.
- What? Call the police?
- Have you lost your mind?
You're drunk.
Don't make a scene!
- Stop! What are you doing?
- Don't touch me!
You're call the police?
You'll call the police?!
- Let go of me!
- My name is Babu!
- You think you can have me arrested?
- Let go of her!
Babu, let go of her!
It hurts.
It's chilled.
He can't hold his drink.
So...?
You called the cops!
You did the right thing.
What he didn't learn outside,
maybe he'll learn it in jail.
What was that?
Who is it?
They sent you to get me out of here?
Couldn't you have told me, you bastard?
You shot me! Damn you!
Anyone could've killed him.
I'll deal with you once I'm out of jail.
But he was killed
by his childhood friend.
Damn you!
And so Babu became history.
They went to the police station
with bombs and weapons...
...in order to kill him.
Who did that, Don?
You could blame a woman's curse for that.
A leaf falls in this city
and you know about it.
They don't want money, they want a share.
They need to know who did this.
Just think...
What person didn't turn up at his funeral?
Did Vijay do this?
Where is he?
Who did it? Where can we find him?
- Tell them one last time, Rafique.
- Yes.
If you want to be my equal,
learn to find information for yourself.
- Out of the way.
- Do you understand?
You don't earn a reputation
just by wearing high heels.
"The weather is romantic
and we should grab the opportunity."
Whether you like it or not...
...one day everyone ends up
working for the don.
You know that, sir, don't you?
But Gawli...
He was a whole different breed.
Dear audience,
we're taking you to the moon today.
Here's our rocket.
And from this rocket, a beautiful girl...
...will land on the moon with her lover...
...and dance to celebrate her love.
"Hey, darling, I want to dance with you."
Dance...
Dance of Love.
Dance on the moon.
"My life is full of dance...dance."
"Devotion is my dance...dance."
"My happiness lies in dance...dance."
"I lose my senses when I dance...dance."
"My body is for dance...dance."
"My love is only for dance...dance."
"My beloved is dance...dance."
"My love is for dance...dance."
And now, I'll take you to another world.
- Venus.
- Venus?
"Eight... Seven..."
"Six... Five..."
"Four... Three..."
"Two... One..."
"Venus! We are Venus..."
"Touch my body with your breath."
"Seal my lips with yours."
"When you peer into my eyes"
"I forget every other thing in the world."
"My life is full of dance...dance."
"My devotion is dance...dance."
"My body is for dance...dance."
"My love is only for dance...dance."
Darling, let's go to another world.
- Mars.
- Let's go.
He does that every day.
Here... Take this.
Tell Pappu that he is getting too greedy.
- Okay.
- I'll knock some sense into him.
- Get going now.
- Okay.
Goodbye, boss.
Hey, Vijay.
Where were you last Monday?
You black dog!
You guys consider yourself
gangsters, don't you?
Babu had become too arrogant.
But he started crying like a baby
when I shot him...
...the bloody pig!
If he were alive,
I would kill him the same way.
- F***ing bastard!
- Hit me... Hit me!
F***ing junkie.
Shoot him.
So you're going to shoot me, you coward?
I've seen you.
Damn you!
Rama, let's go!
Ask your men to leave. Do it!
Move back, or else I will kill him!
Move back!
Arun, let's go!
Who sent you?
Hey! Who sent you here?
Hey! Did Maqsood send you?
- Arun, let him go.
- You bastard!
Arun, let him go! Run!
It still hurts, doesn't it?
So why didn't you arrest
Arun for Vijay's murder?
Why did you declare that he
died in the police encounter?
I knew...
...that you wanted a promotion.
I didn't say a word either.
You can trust me.
They knew it wasn't going to be
easy to fight Maqsood without any support.
Only one man could
get them out of this mess.
Ashok Joshi.
It's so peaceful out here.
Hey, Gauri!
Did you inject the medicine into
Kaushalya? She has a fever.
Yes, I did.
So...why have you come here?
- Mr. Joshi, why don't you...
- Rama!
I've already told you...
...that I'm not coming back.
I'm not getting into that mess again.
I have weapons and I have shooters too.
They both are my trustworthy henchmen.
Sada.
He prefers local guns
to the automatic ones...
...because they never jam.
Newman.
He used to work for Maqsood.
Maqsood would give him all the big hits.
He knew all his secrets...
...so they chopped off his tongue.
You need to oil the weapons...
...not just look after the buffaloes.
Everyone forgets the past...
...and with each passing day,
Gawli is erasing all the evidence.
But I remember everything, sir...
...like yesterday.
I know the rest of the story.
Now do one thing...
Testify against Arun.
You will be safe.
I will see to it.
But... You will have
to stay with us for a while.
Police protection.
Have a look at this, sir.
Documents never lie.
Sir, there's a call for you.
Hello.
Sit.
If Arun learns of this meeting...
...he will never speak to me again.
And you know what will happen to you.
Stop this nonsense.
You dared to call me here...
...because an arrest warrant
for him will be issued next week.
You really hate him, don't you?
You two are old enemies.
The truth is, he is just like you.
Had he been born in your family,
he would have been a cop.
And if you had been born in Dagdi,
you would be a gangster.
How are you?
What are you doing here?
Making some tea. Would you like some?
Dad arranged a marriage for me.
The wedding was to take place yesterday...
...but I ran away.
What are you saying?
Why?
- What do you think the reason could be?
- What?
For you.
Will you marry me?
So, that's done.
No one in your family came.
I don't see anyone either.
Then, who's the witness to our marriage?
Huh?
There was a long line
for the sweets and garlands.
- I had to wait forever.
- There he is.
- He?
- Here you are.
I don't trust this man one bit.
Hey! You won't find another man like me.
I am the guest of honor today. Get it?
- Come on.
- Listen, your stay has been arranged.
What? Aren't we going to your house?
That will take some time.
Mom won't understand.
- Here, have some sweets.
- I had sweets last night.
- Come on...
- Have some. Don't be stubborn.
- Have some
- Let me feed you.
Here, this is for you.
Open it.
What is it?
Look after your own things
and life will be blissful.
Whose house is it?
It belongs to a friend.
- Enjoy. Be a man.
- Stop it!
Where's the owner of the house?
He won't return anytime soon.
He's behind bars... Careful!
You're scared of a rat!
Rama!
Greetings.
Arun, have a look at this.
- Who sent this?
- That...
Have you told anyone about our wedding?
No.
'Congratulations on your wedding
Don'
What's the matter?
Arun left Maqsood's company,
but Maqsood didn't leave Arun.
We never felt as if we were alone.
And Arun had picked up a bad habit.
Have you gone mad? Huh?
He killed Babu, tried to kill us,
and you want to negotiate with him!
You go be his slave if you want to.
Just don't drag me into it.
What? What did you say?
Don't talk nonsense.
What will you do without him?
Rama, we'll do what we are doing.
What are we doing? We're doing nothing!
Don't you want to be successful like him?
That's your problem. You ignore
whatever you don't want to hear.
I don't want to hear anything.
Just do as you're told.
I'II pick you up tomorrow.
Arun, tomorrow is Eid.
Don't go anywhere tomorrow.
Okay?
It's our first Eid together.
I have called family members here.
I know.
God is great.
Arun!
Arun?
That year on Eid, I realized
even gangsters have some cardinal rules.
One: On the festival, everybody meets
like friends to try to settle differences.
Two: Nobody touches family.
"On the day of Eid..."
"...even enemies greet each other."
"No matter how severe the enmity is..."
"...everyone forgets their differences
on the day of Eid."
"We wish you a happy Eid.
It's time to celebrate."
We wish everyone a happy Eid."
Hi, Arun.
Happy Eid.
- Happy Eid.
Give my regards to Zubeida.
"We wish you a happy Eid.
It's time to celebrate."
We wish everyone a happy Eid."
Now listen to me carefully...
There's nothing left
in extortion anymore.
All we get is loose change.
But we can earn a lot
with cocaine.
As you wish, Don.
You see, we're going to
open a college in Mira Road...
...for the Nigerians.
That will make it easier for us
to supply drugs. Hm?
The goods are mine
and I will see how to get it supplied.
You guys open up the docks
in your area.
You'll get a 25% share.
Parekh, did you
see the building plan?
Everything is on track, Don.
The work is going ahead full speed.
So tell me, Rama.
"Eid is the most
blissful day of the year."
Look, friendship does matter...
...but there must be only one leader.
"We wish you a happy Eid.
It's time to celebrate."
Done!
"This is the day to celebrate.
This is the night to celebrate."
"Everyone is meeting their friends."
My hands are dirty.
"We wish you a happy Eid.
We wish everyone a happy Eid."
It's time to celebrate."
"We wish you a happy Eid.
We wish everyone a happy Eid."
It's time to celebrate."
"We wish you a happy Eid.
We wish everyone a happy Eid."
It's time to celebrate."
"We wish you a happy Eid.
We wish everyone a happy Eid."
It's not about selling drugs.
There is nothing wrong or right
about one's work.
Maqsood...
I don't trust him one bit.
Arun, this line of work cannot be trusted.
I want a father for this child.
I want a home.
That's all I am asking for.
I will talk to Rama tomorrow.
I will tell him
I want to get out of this.
Is Rama home?
He's out getting a haircut.
- How are you?
- Mama...
Arun was certain
he didn't want to do this anymore.
He was sick of this.
And he knew where to find Rama
if he wasn't getting a haircut done.
Is Rama here? I want to talk to him.
He isn't here.
Come in.
Pray that Arun doesn't
end up the same way.
He was going to quit.
If you hadn't killed Rama that day...
...Arun wouldn't have become "Daddy".
Arun tried hard to get out of all this...
...but there was a storm approaching.
First it was Babu.
Then Rama.
Who's next?
It's you, Arun.
Which is the other one?
- It's there.
- Use them both.
- Gawli's popularity is increasing.
- Yes.
Elections are coming up,
but we don't have even one confession.
Witnesses are already terrified of Gawli.
None of the shooters are willing to speak.
Everyone says he's going to win this time.
What about him?
Hey...
Leave me... I said, leave me!
Hey! Don't touch me.
Why are you taking me there?
- Come on... You'll see...
- What?
-What are the charges against me?
-Come on!
- Under what charges have you arrested me?
- Come... I'll tell you everything.
The problem of
sexual harassment hasn't been solved.
So that isn't solved yet!
- Didn't we tell Joshi to handle this?
- Yes, Daddy.
- Tell him to fix this.
- Okay.
Brother, Vijaykar has arrested Pamphlet.
Listen... Get our lawyer there.
Sir, that's Pamphlet Bandya.
I arrested him at the brothel.
We found all these things in his bag.
What is this?
That's my hobby.
It's just like gambling.
Is collecting this your hobby too?
I have the same hobby.
Bra... B.R.A.
Babu Rama Arun.
Look...
if there's anything you
know about these three, tell us now.
What's written in it?
What are these codes?
We should know, shouldn't we?
Do you remember now?
- If you recall anything, then tell me.
- Speak!
Speak!
No, sir.
Arun would kill me.
Gawli is not what he seems.
Arun?
It's been a long time...
I suddenly thought of you.
Yes.
- Would you like anything?
- Water, please.
Right away.
Now you drink during the day, too.
What can I do?
There's not a single day...
...when I don't miss Rama.
You remind me of him.
Don't you miss me?
I know it.
I have seen the way you look at me.
You are lonely... Hm?
I remind you of Rama!
Why did you do it?
You tipped the police about Rama.
Gawli knew that Hilda
tipped the police about Rama.
He could have killed her, but he didn't.
This incident gained him respect
among everyone.
Hello.
Okay.
Brother, it's for you.
Yeah...
Arun.
What makes you call me today?
Avenge yourself on the policeman.
And if you stay quiet now,
people will forget about
your gang's existence.
I have an idea.
Call that cop to Dagdi.
Pump bullets into his chest
and have his body dragged out.
Rama was your friend after all.
Rama still dwells in my heart.
But everyone knows
that he was hanging out with you lately.
I have an idea.
Why don't you call that
cop to your area and do the same?
I'm more interested in
the guy who sent the cop to kill Rama.
This was a direct challenge.
And, he decided...
...to go back to Dagdi.
He knew that if he had to fight a war...
...he would need a fort.
- Pass it over.
- One Mouser.
One Mouser, one Magnum...
...two double barrels.
And that's just what he did.
I need this done...
- Pamphlet, have you seen Arun?
- No.
He must be at home.
- I...
- What's going on?
We're renovating.
Fix that quickly.
Arun doesn't trust anyone.
If he knows I'm here,
he won't spare me.
If he kills you,
we won't spare you either.
Sir, we found all this at his place.
I used to be his bookkeeper.
No. 21. Take it.
22... Get going.
This is boring, Brother.
When do I get to be part of the action?
You keep the accounts.
You, come here.
- What's your name?
- Prashant.
- Where are you from?
- Dharavi.
- Dagdi... Dagdi...
- What did I tell you?
It was a mistake... I made a mistake.
Go... Go from here.
Which area are you from?
Where are you from?
Sada, what are
people saying about me?
Brother, since we don't
get out of Dagdi...
...people wonder if our gang is scared.
We need to paralyze Maqsood.
Only then will they
take our gang seriously.
- Are you ready?
- Yes.
- Are the boys ready?
Pamphlet?
They are ready.
That's his family album.
Open it.
This is Manish Duggal, his film financer.
Kill him.
You've been blessed with a girl.
That's good.
Boys cause a lot of trouble.
Lord Shiva has been kind. Hm?
Yes, He has.
Her nose is not like yours.
Can I?
Come to me, baby.
Look at her, Sada. Eh?
Look at those eyes...
They've got power in them. She's got guts.
Don't you? Don't you?
Come on, play your card.
- Hey, give the gun to him.
- Who is it?
Hey! Drop the gun!
Hey!
Move! Move!
You've been cleaned up real good.
Go on.
Do you know why I slapped you?
Because there's no point in killing you.
Either the police will kill you
or Maqsood will.
Now go and tell him...
...that we're coming for him.
Greetings, Don. Sautya's here.
Remember, I told you about him.
Yes, I've heard that name.
He's a real loose cannon.
He'll do anything for you,
and he's even ready to go to jail.
Hey! Sit on the chair.
I'm talking to you.
Sit on the chair.
No, sir. I'm good down here.
What's the job?
This is for you.
- Who is he?
- Get going.
Boss, I guess this is for you.
"Congratulations Arun."
- What is it?
- Sweets.
Open it.
Isn't he your friend?
Yes, he is. But he's a real man.
That's Ashok Joshi's ring.
What are you saying?
What is that?
Get out! Out! Get out of my house now!
Arun, tell them to get out!
Get out! Are you deaf?
What's all this?
Who gave this to you?
They came to Dagdi for this?
Who's in charge of security?
What kind of father are you?
What about your daughter Geeta?
Will we live in fear our entire life?
Look after the child. You're scaring her.
Although Arun had taken over after Rama...
...he was a family man.
How was he to manage
the gang's affairs?
All of us were shitting bricks...
...because he had locked horns
with Maqsood.
Brother, Chinese marvel.
Don't be fooled by the size.
It's fully automatic, and...
- Brother, why don't you rest up?
- Come to me, baby.
Don't cry, baby.
We'll deal with him.
And it's not right for you to go there.
You shouldn't expose yourself.
We're here... We'll handle it.
- Do you have a shot, Sada?
- No.
Shoot him when you do.
- How are you?
- All good.
Go inside. I'll handle them.
Go inside, boss!
Boss, you go inside!
It's not the right time!
With that daring attempt
to kill Maqsood...
...the entire underworld
took notice of Arun.
Sir, a man wants to see you.
He says it's urgent.
- Where is he?
- He's sitting outside.
What's going on here?
Get out...now!
What does he want?
Nothing, I just want to talk.
I heard you're carrying out
a full investigation.
- I know Daddy better than anyone else.
- What do you mean?
I mean you can ask me anything
you want to know about Daddy.
I will tell you.
- I'm writing a book on Daddy.
- Okay.
I want to know what Daddy did
after attacking Maqsood.
I want to know that.
That's what people say.
But do you know what the truth is?
At that time, Daddy was with
all of us at Ratnagiri...
...for a picnic.
"Some call You Benevolent
and some call You Compassionate."
"Some call You the Generous Lord."
"Anyone who bows before You..."
"...fears no one, O Lord."
"Beat those drums really loud..."
"...for here comes Lord Ganesha."
"Bring that vermillion
to adorn my Lord."
"Everybody sing with me.
Hail, Lord Ganesha."
- Son of Lord Shambhu!
- Lord Ganesha!
- Who's the destroyer of troubles?
- Who rules everyone's heart?
- Lord Ganesha!
- Son of Lord Shambhu!
"There's great pomp and show everywhere."
"Everyone's dancing and swaying with joy."
"No one's standing idle, everyone's high."
"Such is the effect of Lord Ganesha."
"I can't live a year without You."
"In fact, we urge You to stay this year."
"Beat those drums really loud..."
"...for here comes Lord Ganesha."
"O Lord Ganesha, Benevolent One..."
"O Lord Ganesha... Glory to Lord Ganesha."
"You're our benefactor, our protector,
you're Almighty, O Lord Ganesha."
"The destroyer of evil...
Glory to Lord Ganesha."
Go home.
Arun.
Arun!
Hail, Lord Shambhu Narayan!
Maqsood killed Gawli's brother.
He broke the rules of the game.
He didn't consider the festival
or family.
But you knew which side
your bread was buttered on, right?
Everyone knows who tipped him off.
You did.
Is that because Maqsood is a cop's son?
Does that make him your family member?
Since we're digging up the past,
here's something else.
We have details about the
flight he caught to get out of India.
We also have the details of
who made his passport.
You remember everything, don't you?
Am I right?
It will take a couple of months.
Maybe we'll have a solution
in the next 6-7 months.
What are you trying to say?
Do you mean the don will have to stay
out of the country for seven months?
You're deciding where we will stay!
Mumbai doesn't belong to anyone except us!
Hm? What do you mean?
Are you giving me a tip
or is this free advice?
Not advice, sir.
The government's policies are changing.
Such cases are going
to be charged under the TADA...
...and it doesn't qualify for bail.
And then even I will be helpless.
I see... Now you're thinking
about government's policies.
Didn't this occur to you
when we filled your pockets?
"TADA will be implemented.
There will be this and that..."
That's bullshit!
You helped Maqsood escape...
...and you used TADA
as an excuse to enter Dagdi.
- Gaitonde, check the meter room.
- Check upstairs!
Hey! Don't move!
"...awaken our spiritual consciousness."
Arun...
"Om..."
Wait a minute, Inspector.
Praise Lord Shiva!
You took the credit for nabbing Arun...
...but the truth is
that Arun wanted to get arrested.
And that's because he knew
he was safest inside.
What is it?
It's for Gawli.
Brother...
Lunch for you.
Keep it here.
I don't want any complaints.
How are you?
Geeta.
She's grown up.
When are you coming home?
That will take some time.
What are you hiding from me, Arun?
Maqsood has sent his men in here.
They want to kill me.
Let's go... Time's up
Get me out of here.
It wasn't just a bad time in the city...
...but in the jail as well.
They separated Hindu prisoners
from Muslim prisoners...
...so that they wouldn't riot.
But Arun knew that
he had to keep Dagdi safe.
Remove this.
No rioting in Dagdi and Chinchpokli.
Our feud is not with any
religion or community!
Stay united.
Dagdi will protect the
Muslims, understand?
Pull it down.
Don't worry...
Stress affects your hair.
Times had changed,
but Daddy was still the same.
He always thought of his people.
Shake hands with me.
Hey...
Shake hands with me!
Brother...it's done.
These are the papers
to bail you out. Just sign here.
I won't sign this.
Why?
I don't want to come out now.
It's a trap.
They're waiting for me outside.
This is what they want.
If I come out, they'll kill me.
They can kill you in here as well.
Get me transferred from here.
Get me out of this place.
Make some arrangements for that.
For 10 years, Arun moved
from one jail to another.
She would get the transfer done.
She would follow his car each time...
...to make sure there were
no traps on the way.
Greetings.
Open up.
Come.
- Everything okay?
- Yes, sir.
Two people are here to see you.
- Uncle...
- Sachin.
- How are you?
- Great.
- Have some vadapav.
- See what the Chief Minister said!
What is this?
It says,
"Our answer to Maqsood is Gawli".
I've got vadapav for you.
It's in the Marathi newspaper, too.
"With our children, Arun Gawli
and the backing of the minister..."
The entire country has gone to dogs.
Now only you can run the country.
- Isn't it true, boys?
- Yes, you're right.
- Yes, he can...
- He can!
Brother, why don't
you run for Prime Minister?
Brother Arun!
Brother Arun! Greetings to you!
10 years is a long time
to spend within four walls.
I went to jail because, unlike others,
I am not a traitor.
I won't flee from my own country.
I was afraid...
...that my people wouldn't
recognize me when I come out.
But your love has made that fear flee,
just like my enemies.
I'll always be indebted to you...
to all of you...
for the love and respect
you gave me and my family.
From now on,
it will be my responsibility...
...to take care of your problems.
Hey...
You're such a grown up girl, Geeta,
aren't you?
- What's this?
- It's for you.
It's in English, so you read it for me.
"Welcome home, Daddy."
I see...
Daddy!
Daddy! Daddy!
Daddy! Daddy! Daddy!
And that's exactly how he got his name.
'Daddy.'
Now that you know everything...
...just tell me one thing.
Where is Pamphlet?
We're here for him.
You see, we want to apply for his bail.
- Yes, we even have the documents.
- Yes, we do.
He isn't here.
Do you have a weak memory?
Actually, old age is a cruel disease.
By the time you're close to retiring...
...you can't shoot straight,
your hands start trembling...
...and you end up appointing a nurse.
Damn you...
I will show you where you belong
once you get out of your house!
I will show you where you belong!
You're just an ordinary gangster.
I've dealt with cops like you before.
I had to lie for you.
I'll deal with him once he comes out.
Your friends are here to bail you out.
No, I won't go out.
Then sit there. Come!
Let him go!
It seems everything was
going well for Daddy.
...so what's his connection
with this guy?
My boss really respects you.
He said that I must get you
into our party at any cost.
Sachin told me...
...that you want police protection.
Right?
That will be taken care of.
Just run from our party.
But Daddy...
...this time you'll run from Chembur
and not Chinchpokli.
I hope you're okay with that.
Who are you?
Daddy, he's in the
Legislative Assembly, Mr. Mhatre.
I came to meet your boss.
Call him. We'll talk.
My boss isn't well.
He can't meet you today, understand?
We came all the way from Dagdi
to meet with you people.
When your boss feels better...
...tell him to come to Dagdi.
We'll talk there.
- This isn't done.
- Daddy...
That's how it works.
My boss will talk to you
when he feels better. He'll meet you.
Sachin, come here.
I want to show you something.
Sada, isn't that where
Khatau Mill was?
Remember how he came crying to us...
...asking us to have the place vacated?
Who gave the orders?
Your boss.
I see that now he has a big house there,
doesn't he?
- Daddy, please...
- I get it.
- These people still think I'm a gangster.
- No...
Yes, that's why they can make me a
candidate but they can't be seen with me.
Daddy, please...
You're mistaken.
At least listen to him once.
It will make our lives better.
Please, I worked really hard for this.
I too worked hard for them,
but what did I get?
They are not like us.
Daddy?
Praise Lord Shiva.
It's only a few more days.
Arun's going to win this election, sir.
I'll be dead for sure.
Start praying.
Pray to God that he doesn't win.
Here...
Yes, Sada.
There's a problem.
Pamphlet has turned hostile.
- Before the election...
- Listen, you won't do anything.
We are white-collars now.
Focus on winning the election.
Once we win, everything will
fall into place. Understood?
You said all the cases and charges
against me were dismissed.
What is this now?
Daddy, all the old cases are settled.
I swear.
If they've filed a new case,
I know nothing about it.
Come fast! Quickly!
- Move back!
-Hey... You coward!
Stop hiding behind women!
I guess I'll have to send a
lady constable to bring you out.
Move back!
What is it? What are you doing here?
I've come to take you back to jail.
Do you have a warrant?
I have pages of evidence
and confessions against you.
Right... Go make paper planes out of them.
Take your pansies and get out of here.
Who the hell did you call a pansy?
Don't ever enter Dagdi without a warrant.
By the way, I heard you are retiring.
Perhaps I could give you
a job as my bodyguard.
- Hey...!
- Beat it!
You want to kill me!
Look at him, he's here to kill me.
That's our police for you...
Encounter specialist.
"Come on, shoot me. Encounter specialist."
Did he discuss this
with any of his seniors? Hm?
"Encounter specialist. Come on, shoot me."
- "Beat it!"
- "Come on, shoot me!"
Sir, I didn't inform anyone...
...or receive anyone's permission.
He outplayed you again.
Just watch how Gawli gets
sympathy out of this.
I messed up, sir.
I should've shot him.
Don't talk shit, Vijaykar.
Don't act smart!
Do you want him to win the election?
There you go.
The Home Secretary is calling.
Talk to him.
Yes, sir.
The number of the bullet
and the name of the shooter...
You see, sir, Pamphlet has
used a different code each time.
And he keeps forgetting
what the codes mean.
I am not sure that this is
admissible in court.
I think we need to find another way.
If we follow the procedures,
we'll get nowhere.
Then what will we do, sir?
Pappu Borivali,
you recognize us, don't you?
You killed your girlfriend.
That's really bad.
You're definitely going to
rot behind bars for 15-20 years.
Do you see my senior there?
He can get you out in two years.
But no one's going to do it for free.
This is a map. Can you memorize it?
Hail Arun Gawli!
Good luck, Daddy.
Come.
Hail Arun Gawli!
Sada, you know what you
have to do, don't you?
Yes.
They've set up roadblocks ahead.
No one will do anything.
"Wait for my instructions."
"I can see them."
Hold on...
Send both men from the left side.
Damn...
"Polling Booth"
You better come back to me.
You go, Brother. I'll handle them.
Let's go.
Hello.
Idiot of a constable,
you're not answering my calls.
Do you know what this victory means?
"Hail, Arun Gawli!"
"Arun Gawli makes history
by winning the election."
"The entire area is
celebrating his victory!"
"And Arun is thanking the people."
"It feels like a miracle..."
"...that Arun Gulab Gawli is
now a member of Parliament!"
- "Keep striving Arun Gawli."
- "We're with you all the way!"
Our dreams have finally come true, Arun.
We won.
What kind of victory is this?
Everyone's left us.
No... Don't say that.
"He has a long way to go..."
The people are with you, Arun.
"He won with the most number of votes..."
"...and it feels like it's just
the beginning of his political career."
On behalf of Mumbai Police...
we ask...
...that Arun Gulab Gawli, aka Daddy...
...not be given police protection.
In order to eradicate
the Mumbai Underworld...
...15 inspectors and 60 cops
have sacrificed their lives.
The Mumbai Police has filed
120 cases against Arun Gawli.
Murder, attempt to murder,
extortions, conspiracy...
If Arun Gawli is given
police protection...
...then it will be an insult
to all the martyred officers.
That's correct!
Silence... Silence, please.
Honorable Speaker...
...in the past, a lot happened
between the police and me.
I paid a very big price for my past...
...by spending more than
half my life in jail.
If the people can forgive me, then
why is it so difficult for all of you?
The people have not forgotten.
You still have the image of a gangster.
The image can be changed
if you let me work.
And for that, I have to
go among the people.
Because of my past, I have enemies.
If the police won't protect me...I'll have
to arrange for security and carry weapons.
And then people will call me
a gangster once again.
Hey, Gawli!
You said you'll carry weapons!
And you want us to
believe you have changed!
If I haven't, it's because
you won't let me. That cop...
...arrests my men without any charges.
He waits outside my home
to kill me in an encounter.
I have changed
but none of you accept that.
Ladies and gentlemen, we won't
tolerate the humiliation of democracy.
This joke on democracy...
...won't be tolerated!
It won't be tolerated!
Your Honor,
Arun's motive was clear.
The reason behind killing MLA Mhatre...
...was Arun Gawli's public humiliation.
They were enemies.
We have both records and
witnesses to support it.
And through our investigation,
we learned...
...that the orders to kill Mhatre
came directly from Arun.
In defense against these charges...
...do you have anything to say?
I am innocent.
Do you know this woman?
My friend knew her.
Confess everything, Arun.
You will feel unburdened.
You're getting another
opportunity, just like me.
I strongly object, Your Honor.
We have enough evidence
to prove Rani's character.
The Police had already
set their sights on Arun.
But it seems they are trying to prove...
...that this hooker's network
is stronger than that of the police.
Point taken.
Your Honor, this man here
kept all the records...
...Gawli's guns, pistols
and other ammunition.
Do you know him, or is it
your friend who knew him?
I know him.
This is a country-made pistol...
...that was used to kill MLA Mhatre.
Does this gun belong to Gawli?
Yes. This is Gawli's gun.
Is this your gun?
I am a gangster, Your Honor.
I use automatic weapons.
Why would I use a country-made pistol?
For 40 years, Gawli has been accused of
many crimes but acquitted at every trial.
This is the biggest case
of the millennium.
They changed the judge again.
According to our sources,
Gawli gave 3000000 rupees...
...to kill Mhatre.
Yes, I gave him the contract.
I don't know this man.
Do you know why you've
been called to the court?
Yes.
Did he fire at Mhatre?
- Yes, sir.
- Are you sure?
Yes, it was him.
- Have you met Arun Gawli?
- Yes, I have.
I strongly object, Your Honor.
Objection overruled.
Have you worked for him?
Yes, I have.
Tell me where he is.
That's him, sitting there.
Do you have anything
to say in your defense?
Five judges changed
and we already have a judgment.
I've never seen any
case wrapped up so quickly.
The police and I never got along,
so they brought fake witnesses.
They claim I accepted the
contract to kill Mhatre.
Why would I kill Mhatre?
I gave my two seats to his party so
they could form a majority.
I served punishment for the
mistakes that I have made.
But now I want to do something good.
I have faith in your system
and that you...
...will make the right decision.
Yes, I will...
Arun Gawli, I should give you death.
But I give you life.
Let's go...
- Sir, one photo...
- Please!
Move back... Move back...
Daddy, I've been following
your story from the beginning.
There have been many ups and downs.
One last question.
What next?
What do I say?
They shut down the mills...
The value of man dropped while the
value of land increased.
Who built skyscrapers on the land...
...that we helped them vacate?
Who lives there now?
Leaders, businessmen...
From those heights
they look down upon me and say...
That's the gangster.