"Tutak tutak"
Welcome to the Truedeal family,
Miss Gurpreet.
Thank you, sir.
- Here you go.
This is your seat.
All the best.
If you have any doubt
or need anything,
you can always come to me.
Don't worry.
Are you single?
Yes, sir.
Excuse me.
Are you single?
Excuse me?
I am single.
Name, Krishna.
Krishna has started his antics!
Really?
- Age, 34 years, 2 months, 27 days.
From Muthampatti,
Coimbatore district.
Father, Panchayat Board President.
Mother...
Please refer to previous question.
She's in my heart.
Okay. - Reached Mumbai,
June 7th, 2013, by Mumbai Express.
Joined this company on June 10th.
Designation despatch officer.
Proposed to 27 girls,
got rejected 30 times.
30 times?
2 girls...
Three times.
Basic salary, 30,000. House
allowance, DA, altogether, 57,000.
I've been a bachelor from birth.
Girl preferably...
Modern...
Very modern...
Ultra modern.
You are perfectly fit for that.
Very lucky you are.
It's impressive.
- I know.
But sorry.
You are late.
I have a boyfriend.
Shyam.
Your form?
If you break up
it will come in handy.
What's the plan?
- Nothing.
We will plan something.
You see a modern girl, you'll apply
for her boyfriend's post!
She has joined only today.
Many come from villages
with zillion dreams.
His dream is to
marry a modern girl.
She seems to be committed
since she was in 7th grade.
You should've prepared to woo her
when you were in kindergarten.
So what if I don't have her now.
She breaks up and I'll be there.
Why do you want a modern girl?
She'll speak English
without grammar mistakes.
Our kids will also speak English
Simple.
- You know what.
You should marry a village belle.
- Me!
Marry a village belle!
A lion doesn't eat grass,
even if it's starving.
A lion.
The best modern girl of Mumbai
will be my wife,
or I will die a bachelor.
- Challenge?
Chall...
- Just shut up!
I hate you.
Don't you ever
show me your face again.
Don't you even dare.
I like it.
Excuse me.
It's me.
"Dance."
"Mesmerising...
Dressed in a short skirt, yeah."
"Your shoes click on the floor
when you catwalk, the cars go by."
"Let me get a taste of your love."
"Let's get lovey-dovey.
Why be afraid?"
"What a figure!
Bend it like Beckham, baby!"
"Dance."
"I am Krishna, I work my magic
and the love bugle plays."
"You will be my queen."
"Flowers bloom all around,
it rains in the desert."
"Say yes and make my day."
"You've stayed single long enough,
you should mingle now."
"Let's get lovey-dovey.
Why be afraid?"
"What a figure!
Bend it like Beckham, baby!"
"Dance."
"Mesmerising...
Dressed in a short skirt, yeah."
Hey, go. Boys, please.
Thank you.
You made me realise
what true love is.
He didn't come to pick me up,
so I broke up with him.
Who?
Him.
Thank you.
Hey, get lost!
- Huh?
Go now!
"Dance."
I came to the station to get you.
See how much I love you.
That was bad.
Are you okay?
It's okay. 32.
Let's have a drink.
Just look at them!
Get up! You...
Krishna!
- What?
Why is your phone switched off?
Your father's been calling me.
Why?
- Your grandma is very ill.
You have to go to the village.
Hey! Move!
Cows, please, please move.
Move!
Hey!
Hello.
Keep the cows off the road.
The road is meant for cars.
Stupid village people.
Right. Aren't you
from this village too?
Hey.
HI, uncle!
[OTHER LANGUAGE]
Dad.
The pulse rate is dropping.
[OTHER LANGUAGE]
Sorry.
She's alive.
- Sorry, friend!
- She's alive!
- So sorry, friend!
[A woman in the crowd]
[OTHER LANGUAGE]
'Grandma is on her deathbed'
'and they are talking
about my marriage.'
'Oh God!
He's thinking about it now.'
You have to be married in 48 hours.
Has your dad
ordered a bride on Flipkart?
Do you think I will do it?
So, you're going to
go against your dad? - Yes.
Won't you be afraid?
Why should I be afraid?
I'll tell him...
My marriage, my decision.
[OTHER LANGUAGE]
Okay.
So, is the wedding cancelled?
Confirmed.
[OTHER LANGUAGE]
They should ask for your reaction,
not someone who cannot respond.
[OTHER LANGUAGE]
Does your grandma love you?
She does.
[OTHER LANGUAGE]
Luck favours you.
Who is she?
- The cow herder.
Oh, the cow girl.
She'll die tomorrow.
Krishna, come here.
- What?
You're in trouble.
I'm wondering how cow girl
will wake you up every morning.
Hey, Krishna...
My dream has come to nought.
I don't like her at all.
What will you do about that?
Think of something.
What if she rejects you?
Forty-three.
Ninety...
You want to marry me.
Do you know Hindi?
If you want to live in Mumbai,
you have to know Hindi.
Do you know Hindi?
Yes, I know Hindi.
My mother is from Uttar Pradesh.
My father hails from this village.
I speak Hindi better than Tamil.
What a twist!
You don't know him.
You should see how he parties.
Whiskey...
Cigarettes...
Ladies...
If you still want to marry him...
It's up to you.
Punchline.
I am worried for you.
You can still refuse to marry him.
Oh no! Her mother!
This man is a drunkard.
He wanted to hit our cows.
You told us that
when you refused to marry him.
But he cares about you.
You won't find
a better life partner.
Alcohol damages the liver...
But he is good at heart.
I had told you.
She's a nice girl.
I will offer a coconut
at the temple.
Hey! Nuisance!
She had rejected me, but your
stupid idea spoiled everything.
Look, the wedding
can't be cancelled,
but can be postponed.
- How?
If a member of
a close-knit family dies,
no weddings are held for a year.
Yours is a close-knit family,
right? - Who will die?
Your grandmother.
She doesn't seem to want to die.
She will die.
Hey!
God!
[OTHER LANGUAGE]
You're so lucky, sir.
Her pulse rate is normal now.
- Really!
[OTHER LANGUAGE]
'So, Krishna...'
'What about you?'
'Nothing can stop
this wedding now.'
Mom.
- Take care.
Take care of yourself.
Goodbye.
Mind-blowing luck, my friend.
There's no escaping this now.
This is what I get
for being a friend.
Bananas.
Come on.
Amusing!
That's the India I'm looking for.
Can you pose?
- What? Excuse me.
What is happening here?
- Sorry.
Same t-shirt.
Alright. I should...
- Hey!
What do I do with her?
Take her home.
I told my friends I'd marry
a modern girl. I'll get rid of her.
What! Where will the poor...
- I am the poor one.
What should we do?
Find another house to rent.
Take them.
Returning from your village?
She's from a village.
I'm from Germany.
Yeah, right.
I'm going to your house.
Find a house soon.
Come on.
Walk ten steps behind me.
Why?
That's how
husbands and wives walk in Mumbai.
[Background music]
Wait.
Hello?
- I found a great flat.
Rs 15000 per month. In Matunga.
Fully furnished.
Should I finalise the deal?
Okay.
Message the address.
Advance?
You pay.
- You...
Excuse me.
Where is Green Gift building?
That one there.
Go there.
Which flat?
- 205.
205!
Sir, the new tenants.
They are a married couple.
- Hello.
1st floor, 205.
He has told you
about the house, right?
Yes, I told them.
Okay, sir.
- Okay.
No lift?
Sir, please give me the key.
Sir, this is the flat.
Excuse me.
What is this?
You took the rent in advance.
You should've cleaned it at least.
You got such a huge flat
for that amount.
Be happy, sir.
Here.
- Thank you, sir.
Okay.
I'll get some food. Stay here.
It's our house. Come in.
- What!
Of course, you are here.
Who cleaned the house?
I did.
On your own?
- Yes.
Can't believe it.
Don't you require help?
There's no need. I'll manage.
The food is ready. Eat it.
You cooked food?
I cooked with
what I brought from the village.
You didn't make pudding?
What food is this!
Not fit for humans.
I won't eat.
- Yes.
South Indian food in Mumbai!
'Sambar, 'rasam', curd rice.
Oh, come on!
If you have to, cook...
Cook continental food,
Chinese food, butter chicken...
Cook good food.
How do you put up with this?
- Wait!
Go back to the village
and learn how to cook those dishes.
Take your time. Go.
Manchurian!
'Roti'.
Why didn't you bring this earlier?
Did you want to eat it alone?
We won't eat...
Mind-blowing! Try it!
Which flat?
Hi.
205.
Bachelor.
Krishna.
I'm single now.
Krishna!
Grandma!
What happened? Krishna!
Krishna! Get up!
Grandma!
- Help him up.
What's wrong? Get up. Krishna.
Grandma!
What?
Too late.
Are these fresh?
- Yes.
Are you new to the area?
Which flat?
- 205.
I live with my husband.
- Madagascar.
No manners.
How much for the cabbage?
Hello!
Yeah, Krishna here.
Gurpreet. Take an extra pass.
Hey, take your passes.
Thank you.
- Krishna, your passes.
I don't want them.
- Have you lost it?
Our company
is sponsoring film awards.
We will get to see the film stars
up close and personal.
There'll be an after party too.
Models, actresses...
They speak in English,
without grammar mistakes.
Once you get on the dance floor,
you're sure to impress
one at least. - No.
I'm not in the mood.
Don't worry.
You'll find a modern girl.
You didn't just shift
out of the house, you've changed.
You're coming to the show.
Superstar Raj Khanna will be there.
People are crazy about him.
Did you hear his new song?
Great music! Great song too!
"Pop some champagne. Go crazy."
"Forget everything tonight."
"Dance the bhangra.
Go to a disco."
"Set the floor on fire."
"Your eyes are mesmerising."
"You're the one
who stole my heart."
"My beloved, my darling."
"Give me a chance."
"Come to me, my darling."
"Let us romance."
"I love the way you dance."
"Dance, dance, dance, dance."
"Dance, dance, dance, dance.
Dance, dance."
"I love the way you dance.
"Dance, dance, dance, dance.
"Dance, dance, dance, dance."
Dance, dance."
"I will flex my muscles"
"and beat up those who look at you.
My six-pack abs I will gift wrap"
"and gift them to you
on Valentine's Day."
"You'll never see one like me,
all over the world."
"I am a Punjabi..."
"Straight away from Moga."
"Chin, chin, chin,
listen to me, ma'am."
why do you torture me?"
"Chin, chin, chin,
O, shake your bum."
"Have mercy on the men
that love you."
"Dance, dance, dance, dance."
"Dance, dance, dance, dance.
I love the way you dance."
"Dance, dance, dance, dance."
Coffee.
What is this?
My company is sponsoring an
awards' show. Passes to the show.
May I go with you?
It was the first time
you asked for something,
that is why I agreed.
Listen carefully.
At the venue, we won't be together.
We'll sit separately.
After the function,
you'll go to the ladies toilet,
I'll go to the gents toilet.
After everyone leaves,
we'll go home. Okay?
Not one question.
This is good.
That was later.
He had chicken-pox at this age.
Here.
Such a cartoon!
Krishna.
You said you wouldn't be here.
Moving on to the next category...
Nominations for Best Director
for Truedeal Awards 2016 are...
'What...'
'Where is she sitting?'
Thank you.
I didn't make this film alone.
Raj supported me a lot.
He's like my brother.
Thank you, Raj.
What an award...
Place where hard work...
The girl sitting next to you
is gorgeous.
Seems like a village girl
and is here alone.
'Best Film of the year...'
- Exchange seats with me.
You're not interested, let me...
- Hey!
Just because she's alone,
you'll behave like this?
Stop it. Respect women.
It could be your friend's wife.
Could we have on stage,
the chairman of Truedeal...
He's not interested,
he won't let us enjoy either.
And the Best Actor goes to...
Raj Khanna...
For Revolver Raja 002.
Everyone has dreams.
But dreams come true for those
who work to realise their dreams.
I was one in a crowd,
then one in thousands...
And today...
I am one in a million.
Super, sir.
- So, go for your dreams...
No matter what.
In life,
play your role with dedication.
Even after the curtain falls,
the applause will continue.
Come on.
Raj Khanna...
I've seen all his movies.
I'm a huge fan.
What are you doing here?
- Just hanging out.
Let's go to the party.
I'm tired. I'll go home.
Are you crazy? You're refusing to
go for the party?
Don't insist!
I told you I'm tired.
What's with him?
- Yes.
'Where is she going?'
'To the after-party!'
You took that seriously, right?
- Yes.
Just for gags. Come on.
- You're too much.
Lift!
Oh gosh!
My wife!
"Hey ya."
"Dance like this..."
"Like Sridevi."
"I'm in Bollywood.
My story is unique."
"My youth entices one and all."
"Shake it."
"Baby."
"Dance like this."
"Sing like this."
Who is she?
Don't know, sir.
"Yeah."
"Money, money, money, money."
"I am popular everywhere I go."
"My beauty is magical."
"I am like a shining star."
"Stay around and clap your hands."
"Dance like this."
"Sing like this."
"Check it out, yo."
"Rhythm on the bass, man."
"Jump it up."
"Dance like this..."
"Like Sridevi."
"Dance like this."
"Sing like this."
What... Oh no...
What?
What did you do to me?
What! You're asking me!
My sari is torn.
I thought you were a decent man.
You... Your sari... You think I...
Then what?
Where did you take me?
What did you give me?
I have a headache.
Forget that.
Come on.
No.
I'll bathe first,
and recite a holy verse ten times.
Only then will I start the day.
Hey! Right.
Ramu, call ma'am here.
Ramu!
- Excuse me.
Who is the ma'am?
I am Mr Raj Khanna's manager.
Sir has sent me here.
Call ma'am here.
There's no ma'am here. Please go.
Hey, ma'am...
Ma'am.
The industry is talking about ma'am
and you...
Call her here.
- Wrong address.
There's just a 'sir' here,
no 'ma'am'.
Okay? Please.
Last night, ma'am took a taxi
from the hotel and came here.
I had a hard time convincing the
taxi driver to give me the address,
and you say she isn't here.
Call her out.
I told you she's not here.
If she's here, where is she?
I am here.
Ma'am.
I am fortunate indeed.
What a performance it was!
What a smile!
You dance so well, so graceful.
I have two groups for you,
on WhatsApp.
'Future Sridevi',
'Future Madhuri Dixit'.
Everyone in the industry
wants to sign you for a film,
but who got here first?
Dilip Kukreja, star secretary.
- Excuse me.
Stop this nonsense!
Come out.
- Shut up! Get lost!
Who is this mad man? We're talking
and he's interrupting us.
He is...
- Hey, mister!
My manager.
What!
Manager! - Manager!
You appointed one already!
Superb, ma'am. Very good, ma'am.
I...
- Hey, Get up.
Get up, I say.
Can't you show some respect?
Mad fellow.
Ma'am, Mr Khanna has decided,
in fact he insists
that you will be the lead actress
in his next film.
Actress!
Yes.
- Leave!
Sir has said
that if you refuse to do the film,
he won't act in it.
Please, ma'am.
Okay, ma'am?
I'll think about it.
Super, ma'am. That is enough.
I'll call Mr Khanna and tell him.
Hello, sir. Ma'am has agreed.
We'll have her sign on Friday
and start shooting immediately.
You speak to her.
Hold on.
Ma'am, Mr Raj Khanna.
Hello?
- Hi.
I saw you at
the award function last night.
It was proved
that stars
are meant to shine bright,
and are visible to the world.
Welcome to the world of dreams.
You're lucky.
- You too.
See you on the sets.
Thank you, ma'am.
What is your problem?
You're sitting on a gold mine
and are behaving stupid.
Listen carefully.
I will take care of ma'am's dates,
agreements and finances.
You just act like her manager.
I will give you
5% of the earnings as commission.
Commission?
You'll give it to me! Hey...
What?
You want a share in the profits?
I'll send a car here on Friday.
Bring ma'am to the location.
I'll manage the rest.
The producer, Sharma...
He'll find the address and
come here to sign ma'am for a film.
What!
- If he comes here...
Like you told me, no one lives
here, bachelors share this house.
Tell him that with confidence.
He's foolish. He'll believe you.
The car will be here
at 10 on Friday.
Who were you talking to?
What?
You haven't had a bath yet?
Have a bath
and recite the holy verse 5 times.
Alright?
Hey!
What do you think?
Are you fooling me?
You dance.
You wear skimpy clothes.
You speak in English.
You change every minute.
Why are you doing this?
What is the plan?
Are you an undercover cop?
Say something.
I understand.
- What do you understand?
You don't like me.
She is...
'Don't walk close to me.
Don't sit with me.'
I thought things would change.
You want to throw me out of the
house by accusing me of all this.
Hey! Me!
Don't take the trouble. I'll go.
You be happy.
Excuse me.
Why are you calling your father?
Not my father,
I'm calling your father.
What did I say to you?
This is normal in a family.
Cook food.
Go.
Cook some food.
What?
You don't want me
to go to the village?
No.
Not now.
Hello, sir.
When I asked you the address,
seemed like you wanted to say
something about Flat 205.
Sir, you rented the house
without inquiring about it.
What?
A girl named Ruby lived there.
She was a model.
She wanted to be an actress.
It's not easy.
She was a nice girl.
She stayed aloof.
She suffered from depression,
I think.
She committed suicide.
The police was here.
A case was registered.
The house was locked
till you rented it.
What did you hear?
Ghost stories.
Why?
Those are just stories.
There are no ghosts.
Tinkling of anklets...
A touch...
It's not true.
You are educated.
Don't believe all this.
Devi!
What are you doing there?
Watch the TV in the house.
Devi.
I'm talking to you.
De...
Ruby.
What happened?
A dream.
Don't you have to go to office?
Get ready. I'll bring coffee.
Ruby.
Ru...
Our Father in heaven.
Holy is Your name.
Who is Ruby?
A colleague is getting married.
Should I give him gold or a ruby?
Let's go.
Where?
- Picnic.
A Mumbai tour.
Why?
Surprise.
Yes.
- For how many days?
4-5 days.
Pack everything.
So many things for 4-5 days?
Will you get ready now?
You won't understand.
Please.
Are you here?
Yes, that's the address.
I'm coming.
Are you ready?
The boot...
- I'll keep it.
Devi!
The bags are back on the cupboard.
What's wrong?
You didn't go to work?
You changed?
You were getting ready,
weren't you?
Why? Where are we going?
For a holiday.
Oh! For how many days?
Huh!
Many days.
Should I pack everything?
Yes.
Please...
And...
That one too.
Hurry up.
The luggage...
- Let's go.
Careful.
Stay here. I'll be back.
Did anyone
take the luggage upstairs?
No, sir.
What happened?
You didn't go to work?
Listen...
No, no.
Sir...
Ma'am...
Sir, I... Ghost...
Sir.
Sir!
Sir, please.
Sir! Sir!
Sir!
'In my house...'
How...
Are you ready?
Coffee.
Take it.
What is this?
He's the one.
My wife.
Who are they?
They are here
to conduct a prayer ritual.
These people perform
prayer rituals!
If we'd told father,
he would've sent a priest.
There was no time. Get coffee.
- Cof...
Sir...
Has the ghost left?
Huh?
It has gone.
It won't come back, will it?
Test.
What?
Ruby.
Why are you calling the ghost back?
Sorry.
"Dance, dance, dance, dance.
I love the way you dance."
"Dance, dance, dance, dance."
"I love the way you dance."
Help!
This is my house.
You came here without
my permission,
but you cannot leave now.
What do you want?
Why have you possessed Devi?
I was a struggling actress.
After years of struggle,
I got a chance
to act with Raj Khanna.
It would've been
the debut film for both of us.
But I was thrown out of the film.
If I had acted in that film,
I too, would've been
a star like Raj Khanna.
Anger, frustration, depression.
One wrong decision...
All my dreams were shattered.
God has given me an opportunity,
through Devi,
to show the world who Ruby is.
No one can stop me
from acting in the film.
If anyone tries to,
I will ruin that person's life.
Devi!
Movie!
I won't accept that.
I didn't ask for your permission,
I stated my decision.
I won't disturb Devi in the house.
You cannot disturb Ruby
outside the house.
Tomorrow at 10 am, Raj Khanna
will send a car to pick me up.
It's your responsibility
to take Devi out of the house.
Me!
You're my manager, after all.
What's wrong?
You haven't slept yet?
Want something to eat?
What?
Who are you now?
What are you saying?
It's late.
Go to sleep.
What's wrong?
You are pacing about.
Don't you have to go to office?
- No, ma'am.
I have cooked only for myself.
If I knew...
- Krishna!
It's 10!
Will you take Devi out or should I?
I can make okra, but you don't like
it, so I can cook something else.
Nothing.
- What?
Where?
- Picnic.
You always say we'll go,
but we never go.
Let me take my clothes.
Wait. Listen.
"Get a reason to live."
"Make life colourful."
"Soar high in the sky."
"Enjoy every moment."
"Don't stop."
"Live life to the fullest."
She's not an actress.
She's my wife.
She's possessed by a spirit.
Listen...
She's not an actress.
She's my wife.
She's possessed by a spirit.
- Please drive faster.
Yes, ma'am!
'He can't hear me.'
'She must've done something.'
"Colour, beauty..."
"This world is beautiful."
"I want to rule the world."
"There's beauty all around."
"Let me admire the beauty."
- Welcome.
"Get a reason to live."
"Make life colourful."
So, ladies and gentlemen...
Here is the lead actress
of Revolver Raja 3, Ruby Singh.
We should've signed her
for our film.
We missed it.
Wow!
She's gorgeous.
- Who?
The actress.
She's the next superstar.
She's not an actress.
She's my wife.
She's possessed by a spirit.
You can't hear me, can you?
Not Hema Malini, Sridevi.
Lights!
First shot!
All in.
It's Lady Luck.
A beautiful woman wins hearts.
An intelligent
woman wins accolades.
A woman who has
beauty and brains...
Wins the world.
Cut it!
Superb, sir! Superb!
You're a star.
I know.
Born star.
Reborn star.
Sir...
What a pair!
Super hit. Mind-blowing.
I already have the feeling that
the film will be a super duper hit.
Hail Goddess!
- Dilip.
Yes?
The film industry
is a dazzling world.
Yes, sir.
The lights you see here...
There's darkness behind them.
The journey from the darkness
into the light
is a short journey.
But often this short journey
takes years to complete.
It took me 14 years.
Many a time,
it may take a lifetime.
What a profound thought!
A lifetime.
You're right, sir.
I have always rejected offers
to act in romantic films.
But...
For the first time,
I didn't want the scene to end.
I know what you mean.
Hail Goddess!
You're a rockstar, sir.
I'll be back.
Krishna!
It's done, right?
Where's ma'am?
We have to go.
- Krishna, wait.
It's not done.
The good times
have just begun.
- What?
I will get film offers. Ma'am
will sign them and you'll enjoy.
Sign! - Mr Khanna wants ma'am
to sign a three-film contract.
Three! You had said one film.
I won't accept
the three-film offer.
Sorry, sir.
I feel very sorry for you.
Who are you to refuse?
Are you her husband?
Mr Khanna has spoken to Ms Singh.
Take the contract and get it back
tomorrow after she has signed it.
Go!
Contract!
- Go!
Stupid man!
She agreed to a contract!
Taxi!
2 minutes.
Come on.
- But...
Fast.
Go.
Hey!
Hello, Miss Ruby Singh.
How dare...
The manager said you agreed
to a three-film contract.
Don't sign this contract...
The key...
What contract?
Nothing.
My manager asked me
to sign a two-year contract.
I don't know if I should.
Where did we go?
To the park, the beach...
We did?
I don't remember anything.
Where we went, what we did...
How can I not remember anything?
I told you...
I don't understand.
I want ghosts.
- What?
I want food.
Didn't you eat anything?
No. Please cook some food.
Give me 10 minutes.
I'll cook something.
Sign it.
What is it?
Contract.
'I, Ruby the ghost,'
'will not possess Devi's body
after this film.'
What the hell!
'I won't possess Devi's body ever
again, whatever the circumstances.'
What kind of a contract is this!
My contract.
Point number three.
'I, Ruby the ghost, accept that'
'I won't do any intimate scenes
with Raj Khanna'
'or rape scenes with the villain.'
Strictly no.
Point number 4...
No smoking. No drinking.
Point number 5...
'I won't use any super powers.'
And...
What?
- Especially,
on the gentleman Krishna.
Swear by God and sign it,
Ruby, the ghost.
Have you gone mad?
- A little.
An actress has to do all that.
You are an actress,
but the body is Devi's.
You ant a ghost to sign a contract?
The ghost wants to act, right?
I won't sign it.
I won't accept.
Hey!
Are you not afraid anymore?
Do you and Devi
want to live peacefully or not?
This is the last day then.
Devi won't leave the house
from tomorrow.
You said you wouldn't possess
Devi in the house.
If you want Devi
to leave the house,
you have to sign the contract.
Sign it.
I am.
Lazy ghost.
There's a problem.
Ruby refuses to sign
the three-film contract.
Good.
Yes, sir.
Even I thought that face...
And three films...
I thought you were...
Tell the director
to wrap up the film quickly.
Yes, sir. We'll send her packing.
Ruby won't act in films
after marriage.
What?
Super decision.
Super pairing, sir.
Both of you
will look great together.
Congratulations, sir.
I'm so happy.
Rockstar.
Ready.
1 2 3 4
Wow!
- Hey!
Excuse me.
Hello, Baby Rajinikanth.
Who are you?
- Heroine's manager.
You're the manager,
not the heroine, right?
What are you doing here?
You know what this is.
Dance is a form of worship.
Dancing is an art.
Do you know the ABCD of dance?
Do you know how to dance?
Get out of here.
"It's bad."
"It's dangerous."
Michael Jackson's ghost!
Here's another ghost.
This is an indoor shoot.
Close the umbrella.
Rehearsals?
No rehearsals.
Let's take.
Steps?
Hit step, Farah.
This one again?
Evergreen, Farah, evergreen.
He knows just this step.
Energy, guys, energy.
- Mind-blowing.
Ready? Taking!
Are there children in the film?
No.
Why are there
children's clothes here?
These are the heroine's clothes.
- Heroine... Look...
Are you kidding me?
What is all this?
She should be covered
from top to bottom.
Be careful, I say.
Yes.
There is no top or bottom.
Ma'am asked you
to stay out of here.
Go.
Darn it!
Rehearsals!
Look, look.
Don't look.
Why?
How dare you object!
She looks se... In a modern dress.
She looks beautiful.
She is a beauty queen.
Lucky is the man who will
marry her, but it's pointless.
He won't allow her
to dress like this.
Beauty should be appreciated.
"One by one."
He won't understand.
Action!
"Tutak tutak."
"The dancing won't stop,
it will continue from 9 to 4."
"Increase the volume,
let's rock the floor."
"The dancing won't stop,
it will continue from 9 to 4."
"Increase the volume,
let's rock the floor."
"Tutak tutak tutiya, let's dance."
"Let's celebrate. Let's dance."
"Let's talk. Let's dance."
"Tutak tutak tutiya."
"Baby likes to use Instagram."
"Going to the gym
has made me lean."
"Baby uses beauty cream."
"I am a selfie queen."
"Tutak tutak tutiya."
"We go to the club every night."
"We catch butterflies online."
"We're single, ready to mingle.
Look into my eyes."
"Tutak tutak tutak tutiya"
"Let's celebrate. Let's dance."
"Let's talk. Let's dance."
"Tutak tutak tutiya."
"Your hair is black,
the hair ornament is red."
"You are a beauty queen."
"You are a beauty queen.
You should be careful."
"Your hair is black. It's black."
"Let's dance."
"Listen. O mister,"
"you find anyone better than me."
"Tutak tutak tutiya."
"Let's celebrate. Let's dance."
"Let's talk. Let's dance."
"Tutak tutak tutiya."
"Baby like to use Instagram."
"Going to the gym
has made her lean."
"Baby uses beauty cream."
"She's called the selfie queen."
"Tutak tutak tutiya."
"Tutak."
- Get out!
Get out of here.
Pack up.
Pack up. Out.
Krishna.
Mr Khanna wants to
meet you in his office.
And he expects me to go.
No way!
Hey, Krishna. Come.
Come here.
Sit.
Yes, sir.
Come here.
Sit.
I want to tell you something.
What?
Raj Khanna, action star.
All that is okay, but...
Love, girl...
- Not right, sir.
I am human too.
- Really?
Superstar.
I've had this problem
since I was in school.
Any girl I liked,
I would write a letter to her,
but never
mustered the courage to give it.
I wrote a letter to Ruby but...
I couldn't give it to her.
You'll give ma'am a letter!
Thank God!
- I won't.
You will.
Krishna...
I won't.
I've expressed my feelings
in this letter.
Give her this letter
and tell her that I love her.
Enough is enough, Mr Khanna.
Take that.
Do you work out that much?
I'm counting on you.
Mr Khanna.
And...
Don't tell anyone.
Thank you.
Devi...
Devi!
Devi.
- Devi.
De...
Krishna...
Dad.
You brought them here? - Yes.
Why do you keep your phone off?
I called you so many times.
What's wrong with Devi?
She walked up the stairs,
without meeting us.
She did?
- Yes.
She did.
Why? We've been
married for so long. - Krishna.
Krishna. - You didn't
come to meet us even once.
On the first floor. Take your time.
What's wrong?
Devi.
- Yes?
What? - Your parents and my dad
are downstairs.
You didn't greet them.
They are angry.
You sleep. I'll attend to them.
Devi. They...
I...
- Take this.
What is this?
What are you upset about?
Everyone makes mistakes.
You are... No.
Devi, you should...
Hug them.
- Mom.
Happy family! Very good.
I'll take that.
Please come in. Mom.
Take that.
Let's go.
In the room.
I don't know how you did it,
but for the first time,
you've done something good.
I swear, it was a mistake.
Hello.
- Sir, the car is ready.
Ma'am won't come today.
Why? What's wrong?
Ma'am is not well and I am mad.
Go to sleep.
Sorry. I'll never bathe again.
Ruby!
Where are you going?
- Raj Khanna is here.
Raj Khanna!
I am a huge fan.
Raj Khanna...
Come on. Raj Khanna is here.
Raj Khanna is here.
Ruby!
- Raj Khanna.
Raj Khanna.
- Do you know where Ruby lives?
Listen...
Excuse me.
Does anyone know
where the actress Ruby lives?
I have come here...
- Raj Khanna.
Ruby...
Devi, come here quickly.
Okay, but I am here...
Mom, it's Raj Khanna!
Ruby's house is here.
- Sir, what are you doing?
Sir, look over there.
Autograph please.
The crowd is getting rowdy.
Let's go.
Sir, please. Let's go.
Are you alright?
- Yes.
Please come.
- Raj Khanna.
Let's go, sir.
Let's go.
Bye.
He's calling.
Hello?
Hello, how is ma'am?
Fine.
Give the phone to ma'am.
Sir wants to speak to her.
She's sleeping.
You said she was fine.
Can't a person who is fine
not sleep?
Let her sleep.
She has to shoot
a scene with sir tomorrow.
Let her rest.
The car will be there at 9.
Why have you lost weight?
- No.
I don't go to the gym
and no home food.
You should come here.
I can cook for an extra person.
Devi. Devi.
I...
- Listen...
She's a gem of a person.
And you don't like her!
Devi, come here.
Where?
Ruby.
What?
They want you to shoot tomorrow.
Our family is here for a week.
How can I take Devi out...
Listen...
You know how it is.
That is your problem.
Tomorrow's shoot
is cancelled. Okay?
That is your problem too.
They will come here
and you will have to
deal with that.
What do I do? You are a ghost.
Do something to make them go away.
But that was not a clause
in the contract.
Good, you're dead.
Else I would've killed you.
Hey!
Friends.
Please do something.
Hey, what did you do?
Who are you?
What are you looking at?
Scoot!
What's wrong?
- See for yourself.
I don't get to spend time with you.
What are you doing? It tickles.
They came here, met us,
they should leave now.
We are newly-weds.
We need privacy.
Devi...
Listen, let's do something.
Till they are here,
we'll go somewhere else.
Be ready at 9. We'll go.
In fact...
We should leave now.
Wait.
Ask them what they'll eat.
Okay.
Listen...
Who?
What would you like to have?
Tell me.
Who is it at this hour?
That man...
Yes.
You should've stayed longer.
Really?
But...
- Wait.
What's the hurry?
- Listen...
Taxi cancelled.
- You can leave in some time.
Give this to him.
[OTHER LANGUAGE]
Let's go.
You won't come downstairs.
She'll wave bye from the kitchen.
Okay.
Go to the kitchen.
[OTHER LANGUAGE]
Action!
Raj!
Ouch!
- Hey, Ruby!
Oh no.
Ouch!
- Are you okay?
It's paining.
She's injured.
She's just pretending.
Over reacting.
One more.
Another retake?
- It's okay.
Roll camera.
- Rolling.
Action!
Sir, he's hitting him for real.
- Quiet.
Looks real.
He's hitting him badly.
- Realistic.
Steady cam, follow me. Come.
No, sir...
If even one tear
falls from her eyes...
What an angle!
Revolver Raja 3.
It's not an action film.
It's a romantic film.
What?
You're hurt.
I'm hurt?
Where?
- I'm searching.
I'd get injured often.
Move.
"The colours of love..."
"Love..."
"Love is everywhere."
"All the beautiful moments..."
"Are all around us."
"I love you, be mine."
"Let us lose ourselves in love."
"Our journey of love has begun."
"Let us go on this
journey together."
"Our journey of love has begun."
"Let us go on this
journey together."
"The colours of love..."
"Love is everywhere."
"You're the one I want."
"I have you now."
"Life is more beautiful now."
"You dwell in my heart."
"I love you."
"I can give my life for you."
"I love you. Be mine."
"Let us lose ourselves in love."
"Our journey of love has begun."
"Let us go
on this journey together."
"The colours of love..."
"Love is everywhere."
Are you Ruby's manager?
We want dates.
A five-film contract.
You may come here to meet me,
but don't discuss Ruby's dates.
I gave the rights for this film.
Go away!
Did you give Ruby the letter?
No.
- Why?
Ma'am's dream, this film...
Full concentration.
If I give her the letter,
she will be disturbed. - Then?
Finish the film soon.
I will give her the letter then.
Raj...
Sir, good behaviour till then.
Good behaviour!
- Even if the director says...
Don't touch. Keep a safe distance.
The more you stay away
from the heroine,
the closer the heroine will get.
Women's psychology.
Old formula...
But works every time.
Am I making sense?
A lot of sense.
"Everywhere I look, I see you."
"You are all I ask for."
"I want to get close to you."
"Take me into your arms."
"I love you. Be mine."
"Let's lose ourselves in love."
"The colours of love..."
"Love is everywhere."
I will.
We will be back.
Cut it!
It's a wrap for Revolver Raja.
The next...
Yes!
I'll see you.
Yes.
You look happy.
The film is done. You'll go.
Happy journey.
The shoot is done.
The film hasn't released.
I have the contract.
You are under control.
Let me see it.
Does it say I'll leave
after the shoot is over?
My dream is to see
myself on the screen.
How can I go?
Grow up, man.
This is not good.
Sir...
Yes, Krishna?
When will the film be released?
In two months.
Two months!
Why? The shoot is over.
Release it tomorrow. Or...
Why two months?
The shoot is over.
Release it tomorrow.
Please, sir. You can do it.
- How is it possible?
Only you can do it.
- Not possible.
Nothing is impossible. Please.
Hey...
- Please.
Technical problem.
You don't get it.
Nonsense!
What technical problem?
Hey you! Hey!
What are you doing?
Hey!
Hello! Stop!
He's gone.
I tried to stop them, but they
took her away. - Where's ma'am?
They took ma'am.
Let's go.
Amazing story.
Hey!
- Hear the narration.
You will like it.
Raj, your film is over.
Now, I can sign her.
Listen...
If I see you around Ruby...
If a tear falls from her eye...
Come
Follow me.
Devi?
What's wrong?
I don't know what's
happening to me.
I don't remember anything.
Where I go, what I do.
My head hurts.
Nothing is wrong.
No.
It must be a fatal disease.
I don't think I'll live long.
I told you, nothing is wrong.
If anything happens to me...
I want you to be happy.
You should remarry.
A girl of your choice.
Why did you say that?
Nothing will happen to you.
I won't let anything happen.
Don't think too much.
Go to sleep.
Hello.
Is the film releasing?
Yes, it's been difficult.
The struggle...
Could I get two tickets?
There's a special show
for people from the industry.
Get the tickets from the office.
Thank you, sir.
Yuck!
I spoke to the manager.
He said I'd get two tickets.
You don't need tickets
to watch the show, Krishna.
Did you give the letter to Ruby?
Yes. Yes, I did.
It's here. I'll give it to her
after the film is released.
I promise.
You don't need to.
Decision changed?
- Yes.
I won't tell her.
I'll tell the world.
At the press conference.
Raj weds Ruby.
And you are my best man.
Don't tell Ruby.
It's a surprise.
Worst man.
Ruby won't be there
after the film is released.
He'll announce
it at the press meet.
I will.
We will be back.
Ruby! Ruby! Ruby! Ruby!
Congratulations.
You're amazing.
Actually, I'm very lucky.
I have a surprise for you.
I'll tell you
at the press conference.
Who are you?
How you look...
I don't know.
I'm sure about one thing.
If you were alive,
you would've been very successful.
Great performance.
Here comes the new sensation.
The heroine of Revolver Raja 003,
Miss Ruby.
You shouldn't have ended your life.
But I am happy,
that through Devi,
you could live your dream.
Can we please have you on stage,
Miss Ruby?
Wear this sari.
Devi and I will go.
We will leave.
Sir.
- Just go and check where she is.
Yes, sir.
Where?
Home.
I won't go.
Hey!
Don't joke. Don't play.
You saw yourself on screen.
You'd said you'd leave.
Go now.
Wear this.
Please.
Didn't you see...
People were shouting my name.
They were praising me.
They applauded my performance.
Think before you speak.
What should I think?
About why I trusted you
or why I allowed this?
You've signed a contract.
Hey...
Devi and her life...
Devi...
Who is Devi?
There's nothing between you two.
You want to get rid of her.
If I use her body,
how will it matter to you?
Go if you want to.
I won't go anywhere.
Ma'am, what are you doing here?
People are waiting for you.
Mr Khanna is on stage already.
Everyone is waiting.
The media people, photographers...
Let's go.
"Ruby, she's here."
"Put your hands together for Ruby."
Welcome, everyone.
This is an important day
for our film.
This...
- Hey, stop this nonsense!
Stop it.
Ruby...
She is...
What is he saying?
What is he doing?
His voice...
Just gestures...
No one can hear him.
Is he okay?
Is he a fan?
What is he doing?
He's saying something.
Sir, people are going mad
after watching our film.
Revolver Raja 3, superhit.
Ruby, next superstar.
Wow! What a manager!
Very good.
This...
Please...
Good evening, everyone.
We make films.
We act.
But when acting turns to reality,
we don't realise.
There's a thin line
between reel life and real life.
I've just realised that.
Ruby is not just my co-star,
but she's the best actor.
Not only is she a good actress,
but is a good human being too.
The best thing that happened
to Revolver Raja.
And of course...
My life.
On this important day,
Ruby and I...
Both of us...
- Ma'am.
Ruby!
- What's wrong?
What happened?
Move aside.
Please.
Sir, the doctor
is calling you inside.
She's fine.
Are you married?
Soon.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
She's pregnant.
Thanks, doctor.
You love ma'am...
But ma'am loves me.
Sorry.
If a single tear
falls from her eyes...
Sir. How is ma'am? Is she fine?
She's pregnant.
Super news, sir.
God...
You're such a rockstar, sir.
You're always rocking, sir.
You didn't tell me.
When did this happen?
When will junior Raj be born?
Hello.
I'll call you.
It's the jewellery shop.
The pendant you'd ordered for
Miss Singh is ready.
What should I do?
Send it.
Where?
Strike my name off
and write Krishna's.
With love.
Why? Sorry, if I can ask.
You won't understand.
You're a real hero.
Amazing! Super!
Ruby.
We wish for many things...
But God's will prevails.
Your life was ruined.
But you don't have the right 'to
ruin others' lives.
I beg you.
Please return Devi to me.
I love her a lot.
Please.
You.
Hospital?
Are you okay?
I...
Is it so bad now?
What am I wearing?
Is it a hospital gown?
It will be the first time
when a husband tells his wife...
What?
You are pregnant.
Devi.
- What?
What are you doing?
You brought the clothes from the
terrace, but left the towel there.
I did?
Towel.
What happened?
Yippee!
There was a nameplate here.
It had fallen down,
so I threw it away.
Was it important?
It wasn't, was it?
Okay, then.
Raj!
- Raj Khanna.
Autograph.
What's your name?
Ruby.
"A gorgeous girl..."
"Wearing dark glasses..."
"And high heels..."
"Her arrival"
"made my heart race."
"It made my heart race."
"She's got style, she looks posh."
"Move away...
- Excuse me."
"Move away, baby,
the train is arriving."
"Hey beautiful girl,
come into my life."
"I love everything about you."
"Please come into my life."
"Please be mine."
"The train moves and halts."
"I will do anything for you."
"You are the best in town."
"We'll go to a club.
That's a done deal."
"You are the best in town."
"We'll go to a club.
That's a done deal."
"When I stretch lazily,
the sky seems to fall."
"Move away...
- Excuse me."
"Move away, girl,
the train is arriving."