Those are tears of joy, right?
Show me..
Salt'!-
Trust me..l guarantee
all kinds of happiness.
This is my card.
ACP Ramesh Sarnayak.
Day and Night service.
I'm comfortable mostly at night.
Sorry.
"Took longer than I expected.
Nice girlfriend.
She's a bit emotional.
How did she fall for
a drug-addict like you?
Sir, we were not taking drugs.
We just happened to be at the party?
- Hey..
Stop ranting in English, right.
Bloody ****
Your mother runs an NGO.
Father is a social
activist on news channel.
And were you giving
spiritual lessons.
...to the girl
on your car's backseat?
Ohhh..if you do it,
its enjoyment.
And if we do it, it's harassment.
You're from a good family.
You've already proved that.
...you care about your
parent's reputation.
Stop ruining your future.
Go in..go inside.
She's waiting for you.
Go on..
"I'm obsessed
aboutmaking you mine."
Karan sir, am I disturbing you?
Speak!
I haven't received my packet yet.
I've already paid you in full.
Look sir, crime and alcohol
become invaluable as they grow old.
Don't they?
It was a big mistake.
...to think that a cunning
basm like you would be loyal.
Loyal as a dog sir..
Have I ever given
you a chance to complain?
You won't anymore.
I am going to settle
your account once and for all.
I hope you mean that, sir.
And you're not furious with me.
Bloody ***
"..come closer and.."
Who..who are you?
Who are you?
I think we're hacked.
Cheap
death by expensive petrol.
A chilling
death which may make your soul shiver.
How
and when this happened?
This
murder of a police officer.
...seems
entangled like a thread.
A murder
as gruesome as most foul.
Probably one of
the saddest in the history of crime.
And we've news that Global
Time Network CEO Mr. Rahul Oberoi..
"The media mogul.
Has been asked for questioning.
Death on rampage.
Grimm
Reapers have a ball.
Is Rahul Oberoi the
mastermind behind all this?
Yes..the same Rahul
Oberoi who owns Global Times Network.
Sir..sir..
ACP Sarnaik was murdered on channel,
What do you have to say about it, sir?
Who dared to summon me
here like a ordinary criminal?
Do you guys have any idea who I am?
Your minister's on my payroll.
Well sir,
who is on whose payroll..
...that's strictly between you two.
That's strictly personal.
We're just doing our job.
I am Rahul Oberoi.
The CEO of Global Times Network!
India's most
power-ful..media house.
Big fan.
Big fan!
I am Kabir Deshmukh.
A humble servant of India's strongest
and most effective Police force.
Mumbai Police.
How dare you call me here?
Every minute of mine
is worth millions.
You should respect time,
not put a price-tag on it.
Sir, I've done some research.
Correct me if I am wrong.
Your ratings were
falling..profits were falling.
You were losing
credibility in the market.
And then..this cheap stunt.
Live Murder on Television!
Was it your idea?
Absolutely right.
Congratulations.
You just solved the entire case.
Must be my idea.
I pay millions in salary to creative
directors, editors and program heads.
...so that they give me
such out-of-the-box ideas..
...and the ratings
of my TV channel soar.
And then I throw a
grand party..in Tihar Jail.
Actually sir,
if you do go to jail..
...you'll be sent to Yerwada jail.
Next question.
If not you..
"Then who?
We were hacked.
How do you know?
We've done our research, officer.
You can talk to
my technical head Mak.
He's in Delhi right now.
But he's arriving
by the evening flight.
Sir..let's take this step-by-step.
Let's deal with you first.
I've an entire question
paper prepared for you.
Officer, stay within your limits.
Don't cross your limit.
- Limit?
We just saw your limit
live on your Television channel.
But you haven't
seen our limit yet.
Pray to God that you're
as innocent as you claim to be.
Gaitonde.
- Yes, sir.
Set the AC to 18
..he's sweating.
Right?
Now, as the
proceedings continue, all we know..
...is that Rahul Oberoi is
still being questioned inside.
And
we all are clueless.
So sir, you have no clue.
You didn't know
ACP Sarnaik as well.
You don't suspect any
of your rival channels either.
You're just a honest
tax-paying citizen.
You don't know how your
systems were hacked either.
Mak does.
Basically you have no clue.
Sir, if this continues any longer,
we can come to only one conclusion.
Either you are..or someone's
making you look like one big..
You're too under-qualified..
...to judge who or what I am,
officer.
Sir, you see..my
qualification is that.
...I can use my service revolver
on whoever..and whenever I want.
“With no questions asked.
You know what,
you're wasting my time.
An entire life got wasted
on Global Times Network.
An ACP has been murdered.
You will have to give us time.
Anyway,
it was a pleasure meeting you.
You must deposit your
passport with us and..
"This is my number, save it.
And please,
don't forward any cheap jokes.
Leave.
Where the hell is Siya.
Call her.
- Okay, sir.
Good morning, ma'am.
- Hi.
Good morning.
- Good morning.
Good morning, ma'am.
- Hi.
"And the Mumbai
Police has accused."
"..Global Times Network's
CEO Rahul Oberoi for this murder.."
I am a national scene now.
All these years I
lead the news business..
...and today I've become
some cheap news myself.
The media mogul
is on trial by media.
That bloody no-good
police officer.
...was treating me like
I was a pick-pocketeer.
I'm left all alone, Rahul.
You're not alone, Rahul.
I am there for you.
I am your legal head,
and you know I am good at my job.
Nothing will happen to you.
Siya, I will destroy
that bloody Kabir.
He thinks,
rather he believes that..
...I did this for ratings.
Did you do it..or not?
Siya, you're sounding
just like Kabir.
I've never met such a
crooked officer in my life.
He's not crooked, he's straight.
He has a clean record.
Don't confuse your ego with him.
I will buy him.
- He has no price-tag.
Just relax, Rahul.
Just follow protocol,
and do as I say.
As long as I am there,
no one can touch you.
And..what if I want to touch you?
Then you will lose this case,
Rahul Oberoi.
Let's pray..there's no sequel
or second episode to this live murder.
Talk to Mak..and ignore Kabir.
Ranvir.
How did you know?
Even the fragrance
of all these flowers.
"Cannot deluge
your fragrance, Ranvir.
Then give this fragrance
a place of refuge.
If I am the rain..
"Then let me shower on you.
The rain doesn't need
anyone's permission.
...to cascade from the clouds.
I love you.
It's been a year, Siya.
But I miss you every moment.
Then take me to some place.
...where we will
just love each other.
Close your eyes, Siya.
"You're the one..who's
always close to my heart."
"Life's a sweet craving..is
what you all say."
"You're the one..who's
always close to my heart."
"Your veil..flutters over
my eyes as the sun sets."
"Each night fall brings..a
series of memories."
"Every time I draw a breath.
I can sense your fragrance."
"And brings
along..a sweet message."
"Even my
heanbeathums your tune."
"You're the one..who's
always close to my heart."
"You're the one..who's.."
"I saw you yesterday...
in my courtyard..."
"Seemed like you were saying,
hide me in your arms."
"What is this bond?"
"What are these dreams?"
"Even though you're a stranger,
you feel like a kin."
"I always think...and scared to say."
"You're the one...
always close to my heart."
Hi.
Late on a date.
You'll have to pay fine.
I am 'fine' with it, Suhani.
Would you convince
mom with muffins too?
No, sweetheart.
This muffin shop hadn't
open at that time.
You miss your mom.
Only when you come late.
Do you miss her?
- No ways.
After all..l get her share
of kisses and hugs too.
Nice try,
but I am still not talking to you.
Why?
A big green monster
came to my room last night.
And I was all alone in my room.
Oh my, God.
There were some complications
in my life, I am so sorry.
But tonight your green
monster is done for.
You think only your life's
complicated? Not mine?
I am the best dancer in the class.
But Archana miss didn't
put me in the centre.
Can your police force do
something about this..serious issue?
Sit down. Sit down.
The police force can't.
But your dad will advise
you to work harder.
Impress Archana miss.
And in your next concert
you will be the show-stopper.
Right?
' Very good.
Sorry. Just a minute.
Phone.
Yes, Gaitonde.
- Sir, we've found Mak.
Yes..l am coming.
Eat.
Okay?'-
You're leaving?
I am sorry, dear.
That dancer behind
stage has come up front.
But I promise, tonight we'll
arrest your green monster together.
Okay?
Give me a five.
See you.
Jai Hind, sir.
Good morning, sir.
- Good morning.
Sir, we were waiting
for you..can we star-t now?
Mr. Rahul, good morning.
Did you sleep well?
This is Siya, my legal head.
And that is Mak, my technical head.
Mak.
Makrand Moge.
Can we star-t'?
- Wait, Mr. Rahul.
You just introduced me to your team.
"Now, how about you meet
our team-player as well.
Mr. Ranvir Bajaj,
State counselor on this case.
Good morning, gentlemen.
And of course, lady.
I hope I've not missed anything.
No-no, we were waiting for you.
So good..we may star-t now.
So gentlemen, as we all
know that our network was hacked.
And it's a fact.
In order to prove this fact,
Mak has made a presentation.
I think after hearing that,
things will be clearer.
So we're living in the age
of fast travelling information.
Information..is created at
one source, and goes to the receiver.
That means, for any
information to travel anywhere..
...we need a source and a receiver.
Same applies to TV broadcasting.
This is the Global Times
Network's source station.
From here, their entire content.
...is transmitted to their
satellite through signal package.
Now, from the satellite it's
transmitted to the broadcast central.
For example 'Sky Dish'..'National
Dish'..etcetera-etcetera..and others.
And..again they transmit
it to the satellite.
And from here, it's retransmitted
to the dish antenna.
Now, the content is decrypted
through our dish antenna..
...and seen on our TV
through the set-top box.
This hacker..hacked our frequency“.
...transmitting from
GTN to the satellite.
Once it's hacked,
then the hacker can play God.
I mean..he can command
what's goes to the satellite.
...and what does not.
So why didn't
your..engineers stop him?
Well..this was a very
high-level hacking maneuver.
By the time we could
understand what's happening.
...it was already over.
And you let it happen.
Well, we tried our best to stop it.
But as you know,
we're a huge organization.
And there are protocols to follow.
So it took us time to
follow all the procedures.
Very interesting.
I am sure that even
your cyber-cell will agree..
...that we were hacked.
And now, if there's anything
that's not understood.
...we'll be happy to answer.
How can we trace a hacker like this?
Actually, first of all
we've to think like them.
Don't tell me your
chaps didn't try that.
Of course we did,
but the hacker was smart.
He used multiple login IDs
to hack the Global Times Network.
And the last ID we traced,
was on the US.
I knew it.
Meaning?
Sometimes you can get hacked
with a simple phone call.
And..how is that?
Well..the hacker just
needs to hack the medium.
And the medium can be anything.
For example, video-calls, phone-calls,
radio-signals..and IP address as well.
IP address as well.
Yes, IP address as well.
You can customize your phone
number through the IP address..
...and call anyone.
And they will never know
who the hacker is, and where.
I hope it's clear.
And what kind of equipments
do you require for all this?
Simple..
High-speed internet..and
a high-end laptop.
Sometimes just a phone maybe.
WOW!
That's it, huh?
And a genius mind.
Like you.
And a motive too.
Absolutely right.
And we've no motives,
we're the victims.
Right?
Establishing a motive..is my job.
And let me do my job, Ms. Siya.
So you can wait for that moment.
We would like to leave.
Thank you for your time, gentlemen.
What do you think?
No chance.
Actually we don't
have any evidence either.
The court won't grant us
even an hour for interrogation.
But trust me.
I know people like Rahul very well.
If he's done something,
he'll definitely make a mistake.
"Which will be in our favor.
So be it, sir.
Sir..Sarnaik sir's phone
records have arrived.
If we want to make
some progress in this case..
...we'll have to go
few steps backwards.
Come, Gaitonde..let's listen
to Sarnaik sir's history.
'Karan sir, am I disturbing you?'
'It was a big mistake.'
...to think that a cunning
basm like you would be loyal.'
Loyal as a dog sir..
Have I ever given
you a chance to complain?'
'You won't anymore.'
I am going to settle
your account once and for all.'
'I hope you mean that, sir.'
'And you're not furious with me.'
Karen Parekh.
Mumbai's real-estate magnet.
Goa's casino king.
Collector of Derby horses.
Ramesh Sarnaik, ACP Mumbai Police.
What cat and mouse
game were they playing?
Sir, I think we've
reached the next level.
For that, we've to understand
the level of Sarnaik's every case.
Back in the headquarters, you
were trying to be over-smart, Ranvir.
Not cool.
If someone's paying you a six-digit
salary, doesn't mean he's innocent.
Rahul is a shrewd business.
Not a psychopath like that hacker,
whoever he is.
And he's honestly admitted
that he's not involved.
Honesty..Rahul?
You seriously believe
what Rahul said?
He can stoop to any
level for his business.
How can you trust him?
So that makes him a murderer.
I have a mind too.
And I feel,
rather I am sure that he's innocent.
Only time will tell.
It's a open and shut case, Ranvir.
No logic, no evidence, no proof.
And I am telling you this.
Siya..
...you know..
- What?
When you get angry..
You look really beautiful.
You know what.
I know.
I think..Rahul Oberoi's
going to be s****
And why do you think that?
Because even God can't
win against a furious lover..
...let alone this owner
of Global Network.
I see..
Furious love and all.
I likes.
Rohini..didn't die in a car accident,
she was murdered.
Karan got her killed.
My child tolerated
that animal for so long.
Later when she realized
it was enough..
"Then we filed for divorce.
We had extensive
evidence against him.
But just one day before
the court's judgment.
...Rohini died in a car accident.
No wife, no divorce, no alimony..
No justice, no daughter.
Karan wrapped up the
case out of the court.
We are..
We're helpless old couple.
We're only waiting
for..God's justice.
I can understand your pain.
I assure you..justice
can be delayed, but not denied.
Right sir, thank you.
- You're welcome.
I'll be in touch,
and if anything comes up, I will..
Sir..do all your cars get
serviced at Trinity Motors?
Do you have service
records of your cars?
Yes, I have them.
Hurry up, come on.
Imagine Gaitonde.
...all the cars of a family..
"Gets serviced
at the same workshop.
...by the same mechanic,
for all these years.
And one of the car
has a brake failure.
So..should we hold God responsible
for it, or the mechanic?
Sir, I feel..we can
suspect the mechanic.
Huh?
- Yes.
But sir..where are the
factssupponing your theory?
Here you go.
- Thank you.
What happened?
Sometimes a small piece
of paper..can solve a big case.
Good day, sir. I'll be seeing you.
Any luck?
I don't know about luck..but
Karan's bad luck is about to begin.
Gaitonde, all the service records
have been signed by the same mechanic.
Some Chanderpal.
You mean to say the brakes
didn't fail, it was sabotaged.
I am not saying it. Chanderpal will.
H ow?
We'll request him..to
please cooperate.
Come on.
- Sir.
Mister.
Yes, sir.
- Who is Chanderpal?
Chandu, someone's here to see you.
There he is, sir.
Yes, sir..what's the job?
We're fans of your talent.
Can you fix..car brakes?
Sir, stop Misting words.
Get to the point, what is the job?
I like him.
- Me too.
Well..I'll get to the point.
Can you sabotage brakes?
Are you police officers?
Hey..only two kinds
of people recognize police.
The Police..or criminals.
You're not the Police.
Look sir..l am a poor mechanic.
I don't understand
what you're trying to say.
Who told you to sabotage
Sabarwars brakes?
What?
Look here, Gaitonde here
is just as good with a stick..
...like you are in acting.
Come on.
Don't hit me! Don't hit me!
I'll tell you, sir..I'll tell you!
Let Gaitonde practice some more.
It's been really long
since he's had a chance.
Sir, I beg you..
Let me go.
Karan sir gave me the
money..to sabotage the brakes.
How much did he pay you, Chandu?
He paid me 70,000.
What did you do with
the money, Chandu?
I bought a 40 inch TV, sir.
Oh..now taste this
52 inch police truncheon.
Sir..don't hit me, sir..don't hit me.
I told you everything, sir.
Leave me sir.
This punishment is just
for sabotaging the brakes.
You still have to pay for the
death caused by the brake failure.
Sir, please..please..
If the brakes failed..then how did it
become a accident case in the court?
Sarnaik sir had a hand in it, sir.
I see..
- Yes.
H ow?
Sir, I am a poor man.
I don't know so much in detail.
What do you think, Gaitonde?
Does he really not know anything else?
You know what,
sir..l don't want to believe him.
Okay?'-
You can have your fun with him
until you're not completely assured.
And yes..get the paperwork
done and keep him inside.
Or else he'll sabotage
our investigation.
Isn't it?
No, sir..
Sir!
I can arrest Karan right now.
He got his wife killed.
Sarnaik covered it up.
Later Sarnaik blackmailed
Karan for money.
And Karan killed Sarnaik.
There's a logical flow in all of it..
"But it all gets
stuck in one place.
...why telecast it live
on Global TV Network?
And how does Rahul
Oberoi fit in all this?
I'll help you.
Huh? What?
You know Karan and
Rahul were partners.
In fact, Karan had a
stake in Global Times Network.
But these two had a major
fallout regarding money.
They in fact had a big
spat in the board meeting.
Rahul sc**** Karan out
of approximately 10 billion.
Then what?
Karan was so furious,
that he openly claimed to ruin Rahul.
Are you serious?
How do you know that?
Even I have my sources.
Inside-trading.
Revenge was the motive.
He got two birds with one stone.
Fantastic.
With Sarnaik dead, there's
no evidence to Rohini murder case.
And live murder on TV
means..Rahul Oberoi is finished.
Where are your feet, sir?
No-no..right now,
you must trouble your feet.
And take a statement from Rahul..
...stating that Karan
threatened to kill him.
I am sure Rahul will
be happy to give it to you.
Come on..run before Karan runs away.
Siya..do you have any
family details of Sarnaik?
Why?
I wanted to send some
flowers and a thank you card.
You know..while dying,
a stranger..made our channel no. 1
It's funny.
There's success hidden
behind my ruination.
I am having a dream run.
You're such a sick man, Rahul.
Then why don't you cure me?
Believe me,
Siya..only your love can cure me.
In your dreams.
Yeah.
Sir, ACP Kabir Deshmukh from
Mumbai Police is here to see you.
Shall I send him in.
Send him.
- Okay, sir.
Kabir?
- Yeah.
Relax, Rahul.
Hello.
Sir, why do you make
faces when you see me?
The police don't always
come with an arrest warrant.
Right?
This time I have good news.
Sorry..breaking news.
What do you mean?
Karen.
Karen Parekh.
Your best friend.
That rascal.
What rascal, Mr. Rahul.
He just made your ratings soar.
He's been a true friend.
He did break a few laws in
the process, but we'll handle those.
You just sign this statement..
And later you can play
'Breaking-news' all you like.
Can I see this statement?
- Of course, yeah.
What is all this, Rahul?
Sir, you can sign this later.
You can explain this to him later"
...and you can understand
this from her later.
I have to go.
I'll send someone
for the signed copies.
Sir..you can brighten
up your mood now.
Karan's arrest warrant.
What you wanted.
Thank you, sir.
"Heart's filled with pain,
that I want to cry."
"Without you...my hear-t
wants to just fade away."
"I loved you...more than God."
"Yet I couldn't make you mine."
"Always dwelled in your heart..."
"...but couldn't
reach your heartbeats."
"So close...yet
we were so apart."
"Who can listen my
heartbreaking apan?"
"Sweetheart...love's true."
"Destiny's craves
for something else."
"Struck by destiny,
what can we do?"
"Destiny cannot be controlled."
"Sweetheart. .
"Sweetheart. . Sweetheart. .
"It's the grace of time..."
"...that you're sitting
so close to me."
"It's hard to explain in
words...how much I love you."
"Look at me...just once."
"Who can listen my
heartbreaking apan?"
"Sweetheart...love's true."
"Destiny's craves
for something else."
"Struck by destiny,
what can we do?"
"Destiny cannot be controlled."
"Sweetheart. .
"Sweetheart. . Sweetheart. .
"Heart's filled with pain,
that I want to cry."
"Without you...my hear-t
wants to just fade away."
Karen Parekh.
Does sir know you're coming?
No ma'am,
we're here to give him a surprise.
Sir is in room no. 1211.
Thank you.
Gaitonde.
- Sir.
Staircase.
- Okay, sir.
Let's go.
- Quick.
1211?
Where is Karan?
- You guys...
But he just got up to open the door.
What?
How long ago?
Just 5 minutes before you arrived.
'1211...'
House-keeping service
at this late hour?
Gaitonde.
Seal all the
entry/exits of the hotel.
Check every floor,
search every corner of the hotel.
Karan shouldn't get out of here.
Exits block.
What's wrong, sir? What is it?
What happened?
Yes, Avinash?
- Sir, Karan's live on GTN.
What?
- Yes, sir.
May I have the remote please?
- Yes sir.
Rahul, are you watching?
Yes.
I am coming.
Keep trying-
Sir...
Got it.
Yes, Avinash?
Sir, we've traced the
location to an IP address.
Where? - There's a chawl just
ten minutes from where you are...
...Shanti Niwas,
Purshottam Narvekar Road.
He's not very far away.
- Let's go guys.
Yes, Avinash.
Sir, the location has shift.
I think he's jumping the IP address.
We've lost him.
Sir, give me a team...in
the middle of the night...'
'Give me this...give me that...'
And what was the result?
Do you know...Human Rights,
Media, the common man...
The entire world is laughing on us.
When you go out there,
people will laugh at Mumbai Police.
Two live murders were
telecasted on TV back-to-back.
The one you called the
murderer...gets murdered.
And you gave a clean
chit to the one suspected.
Go and arrest that
Rahul Oberoi first.
And make him spill the truth.
Sir, I don't think that Rahul...
You can see the result of
your opinion...outside the window.
Now do as I say.
Grill the one we suspect first.
Yes, sir.
Jai Hind, sir.
Mumbai police...
- Down! Down!
Sir, let's arrest Rahul.
The Commissioner is right.
Why will Rahul make
the same mistake twice?
Mumbai police...
- Down! Down!
The murderer is someone else.
Who, why and where...
Mumbai police...
- Down! Down!
And finding him is the
real pride of this uniform.
Otherwise...uniforms
can be rented too.
Rahul Oberoi.
CEO and Chairman
of Global Times Network.
He's under the
debt of 4.65 billion.
His main business is news.
And he's got only
one medium of income.
Sensationalizing of news.
And..in order to repay
the debt of 4.65 million..
...one needed a big explosion.
More ratings.
More advertisers, more money.
Simple.
Your honor, first murder;
ACP Sarnaik.
And Rahul knew that ACP
Sarnaik was blackmailing Karan..
...for cover up his wife's murder.
ACP killed on live TV..the
suspicion goes on Karan..
...and ratings to Global
Times Network..excellent.
The second murder
of Karan himself.
Reason..a strong and
bold criminal psychology.
Rahul Oberoi is a hardcore
criminal, a cunning murderer..
...and a big threat to the society.
Theory-theory and more theory.
Whatever the defense
council just said..
...is all based
on some imagination.
Like..a writer's fantasy.
Is there any evidence, any proof..or
any eye-witness to this approach?
Baseless. logic-less. abstract.
My client Rahul Oberoi
completely cooperated..
...with the Mumbai Police
officer in every investigation.
But now..we will not cooperate.
Now,
the law will cooperate with us.
Your honor,
it's a complicated case.
This is not a
chain-snatching case.
"Which can be solved
in a single day.
It takes time to gather evidence,
Ms. Siya.
One of your own officer's
has been murdered.
And you say you need more time.
Every kid in the country is watching
this horrific death on television.
And you say you need more time.
An honest, tax-paying citizen
has been called murderer, psycho.
...and in no time he's
been summoned to the court.
You can't catch the murderer.
And just going around in
circles..to hide your failure.
Our cyber-cell team is working.
- Your cyber cell was clueless.
It was we who told them..that
our systems were hacked.
And why will
Rahul Oberoi help you.
To incriminate himself?
- No, to clear the suspicion on him, Ms. Siya.
Do you have proof?
That's why we want judicial
custody of Rahul Oberoi.
This is not some
chain-snatching case.
...where you can arrest
anyone you suspect.
The Mumbai Police should
do their homework properly.
Is Rahul Oberoi
thier only suspect?
They can't prove him murderer
by calling him 'Murderer'.
Give me a proof..give
me an evidence.
...and you can definitely
take Rahul in custody.
But that will never happen.
Because your entire department.
cannot find a single murderer.
He's always a step ahead of you.
And you just want
to cover-up your failure.
Your honor,
my client deserves his lawful freedom.
The Mumbai Police hasn't presented
any evidence against Rahul Oberoi.
Nor could they prove
any motive of his involvement.
So permission for judicial
custody..is refused.
Suhani, put this piece here.
- No-no..
Poppy..come quickly,
I need your help.
WOW!
That's a big puzzle.
It's so confusing.
You're an expert
in solving puzzles.
Which piece will fit here?
You tell me.
I don't know.
Focus, dear. Focus.
Sometimes the piece is right
before us..but we don't see it.
Got it.
- Yeah.
Thank you, poppy. You're a genius.
Let's play together.
Sometimes the piece is right
before us..but we don't see it.'
We know the connection
between Karan and Sarnaik.
And the connection
between Rahul and Karan.
But what connects Karan,
Rahul and Sarnaik.
Three dots.
...how can you connect them?
Gaitonde.
- Yes, sir.
I want a information.
Hi, baby.
What's the matter?
What brings you here
so early in the morning?
Coffee? Breakfast?
What would you like?
You're defending this case
with your eyes and ears closed, Siya.
Why don't you understand..that Rahul's
involved in this case. he is involved.
Don't you dare shout on me!
I am not shouting.
I am just trying to tell you,
rather explain you..
...that you're making
a big mistake, Siya.
What kind of a job is this
which compels you to help a murderer?
I know such people really well.
These people
have no fear of the law.
They can do anything they
want on the basis of money and power.
And they get someone
like you to save them.
What do you mean 'Like you'?
I genuinely feel
Rahul is innocent.
And I'm trying
my best to defend him.
That's what the law thinks too.
Ranveer, give your mind some rest.
You're going around in circles.
I am going around in circles?
Fine.. Then tell me,
weren't Rahul and Karan best friends?
Rahul owed 12.2
billion to Karan.
12.2 billion.
And that Sarnaik.
Why was he murdered?
Don't you think they
are all connected together?
Ranveer, you're hurting me.
And the thought of this
killer lose is killing me.
Rahul is innocent.
Kabir?
I have proof.
- What proof?
Rem rape case.
Rajni rape case is the only case.
...that links Rahul,
Karan and Sarnaik together.
What is Rajni rape case?
This case is the
pan of this puzzle..
"Which no one bothered to see!
Ranveer, what's this case?
Who is Rajni?
My first client.
Global Times Network's
employee of the year.
She was raped by Rahul and Karan.
- What?
Leave me..
Please let me go, sir.
Please let me go..
Let me go, sir.
Sir, please..
- Come on.
Sir, please..Rahul sir, let me go.
Sir please..
Sir, sorry..please. Let me go.
Sorry, sir.
I really don't get you girls?
You can sleep with your boyfriend.
It's casual.
But, if someone like
us genuinely asks for it..
"Then you get offended.
You slapped me..
Sinplease, sir.
Let me go.. please.
After getting slapped..my mercy has died.
- Please..
Please..
Karan sir, please..
- Look-look..
No..
Either you make love
to us..one-by-one.
Or you really make
it tough for yourself.
Please sir, I have a boyfriend.
I am getting married, sir..please.
That's like a good girl, baby.
Well..now we'll make
a small mistake as well.
No..
Then you can forgive us too.
- No-no-no..
Who's in there?
Open the shutter.
Open LIP--
Hey..who's there?
Let that poor girl go.
You won't, huh!
I'll go get the police.
Hurry up bro,
this is my second cigarette.
All yours, bro.
Come on, baby..
Sir please, come quickly.
Some girl is being
raped in the garage.
Who is getting raped?
This is not the time for question
and answers. Come with me now.
Two men are raping a girl.
So you should've helped her.
Why did you come running here?
You should've beaten
up those rascals.
You think this is a joke.
That poor girl is in trouble.
And you're wasting time.
Get up! I said get up.
Come..come, inspector.
They were raping her here.
There was a car parked here.
I don't know where it is now.
Maybe it's too late.
I saw it with my own eyes.
- Who's getting raped?
Where is the rapist?
- Here..
Oh no..
Don't just stand there.
Call the ambulance.
We must take her to the hospital.
Go on!
The wound on your body will heal.
But,
I won't rest peacefully until..
...I don't make them pay
for hurting your self-esteem.
Madam, would you
like to talk now, or..
'Rajni told police everything.'
'Mr. Sharma was with her too.'
She star-ted preparing
to drag powerful people..
...like Rahul and
Karan to the court.'
But I want to tell you..
This is going to be a long,
painful, tiring and humiliating case.
Think about it.
When a rape case is
discussed in the court.
...it's not less than
a rape case itself.
Doesn't make a difference to me.
I want justice.
Rather..l want my revenge.
Karan sir, am I disturbing you.
Go on.
You should've broken the
toy after playing with it ,
But you spared it.
And now..the case has been filed.
And they have a lawyer too.
They've a strong witness
So..what to do?
What else..buy out the lawyer.
Sir, not everyone
is cooperative like me.
But Still..l will try.
Call up your Karan sir.
- Of course, sir.
Just a second.
- Yes.
Sir..I've handed over the package.
He likes it.
Yes, he wants to talk to you.
Wants to say thank you.
Here you go, sir.
Did you hear..my thank you?
Your ideals.
...your principles.
It's alright, Mr.
Lawyer..see you at the coun.
Your honor, unfortunately
the punishment for gang-rape..
...in our law is only 10 years.
You must take a
decision which will ..
...eradicate the mentality
of people like Karan and Rahul.
To put the last nail in the coffin
of these two, Karan and Rahul..
...I would like to call the
only eye-witness of this case.
Mr. Bijendra Sharma.
Permission granted.
Sir,
we've have some very bad news.
Last night a fire broke out in Mr.
Sharma's house.
...and he burnt to death.
Burnt to death? So simple?
Mr. Sharma was burnt to death!
There was a short circuit,
fire broke out, and..
Finished.
And then what?
They were acquited.
I lost my first case.
And.. Rajni?
I don't know where she
disappeared to after that.
Karan and Rahul raped
my capability in the court.
They turned a rape
case into consensual sex.
After that I heard that..
Rajni left the city.
But no clue about where she went.
But she's back now..
...and what a comeback.
No judge or lawyer,
no evidence or witness.
She is giving her own judgment.
Let Rahul die if has to.
It will only mean one
less animal on this earth.
We must save Rahul.
Sir.
I want every detail of Rajni
rape case..as soon as possible.
As you wish, sir.
Bloody..
"The reason..l feel
overwhelmed every season.."
"The reason is you."
"The reason..I've
become so poetic.."
"The reason is you."
"I was shattered in pieces..but
I feel complete now.."
"I strolled down
your lane every day."
"The reason is you."
"I was never
like I am these days."
"I hardly meet anyone
else..except for you."
"I've star-ted
changing these days."
"The reason is you."
"Whenever I look for you,
I find you inside me."
"Where do you begin..."
"...and where do I end,
it's hard to say."
"Where do you begin..."
"...and where do I end,
it's hard to say."
"I am deeply, madly in love."
"The reason is you."
"I was like shattered
in a million pieces."
"But I feel whole again."
"As I pass down your lane every day."
"The reason is you."
You know poppy,
I finished my homework on time.
Good girl.
Hello.
How are you, Kabir?
I am fine, and you are?
- I am not fine, Kabir.
Because you're not letting
me do my job. - Who's this?
You're a good Police officer,
and I respect you for that.
But I request you..please
back out this 'live-murder' case.
It's not worth it.
Rahul has to die,
and you can't stop it.
Confidence is a good thing,
but over confidence is bad.
Please, I've no interest
in harming you in anyway, Kabir.
Because you have
a beautiful daughter.
...and you have to live for her.
Listen, you sound like
you're an educated guy.
But you're threatening
me like cheap.
Kabir..I've done my
duty of warning you.
Now you must do your
duty as a good father.
Stay away from this case.
You can customize
your phone number..'
...through the IP
address and call anyone.'
And they won't even know
who the hacker is, and where.'
Yes?
Makrand Moghe.
He's not at home right now?
Who are you?
Kabir Deshmukh.
Mumbai Police.
When will he be back?
He'll be back soon.
Can I wait for him inside?
Okay, come in.
Here.
- Thank you.
The wheels of time stopped
spinning for me long ago.
But the tracks of my wheelchair
finally led you to me.
Rem .
Puzzle solved.
Mak's home..and photos of Rahul,
Karan and Sarnaik.
And the guest at home is Rajni.
One can let a guest
like this in his home..
...when she already
dwells in his heart.
Mak is the boyfriend
Rajni wanted to marry.
Revenge, you have many faces.
For the first time
in my entire career..
...my hear-t and mind
are in disagreement.
If I listen to my heart, then
I should let you go as the victim.
If I listen to my mind,
I should arrest you as the culprit.
What should I do?
Gaitonde. - Yes sir.
Send the fingerprints and
all the documents connected..
...to this case to forensics.
Rajni will stay under
house-arrest for the time being.
Gaitonder, I want these
repor-ts..as soon as possible.
Okay sir.
We must trace Mak.
We cannot let Mak
slip out of our hands.
And in the mean time,
keep a watch on Rajni. Okay?
Right.
The case has been solved.
Makrand Moghe,
also known as Mak is the accused.
Mak, who is also the technical
head of Global Times Network.
...planned these murders.
But why did Makrand
Moghe do such a thing?
Revenge.
And the motive for revenge
is linked to a 5 year old case.
Since the matter will
now go to the court.
...we cannot disclose
any more information.
Thank you everyone for your time.
Sir..
"As you saw, ACP Ramesh Sarnaik and
Karan Parek murder case has been solved."
Unbelievable.
Mak..Rajni's boyfriend.
ACP Kabir Deshmukh.
A humble servant of India's strongest.
and most effective Police Force.
Mumbai Police.
Isn't the Mumbai Police
a little helpless?
Catch him and explain him.
“That I didn't
rape his girlfriend.
I was acquitted.
He's a f**** psycho, God dammit.
What a rascal..striking
from the shadows?
What's the guarantee
of my safety, Kabir?
When are you going
to arrest that rascal, Mak?
Soon.
And you don't worry.
Your safety is our priority.
Priority?
My safety?
Your priority
should be arrest Mak.
That Will
automatically make me safe.
You better do your job Kabir.
Manisha. - Yes, sir.
Please come in.
Manisha,
collect my passport from him.
And book me on the
first flight to New York.
Sure, sir.
And pack my insulin
shots also. - Okay.
Thank you.
And Kabir, make sure you get
me to the airport safe and sound.
I'll talk to your Commissioner.
You do have my number.
Whatsapp me when you get Mak.
And listen.
Don't forward me any cheap jokes.
Oh..
Siya! Siya! Siya!
I didn't know that
I was helping a rapist.
Siya, I am not a rapist.
I know who..and what you are.
But..how can you decide
from such a distance?
I've already decided.
Then...
Here's my resignation letter.
Do you want to spend
the night with this rapist?
You want to pay my bills?
"As I saw you...
my hear-t skipped a beat."
"It's not your fault,
it's my eyes that deceive me."
"As I saw you...
my hear-t skipped a beat."
"It's not your fault,
it's my eyes that deceive me."
"The thing you're scared of most..."
"...I'll do it for you."
"Don't look at me like so,
I'll take you in my arms."
"I will steal you away..."
"...and hide you in my arms."
"Don't look at me like so,
I'll take you in my arms."
"I will steal you away..."
"...and hide you in my arms."
"I never saw anyone like you before."
"Your sight takes my breath away."
"I never thought..."
"...this night will come to
a standstill in your arms."
"And my dawn star-ts from you."
"The thing you're scared of most..."
"...I'll do it for you."
"Don't look at me like so,
I'll take you in my arms."
"I will steal you away..."
"...and hide you in my arms."
Sir.
I feel your bad luck's
finally going to end today.
Ours. - Ohh...
sorry...
Passport - Thank you.
Excuse me, officer.
There's something I
want to say before I go.
Bye-bye.
"Now
calling for RT 2145...'
"Mumbai to New York
passengers are kindly requested..."
...to move
towards gate no. 5 for boarding."
"Thank you."
"Passengers travelling from Mumbai
to New York are kindly requested..."
...to move
towards gate no. 5 for boarding."
"Thank you."
Are you on medication?
I mean. . .any
prescribed medication.
I am diabetic.
You need to be admitted right now.
No...l won't.
You want to die in mid-air?
Yeah...
- Sir, Rahul Oberoi suddenly fell sick.
He's being taken
to Life-Care Hospital.
What? - Yes, sir.
Seems like Rahul Oberoi's
bad luck isn't over yet.
Mak.
Mak. Listen to me, buddy.
We can talk it out.
Please listen to me.
L...l didn't rape Rajni.
You can trust me.
Let me convince you.
I'll give you enough money,
so that Rajni and you...
...can live comfortably
for the rest of your lives.
Please leave me.
Everyone makes mistakes.
I apologies.
I surrender.
I'll accept any punishment
that the law gives me.
I Will take it.
But...please don't kill me man.
Don't kill me.
We won't kill you, Rahul.
We will make
an example out of you.
Siya? You?
Just like you did with our lives.
'What is it?'
'1211.'
'Rahul, are you watching?'
Hi, Rahul.
What the f*** Siya?
You too.
No Rahul, just me.
How have I harmed you?
Oh, but you did.
What?
Short circuit, Rahul.
Short circuit.
It didn't just happen...it
was made to happen.
And the person who
died...wasn't just a witness.
He was my father.
Dad, you've to be careful.
They are very powerful people.
If everyone gets intimidated...
...then people like Rahul
will commit rape, murder...
...and anything else they want.
I must step up...so that they
are scared of people like us.
I am proud of you, dad.
You people.
Sorry, sir.
We showed up uninvited.
Sharma sir,
we won't waste much of your time.
We just came to say sorry.
Dad.
We're sorry that...we'll
have to kill you.
Dad!
People like you never
achieve anything in life.
No success,
no fame or achievement.
But then you think of achieving
something in this old age.
You want to become a celebrity
by sending us to jail.
Dad!
Stop it your rascal.
We'll douse that
fire of activism in you...
...once and for all.
Please leave him! Please!
Stop it.
- What are you doing?
What are you doing?
- Stop it.
Help. Anybody there!
Dad..
Help.
Stop it please.
Anybody there? Help!
Leave him!
Dad!
I saw my dad...die
right before my eyes.
And now...the world's
going to witness your death.
On your channel.
Mak has abducted Rahul.
At any cost we've to stop
this murder from going live.
Use the best brains.
Do whatever you have to do.
Blow up the satellite...shutdown
their entire station if you have to.
We have to stop this. - Okay, sir.
How did Mak get to Rahul?
He's a sharp mind...Rahul Oberoi.
My foot.
I planted Mak in your office.
She tried to commit suicide,
but survived.
But ..she's as good as dead.
So..what should we do now?
Mourn for them.
...or make an example
out of those responsible?
I kept track
of all your movements.
I exchanged your insulin
shots with sugar syrup.
In your efforts to
get me in your bed..
...you just walked
up to your own grave.
Guys.
Orders from the government.
We've to shut down.
Okay sir.
Rahul.
This is highly
concentrated sugar syrup.
No, Siya.
Siya you can't do this.
We will gradually
inject this in your body.
Siya, don't do this.
Your sugar levels
will star-t increasing.
And there will come a time"
...when your body won't be
able to tolerate the sweetness.
Siya.
Siya, don't.
All the toxic elements..will
go to your brain.
And then..you will in
a state of diabetic coma.
Rahul.
It's time for
your television debut.
Siya.
I think the GTN frequency
cannot be hacked.
I think they got us.
Well done, Kabir.
Smart.
But how can
you..stop him from dying.
Sir.
I've found some new
information from the court.
"About the Rajni rape case.
It also has details..on Sharma,
the main witness.
After the death of Brijendra Sharma,
the witness in Rajni rape case.
"His daughter Ankita
Sharma claimed his body.
Studying at Massachusetts
School of Law.
Gaitonde, how did we miss this?
Sweet revenge Rahul Oberoi.
My revenge is complete.
No.
...it's still incomplete.
It wasn't three...
...but four of us.
That's an old trick Rahul.
You're lying.
The truth is..that you're dying.
A dying man never lies.
There's a fourth person.
The mastermind.
Who? Who's the fourth one?
You..
You know him.
Speak up you rascaLspeak!
You..you just killed the pawns.
Who?
The real mastermind..was him.
Who? Who?
Your.. Your..
Boyfriend, Ranveer.
Hello, I am calling from India.
I need some information about
an ex-student. Ankita Sharma.
She graduated four years
back from your college.
Please connect me
to the right person.
I am sorry, sir. But we
cannot disclose any information.
"Without checking
proper procedures first.
Ma'am, I am calling from the
Maharashtra State Police Department.
I can send you the paperwork,
but then it might be too late.
We need your law school
to cooperate the law-keepers here.
Alright.
- Right, thank you.
Your mail ID is?
- It's admin
Thank you.
Gaitonde,
this case is like an onion.
Peel one layer off..and
there's another.
I can't understand.
Ankita is equal to Siya.
Siya is equal to Ankita.
Maybe this is the last layer.
We need to catch Siya.
I hate you! I hate you!
I hate you!
Siya, where the hell are you?
I've been trying
to call you for so long.
Ranveer..l want
to take you somewhere.
You didn't say a word throughout.
Now this place.
What's so special
Siya..about this place?
Do you love me, Ranveer?
What?
How much do you love me?
Siya..
- How much?
I love you so much that.
...I can kill or give
up my life for you.
My dad's as well?
Are you alright?
What are you blabbering?
Brijender Sharma was my father,
Ranveer.
Brijender Sharma?
- Yes.
Sarnaik,
Karan, RahuLthey all knew him.
So I killed them all.
Right here.
You can give your life for me,
Ranveer.
But I love you a lot.
I can spare your life.
Just do one thing.
Admit to your crimes.
Handover yourself to the law.
You only told half the story
about Rajni rape case to Kabir.
Now complete it.
Tell him the truth.
Even I will admit to my crimes,
Ranveer.
Go to jail..for what?
I didn't work this
hard to rot behind bars.
I was a poor lawyer,
struggling my way through.
I wanted to move up in life,
and who doesn't?
Whatever I did,
I only did it for my career.
And who the hell is Kabir?
Why should I confess to him?
I'll tell you.
Did you hear..my thank you?
It's alright, Mr.
Lawyer. We'll meet in court.
Karan sir, you should've
made a more fitting offer.
We respect you, Kabir.
We never met a talented
lawyer like you.
But what's the
use of such honesty?
A flat..10 million..and a car.
And your life will be set.
That it?
Is that all you respect me?
Oh, sir..
Your offer tells me that
you don't respect me at all.
My scorner has
s"""" my waver-back.
If you win the case.
...you'll catch your
chartered plane to Hawaii.
Won't you?
Once in Hawaii,
you will relax in a big penthouse.
Even I deserve a small
sea-facing penthouse.
And if you win the case..which
I don't think you will.
But if you do..you will
make at least a billion or two.
Oh my God.
I at least deserve 100 million,
with due respect.
Tell me your plan,
Well..
...just stop that witness
from coming to the court.
And I will control my emotions.
Your dad had to die.
Wouldn't they have thought about
it, if I hadn't given them that idea?
Of course.
But I didn't know he was your dad.
If I had known you,
if we had been in love...
...you think I would've
let your dad die?
No way, Siya. No way.
Back then I just
grabbed the opportunity.
I tried to keep you away from Rahul,
because I knew what a rascal he is.
I love you always, Siya.
Forgive me for your dad,
it was not my fault.
Sometimes we've to do
these things in our profession.
Everyone does it.
And yes...
Please stop lecturing me about.
Surrender to the
law' and 'Face the truth'.
What is this, Siya?
We've our entire life ahead of us.
You don't get it, Ranveer.
I don't want to live with you.
I can't spend a moment
with my dad's murderer.
Why bring someone
who's dead between us?
I am apologizing to you?
You want forgiveness.
Fine...I'll forgive you.
But please Ranveer,
admit your crime.
Like father like daughter.
Don't you get a simple thing
that everything will be ruined.
Your father died because
of his obstinacy, and so will you.
Take my dad's name with respect,
Ranveer.
You just have to surrender
yourself to Kabir.
Surrender?
Don't forget that
you're a lawyer as well.
And what do you think?
I will get punished
if I surrender.
For that you need proof,
or I will have to confess.
And I won't.
You don't have to confess.
Meaning?
I mean...you've already confessed.
Cut the phone, Siya.
I say cut the phone Siya, or else...
Or else?
Or else what?
You will kill me too.
If I have to.
"I fell deeply in love with you..."
"The reason is you."
Kabir, you're mistaken.
She killed Rahul,
Karan and Sarnaik.
You do the wrong
deeds...and I am mistaken.
Surrender yourself, Ranveer.
Surrender myself?
I see...
It will take me less
than an hour to get out.
Only time will tell...
We're two sides of the same coin,
Ranveer.
But you lost the toss today.
Game over.
"The reason...l feel
overwhelmed every season..."
"The reason is you."
I can't believe this Ranveer.
But I will live with this truth...
...that you're the reason
for all my crimes.
Sometimes we've to
live with pain, Siya.
There's good news for you.
Your case has been closed.
You could've
have arrested me, Kabir.
I listened to my hear-t instead.
I did what I thought was right.
Can you continue doing
your job with this burden?
I resigned.
Now I'll spend
some time with Suhani.
And open up a private
security firm or something.
How is Suhani?
- She's fine.
And she's the main
dancer in the concert now.
Good.
I pray to God that every
father has a daughter like you.
You're a good dad, Kabir.
You're a better daughter.
"The reason...l feel
overwhelmed every season..."
"The reason is you."
"I was shattered in pieces...but
I feel complete now..."
"I strolled down
your lane every day."
"The reason is you."
"I was never
like I am these days."
"I hardly meet anyone
else...except for you."
"I've star-ted
changing these days..."
"The reason is you."